Chapter 1239: Hoist By Your Own Petard

Thunderclap's two close-ranged classes rushed forward. Xiao Shiqin didn't even blink as he looked around. But Thunderclap's attack formation didn't weaken because of this though, and Xiao Shiqin didn't neglect his shotcalling.

Happy might just be purposely trying to confuse them, using this to divert their attention and reduce the pressure. Xiao Shiqin considered this possibility. So even as Shattering Wind and Demon Talent pressed forward, they weren't just looking for Lord Grim, they maintained their attacks toward Happy's players. Happy didn't reduce the pressure, and in fact because of Lord Grim's disappearance, they had to work even harder under the conditions of a 4v5.

Show yourself!

Xiao Shiqin thought to himself. Ye Xiu couldn't play like this all the way until the end.

"2 o'clock." In the Thunderclap chat, Dai Yanqi suddenly called out. As she spoke, she prepared to fire a spell in that direction.

"Don't split your attention, leave it to me!" Xiao Shiqin immediately shouted. He was scared of this scenario exactly. If everyone switched their attention to target Ye Xiu's Lord Grim, then wouldn't this situation, which they had established with such difficulty, be broken? Seeing Dai Yanqi's Firebird Messenger already turning her head and about to cast in that direction, Xiao Shiqin truly applauded Ye Xiu.

It was just a small trick, but it caused a great disruption to Thunderclap's strategy. Ye Xiu truly understood the players' logic and reactions too well. At a time like this, anyone who suddenly discovered Lord grim's whereabouts would instantly try and attack, and with that, Thunderclap's strategic rhythm would be disrupted.

"But it's a shame, Ye Xiu's opponent is Xiao Shiqin." After seeing Xiao Shiqin's direction in the team chat, Li Yibo spoke with a smile. With an omniscient view, they of course saw Lord Grim's actions more clearly than Xiao Shiqin could. Li Yibo reached the same conclusion as Xiao Shiqin, but seeing that Xiao Shiqin saw through it entirely and was prepared against it, Li Yibo didn't feel like going to praise Ye Xiu.

"Yeah…" Pan Lin agreed, his heart beginning to waver. It looked like Happy was really struggling in this match! Should he begin to sing praises for Thunderclap?

As Pan Lin wondered, the situation onstage changed again.

The exposed Lord Grim suddenly began to move. Dai Yanqi's attack toward him had been stopped by Xiao Shiqin, but he still continued to charge toward Dai Yanqi.

"Don't panic, it's Mechanical Seeker," Xiao Shiqin called.

"Haha, seen through again," Li Yibo laughed. "A Mechanical Seeker and a character are very different in size, and so they move a little differently. Perhaps a lot of people wouldn't be able to tell the difference, but Xiao Shiqin is an expert Mechanic!"

The little trick once again failed to come to fruition. Ye Xiu seemed rather helpless, and Lord Grim finally charged out, this time toward Zhang Jiaxing's Returning Wind.

Attacking from behind to try and save your allies?

Xiao Shiqin smiled. He'd already thought of this possibility long ago!

Fang Xuecai's Assassin Demon Talent twisted and used a Shining Cut in the direction of Lord Grim's movement. If this kind of thing didn't happen, no one would notice, but as soon as it happened, everyone suddenly realized that Thunderclap's players, in maintaining their nonstop offensive, were coordinating with each other extremely well. The tactics of this team proceeded as precise and orderly as the gears of a machine.

Zhang Jiaxing wouldn't just sit around doing nothing. When he saw Lord Grim coming toward him, he cast a Sacred Fire, hidden in the grass.

Would it hit?

Zhang Jiaxing didn't know. He was too familiar with this opponent in front of him and knew just how scary he was. A little trick like this wouldn't be much use, would it?

This thought hadn't even finished crossing his mind when, at the position of his Sacred Fire, a blindingly white fire blazed to life.

It hit!

Fang Xuecai was delighted at this development, and of course he wouldn't let this skill-sealing opportunity slip away. Demon Talent used Swift Run and Swift Movements, prepared to instantly kill with a Heart-Piercing Stab.

This is?

Fang Xuecai stopped. A green-skinned Goblin waved a club as it came toward him. From its excited state, he could tell that it must have eaten an attack, otherwise how could it run so quickly?

This was a trap!

"It's a Goblin!" Fang Xuecai hurriedly sent a message. This lowest-level little summon was of course nothing to him, and he quickly took care of it.

A Goblin!

Xiao Shiqin jolted. This wasn't an attack from the rear to save the allies, this was… making a sound in the east and striking in the west!

Just as he reached this realization, Xiao Shiqin watched as the grass began to rustle once again. This time, Ye Xiu no longer bothered to hide Lord Grim's body, because now there was no one nearby to stop him.

Slide Kick, Charge, Colliding Stab, Shining Cut…

Lord Grim chained all of these low-level quick movement skills from various classes. Relying on the effects of all of these skills used consecutively, Lord Grim's speed at that moment couldn't be bested by even an Assassin, let alone any of the slower classes.

Cheng Tai's Shattering Wind wasn't fast enough to block him, and in an instant, Lord Grim was in front of his target.

"Captain Xiao, having fun?"

Lord Grim made his move. Dragon Tooth!

As soon as he knew about the Goblin, Xiao Shiqin instantly realized that he himself was Ye Xiu's true target, and he was already defending himself. But Lord Grim arrived too quickly, so quickly that Xiao Shiqin was feeling regret. Lord Grim could use skills to achieve this kind of movement speed; they really shouldn't have been tricked by that Goblin.

Roll!

Life Extinguisher rolled to the side, dodging the Dragon Tooth. He swung his Mechanical Box to the side and a Magnetic Field Coil was thrown onto the ground.

Boom!

The Magnetic Field Coil hadn't had time to release its magnetic energy when Lord Grim's spear pierced it, directly disrupting it. The spear jumped and again flashed in front of Life Extinguisher.

In the end, Ye Xiu was most familiar with handling a spear. All those years controlling the Battle Mage One Autumn Leaf hadn't gone to waste.

Xiao Shiqin could only have Life Extinguisher dodge again, but Lord Grim wasn't some ordinary Battle Mage. If the spear's range wasn't enough… The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shifted to gun form, and Anti-Tank Missile was launched!

Boom boom boom!

The flames of the explosions swallowed Life Extinguisher whole, but at this moment Xiao Shiqin still sent a message in the chat. "Leave me, maintain the rhythm."

The Thunderclap players who had been prepared to rescue him suddenly stopped, but they understood their captain's intentions. Ye Xiu's powerful offensive toward Xiao Shiqin was his attempt at breaking the current situation. If the Thunderclap players broke formation to save thier captain, Happy would be free of their current difficult situation, and might even be able to launch a counterattack. This could be considered a variation of BOX-1 tactics, and Thunderclap's players, with their high tactical background, instantly understood.

"Maintain the rhythm, respond as appropriate," said another Thunderclap player. It was Fang Xuecai, a longtime teammate of Xiao Shiqin's in Thunderclap, the vice-captain of Thunderclap. He knew that Xiao Shiqin didn't have much space to give commands, so he supplemented the strategic plan.

They couldn't gather the strength of the entire team to force a rescue, but they couldn't not rescue him. Maintain the rhythm, respond as appropriate, a playstyle like that was to incorporate Lord Grim and Life Extinguisher into the rhythm of the battle as a whole. It was the logical way of breaking BOX-1 tactics.

But… To Thunderclap, Xiao Shiqin was more than just a battle core. He was the commander. This battle against Happy in particular required many directions from him, constantly adjusting their tactics and attack rhythm to target Happy's weak point, An Wenyi. But at this moment, under Ye Xiu's offensive raining down upon him, an offensive that could instantly defeat countless formidable players…

"How about it? Still have time to type any words?" Ye Xiu, shockingly, could still find the space to ask this question.

The crowd was silent. No one knew how to express their current emotions.

Xiao Shiqin… This was retribution, wasn't it?

Against Blue Rain, he had bullied Yu Wenzhou. Yu Wenzhou's handspeed was too slow to keep up with a rapidly changing battle, so Xiao Shiqin purposely directed his team so there were many changes and ultimately defeated Blue Rain.

And now, Ye Xiu, this Glory Textbook was teaching a lesson to the helplessly sighing Blue Rain. Was there really no way of dealing with Xiao Shiqin's harassment?

Of course there was, and it was simple. Tooth for Tooth, use their own strategy against them!

If he wanted to harass with a complex and changing battle style, Xiao Shiqin also needed to rely on a large number of commands. His handspeed wasn't a problem, but, when faced with this explosion of attacks raining down upon him…

"Your life or your commands?"

Ye Xiu's question was the dilemma with which Xiao Shiqin was currently struggling.

Thunderclap's players quickly realized as well, without Xiao Shiqin's commands, the amount of damage they were dealing was quickly slipping, and it seemed like Happy's weak point An Wenyi could endure this level. After all, he had walked with Happy through the Challenger League and played half a season with them on the main roster. He didn't neglect his daily training, either. Perhaps his talent was limited, but after a year and a half of growth, he was far from mediocre.

Thunderclap's strategy, broken!

The live crowd finally reacted with applause and cheers. And once An Wenyi was able to stabilize the situation, Happy's counterattack finally arrived. With regards to player quality, many people had already realized prior to this match that Happy was superior to Thunderclap.

"We have to save Captain!" Dai Yanqi said in the chat.

The others were also debating, but they also wanted to wait for Xiao Shiqin's direction. A "save" could be typed out! While he was tangled with Ye Xiu, Xiao Shiqin still occasionally had the space to issue a direction.

His life or his commands? This was the dilemma Xiao Shiqin faced.

To save or not to save? This was the choice Thunderclap had to make.

But Ye Xiu seemed like he knew that Thunderclap was facing this difficult decision. Lord Grim's attacks grew even more ferocious, so much so that people felt that the slightest slip could send Life Extinguisher straight to death.

Was it so bad that he couldn't even type a single word? The blood of the Thunderclap players went cold.

"Dai, help him!" At last, Fang Xuecai couldn't resist any longer, directing Dai Yanqi to give some support, or at least make an opening so that Xiao Shiqin could give a command. Just pointing them in the right direction would be enough!

"Understood!" Dai Yanqi's Firebird Messenger turned around.

The crowd saw all of this. Xiao Shiqin was suppressed, Dai Yanqi went to help him, this… this was a strategy often used by powerhouse teams with top-tier players during team competitions. Star 1v2.

This Ye Xiu… When the other side had stars, he played tactics with them. When the other side played tactics, he played as a star?

Chapter 1240: Bitter But Unable to Complain

Dai Yanqi shifted targets to Lord Grim. Fang Xuecai thought that as a long-ranged attacker, switching targets would be fast and easy. Dai Yanqi wouldn't need to approach either, saving time while still letting her take care of the other side simultaneously.

His thinking wasn't wrong. At the moment, this was the best way to maintain balance on the field. However, since she needed to take care of two sides at once, her presence on one side would be weaker. This small difference was quickly seized by Happy.

Who had Happy sent out for the team competition today?

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Wei Chen, An Wenyi.

Apart from An Wenyi, the rest were experienced veterans of the game. As soon as Thunderclap's balance tipped a little, those three raced towards a small opening that appeared.

Thunderclap's players felt their hearts suddenly turn cold. This feeling was as if they had caught a net packed with fish, but then a small hole ripped open in the net, resulting in all of the fish escaping for their life through this hole. In an instant, the hole enlarged, leaving them no opportunity to patch it up.

"Stop them! Stop them!" Fang Xuecai roared.

But Thunderclap's players felt powerless. A hole had been exposed already. They couldn't stop them. Agreeing by chance, everyone turned to look towards their captain. If Xiao Shiqin's shotcalling hadn't been cut off, this situation wouldn't have happened.

How could Xiao Shiqin not feel bitter? It wasn't that he didn't want to give out commands. If he had even a fraction of a chance, he would certainly take it to instruct his teammates on what to do. But he wasn't given any chances. He could only watch as their complete and perfect offense slowly fell apart due to a lack of precise adjustments. There had been numerous crucial moments that Xiao Shiqin had wanted to say something, but he couldn't, because he discovered that whenever these crucial moments appeared, Ye Xiu would suddenly press even harder.

Ye Xiu… he wasn't only looking at the opponent in front of him. He was also carefully watching over the entire battle and then adjusting his attacks according to the situation. If Xiao Shiqin tried to type anything, he would be taking on a full frontal assault from an unspecialized. Under Lord Grim's explosive storm-like attacks, he might just die as a result.

If he lived, there would at least be hope. If he died, then it would mean he wouldn't be able to give any orders anymore.　

In this instant, Xiao Shiqin hated the Alliance's ban on voice chat. He could completely feel the helplessness and misery that Yu Wenzhou had felt facing against him.

Fang Xuecai had Dai Yanqi provide support for him, and he knew that this wasn't that great of a decision. The outcome could be disastrous, but what else could be done? If they had continued like that, it would have been disastrous too. Change always created something. For example, what if Dai Yanqi suddenly played out of her mind and was able to completely take care of both sides at once?

That didn't happen, unfortunately. As soon as Dai Yanqi switched targets, she didn't even get the chance to show if she could overperform. Happy had immediately seized the opportunity to break free from Thunderclap's offense. The players that Happy sent out this time were too experienced. They wouldn't miss such a golden opportunity.

Is it over?

No!

Not yet.　　

Happy had broken free from their offense, but Dai Yanqi didn't hesitate. She became even more determined to rescue Xiao Shiqin.

Good!

Xiao Shiqin felt grateful for Dai Yanqi's decision. When making a tactical decision, the biggest taboo was hesitation. For the tactics-oriented Thunderclap, no one was indecisive. 　　

Lightning Bolt!

A bolt of lightning flashed in front of Lord Grim. The purpose of this predictive attack was that even if it didn't hit, you still had to be wary of it. This pause would at least let Xiao Shiqin free himself from a defensive position, giving him an opening to either counterattack or give an order to the team.

However, Lord Grim stubbornly took the step forward.

How persistent. The stun from lightning spells weren't weak. Even if you take it, an opening will still appear. But as Lord Grim stepped forward, he swung his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella to the side. The moment the Lightning Bolt arrived, his umbrella opened up with a whoosh.

Zzt. Lightning struck the umbrella, but before the electricity spread out, the umbrella closed, or it could be said that the umbrella never stopped. This was simply another attack towards Life Extinguisher. It was just that it came from the side, blocking the Lightning Bolt coming towards him in the passing. Lord Grim's offense wasn't interrupted one bit.

Dai Yanqi felt frightened by such precise movements, and she didn't cast her prepared follow-up. Dealing with Ye Xiu wasn't how she had thought it would be.

It wasn't until after she saw Life Extinguisher continue rolling to dodge did she regain her senses. She immediately cast another spell to attack, but Ye Xiu wasn't just fighting alone. The rest of Happy was helping him too. Before Firebird Messenger could cast her spell, a boom sounded first. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain had started providing support for Ye Xiu. Not only did this attack interrupt Firebird Messenger's casting, it also helped blast Ye Xiu towards Life Extinguisher.

Fang Xuecai's Assassin, Demon Talent, rushed forward to try and stop Dancing Rain, but Su Mucheng had noticed him long beforehand. Dancing Rain Aerial Fired away. No matter how fast an Assassin's speed was, he wouldn't be able to catch up to her in a short amount of time. And right now, how could he have the time to blindly chase after someone? He wasn't like Dancing Rain. He wasn't a Launcher, who could move around while also providing support to the rest of the battlefield. His Assassin needed to get close. If he was just kited around by Dancing Rain, then his presence would be equivalent to empty air.　　

Fang Xuecai was helpless. He just thought of it as bothering Su Mucheng for a bit. He looked around to see where to go next and in the end, he locked onto Little Cold Hands.

An opening!

Fang Xuecai keenly discovered that because Happy had been trapped for so long, after breaking free, they ran wild, unexpectedly forgetting to protect their healer. If he could eliminate Happy's healer in one go...

This was definitely possible because Fang Xuecai's Demon Talent was an Assassin. He also knew Life-Risking Strike. He may not love the move as much as Void's Li Xun, but no Assassin would completely give up on Life-Risking Strike. The mere existence of Life-Risking Strike was a threat, and in certain moments like these, it could also be used.

Right now… is that moment...　　

Fang Xuecai pretended to have his Demon Talent continue chasing after Dancing Rain. Suddenly, he moved diagonally as if trying to circle around Dancing Rain. But halfway through this movement, his figure flashed. Shadow Clone Technique. His real body instantly moved towards Little Cold Hands, and he closely followed with a Shining Cut to suddenly reach Little Cold Hands' side.

Life-Risking Strike!

Fang Xuecai directly used this risky strike. Little Cold Hands' health wasn't full. He had been pressured by Thunderclap's fast changing offensive, resulting him in being unable to keep Happy's characters above a safe line. Every character including Little Cold Hands himself had lost quite a bit of health due to An Wenyi's panicked healing.

This is more than enough!

Fang Xuecai calculated it precisely. He was certain of this attack. They had analyzed An Wenyi's strengths and weaknesses very clearly. His reaction speed and hand speed wasn't that great. An Wenyi definitely wouldn't be able to react to this sudden sneak attack.

Go die!

Fang Xuecai roared in his heart. Afterwards, even if his own health dropped to nothing, if his character could trade for Happy's healer, then it would 100% be worth it.　

But the instant the dagger was about to strike, Fang Xuecai saw the gown of Little Cold Hands flutter and a wave of qi circled around Little Cold Hands, slicing into Demon Talent's waist.

Qi Blade!

This was Fang Xuecai's final thought on the battlefield. After using Life-Risking Strike, he didn't have the health to take any attacks. A single Qi Blade was more than enough to take him down.　　

To use a Cleric as a cover and so perfect too! My intentions were completely seen through! Yet to dare use it at the last moment was brave. If that Qi Blade had been one beat too late, my dagger would have taken Little Cold Hand's life! Even if I were killed by the Qi Blade later, who cares?

This guy… is so bold, so dirty!

Demon Talent fell despite Fang Xuecai's unwillingness. Fang Rui hollered in the public chat: "This brother's Golden Right Hand is beyond precise!"

"Who would get actually get hit by such a cheap trick? You call this tactics?" Wei Chen sneered.

No one would have thought that in the blink of an eye, Thunderclap would lose a player. 4v5. The situation completely reversed. Thunderclap had no way of stopping Happy. Happy immediately found their target and focused on Life Extinguisher. They stopped at nothing to kill him and before Thunderclap's sixth player could arrive, Xiao Shiqin was sent out of the battle. Xiao Shiqin wasn't just another player in Thunderclap. Without him, Thunderclap's momentum was halted and, in the end, Happy won the team competition.　　

9-1. Another thrilling victory. Everyone was completely dumbfounded by this sudden reversal. Pan Lin and Li Yibo looked at each other with lingering fear in their eyes, especially Li Yibo. He had practically ascertained Thunderclap's win and nearly blurted it out, but he didn't, saving him face. As for Pan Lin, he had a feeling of relief. His caution had paid off. In the end, Happy had pulled off another bout of black magic.

"What a brilliant match…" Li Yibo said. He felt like he had just survived by the skin of his teeth and for a moment, he didn't know what to say.

"Yes, Thunderclap played very well for the first half, demonstrating how to give trouble to Happy."

"Happy also responded brilliantly. Yes… they… also showed how to stop Thunderclap's outstanding tactics." Li Yibo followed up with Pan Lin's words with some hesitation because Happy's way was similar to when Thunderclap beat Blue Rain. It was a sort of dirty way and shouldn't really be praised.

After Blue Rain had lost, they could only feel wronged at the voice chat restriction. But Thunderclap? They had benefited from it and then suddenly became victims to it. Thunderclap had no choice but to suffer in silence. Even if they were bitter about it, there was nothing they could say!

Chapter 1241: Keep Working Hard

The last time Thunderclap had failed in the team competition was during their away game against Royal Style in Round 9. After that, they went on a beautiful six round win streak, but in Round 16 their golden statue cracked again. And this time, their opponent was none other than the team Xiao Shiqin had already lost to last year in the finals of the Challenger League, Team Happy.

In that match, Happy had used lots of unusually exciting tactics against Excellent Era. In the Glory world, it was generally agreed that as Master Tacticians, Ye Xiu was still a bit more shrewd and ruthless. But after losing that battle, it seemed as though Xiao Shiqin had gained something. He returned to Thunderclap, which hadn't changed aside from the addition of the Cleric Zhang Jiaxing from Excellent Era, and he had obtained startling results for his team.

It was impossible for Xiao Shiqin not to be at least a little pleased. Such outstanding results would naturally bring high spirits. Xiao Shiqin now had more self-confidence than before. But this time, he once again fell before the opponents who had just recently defeated him.

When he shook hands with Ye Xiu after the match, Xiao Shiqin's emotions were complicated, and he was certainly a little frustrated. He felt that his year at Excellent Era hadn't been a waste, for in those depths, he had learned a lot and grown a lot. But after growing and improving, he found that he still had no way of defeating this person before him. No one could find happiness in such a situation.

"Keep working hard next time!" Ye Xiu patted his shoulder, as though encouraging some rookie.

Xiao Shiqin smiled bitterly. Of course, he was no rookie, he was someone with prestige and reputation in this circle. But this person in front of him had more qualifications than him, had more honors, and had defeated him twice in a row. When Ye Xiu said something like that, how could Xiao Shiqin respond?

He could only smile bitterly like this and watch as the other walked aside. And then, another hand shook his, and patted his shoulder, and said, "Keep working hard next time."

Xiao Shiqin didn't know whether to laugh or cry. This Su Mucheng hadn't been like this during their time at Excellent Era together! After being with Ye Xiu, she had really changed a lot, hadn't she?

She hadn't even waited for him to say anything before vanishing, and another person shook Xiao Shiqin's hand, and patted his shoulder, and said, "Keep working hard!"

Fang Rui! By year, Xiao Shiqin was actually the senior of this kid, yet even he was going along with this act! Xiao Shiqin glared at Fang Rui, but Fang Rui cleanly ignored him and was all puffed up as he walked away.

"Kid, you gotta keep working hard!" After that, a more boastful voice reached his ear with this encouragement. This person skipped the handshake entirely and directly went to pat him on the shoulder.

"We're not like those little Blue Rain brats," the person said.

Little Blue Rain brats… Blue Rain did have a little brat, but Xiao Shiqin knew, in front of this person, "little Blue Rain brat" referred to more than just Lu Hanwen. Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian, two major players in the Alliance, were really just little brats in this person's eyes.

Blue Rain's former captain, Wei Chen. The person with the most status to call the Blue Rain players little brats. Xiao Shiqin could say nothing to him.

After enduring four consecutive encouragements, this blatant ridicule, Xiao Shiqin really couldn't stand it much longer.

Was there more?

Xiao Shiqin adjusted his glasses and prepared to unleash some killer intent, but the youth who walked in front of him now was very respectful in tone.

"Thank you Senior for your teachings."

"Ah?" This sudden change of style caught him completely off guard. This person in front of him now was Happy's sixth player for this match, Qiao Yifan.

"You're welcome…" Facing this kind of respect, there was no way Xiao Shiqin could insert any mockery in his response.

The last one, An Wenyi, the weak point in Xiao Shiqin's eyes. This match, Thunderclap's strategies almost entirely targeted him. He must have a lot of resentment right now, no? As Xiao Shiqin thought this, he was already bracing himself. This was just a rookie, he couldn't lose in dignity.

But when An Wenyi came up to him, the rookie just extended his hand very ordinarily, shook hands, and nodded his head in acknowledgement. Without revealing any unusual expressions, An Wenyi departed.

The players of both teams finished their polite greetings just like that, and Happy's players gathered together and left, basking in victory. Xiao Shiqin was left onstage. He stared at the hand he had just used for the handshakes, and in the end he used it to pat his own shoulder. "You still need to work even harder, Xiao Shiqin!" he told himself.

During the post-match press conference, seeing those eager expressions of the reporters overflowing the space, Xiao Shiqin knew that this upcoming battle today wouldn't be a good one.

During this season so far, they had received too much phrase. But he should still be able to deal with an awkward situation like this!

He had to work hard! Xiao Shiqin lifted his chin, sat straight in his chair, and welcomed the media's interrogation.

The results of Round 16 of Season 10 continued to release, and those who liked statistics quickly found a pattern. In Round 9, the round where Thunderclap lost the team competition, there were five 10-0 swept matches. And this time, in Round 16, when Thunderclap once again lost the team competition, four 10-0 sweeps appeared this round.

Was Thunderclap's performance in the team round a weather vane for powerful 10-0 showings? The bored gave this title to Thunderclap's team competitions.

Looking at the four 10-0's, they were earned by Samsara, Tyranny, Blue Rain, and Wind Howl. Among them, Blue Rain and Wind Howl's performances had been lagging recently, but their 10-0 scores this round were a clean answer to those voices of doubt. And Samsara, after after achieving this 10-0, finally took the lead over Happy in terms of 10-0 match count. Right now, they had six 10-0 matches, one more than Happy.

Aside from them, Hundred Blossoms, Void, Misty Rain, Tiny Herb, and Miracle all achieved victory. This round had been a huge victory for the home teams - among all ten matches, it had been the home team who had won, and the victories were very close to what was predicted by comparing the teams' strengths on paper. There had been no surprises or unexpected outcomes, if one didn't count Happy's victory over Thunderclap as a surprise.

With this, Happy's ranking increased by one on the leaderboard. With 107 points, they were now in fifth place. And the team they had defeated, Thunderclap, was the only team among the current top ten that had lost during this round. Because the other teams had all gathered a sizable number of points this round, Thunderclap instantly slid down two places, from fourth to sixth, with 105 points. And the team that now rose to fourth was a team that had swept 10-0 this round, Blue Rain. Tyranny and Tiny Herb had the same number of points this round, but Tyranny had defeated Tiny Herb in their match, so Tyranny was second, and Tiny Herb third.

Even as the debate continued over whether or not Tyranny was still strong enough, the team had actually quietly climbed up to second place. Samsara was truly too strong this season, leading by such a large margin that people overlooked their presence. The conflict that people paid attention to was that between all of the teams aside from Samsara. People still held the impression that Tyranny was stumbling had nothing of the dominating strength they had shown last season, but just as the season was about to reach the halfway point, they had returned to their place second only to Samsara?

How in the world had Tyranny chased them up here? Even as everyone was still worrying over whether or not they could even secure a playoff spot, now they were actually second place on the leaderboard?

What was Tyranny's performance?

Everyone discovered that their minds were empty. Their impressions of Tyranny had apparently stopped at when they had begun their rotations. After that period of stumbling performances, they had begun to steadily obtain points. Had anyone noticed? Without drawing attention, they had already quietly risen to second place. This sort of cool and calm performance sent chills down everyone's spines. These old generals in Tyranny still couldn't be overlooked!

Although the rankings among the top 8 had changed, it was still the same eight teams. Wind Howl and Hundred Blossoms were sitting steadily at seventh and eighth place, respectively. Void was chasing them ferociously, but they were still five points behind the eighth place Hundred Blossoms. Below them were Misty Rain and 301, with 82 and 81 points. The gap between them and the playoff zone was in the double digits.

Behind the top 10, among the teams in the lower half, the team that surprised everyone was Miracle. After sixteen rounds of play, this team was at 13th place. For a team that had just joined the Alliance, such a performance was extremely outstanding. As of now, they were even higher up than Heavenly Justice, who had garnered such high hopes last season. Everyone praised Miracle, but it seemed like they had forgotten, the other new team this season was solidly in the playoff zone! But no one thought of Happy as some new team. They had Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, these All-Star level players with whom everyone was familiar. No one could continue to view them as some new team.

After this round, the end of the year was upon them. The Christmas event, the New Year event, and the first weekend of the new year, the All-Star Weekend, they were all rapidly approaching. The in-game event during summer break had been officially named Carnival, but for those in the Glory circle, whether pro or ordinary player, these two weeks crossing the end of the year made up the true valuable carnival.

Every year, the Christmas event that rewarded wonderful presents took place in-game. Ye Xiu had participated in this event for two consecutive years, with great profits. But this year wasn't like previous years. Christmas Day was a Wednesday, and on Friday they still had a professional match to play. The in-game event mainly had to be left to Wu Chen, leading the guild to participate. If pro players were interested, there was nothing stopping them from helping out, but if they spent too much energy there, it could ruin their condition for their match.

Competitive condition, this wasn't just something that existed in the competitive Glory scene. Any sort of competitor for any event had to maintain their condition for competition.

Generally, one's competitive condition would vary cyclically through the weeks. For any sort of event, competitors relied on practice to adjust and maintain their condition. With different events and different competitors, the changes in condition might be different. Some people might only reach their peak condition once a year, and others might reach it two or three times. This required specialized team scientific systems to help every person achieve some control. For Glory, the teams that were aiming for the championship needed their players to reach their full explosive potential during the playoffs.

Ye Xiu was the Glory Textbook, true, but that referred to his knowledge of the techniques of the various classes and the strategies within the game. As for competitive condition, which depended on an individual's skill, personality, skill, and even psychological strength, he truly had no solid grasp of it.

Happy didn't have anyone with such specialized knowledge; the Glory circle as a whole lacked such talents. After all, the Glory Alliance was a competition only ten years old, and everyone was still studying and researching how to best adjust the conditions of the Glory players.

For now, Happy had no way of having such a high-level department, and could only rely on Ye Xiu's intuition from years of accumulated experience to make judgments. And Happy's recent strong performance was unexpected even for him. They… had they entered their peak condition too quickly, too early?

Chapter 1242: Christmas Presents

Eght consecutive wins, plus it was almost Christmas. From top to bottom, Happy was filled with a joyous atmosphere. Ye Xiu didn't want to ruin the spirit. At least wait until after the holiday passed to remind everyone to stay cautious and focused!

That little clumsily handmade Christmas tree was brought out by Chen Guo again. But this time, she didn't set it up in the main area of the Internet cafe for some activity. Instead, she carried it to the practice room of Happy Internet Cafe, and after setting it in a corner she carefully began to decorate it.

Seeing this Christmas tree, Ye Xiu couldn't help but pause. This was now his third time seeing this Christmas tree, and it was now two years since the first time he had seen it. At that time, it had been less than a month since he left Excellent Era. In the blink of an eye, two years had passed, and he had actually established a professional team in this Internet cafe, slaughtered his way back into the Alliance, all the way to fifth place on the leaderboard…

Looking back, even Ye Xiu himself couldn't believe that all of this had happened. They had actually managed to do something like this, and they'd done a pretty good job of it, too.

"What are you spacing out for, come here and help!" Chen Guo's shout interrupted Ye Xiu's thoughts.

Chen Guo was currently hanging presents on the tree. These were all presents that she had prepared for everyone at Happy, each one carefully wrapped so that from the outside, you couldn't tell what they were at all.

"Which one is mine?" Ye Xiu casually asked as he helped her hang them on the tree.

"I don't know. When it's time, everyone will pick one for themselves, and whichever one they pick will be theirs. That way it'll be interesting," Chen Guo said.

"Then what about yourself?" Ye Xiu asked.

"There's one for me too, of course," said Chen Guo.

"You got yourself a present? What's the meaning in that?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"What do you mean I got myself a present! This is a present from Happy to Happy's every member. Am I not a member of Happy?" Chen Guo asked, filled with righteousness.

"Of course." Ye Xiu hurriedly nodded.

"Very good, then we'll just leave it like this!" Chen Guo hung the last present on the tree, studied it critically for a while, and after confirming that nothing was wrong, she nodded her head in satisfaction.

"Aside from picking presents, are we doing anything else interesting?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Isn't casually playing some Glory the most interesting thing for you guys anyway?" Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu froze, and then laughed bitterly. "I don't object to playing some other things occasionally."

"Oh?" Chen Guo thought for a bit. "Go online and play Astrogeddon?" Astrogeddon was currently the most popular RTS game at the moment.

"It looks like you can't think of anything besides playing games, either," Ye Xiu said.

"Yes, I can't either." Chen Guo put special emphasis on the "either." She didn't think that Ye Xiu would have any good suggestions himself; after all, this wasn't the first holiday they had spent together.

"Let's wait for everyone to show up!" Ye Xiu sat down on the couch.

"Brainstorm?" Chen Guo sat down as well.

The two of them sat there like that, staring at the ceiling. One was Happy's captain, one was Happy's boss, but for something like this, neither of them had any good solutions. Perhaps it was because they had both spent too many lonely days without their loved ones.

Bang!

The door to the practice room was roughly pushed open, and Steamed Bun, clutching a steamed bun in his hand, walked inside.

"Yo, Boss!" Steamed Bun waved his steamed bun and greeted Ye Xiu, but just as he was about to greet Chen Guo as well, he saw the Christmas tree at the corner of the room. "Yo, a Christmas tree!" And so Steamed Bun's greeting skipped right over Chen Guo and was sent to the Christmas tree.

"Yup, it's a Christmas tree." Chen Guo wasn't upset that Steamed Bun had skipped right over her, and was actually quite satisfied with his reaction after seeing the tree.

"There are presents hanging on the tree. When it's time, everyone will pick one," Chen Guo explained.

"Alright, thanks Boss." Steamed Bun nodded, and then picked a present off the tree.

Something didn't seem right? Chen Guo blinked.

"What is it?" But Steamed Bun was already unwrapping the present.

"You-! When it's time, I said when it's time! Didn't you hear?" Chen Guo jumped up.

"When it's time? When it's what time?" Steamed Bun asked.

"When it's Christmas!" Chen Guo said.

"Isn't that today?" Steamed Bun was confused.

"That's tomorrow, today is the 24th, the day before Christmas, Christmas Eve, do you understand?" Chen Guo fumed.

"Oh, then I'll unwrap it tomorrow." Steamed Bun nodded, and finally stopped unwrapping. Chen Guo almost went up to get it back, but… Steamed Bun had already left his fingerprints all over the wrapping, since he had just been holding an actual steamed bun. Chen Guo was quite depressed. Should she just rewrap it? Just as she was pondering this, another person entering the room. With a "Huh?", they discovered the Christmas tree as well.

"It's a Christmas tree," Steamed Bun quickly introduced. "There are presents hanging on it, we all pick one, but you can't open it immediately! You gotta wait until tomorrow." After explaining, Steamed Bun shot a "you're welcome" look at Chen Guo.

"Hahaha, little kids, where's all this fuss coming from!" But the new arrival strode forward in large steps. Without waiting for Chen Guo to stop him, he had already come right in front of the tree, plucked the biggest wrapped present off, and swiftly tore it open.

"I…" At this moment, Chen Guo really wanted to burst into tears and wail.

"Let's see what this is, ha!" Wei Chen had already torn all of the wrapping off the present. As it turned out, this largest present was… a cartoon Xiha Monkey pillow.

Wei Chen, growing a chin of stubble over the new year, looked a bit clumsy and helpless as he held this cutesy pillow, with an air of not knowing what he should do with it.

"Is this for me?" Wei Chen didn't know whether to laugh or cry. This present didn't fit him at all!

"You picked it yourself." Chen Guo's voice was extremely cold. She'd said that everyone would pick their own present, but in reality she had prepared to give some hints and prompting. But this guy hadn't even waited for the event to start before rushing forward and snatching a present. Chen Guo was truly heartbroken.

"This… this… Can I have a redo?" Wei Chen looked down. "The wrapping isn't too messed up. Steamed Bun go find some scotch tape, let's rewrap this."

"Yeah, you can't open it now, you have to wait until tomorrow, Christmas Day!" As Steamed Bun spoke, he really did go to find some tape just like that.

"No way! That one's yours!" Chen Guo refused to accommodate them any further. She took a few steps forward and roughly shoved the pillow back into his arms. Seeing the gruff old Wei Chen trying to put on an innocent face, combined with this Xiha Monkey, Chen Guo thought it was both infuriating and hilarious.

"This one! No trading allowed." And so she fiercely emphasized this again. This guy brought this upon himself, let him hold this Xiha Monkey and be embarrassed!

But Chen Guo had underestimated Wei Chen's ability to withstand anything.

"Alright!" Seeing Chen Guo's determination, Wei Chen just casually laughed. He carried this pillow over to the sofa, as though he were the pagoda-wielding Heavenly King Li, plopped himself down, and tucked the pillow behind his back and leaned against it.

"What's yours?" Wei Chen asked Ye Xiu, who was standing at the side.

"Don't know, haven't picked yet."

"Aren't you so noble," Wei Chen said disdainfully.

Ye Xiu was silent. He wanted to laugh, but Chen Guo was glaring at him.

"How about, I pick one too?" Ye Xiu said, cautiously testing the waters.

"Pick one, pick one!" Chen Guo was helpless. There was no point in resisting any longer.

And so Ye Xiu went over and plucked one at random.

"What is it, take a look," Wei Chen urged.

Ye Xiu looked at Chen Guo, who didn't seem to have any murderous spirit left, and was probably already in despair. So, he also began to tear open the wrapping. To the side, Steamed Bun saw that even Boss was opening them, he'd better keep up with the pace! So he too began quickly opening the present in his hand.

At this point, Su Mucheng and Tang Rou entered the practice room together. The girls were all close with each other, so although Wei Chen and Steamed Bun and the others didn't know about this, the girls had all gotten together and talked about it. But now, they saw Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun were already hurrying to open their presents, this… wasn't what Chen Guo had planned!

"This is?" The two were confused.

"Forget about it. You two go and pick too!" Chen Guo was depressed.

At this point, Ye Xiu had already opened his present. Holding what was inside, he laughed in delight. "Haha, this is useful."

"I'll switch with you." Wei Chen instantly said, without a moment of hesitation.

"Hehe." Ye Xiu used his laugh to reject him. He had gotten a lighter. At Happy, he and Wei Chen were the only ones who smoked, so it was clear that this present was intended for one of them. Ye Xiu had gotten quite a suitable present.

"What did Old Wei get?" the new arrivals Su Mucheng and Tang Rou asked, curious.

Wei Chen shifted on the sofa, pulling out the Xiha Monkey pillow to show the two of them.

"Hahaha…" The two burst out laughing. This present plus Wei Chen was a combination that you couldn't not laugh at!

"You're really good at picking!" said Su Mucheng. Seeing that Wei Chen had gotten that present, she knew that this situation had gotten out of Chen Guo's control. No wonder Chen Guo was a bit depressed. But the important part of sending presents was the feeling behind it. Su Mucheng didn't care too much about the process or result, the most important thing was creating this atmosphere, no?

"Will you bring that with you everywhere you go from now on?" Su Mucheng asked Wei Chen with a laugh.

"You hurry up and pick, if you get another lighter I'll trade with you," Wei Chen said.

"Don't even think about it," Su Mucheng said. "No matter what I get I'm not trading with you." She also picked a present from the tree and opened it. "Oh no, how'd I get this one?"

"What is it?" Wei Chen carried his Xiha Monkey pillow as he scurried over, prepared to exchange.

"This… should've been given to him!" In Su Mucheng's hand was a slender voice recorder, and in the direction of her gaze, Mo Fan had just entered the practice room by himself.

A voice recorder, the silent Mo Fan… This was really an exquisite pairing.

"What a shame, I suppose it's mine now." Su Mucheng put the present away.

Wei Chen appeared not to be very interested in this voice recorder.

"What did Little Tang get?" He made his way to Tang Rou's side.

The wrapping was torn off, Tang Rou's present was a more general gift, a beautiful music box.

"Are there any more manly gifts?" Wei Chen called.

"Are you talking about mine?" Steamed Bun turned around, wearing a glove on his right hand. Ordinary people might not recognize it at first, but everyone here instantly realized that this was the glove weapon used by Qi Masters in Glory, a piece of Glory merchandise. The intent of this present was also rather clear; it had special meaning for Fang Rui, who had just changed classes to Qi Master. Unfortunately, now…

"Steamed Bun, did you wash your hands?" Chen Guo asked with a sullen expression.

Chapter 1243: Art Book Signing

Chen Guo had by now entirely abandoned her original plans for Christmas Eve. By the time Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, and the others entered, she voluntarily told them to pick their presents. By the end, the planned gift matchups had become a complete mess, resulting in hilarious pairings that everyone was laughing over. Chen Guo's initial bit of unhappiness quickly faded away. What was the point of giving gifts? Wasn't it just to make people happy? And now everyone was so happy, there was nothing wrong with this. It looked like the surprise element of this random selection was really quite exciting!

The presents that Chen Guo had gotten weren't just for the players. The in-game department, the R&D department, these were also crucial components of Happy. Chen Guo had done a headcount and gotten enough presents for everyone. These workers didn't work in the practice room, but Chen Guo quickly called them over.

Wu Chen and the others came over and picked their presents, and their unwrapping brought another wave of enjoyment. Guan Rongfei was a bit disappointing though. He had to be forcefully dragged over here, his face filled with reluctance. He charged over, snatched a present, and left, spending a total of less than ten seconds in the practice room before vanishing.

At the end, everyone finished picking their presents and chattering about their suitable or unsuitable presents. Everyone's eyes fell upon Chen Guo, and the final two presents hanging on the Christmas tree.

"Huh?" Chen Guo was surprised.

"Is someone missing?" she asked. The presents had been counted correctly, and she hadn't chosen yet, so by logic there should only be one present left. But in her memory, everyone in Happy had arrived! Even Guan Rongfei, who had only existed here for ten seconds. Chen Guo had clearly seen him holding something as he left.

"If there was no choice at the end, wouldn't that be very boring?" Ye Xiu said.

"Oh?" Chen Guo heard something significant in his voice, and turned back to look at the tree. Two presents, one very familiar to her eyes, undoubtedly one that she had prepared, and the other…

"You put it there?" Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

"It's your turn to pick now," Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was startled. She never would've expected that at the very end, there'd be this little surprise left to her. If she was choosing, then of course she'd pick the one that she didn't know, but… Ye Xiu, that guy, he wouldn't have randomly and hastily thrown something together just to make fun of her, would he? Like a half-smoked pack of cigarettes or something? Something like that, Chen Guo felt that Ye Xiu could easily do.

But… Chen Guo walked up and studied it. That unfamiliar present was wrapped just as neatly as the others. It definitely didn't look like something that was slapped together last-minute. Was it also carefully prepared?

Chen Guo felt a bit moved. She didn't hesitate any longer, and plucked from the tree this present that had been specially prepared for her.

"What is it?" Chen Guo wanted to see what it was, and yet was a bit nervous at the same time.

"You'll know once you open it," Ye Xiu smiled. "It's something that you've really wanted."

"Something that I really want?" Chen Guo was at a loss. At the moment, she couldn't think of anything that she really wanted, and was even less clear on how Ye Xiu would know.

The present was very light, and when Chen Guo took it, she did wonder if it was really was a half-empty pack of cigarettes or something. But hearing Ye Xiu say this, Chen Guo felt that this wouldn't be some prank. She unwrapped the package, lifted out the paper box inside, opened it, and saw a card, a Christmas card.

This was what she really wanted?

Chen Guo was puzzled, and in her heart there was the tiniest trace of disappointment. She took out the card and opened it. At the top was written, in none-too-elegant handwriting:

What you've always wanted, as you wish.

And then, two signatures.

Ye Qiu.

Su Mucheng.

Stunned, Chen Guo flashed back to several years ago, back when she was just an ordinary fan alongside all of the other Excellent Era fans, passionately supporting Excellent Era, loving Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng, these two gods. Of course, autographs from the gods were things that they all wanted. And then afterwards, on that snowy night, Happy Internet Cafe saw the arrival of a stranger, who used Chen Guo's account to defeat an opponent in the Arena in 40 seconds, and then asked to become an Internet cafe employee.

At the time, Chen Guo thought that this was some nobody kicked out of his team with nowhere to go. She invited him to stay, encouraged him, and jokingly asked that when he returned to the professional circle, he would get Ye Qiu's and Su Mucheng's autographs for her.

That had just been a joke, Chen Guo hadn't been serious. But two years later, she received this Christmas gift.

The autograph itself didn't mean anything anymore. If Chen Guo wanted a signature from Ye Xiu or Su Mucheng now, she only needed to say the word.

But it was exactly this point that reminded her. The Chen Guo of today was no longer one of those ordinary fans that could only quietly support their idols from afar. She stood right beside the people she had once worshipped. They were friends, and they fought together. This time, she was no longer a bystander; she was a participant.

Team Happy, it had Ye Xiu, it had Su Mucheng, and it had her, and it had everyone. This was the meaning behind these two signatures. Chen Guo instantly understood, and she felt the tears welling up in her eyes. But so many people were watching, and if she cried now that would just be too embarrassing.

Chen Guo quickly turned away and rubbed at her face. Fiercely gathering her emotions, she waved the card around and said, "This, this is just… just…"

Chen Guo wanted to make a joke, wanted to say "this is just too cheap," but she truly couldn't get it out, because she understood the significance of this card. She wanted to pretend she didn't understand, but she couldn't bring herself to do it.

"Fuck, just two signatures, that's so lame! So shameless!" In the end, she didn't say it, but someone else did for her. What was the present? This was something everyone was curious about, and they had all politely waited for the revelation. But Wei Chen was never that kind of person, and barged over to take a look. Seeing what was written on the card, he hadn't thought as much as Chen Guo did. He immediately treated this as a prank that Ye Xiu was pulling, and began to condemn him.

"And you too!" After scolding Ye Xiu, Wei Chen turned on Su Mucheng. "You're just as shameless as Old Ye. Our boss doesn't have it easy, she pulled together this Christmas celebration for us, and you two use your pathetic signatures as a gift to brush her off? If you're going to give signatures, at least have everyone sign it! Don't cry Lady Boss, come come come, I'll sign for you too."

"Sign, everyone come and sign!" Chen Guo called, but she had already closed the card. She returned to that Christmas tree and retrieved the final gift that no one had chosen.

"We'll just sign this!" This final present was opened, and it turned out to be an art book. Chen Guo had prepared all of the presents, and so she had an idea of which present was which just from the wrapping. This art book was merchandise that Happy itself had produced. The pages were filled with art of their characters, made by professional artists based on the character designs. To invite everyone to sign their names on this, it couldn't be any more meaningful.

"Huh, the art book was printed?" Wei Chen took the book and flipped through it. Everyone knew that Happy was producing this, but they had no idea that it was already out, so Chen Guo obtained a copy from the first round of printing to serve as a present.

"Hm, not bad." Wei Chen quickly flipped to the page with his Windward Formation, and he was very satisfied with the image of the Warlock in the middle of casting.

"Look at me, look at me." The other Happy players all swarmed over. Even Mo Fan, this antisocial person, was curious at this moment. He left his seat, but still maintained a distance of two meters from everyone, as though he were still considering whether or not he should join in.

"Hahaha, Mo Fan's here, so sneaky, so graceful!" The person in question hadn't even arrived, but everyone was already commenting on Deception's page. They then turned to look for Mo Fan, and saw his hesitating figure two meters away.

"Come and take a look," Su Mucheng invited him, and after a tiny bit more hesitation, Mo Fan finally came over.

In the image, a masked Ninja carefully crept along, indeed looking very sneaky.

This was him?

Mo Fan really didn't think he should look like this, but looking at everyone around him, they all seemed to think this was very accurate.

"Sign your name!" Chen Guo passed a pen to him, preparing to let Mo Fan be the first to sign the art book.

Mo Fan tentatively accepted the pen. Under the eyes of everyone watching, his writing hand trembled a bit. The written characters weren't much in the first place, and with this they suddenly became more askew.

"Your handwriting really needs work!" Fang Rui said from the side. "Here, let me show you guys my Golden Right Hand!"

After speaking, he took the pen from Mo Fan, flipped to the page with Qi Master Boundless Sea, and signed the two characters "Fang Rui" with a flourish.

"How about it, it's a hundred times better, right?" Fang Rui even flipped back to Deception's page to compare. Indeed, his signature was much better; those that wanted to speak up for Mo Fan couldn't open their mouths.

"Try writing a third character," Ye Xiu said.

"Go away!" Fang Rui had already swiftly passed the pen to someone else. Everyone paused, but understood soon enough. Fang Rui was an All-Star level player, and definitely wasn't a stranger to signing autographs. No matter whether or not he practiced on purpose, after signing so many, he would definitely be practiced enough to have a good-looking signature. But aside from these two characters of his name, how good he was at writing any other characters remained to be discussed.

The art book continued to be passed along, everyone signing their name on the page of their character, and was finally passed to Chen Guo. She flipped through the pages, silent until she reached the end, when she said, "When you have time, you should practice your signatures!"

Aside from Fang Rui and Su Mucheng, who had to sign things often, only Tang Rou had a rather

eye-pleasing signature. Of the rest of them, none of them could be brought onstage, not even Ye Xiu's. When Fang Rui took a look at it, he fell over. "And you criticized me! Your third character isn't any good either!"

Everyone looked at Lord Grim's page. The two written characters "Ye Xiu," no matter how they looked at them, were awkward and misaligned. Chen Guo was stunned for a while, then pulled out the card she had received. Once she compared them, she understood.

Ye Xiu was incomparably practiced at signing "Ye Qiu." Even though he never revealed his face, he still would often sign merchandise for the team, at the level that Su Mucheng and Fang Rui had to. But now, he had to sign Ye Xiu, this "Ye" was still the same, but the "Xiu" couldn't keep up with the rhythm at all. Then, putting the two characters together, it was even uglier than the chaotic mess of equipment worn by Lord Grim.

It looked like Ye Xiu's "Xiu" was, unfortunately, his third character.

Chapter 1244: All-Stars

Early in the morning, Team Happy had already finished celebrating what was originally supposed to be the most lively holiday: Christmas Eve. Afterwards, Christmas Day wasn't a holiday for them. The things that they needed to do still had to be done, and the matches that they had to play still had to be played. Originally, Ye Xiu wanted to remind everyone to maintain a steady mental state for the next match, but after seeing their opponent for the next week, he had no way of saying these words out loud.

On the 27th of December, Round 17 of the regular season, Happy's opponent was Team Bright Green.

After Round 16, Team Bright Green had only accumulated 30 points and was ranked second from last. The gap between them and the 18th place team had already risen to 14 points. Along with Team Seaside, they were considered to be the two teams who would be relegated without suspense this season.

Faced with a team with such an awful record, Ye Xiu felt that nagging the team about being cautious and prudent was somewhat excessive. The Alliance could be said to not have any weak teams, with examples of strong teams being defeated everywhere. Even so, for a playoff team facing against a team struggling to keep their place, simply having the appropriate attitude would be good enough. Any serious talk about not underestimating their opponents could instead backfire and cause the team members to lose confidence.

Thus, at the end of the day, Ye Xiu didn't say anything unnecessary, only getting ready in the same way they normally did. Preparing against the opponents, coming up with strategies: they didn't belittle their opponents, but neither did they attach too much importance to them.

Team Happy, who was in their peak condition, naturally didn't get defeated in an upset by Team Bright Green. In their away match, they scored a grand 10 to 0, once again catching up with Team Samsara's perfect sweep record. In Team Samsara's away game against Team Conquering Clouds, they accidentally lost an individual match, resulting in a 9 to 1 victory. Team Samsara thus remained with six 10 to 0 victories under their belt.

At the same time, Tyranny, Blue Rain and Wind Howl all achieved landslide victories in their away games. Tiny Herb lost in a surprise loss against Heavenly Swords after a fierce battle in the same city, but in terms of the number of fans, it could be said that the number of Tiny Herb fans completely overwhelmed the number of Heavenly Swords fans. Yet in Glory, the most benefit of playing a home game wasn't just the fan support received. More importantly, having the right to select the map was more crucial.

In this round, after winning one individual competition, Heavenly Swords suffered defeat after defeat, but finally pulled off a strong comeback in the team competition, defeating Tiny Herb with a score of 6 to 4.

It was just one tiny victory, but it was enough to make the brothers at Heavenly Swords go crazy with excitement. From their debut in the professional league until now, this was their first time defeating a true powerhouse team!

It wasn't too long ago when the team was formed and the rich kids from Heavenly Swords were in high spirits, fantasizing about winning the championships until Ye Xiu helped them to come back to reality. Thus ,when they entered the Alliance, they started off carefully and cautiously, and finally realized the true gap between reality and their expectations. Glory champions? To them, this was truly too distant a goal.

Heavenly Swords' cautious progression seemed to be the most suited for their specific circumstances. But deep in their hearts, could the players from Heavenly Swords really be satisfied dithering around near the relegation zone?

Their dream of winning the championships was something that they just carefully kept away, but it wasn't something that they had completely given up on. They weren't the kind of people who accepted mediocrity after facing reality.

They persevered and worked hard, but their team roster being fixed meant that they couldn't rely on external helpers to increase their fighting strength. They could only increase the strength of their characters and equipment, but otherwise, it was all up to their individual bitter training.

But in this season, Heavenly Swords' results couldn't be said to have improved very much. The bunch from Heavenly Swords may have been a bit too idealistic, but they didn't actually believe themselves to be infallible. With these results, it was inevitable that they would begin to doubt themselves somewhat, feeling that they only had so much skill in Glory. Could they really achieve greater heights?

But at this very moment, they had unexpectedly defeated Team Tiny Herb.

This tiny victory had ignited a single answer in their hearts: we can!

No matter what the reason was, if they could win this round, they could win a second round, or a third. With enough successive victories, who could say that the dream hidden deep within their hearts was unreachable?

"God, isn't that right?"

This glorious and uplifting victory for Heavenly Swords led Lou Guanning to specially discuss it with Happy.

"Yes, that's exactly right, keep working hard!" Ye Xiu replied.

"Alright, you too. Happy New Year in advance!" Lou Guanning called.

Right, it was close to the new year already.

Round 17 had ended on the 27th of December. The next week was a winter break for the Pro Alliance, so the rounds put on hold temporarily, but the once-a-year All-Star Weekend would still happen the following weekend.

The voting for the All-Stars had already entered its final stages. The Alliance was counting the votes, the fans were watching closely, and even the pro players would talk about it in their free time.

From the start of the voting until now, Zhou Zekai's first place in the All-Stars was completely untouchable, and no one had any hopes for such a miracle to take place anymore.

But in second place was surprisingly Ye Xiu!

The Ye Xiu that had routed Excellent Era in the Challenger's League and proclaimed "I'm back" had become a real talking point over the past half a year. When the voting had just begun, there were a few old fans of Ye Xiu and a few people who just went with the crowd who voted for him, allowing him to break into the list of 24 All-Stars.

Afterwards, at the start of the regular season when the teams were feeling each other out, aside from one great victory against Hundred Blossoms, Happy seemed to be on a losing streak. But after the 8th round when they lost to Tiny Herb, Happy rose abruptly and went on a winning streak, continually winning 10 to 0 and violently sweeping through the entire Alliance.

Some conspiracy theorists thought that the difference between Happy's strength at the start and end of the season was too dramatic. They even suspected that Happy was deliberately throwing games at the start of the regular season, waiting till the teams had a good idea of each other's strength before revealing their true prowess and snatching as many points as they could. And from Round 2 onwards, Ye Xiu swept through the individual competition without losing a single match.

Such a strong player not competing in the group arena and instead competing in the individual rounds from start to finish did draw some criticism from people, but such a trivial matter had no way of diminishing his real battle records. Ye Xiu's individual record was very domineering, Team Happy's record under Ye Xiu's leadership was also very domineering, and this fact caused his All-Star votes to continually climb upwards. Both veterans and rookies were watching this already legendary figure. This time around, was he getting ready to create yet another legend? Currently, he had already cemented his name for the number of consecutive individual matches won. And this was a constantly updating record, as he broke his own record again and again…

Even until Round 17, Ye Xiu's record was unstoppable, and Happy's consecutive victories were unstoppable. Afterwards… for now, there was no afterwards. The next round of competition would have to wait until next year, and the All-Star voting for this year would end here. Team Happy, which had never participated in the Pro League before, and its players, who mostly had never had the distinction of winning a championship, would naturally have a weaker standing in the All-Star voting. Even so, the matches that Happy had participated in were significant enough, and in defeating Excellent Era, they displayed a might worthy of a playoff-level team. On top of that, in defeating Excellent Era, Happy had created a miracle, and the effects of that miracle were tremendous. Ye Xiu originally had a firm standing in the Glory circle, and even though he had left for a year and a half, his powerful return meant that it was completely unsurprising for him to have a place in the All-Stars.

With his valiant return, and the strength he displayed after his return, his rise in the All-Star rankings was unstoppable. It was now coming to the end of the voting period, and it looked like there was little hope of him catching up to Zhou Zekai, but it also looked like his position as number two was very stable. Because just behind him was Team Thunderclap's captain, Xiao Shiqin, who was relying on the astonishing results that Thunderclap produced under his leadership this season. After his failure at Excellent Era in the first half of the year, he had returned in full force, surprisingly crushing many top teams.

Originally, the number of votes that the two of them had was really too close to call, but on the 20th of December in the 16th round of the regular season, the two teams faced directly, and Team Thunderclap was defeated 9 to 1 by Team Happy, indirectly proving an answer to this question. To many of the indecisive fans, their votes depended on the player's performance. Happy defeating Thunderclap indicated that Ye Xiu was stronger than Xiao Shiqin, and so after that day, the results of the struggle gradually became clear. The two player's vote count now had a clear difference between them, and this tussle between second and third place was resolved in this way.

Fourth place in the polls went to Tiny Herb's captain, Wang Jiexi, fifth place belonged to Blue Rain's Huang Shaotian, but sixth place was once again taken by a player from Samsara, the new addition to their roster, Sun Xiang.

People had long become numb to Team Samsara's strength, but this numbness didn't mean that people had overlooked their abilities. Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf, this new duo had attracted explosive amounts of attention from the very beginning. This was a duo between two Gods at the peak of Glory, one old and one new. Just this topic alone was enough to be discussed for days on end. On top of that, there was Samsara's undefeated winning streak… that's right, undefeated.

Seventeen rounds of competition, and Samsara had won seventeen rounds without even a single draw.

Victory belonged to every single player in Samsara, but within these people, there would always be those who would shine brighter.

The first of them was Zhou Zekai, the second of them was Sun Xiang... afterwards, the value of Jiang Botao, the vice-captain of Samsara had long been recognized, and he was in ninth place.

In the top ten ranks of the All-Stars, Samsara had already monopolized three of the places, and their Grappler, Lu Boyuan was also ranked at twentieth. After transferring to Team 301, the previous All-Star Grappler, Li Yihui, had gradually lost his former fame, and didn't make it into this year's list of All-Stars.

Four All-Stars! Team Samsara's lineup was truly shining with talent. What about Team Tyranny, who had four All-Stars last season? Now, they only had two. Zhang Xinjie, ranked seventh, and their captain, Han Wenqing, had fallen out of the top ten for the first time in his career, and was ranked twelfth.

In reality, Team Tyranny was currently rank number two in the regular season, but they had very quietly made their way to this position. In the All-Star voting, it was easier for everyone to notice the performances of those with strong, flashy performances. In this season, Team Tyranny had rotated their players. Even Han Wenqing's votes had seen a significant decrease, while Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan had finally been dropped from the list of All-Stars.

What about new players replacing the old?

Regrettably, it was very rare for rookies to appear amongst the ranks of All-Star players. Last season, Gao Yingjie and Lu Hanwen received an unprecedented number of votes, but after their novelty faded away, in this season, they didn't even receive as many votes as last year.

Tang Rou was originally amongst the rookies who had a great number of votes, but unfortunately, after the 1v3 incident, her votes plummeted. There was no need to consider the top 24, her name couldn't even be found within the top hundred players.

Aside from the four players, Ye Xiu, Xiao Shiqin, Sun Xiang and Su Mucheng who had returned from the Challenger's League and become All-Stars, there was one new name in the list, but it wasn't a newcomer to the Alliance.

Team Wind Howl, Liu Hao.

Chapter 1245: The Fortunate and the Regrettable

Liu Hao had entered the Glory Alliance in Season 5. He had joined Team Excellent Era just after their reign was ended by Team Tyranny.

No one had expected such a fall from grace. After all, at the time, they had only lost their streak as champions. In the Pro League, there were always ups and downs. Losing now was no issue, just aim to win next time. Team Excellent Era's Season 4 recruit, Su Mucheng, had been astonishing to see with Ye Qiu. At the time, Team Excellent Era had still been viewed favorably, with an expectation that they would quickly pull themselves back together.

Liu Hao had also carried this type of confidence for Team Excellent Era when he became a member. But who, himself included, would have expected that Excellent Era wouldn't even make it to the finals from this season onwards?

Tiny Herb, Blue Rain… team after team, new champions arose. Player after player, All-Stars appeared. But as for Liu Hao?

It seemed like Liu Hao of Excellent Era was the only vice-captain of an Alliance powerhouse to not have been selected as an All-Star?

This made Liu Hao very dejected. But what could he do about it? Excellent Era already had the ever-radiant Ye Qiu. Then appeared the outstanding beauty Su Mucheng. They became Best Partners, and there was no shortage of rumors about a kindling relationship between the two. Besides these two protagonists of the story, not even the vice-captain could escape being given a side character role.

Liu Hao didn't want to be a side character. He watched as the others who started in the same Season as him became All-Stars one by one: Zhou Zekai, Wu Yuce, Fang Rui. All-Star status meant popularity, but it also required true skill as a foundation. In the pro scene, popularity did not come without skill.

Liu Hao did not have this popularity, but he was adamant that he had the skills. The problem was just that he paled in comparison to his ever-radiant senior. Compared to the founder of the dynasty of back-to-back-to-back championship victories, who in the Alliance wouldn't come up short in comparison? Initially, Liu Hao was proud and content that he could share in the glory, but then he realized that this glory was blinding. No one could see him. He wanted to bask in his own glory.

But… it was so difficult!

Enthusiastically showing his talents would put him off-rhythm with the rest of the team. Limit himself to the team's pace and he would get outshone by the Best Partners.

This team's structure was made for these two and they outshone those around them. Liu Hao thought about this somewhat angrily. What he conveniently failed to think about was that if you picked any random team, of course the core players would be the most prominent. If another player can overshadow the core player's existence, wouldn't they have that title instead?

If he wanted to be noticed, he had to establish his own relevance first. Liu Hao, when unable to do so, instead thought up various excuses for why he was not being noticed. This was too backwards. If he had this kind of mindset, then any ordinary arrangement would seem like a elaborate plot to undermine him.

Liu Hao really didn't want his "radiance" extinguished like this, so he continued to search for opportunities. Although Ye Xiu's ultimate departure from the team couldn't entirely be called his victory, it was at least an outcome that he was pleased to see.

His moment to shine had finally arrived, but right after, Excellent Era was promptly relegated.

This outcome was really some miles away from what Liu Hao had expected. However, Excellent Era was still Excellent Era. Even though they were relegated, their influence was still strong, and they even managed to grab the All-Star Xiao Shiqin from Thunderclap.

Sun Xiang filled the gap left by Ye Xiu's departure, but the gap he filled was only the position of One Autumn Leaf's controller; the role played by Ye Xiu in Excellent Era was much greater than that. After all, he was one of the four Master Tacticians. The arrival of Xiao Shiqin was evidence of Excellent Era's prestige as a powerhouse. However, the hidden motive behind these actions was not noticed by many.

Sun Xiang was not Ye Xiu's successor.

The role of successor fell to Sun Xiang plus Xiao Shiqin.

Two people to replace one. Excellent Era definitely could not reveal this intention.

Following this addition, Liu Hao found himself heartlessly abandoned. It was at that moment when he realized that he would forever be a side character in Excellent Era. When Ye Xiu left, Excellent Era spared no expense to find a replacement and to quash certain rumors. They even started preparing far in advance. But for Liu Hao?

Player trade, you're going to Thunderclap.

All Liu Hao received was this phone call.

Yes, breaking the news to him with a phone call. How much more disrespectful could they get? Forget about a send-off for him, Excellent Era was too busy with welcoming Xiao Shiqin!

Liu Hao left with resentment in his heart. He had thought about exposing how Excellent Era had been unhappy with Ye Xiu, and how they had schemed to pressure Ye Xiu into retirement, while at the same time being afraid of having Ye Xiu become an enemy that they would need to face; Excellent Era had been forced into some very careful maneuvering with regards to the issue. But Liu Hao didn't dare. Speaking of reasons for Ye Xiu's departure, plenty of rumors were floating around the competitive scene, some more accurate than others. However, those were still simply guesswork from outside observers. How much influence would their words have? The worst a comment here and a remark there could do was to give people something interesting to gossip about.

Of course, Liu Hao was not an outside observer. If he decided to blow the whistle, the media would be all over the story. But if he did this, it would not bode well for his future. In the Pro League, which team didn't have some skeletons in their closet? A brave Warrior of Justice may be loved by the media or the masses, but which team would dare let him join?

Liu Hao didn't want to get himself into this lose-lose situation. He still wanted to shine! He should wait until he retired before he exposed the Excellent Era scandal.

Liu Hao buried his bitterness towards Excellent Era who had abandoned him. Who would have guessed that Ye Xiu would be the one to avenge him, by eliminating Excellent Era with a grassroots team?

Life is… just absurd...

Liu Hao absentmindedly thought this at the time. I didn't do anything at all, but the person I hate and the team I hate are locked in a battle to the death. What kind of luck is this?

Liu Hao reflected upon his good luck, but then that year he still didn't make it into the All-Stars, what he'd dreamed about for so long.

It's because my team is too shit.

Liu Hao thought this helplessly.

His performance in Thunderclap that season wasn't bad at all. The team performed reasonably well too, but still did not manage to make it to the playoffs. That meant he, Liu Hao, was still no match for Xiao Shiqin. So in that season, everyone in Thunderclap, from top to bottom, missed their former Captain Xiao Shiqin. Liu Hao felt repulsed being confined in this atmosphere. Even a person long gone still outshone him! Thunderclap was even worse than Excellent Era!

Liu Hao originally did not want to stay long at Thunderclap. Add on his disgust for the atmosphere in the team, and he directly turned down Thunderclap's request for him to stay for the next season. He moved to Team Wind Howl of his own accord. It looked like standing out in this team wasn't going to be an easy task. Just as he was beginning to more carefully consider his situation, issues arose within Wind Howl and vice-captain Fang Rui left the team.

Liu Hao got his foot in the door.

In terms of skill, he was never a weak player; in terms of seniority, he had five years in the Pro League; in terms of experience, he had been both vice-captain and captain. His only weakness was that he was still a newcomer and may not have too much influence in the team yet. However, Wind Howl didn't really have anyone better, so those three advantages were enough for Liu Hao to stand out.

Liu Hao lived up to expectations. He performed well both on and off the field, and everyone could see his worth to Wind Howl. With the highest priced transfer in the summer transfer window but never a spot out among the 24 All-Stars, he seemed to have taken a decisive step forward during the season. Coincidentally, his current All-Stars ranking was at number 17, the same as Fang Rui's last year. Liu Hao was replacing Fang Rui's position both on the All-Star rankings and in Wind Howl.

Unfortunately for Fang Rui, he didn't make the All-Stars. Changing classes was damaging to a player's reputation, regardless of their skill level. However, Fang Rui's performance could still be considered satisfactory. In his very first few matches where he was getting used to the class, he could only rely on a few tricks. Following this, he had incorporated his own playstyle into the Qi Master class, resulting in improvements match after match.

But he still didn't make the All-Stars.

"Qi Masters don't understand love!" Fang Rui noted indignantly.

No one could really tell whether this indignation was real or tongue-in-cheek. Fang Rui didn't seem the type to get hung up on being an All-Star. As one whose style was to play dirty, Fang Rui should have expected divided opinions, leading to a smaller portion of this love. It was rare to witness the situation where Fang Rui would flip this reasoning on its head and say that those who didn't appreciate dirty play were the ones who didn't understand love.

The All-Stars polls closed as the New Year ticked over. With no matches, the votes did not change very unexpectedly. Most did not care about any changes in ranking within the top 24; they only cared if any at the bottom of the poll were changed.

Yes, there still were some changes.

The names on the last two All-Star spots, 23rd and 24th, frequently switched. This time, as the voting closed, two names squeezed in: Zou Yuan and Yang Cong.

After years of loyalty and diligence, Yang Cong finally made it onto the All-Stars. On the other hand, Zou Yuan made it twice previously when he shouldn't have. This time, his performance had really stood out from the rest of the pack, and he had secured a spot in the All-Stars. This time, his true value was demonstrated, and his votes were not from fans who were hung up on a character or who wanted to be spiteful towards a certain other player.

Seeing the names now at rank 25 and 26, everyone felt that it was a shame. Those two were definitely qualified to be All-Stars.

Zhang Jiale, a player in the Alliance since Season 2. Aside from his retirement during Season 8, this was the first year he had failed to make it into the All-Stars.

Liu Xiaobie. This was the second time he had missed out on a spot by an inch.

Lin Jingyan and Fang Rui, the former Criminal Duo, were now neither a combination nor teammates. However, they stood together outside the All-Star rankings.

Finally, Tian Sen and the former God-level character Peaceful Hermit could not defend their last shred of glory and were also out of the All-Stars. What might be going through Tian Sen's head right now?

The All-Star Weekend drew near!

Chapter 1246: The One and Only

The clocks chimed to signal the beginning of the New Year, and players of the Alliance gathered in City Q, where the All-Star Weekend was being held this year. Tyranny's once-outstanding old generals' days were numbered. The Alliance seemed to have taken this into account and decided to give hosting rights to Tyranny's home city. However, it looked like fans voting for the All-Stars did not share the sentiment. It was quite unfortunate that Tyranny's Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan were both unable to make it into the All-Stars.

On the night of January the 3rd, City Q, in Tyranny's home stadium, Glory Alliance's Season 10 All-Star Weekend finally began. The 24 All-Stars' characters were introduced by projecting them in the stadium with hologram technology, along with New Year's greetings.

Ever since the introduction of the hologram technology, the presentation of Glory's players and characters reached new, astonishingly heights. These heights were paralleled by the characters, representing the very apex of Glory. For these events, the hosting team would go all out to make everything as spectacular as possible.

Usually, they arranged the characters to appear one by one and perform some actions, such as training moves or a choreographed fight with another character. This time, under the direction of Tyranny's hosting, a new theme was introduced: duos.

Samsara's Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf;

Blue Rain's Troubling Rain and Swoksaar;

Tiny Herb's master and apprentice Witches;

Void's Ghost Duo;

Hundred Blossoms' Blood and Blossoms;

Happy's Lord Grim and Dancing Rain;

As the duos appeared pair by pair, the other theme was introduced: Memories!

The screens within the stadium began to play the classic moments created by each of these duos. Many Glory veterans could recognize familiar scenes from just fleeting snapshots.

In the ten years of Glory, players and characters were constantly being passed on. Likewise, within each and every team, duos were constantly being created.

However…

A pause appeared in the on-screen action, and a question cropped up.

Was there a duo that had survived since Season 1 of Glory for the entire decade, and had fought side by side until today?

Everyone gave a start, and considered each duo that had flashed up on the screen.

Cloud Piercer and One Autumn Leaf? They only started fighting alongside each other this season.

Troubling Rain and Swoksaar? Swoksaar was a legend passed down ever since the beginnings of Team Blue Rain, but Troubling Rain made his debut in Season 4, the same time when the Golden Generation's Huang Shaotian began his professional Glory career.

Tiny Herb's Witch duo only existed after Gao Yingjie made the main roster starting from last season.

Void's Ghostblade duo formed after Wu Yuce joined the team in Season 5 and insisted on playing the Ghostblade class.

Hundred Blossom's Blood and Blossoms were formed in Season 2. However, they were separated after Sun Zheping had to retire due to injury. It was reformed after Yu Feng was transferred to Hundred Blossoms.

As for Happy…. you couldn't get any newer if you wanted to.

None of those duos had endured the test of time, so who had?

Loud shouts rang out across the stadium before many were able to work it out. This was Team Tyranny's home stadium, and of course had more local Tyranny fans than anyone else. These fans were also the only ones capable of causing such a loud ruckus.

Thus, the answer was revealed amidst the clamoring.

Desert Dust and Immovable Rock.

Since the birth of the Glory Alliance, the Striker Desert Dust and the Cleric Immovable Rock, from Team Tyranny, were the two All-Star characters that had fought side by side until today.

The hosting team's duo was the epic climax afterall.

After countless calls from the crowd, the King of Fighting Desert Dust, who had not once known retreat in ten years, appeared on stage with the ever-present Immovable Rock by his side.

Ten years…

The clips of this duo played for longer than any other. From the birth of the Alliance until today, these two characters had become a symbol of Team Tyranny. No other team had a duo that always stood at the peak. Not even the former Excellent Era with their unrivalled accomplishments!

Many of Tyranny's old fans that had followed their team for ten years could no longer control their emotions.

Fuck, you're trying to tug at our heartstrings? This isn't Tyranny's style, why are you trying make us cry? Tyranny's manly men do not cry. How embarrassing is it to have tear-streaked cheeks?

"A partnership that has lasted ten years. Unwavering. Steadfast. The character may be timeless, but the player eventually departs. However, only one player, from our Team Tyranny, has brought Desert Dust with him onto the stage. He has lead Team Tyranny into battle from day one and continues to do so. Season 1, Season 2, Season 3, all the way until today in Season 10! He has stood here eternally, at the summit. This player, the one and only. WHO IS HE???"

"HAN WENQING!!!" The whole stadium erupted into a thunderous roar. Han Wenqing was the only player in all of the Glory Alliance who deserved this portrayal. Originally, his arch-rival Ye Xiu would be his equal for this, but unfortunately Ye Xiu took a year and half break starting in Season 8. Therefore…

There stood Han Wenqing. The one and only.

Not only had he lasted ten years, he had lasted ten years while being the best of the best. While his age might have slowly robbed him of his mechanical speed and reactions, his spirit and indomitable will never swayed. This was Han Wenqing, the player behind Desert Dust, the captain of Team Tyranny, for ten years straight.

Han Wenqing quietly stepped onto the stage. Desert Dust's projection stood beside him. The stadium gradually quieted down, expecting this warrior who has fought ten years' worth of battles to give a speech.

But he didn't!

Han Wenqing refused the microphone that was handed to him by the MC. He said nothing, while glancing at the projection of Desert Dust that was beside him.

Seeing the character that he has controlled for ten years standing next to him was a rare experience for Han Wenqing. As he glanced sideways, he stretched out his right hand and actually gave the hologram a pat on the shoulder. Then, he lifted his outstretched right hand and clenched it into a fist. Towards the entire audience, the players, he waved his fist once. Although it was not forceful, it carried a distinctive air of conviction.

He didn't need to say anything.

I'm still standing. I can still clench my fists. That is enough!

Han Wenqing's gesture set off another passionate round of cheering. At the same time, Zhang Xinjie also walked onto the stage, his meticulously calculated footsteps landing him precisely next to Han Wenqing.

Zhang Xinjie was not the first owner of Immovable Rock; however, he had fought by Han Wenqing's side for almost seven years. Players were not like characters and could not fight on endlessly. From this, each player could be considered an inheritor. From the bygone past, to now, to the distant future, through their characters they passed on their spirit and willpower forevermore.

The two players clasped hands tightly and embraced each other under the gaze of tens of thousands of spectators.

The whole stadium erupted into applause.

No one felt that Tyranny was being biased in showing their own team's players in this All-Star Weekend. Han Wenqing was the most befitting as the main character of the Glory Alliance's tenth anniversary. He was the only one to have experienced the full ten year history of the Alliance, and at this moment, it did not matter whether he was on Team Tyranny or not.

The applause did not dwindle. Even though Tyranny did not actually plan to only show off Han Wenqing, all the others who appeared on stage next naturally didn't get the same kind of resounding welcome. The other 22 All-Stars joined the stage while clapping along with the crowd. They stood on either side of Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie, placing them in the very middle, in a gesture that gave more than enough face to Tyranny's hosting arrangements.

The lively opening had finally come to a end. Each player left the stage and joined their own teams in the players' stands. The All-Star Weekend was a festive occasion, so everyone was being very casual. Many players mischievously snuck off to other teams' areas and found their more familiar colleagues, greeting each other and chatting about who-knows-what. On stage, the preparations were being made for what was always the first event of the All-Star Weekend: the Rookie Challenge Competition.

The first onto the stage was a rookie from Team Parade.

Many audience members let out a yawn. Compared to the excitement brought about by the dramatic appearance of Han Wenqing earlier, this was too much of a slump.

Li Jiu?

Who was that?

Small- to medium-sized teams already only received a limited amount of attention, let alone a rookie who did not get a chance to appear on stage very often. Li Jiu really was an unfamiliar name to fans. This kind of Rookie Challenge was no fun! The viewers felt that not having an exciting rookie might impact the turnout for Day 1 of the All-Star Weekend. It honestly was not interesting to follow or discuss a rookie who had no reputation. This was in contrast with last year, which had very exciting Rookie Challenge matches where many rising stars stole the stage. The viewers racked their brains and thought: of all ten years of professional Glory, it seemed like there was no good crop this year! There didn't seem to be any strong rookies?

Tang Rou?

When everyone considered this question, this name was the one that popped up in the minds.

Peh peh peh!

Many people spat. This woman doesn't know heaven from earth, and she even went back on her own word! Where do you think this is? Did you expect everyone to easily forgive you? Don't feel so privileged just because you have good looks! Fuck off!

This was the opinion of many towards Tang Rou. Even within Happy's fanbase, many people felt unbelievably upset when they remembered that there was such a person on the team; their hearts were very conflicted..

Everyone came to the conclusion that there really were no rookies this season who were especially notable. How about second-year rookies? They also qualified for the Rookie Challenge. They thought of Lu Hanwen, but since he already participated last year, it didn't seem like they would support him going up again?

Poor Li Jiu was already completely forgotten by the masses, who were all pondering whether there was anyone after him worth watching. Meanwhile, Li Jiu's voice rang out: "I would like to challenge Senior Ye Xiu from Team Happy.".

Chapter 1247: Asking the Senior to Advise

"The one I want to challenge is Happy's Senior Ye Xiu." Li Jiu's voice echoed throughout the stadium.

Everyone was stunned, and then suddenly exploded into a large clamor.

"This kid is so daring!!" Tyranny's crowd was always wild, and quite a few people cried out. Although they hated Ye Xiu, their shameless rival, they would never deny his strength. And this newcomer actually challenged Ye Xiu! Interesting, really interesting! If Ye Xiu really lost, then it'd be interesting to the limit!

At the thought of this possibility, the audience suddenly grew excited.

In this season so far, Ye Xiu had won the individual competition 16 consecutive times. At the thought, Tyranny's fans were furious. This arrogant fellow! Can no one stop him?

The success of the All-Stars match didn't include the statistics, but Tyranny fans didn't care about that. As long as this guy admitted defeat, then they would be ecstatic!

The player that walked out was a rookie, but this was the All-Stars stage. Anything was possible. Perhaps in a less serious atmosphere, there would be mistakes he could take advantage of? The disparity between a God and rookie was not so large!

"Oh! Li Jiu wants to challenge Happy's Ye Xiu! Alright, let us welcome Ye Xiu to the stage!" The host took the lead to applaud, but the audience booed in response.

　

"You really are unpopular! How did you even become an All-Star? And second place too! You secretly found people to vote for you, didn't you? " Fang Rui lamented.

　

"Why is power of hatred so strong?" Ye Xiu deeply contemplated on this thought. He had already left the professional circle for a year and a half, but Tyranny's "welcome" was still as before!

"Stop being so disgusting! Hurry up and get on stage!" Wei Chen scolded.

Ye Xiu helplessly stood up amidst the sea of boos and bitterly smiled as he entered the stage.

This was the second-place All-Star player, plus he was someone who had never made a public appearance like this before. The host was obviously excited as well. Even before Ye Xiu got onstage, the host had already appeared before him.

"Senior Ye Xiu, hello. I suppose it's been a while since you've been here?" The host also referred to Ye Xiu as a senior.

"Yes," Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Tyranny's home stadium? After he retired in Season 8, he hadn't come back here. Although he had fought against Tyranny this season, that had been Happy's home game. If he were to try and recall, Ye Xiu couldn't really remember how long it was since he'd last been here.

"Do you have any feelings about returning to this stage?" The host asked with a smile, obviously also very attentive to the enmity between Ye Xiu and Tyranny. Thus, he purposefully asked such a question.

　

"Haha, it's still just as noisy," Ye Xiu said.

The audience immediately booed in protest, as if they had specially coordinated with him to create such a scene.

"What are your thoughts on being the first one named for a challenge?" the host asked again.

"Fame follows merit," Ye Xiu answered simply.

"Ah? What does that mean?" The host was baffled.

"Number one!" Ye Xiu said.

The host was stunned. What was this troublemaker trying to do? The host resisted the urge to boo alongside the audience.

"Alright, let's ask Li Jiu a question. Why did you choose to challenge Senior Ye Xiu?" The host turned his attention to Li Jiu, paying no heed to Ye Xiu.

"Because Ye Xiu's record this season has been very good. I want to try and challenge him." Li Jiu merely replied.

"Oh, so to say, you want to end Senior Ye Xiu's winning streak?" the host asked.

"No, I don't dare!" Li Jiu immediately responded, but his gaze still revealed a faint anticipation.

So, the host turned to Ye Xiu with a smile. "Senior Ye Xiu, would you accept that if you lose this match, you break your winning streak?"

Ye Xiu grinned. "So if I win, will that count toward my winning streak?"

"Haha, sincere fans will surely remember." Quick witted as he was, he responded to Ye Xiu's question very quickly, and then seamlessly changed the topic. "Is there anything the two of you would like to say to each other?"

"Better work hard, kid. On the battlefield, I'm very serious and very ferocious," Ye Xiu said.

　

The audience's jeers grew in volume and the host was overcome with emotion. Ye Xiu and Tyranny's enmity really had an undeserved reputation. Ye Xiu had only been on stage for only a few minutes, but the deafening boos reverberated for what must have been the fourth time.

　

"Please advise me, Senior." Li Jiu's response was very ordinary, but the thunderous applause from the audience surprised him. Confused, he asked himself, had he actually said something brilliant?

His words were certainly not brilliant. Tyranny's fans simply wanted to make Ye Xiu lose face, so they purposely supported the rookie.

Both players entered their respective booths and logged into their characters. The host then walked offstage. With such an easy-going atmosphere, he stood at the side of the stage and trash talked like a fan.

"Good! The match started! Let us see how serious and cruel God Ye Xiu is!"

"Both sides meet! They're starting!"

"Oh!"

"Oh no..."

"Oh my god!"

"This… Li Jiu totally cannot counter God Ye Xiu's seriousness and cruelty!"

　

"Alright, it's over..."

　

A little over a minute. That was how long it took for the match to conclude. Li Jiu's loss hadn't been too unsightly, but when he came out, his face was completely flushed red to the tips of his ears. The match had been totally one-sided. He could say that he was completely defenseless against the formidable Unspecialized. He, like many others before him, only knew after having experienced it, that all his prior preparations and plans could not be put forth in the match at all. He could only subconsciously respond and follow the unspecialized's fighting rhythm. What was more, he couldn't even fully grasp the rhythm, much less try to win.

"Many thanks for your guidance." Li Jiu had lost thoroughly, and that wistful hope of victory made him feel extremely ashamed.

"Keep trying harder," Ye Xiu chuckled. Then he waved at the audience and walked off amidst the jeers.

"He went too far! Towards a rookie, that was so cruel!"

"Yeah! He doesn't have any human feelings!"

"Any other player would have gone easier on him!"

The various discussions weaving through the audience weren't whispers. Everyone hoped these words would make it to Ye Xiu's ears. They wanted to make him feel ashamed.

But it was a shame. In the midst of the discussions, Ye Xiu had taken it in stride and was cheerfully chatting with his fellow Happy players.

"What a shame! Li Jiu couldn't stop God Ye Xiu's winning streak!" Onstage, the host joked, and then looked at the card in his hand. "Then next up, let's invite Miracle's rookie, Guo Shao!"

"Oh, Guo Shao! I've paid attention to this player before! He's pretty good!"

Compared to their reaction to the previous player, Li Jiu, the audience was more spirited this time. Team Miracle. This team had just joined the Alliance, and after 17 rounds, they sat at 14th place with 58 points. For new teams, this was considered quite good. Although this team were mainly made up of Excellent Era's ex-team members, Guo Shao originally came from Miracle and had caught the attention of many parties. Based on many of the individual statistics, Guo Shao was a strong contender for the title of Best Newcomer this season. Even if Miracle's overall placing was relatively weak, there was no reason for a rookie to bear responsibility for the team's results. . This was an important difference between the awards for Best Newcomer and MVP.

　

For Best Newcomer, the main topic of consideration was the rookie player's performance and statistics.

But for the MVP, the team's performance as a whole was an extremely important consideration. Otherwise, where else could the three words "Most Valuable Player" come from?

Guo Shao received booming applause, but very quickly, the jeers filled the stadium once more.

"Yes, the one I would like to challenge is also Senior Ye Xiu..." Guo Shao said.

Ye Xiu was in a daze. His butt hadn't even warmed the seat yet! But he had to go onstage again?

"Go, go. Keep up your win streak!" Fang Rui relished in Ye Xiu's misfortunes.

Ye Xiu had no choice but to stand up with another bitter smile and return onstage amidst the jeers.

The host chuckled, delightfully greeting Ye Xiu. "I didn't think we'd meet so soon again."

"You're too kind," Ye Xiu responded.

"Then, Guo Shao? Why did you choose to challenge God Ye Xiu?" the host asked Guo Shao.

"Ever since we met last time in an Alliance battle, I've been looking forward to having another match with Senior!" Guo Shao didn't hide his excitement.

"Sounds like you've come prepared?" the host asked with a smile.

"Of course," Guo Shao nodded.

"Really? Then show me what you've got!" Ye Xiu said.

"Okay Senior, let's start then!" Guo Shao rushed to his competitor booth.

　

After several minutes...

"You prepared quite well," Ye Xiu said.

"But I still lost." Guo Shao was upset.

"Winning isn't so simple." Ye Xiu said.

"Being able to quickly chain together so many low-level skills really allows the Unspecialized to have incredible movement ability!" Guo Shao lamented.

"Yeah, Launchers need to fight at a distance, so it's especially difficult," Ye Xiu said.

"Yeah, I thought of some solutions, but after this, it looks like they still weren't enough!" Guo Shao said.

"Hey hey, like I said, it's not so simple."

"But I felt there was a tiny short lag when you tried connecting the Slide Kick with Shining Cut."

"Oh? You noticed?"

"I tried to take advantage of that opportunity, but it was still very difficult," Guo Shao scratched his head.

"Do you need me to repeat for the third time that it's not that simple?" Ye Xiu sighed with emotion.

"I'll continue to work hard!" Guo Shao gave Ye Xiu a thumbs up.

"Alright, I look forward to meeting you the next time!" Ye Xiu nodded.

"Thank you to the two players for the splendid match," the host said, a helpless expression on his face. "But the two of you, next time can you not just talk amongst yourselves? Say some words to the audience too," he complained weakly as he eyed the retreating backs of the two players that conversed until they returned to their teams.

Chapter 1248: There’s No End

Ye Xiu and Guo Shao chatted as they walked back, and soon enough Guo Shao arrived at where his teammates were sitting.

Ye Xiu's gaze swept over them, and he saw He Ming, Shen Jian, and Wang Ze sitting together, these three former players from Excellent Era, or in other words Ye Xiu's former team. The players to the left were chatting with each other, the players to the right were chatting with each other, so these players in the middle were suddenly left with no one to talk to. They lowered their heads, and refused to look at Ye Xiu and Guo Shao, who had just stopped right beside their seats.

"Next time, if there's the chance, I would like to learn from senior some more." Guo Shao reluctantly bid Ye Xiu farewell.

"Good to hear! Go and rest now, I'm heading back." As Ye Xiu said this, he suddenly heard a distant shout.

Ye Xiu?

Are they calling me?

Who's calling me?

"It looks like there's no rest for senior!" Guo Shao said.

Ye Xiu turned back. The host onstage, whom he and Guo Shao had left hanging, was staring in his direction, clearly struggling to conceal his glee at Ye Xiu's misfortune.

"Ah, I'm so jealous! I'd love to go onstage again to challenge senior," said Guo Shao longingly.

"Don't." Ye Xiu quickly waved his hand. Onstage, the host was repeating what he had just said.

Yes, that was correct. Another rookie had come onstage, and the player he wanted to challenge was once again Ye Xiu.

"God Ye Xiu, I know you're working hard! We'll have to trouble you to once again come onstage!" the host said.

The helpless Ye Xiu could only retrace his steps.

This third challenger was a player with whom Ye Xiu was somewhat familiar.

Wen Kebei.

Wen Kebei of Team Heavenly Swords.

Heavenly Swords joined the Alliance last season. Lou Guanning and the other four were considered second-year players, so they were still eligible to issue challenges in the Rookie Challenge. Last season, Lou Guanning challenged Yu Feng, and this time, Wen Kebei jumped up to participate, and the opponent he named turned out to be Ye Xiu as well.

"Is there a point to this? It's not like we've never fought before." This was the first thing Ye Xiu said to Wen Kebei upon returning to the stage.

"Ah… We've never played in an official setting, have we?" said Wen Kebei.

"This is hardly an official setting!" Ye Xiu said.

"Ahem!" The host coughed emphatically. True, the All-Star Weekend can't be considered any official setting, but God Ye can you not use such a contemptuous tone! Of course you've had enough of this place, but this is a rare chance for rookies to show themselves under the eyes of such a large audience!

"Haha, after hearing Wen Kebei's words just now, we can pretty much know the reason for his challenge." The host worked hard to keep up appearances.

"I hope that Senior may teach me," said Wen Kebei.

"Haven't I taught you enough times by now?" Ye Xiu smiled bitterly. Wen Kebei played Battle Mage. Among the Heavenly Swords players, Wen Kebei had definitely received the most lessons.

"It's never too much!" Wen Kebei's manner was quite shameless.

"Alright, come on!" Ye Xiu was helpless and could only accept the challenge.

A few moments later…

"Keep practicing!" Ye Xiu said to Wen Kebei.

"Yeah…" Wen Kebei sighed. He had lost quite miserably. How come the difference between him and the God was still so large?

The two people left the stage together, but this time they hadn't even left the stadium floor when Ye Xiu once again heard his name being called.

"Ah!" Wen Kebei was shocked. This was the fourth now, right? When he came back to his senses, he saw that Ye Xiu didn't seem to have heard, and was still leaving the stadium floor.

"God Ye!" Wen Kebei quickly caught up to Ye Xiu to remind him.

"Shut up! Let's go!" Ye Xiu said, his steps not stopping.

Wen Kebei didn't know whether to laugh or cry. Can you really pretend not to hear something like this? But Ye Xiu was acting like this anyway. As the host called his name louder and louder, Ye Xiu walked faster and faster.

It looked like shouts weren't enough, so the host could only take direct action. With the speed of a hundred-meter sprinter, he reached Ye Xiu's side and grabbed his arm.

"Let go of me, what are you doing!" Ye Xiu fumed.

"God Ye, the fourth rookie still wants to challenge you." The host's face was sympathetic, but his stomach was hurting from stifled laughter. He of course knew that Ye Xiu was just pretending to be ignorant. How childish! The host's thoughts were quite similar to Wen Kebei's.

"Be honest now," Ye Xiu said, glaring at the host. "Did Tyranny purposefully plan this out to mess with me?"

"Of course not!" the host immediately said. "Don't you know? The rookies are free to choose anyone they want once they're onstage! The fact that so many rookies wish to challenge you is a sign of your position in their eyes!"

"You think I'd believe something like that?" Ye Xiu said.

The host began coughing again. Just as the host had said, for the Rookie Challenge, the participating rookies had completely free will to choose any of the players to challenge. But how were these participating rookies selected? The All-Star Weekend was designed to be an exciting event, so the organizers wanted to try and deliberately create many exciting situations that the audience would enjoy.

And so, was it a coincidence that all of these rookies wanted to challenge Ye Xiu? Ye Xiu didn't think so. He had a strong suspicion that this was the Alliance's doing, that they wanted to have him face this string of challengers. The best evidence for this was that from Happy, both Tang Rou and Steamed Bun had applied for the Rookie Challenge, but neither of them had been selected. The official response was that there were many applicants this year, and that they wanted to give more opportunities to the second-year players for whom this was their last chance at participating.

This reasoning seemed sincere enough, but now Ye Xiu had defeated three players, and aside from Wen Kebei, weren't the other two first-year rookies? From this, barring Happy's players from participating seemed like an intentional move. After all, Happy's players were most likely to disrupt this situation.

"It really is a coincidence, God Ye Xiu just please try and cooperate!" The host was still maintaining what he said, but it was clear that he knew very well that it wasn't that easy to fool this experienced God. His plea of "try and cooperate" could be considered his attempt at making peace.

"Alright…" Helpless, Ye Xiu shook his head. The host was delighted on the surface and snickering in his heart, but then he heard Ye Xiu say, "Then I'll take this a bit more seriously. I won't use my main to bully the rookies anymore, give me an unspecialized account."

The host instantly spat blood. The God wouldn't just casually compromise, he'd already begun his counterattack. Like this, for example, he was deliberately making things difficult! Everyone knew that the unspecialized Lord Grim only worked because of that Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, and the core of this weapon wasn't its stats, but its ability to shift forms. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was unique; Lord Grim was unique. Unspecialized? Lord Grim was no traditional unspecialized. For this unique character, even the Alliance had no way of supplying an alternate account.

"God Ye! If you used an alt, the rookie would have no way of appreciating your true style!" implored the battered host.

"Aren't the alts supplied by the game company? Let them make a copy of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, and after this is over I'll keep it," Ye Xiu said.

"Ahahaha, God Ye you have such a sense of humor! But this is so last minute, it's a bit late now, isn't it?" said the host.

"You didn't prepare beforehand? This was very poorly organized," Ye Xiu criticized.

"Before this we didn't expect so many people to challenge you!" The host was also becoming a bit shameless. Ye Xiu had even pulled out a "after this is over I'll keep it," so the host certainly wasn't going to fall behind.

This sentence managed to shut Ye Xiu up, finally. He glanced at the rookie standing to the side, pitiful and innocent and not knowing what he had done wrong. Ye Xiu sighed and headed back to the stage.

"Thank you senior for your teachings."

"Keep working hard."

A few minutes later, the battle was over. The rookie walked offstage, satisfied, but God Ye Xiu didn't move. He stood alone on the stage, staring at that host.

"Er, is God Ye Xiu not going offstage to rest?" the host said timidly.

"Don't give me that. I want to see if you guys are done yet," Ye Xiu said.

"We have no say in it either!" Helplessness was written all over the host's face. He then announced the next challenger to come onstage: Team Void's second-year rookie, Ge Caijie.

Ge Caijie walked onstage as Ye Xiu watched him all the while. This was already the fifth person, but Ge Caijie, this second-year rookie with the commanding presence of a veteran, didn't waver because of any of this. When the host asked him, he announced the player he wished to challenge without any hesitation: "Ye Xiu."

The host didn't make a sound, and he put on a face of helplessness as he looked at Ye Xiu. His gleeful laughter was concealed in his stomach.

"There's really no end, huh? I'm going to throw this match!" Ye Xiu said.

"How could you do that!" The host laughed.

"Let's go!" Ye Xiu didn't say anything else as he walked toward the competitor booth. Ge Caijie didn't say anything either, and as he walked, he was already adjusting his emotions for the upcoming battle. Although this was only the All-Star Weekend, he took this very seriously, for he didn't want to lose. In Ye Xiu's individual match win streak this season, Ge Caijie was one of the ones he had crushed, but in that battle, Ge Caijie felt that he had still had a bit of a chance. If he had better handled a few details, if he were able to more thoroughly address a few problems…

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, there was no way he'd brought two copies of it this time, right?

This is what Ge Caijie thought. Battling with two Myriad Manifestations Umbrellas had clearly been specifically guarding against the Exorcist's Seal Talisman. There was no reason for him to bring them with him everywhere?

And even if he had brought both, Ge Caijie didn't need to worry too much.

The Seal Talisman was a form of suppression, used to give Ye Xiu pressure, forcing him to change his techniques. If he didn't use the Seal Talisman, that might even be more useful than the effects of his using it.

Ge Caijie mentally organized the data he had from their last battle. He took a deep breath, stretched his fingers, and his character loaded in.

"Alright, next we have the fifth round of the Rookie Challenge, with Void's rookie Ge Caijie challenging Happy's Ye Xiu. These two players met in Round 14 this season. Does Ge Caijie plan on using this opportunity to wash away his previous loss? Okay, the battle officially begins, the two characters appear on the two ends of the map, this map is…"

"Huh?"

The host was stunned, the entire crowd was stunned. After a beat of silence, booing. Even though Ye Xiu had been constantly booed by the Tyranny fans from the very start, this time was undoubtedly the loudest.

Because this match had already ended, after only one second.

The only trace left was the message that Ye Xiu had sent in the chat: "GG."

Ye Xiu really did throw the match!

Chapter 1249: Everyone Come at Once

GG!

He actually just typed GG!

In the next moment, Lord Grim very naturally logged out from the game, and the system announced that Blue Exorcist had won.

It ended just like this?

BOOOO! The sound was so loud that even with the aid of the host's audio equipment, his voice was completely drowned out by the surging boos of displeasure from the crowd. In this moment, that booing sound could only be described by one word: deafening.

That's right, it was deafening.

During the festive atmosphere of the All-Star Weekend Tournament, someone was actually greeted by such a loud, angry boo.

"He truly deserves to be called God Ye Xiu…" the host thought, with a face full of tears. Even though it was just an All-Star match, there was still a referee, and now that referee was sitting there, completely dumbstruck.

Ye Xiu walked out from the player booth, but he didn't leave the stage, instead directly walking back to the side of the host.

"God Ye Xiu, you're really…" the host didn't even know what to say. Who had experience dealing with this kind of unprecedented situation?

"I kept my promise, aren't I amazing?" Ye Xiu said.

"..."

At the other side, Ye Xiu's opponent Ge Caijie also walked out of the player booth and headed back to the center of the stage with a face full of regret. He was obviously extremely disappointed that he couldn't fight against Ye Xiu but could only helplessly and silently leave the stage.

Ye Xiu and the host watched Ge Caijie's lonely figure leaving. They watched for a long time before the host suddenly asked, "God Ye Xiu, how could you have the heart to disappoint the cute rookies like this?"

"Sigh..." Ye Xiu let out a deep breath. Ge Caijie's disappointment was something he could also see clearly, and for a moment, he felt a little bad about it. The Alliance and Team Tyranny could at most pick out those rookies who wanted to challenge Ye Xiu and group them together. To these rookies, challenging Ye Xiu was something that they were very sincere about. But when they went onstage, filled with anticipation, they were unable to do anything before being sent off with a "GG.". They had won nominally, yes, but in these All-Star matches, winning or losing was never the most important thing. The most important thing was how they won or lost. Just sending them off with a "GG" was very satisfying to Ye Xiu, but to these rookies who wanted to challenge him, it couldn't have been any more cruelcrueller.

Having said this, the host snuck a peek at Ye Xiu's expression and knew that Ye Xiu had been a little bit moved by his words. Obviously, he was also reluctant to disappoint the rookies in this way.

"When the next two contestants come, if they still want to challenge God Ye Xiu, will you… still GG immediately?" the host asked him.

Ye Xiu looked at him and asked, "There's still two more?"

"Yes, there are," the host confirmed.

"Then there's no need for them to fight one by one, let everyone come at once!" Ye Xiu said.

"What?" the host was at a loss for words.

"I'm saying, let them come at once!" Ye Xiu said.

"You mean… 1v2?" the host was stunned.

The boos took a great deal of effort to quieten down, but when they heard this conversation, the whole stadium was dead silent. Shortly afterwards, however, the booing began again, only this time it clearly wasn't as valiant as before. After all, sending out such vigorous boos of displeasure also required a lot of energy, and it was evident that the Team Tyranny fans were already tired, but they still persevered. They wanted to kill this shameless archenemy of theirs with their booes. GG? 1v2? Is there anything you can't do?

"This… isn't really in accordance to the rules, right?" the host said.

"What are you being so serious for? If I don't mind, then just let them come up! Who are they?" Ye Xiu asked.

"It's Zeng Xinran of Team Hundred Blossoms and Song Qiying of Team Tyranny," the host replied dumbly.

"Alright!" Ye Xiu grabbed the microphone from the host's hands, raised it to his mouth and called, "Zeng Xinran of Team Hundred Blossoms and Song Qiying of Team Tyranny, the two of you kids can both come at once!"

"This this this…..." the host hurriedly wrestled the microphone back. Momentarily, he had no idea how to deal with the situation, and could only desperately communicate with the backstage team for ideas. Team Hundred Blossoms' Zeng Xinran and Team Tyranny's Song Qiying also had no idea what to do. Rookies were the ones who took the rules most seriously, but Ye Xiu was doing something that clearly didn't follow the rules and wanted them to join in, leaving them at a loss.

"Then… the two rookies, do you mind this arrangement? If you don't mind, then please come onstage!" After the host's rapid communication with the people backstage, they eventually decided not to stop Ye Xiu. After all, it was All-Stars, where they were looking to make things more lively. If Ye Xiu was so brave as to want to 1v2, then let him do it. At the end of the day, if he lost, the only person who would lose face is him, and to Team Tyranny, they absolutely wouldn't mind.

Zeng Xinran and Song Qiying were both in the player seats looking at each other, waiting to see how the other would respond before deciding what to do, but after taking a look, the other person's response was to wait for them to react. With no ideas left, the two of them went to consult their team captains for advice.

"Just go!" the two captains said. After receiving their orders, the two players went onstage.

"Ah… the two rookies have already arrived. Then let me check first, is the player that the two of you want to challenge God Ye Xiu?" the host asked.

The two rookies were still a little out of it, so one of them just said yes while the other nodded his head.

"Oh… then next will be a 1v2 battle, the two of you will face God Ye Xiu together, are there any problems?" the host asked.

The two rookies glanced at each other. They were already on stage, what problems could there be? The two of them nodded.

"Great, then let's hurry up and start!" Ye Xiu waved his hands and headed towards the stage.

"Then, do the two of you want to say anything before you begin your challenge?" the host asked as he interviewed the two rookies.

"Uh… I… I have nothing that I want to say." Zeng Xinran was clearly quite nervous.

"Then what about you?" the host asked the other player, Song Qiying.

"This is against the rules..." Song Qiying said with a conflicted expression. It appeared that this arrangement was very difficult for him to stomach.

Having reached this point, the host didn't want to get side-tracked anymore and applauded the two rookies before directing them to their booth.

The competition was no longer an individual round and was instead set as a team battle. Ye Xiu alone made up one team, while Zeng Xinran and Song Qiying made up the other team.

"Little Song, teach this guy a lesson!!" the shouts in the stadium resounded. This was Team Tyranny's stadium after all, and Song Qiying could be the future successor of Desert Dust, so he naturally received a lot of attention. On top of that, he was about to face Team Tyranny's bitter rival of many years, Ye Xiu, so the fans were extremely excited, not caring about whether or not it was 1v2, deciding to cheer first and think about it later.

"Alright, then rookie challengers 6 and 7 will fight against Ye Xiu together, which is what Ye Xiu requested himself. The match is about to begin," the host announced. As the map loaded, the host suddenly felt flustered. This guy… he wouldn't pile these two together and then just send the two of them off with a "GG", right?

Having suddenly thought of this terrifying possibility, the host felt extremely restless. As the map finished loading and the players entered the game, the host could barely watch any longer. Has he said "GG" already?

The crowd was still quiet, so… he shouldn't have, right?

The host looked at the screen and finally let out a deep breath. There was no GG. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was charging out directly, was he getting ready to take the competition seriously?

But if it's a 1v2, even against two rookies, Ye Xiu should have a hard time, right?

Team Tyranny's successor for Han Wenqing, Song Qiying, now had a soaring reputation within the pro circle. Because of Team Tyranny rotating their player roster this season, he had very consistent opportunities to appear onstage, and iwas a strong contender for the Best Rookie award. In contrast, Team Hundred Blossom's Zeng Xinran looked inferior. The character he used was Tang Hao's character during his time at Team Hundred Blossom's, the Brawler Delillo. In Season 8 of the All-Star Tournament, Tang Hao used this very Delillo to defeat Lin Jingyan's Demon Subduer, convincingly winning the title of Number One Brawler. But now, Tang Hao's character was Demon Subduer, leaving Delillo in the hands of Zeng Xinran. Number One Brawler? Zeng Xinran was still extremely far away from this title.

In his first match, he encountered Ye Xiu. During that match, he could hardly play at all because he was too nervous; every joint in his hands was stiff. Luckily, the team didn't abandon him because of his first poor performance. Gradually, he adapted to the atmosphere of the competitive scene and became less and less tense. But that nightmare of a first match had still left a shadow in his heart.

This was really too awful of a memory for him. Zeng Xinran desperately wanted to find a way to cleanse himself of this memory, so he signed up for the All-Stars's Rookie Challenge. From the very start, he wanted to challenge Ye Xiu, letting himself rise from the same place where he had once fallen.

Today, I will not be nervous again!

From the start of the match, Zeng Xinran was very active.

"Hey, make sure you don't drag me down!" he told Song Qiying. Song Qiying was a first-year rookie just like himself, but his fame and reputation had far surpassed his own. Zeng Xinran couldn't complain. Who asked his very first performance to be so awful? Even so, he could still feel a sense of inferiority, so at this very moment, he wanted to prove himself where he had previously failed.

"Since we have two people, let's cooperate a bit more!" Song Qiying said.

"Cooperate? The two of us? How can we cooperate?" Zeng Xinran said. The two of them weren't familiar with each other at all, but inexplicably ended up fighting side-by-side. Cooperation? With this person? Zeng Xinran had no idea how to do so.

"You're a Brawler, I'm a Striker, from a class perspective, we can at least coordinate our low-level skills. What low-level skills did you add skill points into?" Song Qiying asked.

"Reinforced Iron Bones, Back Throw and Fling," Zeng Xinran replied.

"Oh, you really like grab skills! I've learnt Fling and Dismantling Throw, maybe we can make use of these." Song Qiying said.

"How do we make use of it?" Zeng Xinran asked.

"Have you not paid attention to the strategies used when two characters with the same class play together? It's in fashion now!" Song Qiying said.

"Ah..." Zeng Xinran started to recall. Strategies involving two characters with the same class were indeed being used by many teams nowadays. Team Blue Rain's Dual Blade Masters, Team Tiny Herb's Dual Witches, Team Misty Rain's Dual Sharpshooters, and even less needed to be said about Team Void's Dual Ghostblades.

How did they fight together?

Chapter 1250: Rookies’ Partnership

The players who frequented the All-Stars list would not make a big deal out of the matches here, but most rookies did not share this sentiment. This was especially true for many first-year rookies. They had very few opportunities to get on stage, and all had a thirst to prove themselves. The All-Star matches received plenty of attention, and the rookies could face strong opponents, which made it quite a good opportunity to show off their skills. It didn't really matter if the matches were not played very seriously. Anyone would brag if they defeated the Battle God, the Great Gunner or the Sword Saint.

For this reason, the rookies were quite enthusiastic for the All-Stars Weekend. Enthusiasm translated to diligence. If they came on stage and faced a God, they would deep down be hoping to win, regardless of how courteous they appeared to be. Right now, Zeng Xinran and Song Qiying were about to play in a two on one. Even though Song Qiying felt apprehensive since it was against the rules, his mind was still focused on winning as soon as the match began. Two on one meant employing tactics for a two on one; Song Qiying did not entertain the thought of deliberately creating a one on one scenario in this situation. Thus, as soon as they entered battle, he actively communicated with his partner. The two weren't too familiar with each other, and it was probably a bad idea to rely on pure observation and skill to reach a tacit understanding. Therefore, Song Qiying hoped to communicate a basic battle plan first.

A battle plan that involved two characters of the same class.

Technically, they were not the same sub-class. They only shared some low-level skills, but approaching the current problem from this angle was undoubtedly the quickest way for them to find common ground. Song Qiying's judgement here was quite spot-on.

Same class duo tactics?

Zeng Xinran was also a reasonably diligent rookie. When he heard Song Qiying mention this, he immediately thought of some same-class duos in strong teams. The double-act of a same class duo could be said to be the most prevalent type of cooperative play in the pro scene. His Brawler and Song Qiying's Striker could qualify for a bit of a double-act as well.

Except...

Song Qiying was admittedly apprehensive about a two on one at first, but still managed to focus when the match started. But Zeng Xinran had other plans. What he wanted the most was just to defeat Ye Xiu, displaying his own talent in the process. A two on one? He didn't really think that far. When he heard Song Qiying's suggestion for cooperating, he didn't dismiss it entirely, but did he put too much thought into it either.

"Yeah… I guess as a Striker and a Brawler we could…"

"It can wait! The opponent is already closing in!" Zeng Xinran interrupted Song Qiying, and had his Brawler Delillo rush forward to meet Lord Grim.

"Don't be too hasty!" Song Qiying called out quickly. He had quite a few ideas for a Striker and Brawler duo. Don't forget that his team Tyranny currently had the same duo, made up of the most experienced Striker and Brawler in Glory history! But right now, it didn't seem like his partner was patient enough or very interested in cooperating…

"I'll test the waters. Follow up appropriately!" Zeng Xinran didn't refuse Song Qiying entirely; he was well aware of his own limits. Defeating God Ye Xiu, who had a sixteen win-streak in the individual competition? Of course Zeng Xinran had this desire, but he didn't dare have that much confidence in himself. But at least within the partnership between him and Song Qiying, he was happy to give himself the main role. It didn't matter that right now, Song Qiying was slightly more reputable than him. Since they were both rookies, Zeng Xinran had some confidence that he could steal the spotlight from Song Qiying.

"How do you plan to test the waters?" Song Qiying asked, while quickly following close behind with his character River Sunset. The two rookies could keep communicating because the voice channels were open. The All-Stars matches were slightly more lax on the rules and had never forbidden voice chat. However, with the recent lively debate about voice chat in the Pro League, the arrangement at the All-Stars matches also doubled as a trial of sorts.

"We'll look for an opportunity," Zeng Xinran answered.

"At least have some semblance of a plan!" Song Qiying was alarmed by how casual Zeng Xinran was being.

"Okay, I'll go first, you follow up." Zeng Xinran revealed his plan.

"..." Song Qiying was looking for something to say but became lost for words.

"Dodge!" Zeng Xinran suddenly shouted.

Boom!

Lord Grim's raised his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella. It blazed with gunfire and attacked the rookie duo from afar.

"He has a significant range advantage over us, I'm sure he won't let us get close too easily. We need to flank him," Song Qiying called out.

"What's your plan then?" Zeng Xinran said, while having Delillo continuously roll. Lord Grim unleashed a never-ending stream of skills from gunner, mage or whatever classes; his selection criterion simply being that the attack range was enough to reach the enemy. Even though Zeng Xinran's brawler had some mid-range skills, he was still forcibly zoned out.

"Split up and flank!" Song Qiying said.

"Fuck, and here I thought you had some master plan!" Zeng Xinran said.

"Flanking isn't just charging from two different directions! We need to watch the opponent's attack rhythm and skill rotations, and find the optimal angle of approach," Song Qiying explained.

"Blah blah blah, just tell me which angle!" Zeng Xinran yelled.

"I'll take the left. You go right," Song Qiying said.

"Could you be any more vague?" Zeng Xinran said.

"Split up first, we'll look for opportunities," Song Qiying called out.

"Isn't that what I said in the first place?" Zeng Xinran muttered. The two rookies' characters, Striker River Sunset and Brawler Delillo, took the left and right respectively, and began to close their distance.

"Spread further! Further! Okay, line it up!" Song Qiying called, while observing Lord Grim and dodging his attacks. The two characters ran up and managed to form a straight line with Lord Grim in the middle.

"Sweet, that reduced his damage output by a lot. Cover me while I try to get into attack range!" Zeng Xinran yelled.

"How am I meant to cover you?" Song Qiying felt gloomy. Strikers had the shortest effective attack range out of all 24 classes in Glory. Since when did this class provide cover fire?

"Be forceful and charge, attract as much of his attention as you can!" Zeng Xinran said

"That's nice of you, letting me be the cannon fodder," Song Qiying complained, but still had River Sunset charge forward. He believed that Zeng Xinran's suggestion was still the best way forward.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

River Sunset quickly activated this skill which gave Super Armor and increased defence, then followed up with Cloud Body and charged in forcibly.

As expected after seeing such a forceful charge, Lord Grim focused more of his attacks in the direction of River Sunset. He also started retreating to widen the distance between the two.

"Good job!" Zeng Xinran praised; he felt the pressure towards his own side lessen noticeably. Delillo seized the opportunity and charged forward madly.

Should I focus on my left or right?

Ye Xiu seemed to have been put in an awkward spot. Song Qiying's River Sunset seemingly aimed to draw his attention, but the threat of his every step was very real. If Lord Grim toned down his attacks towards River Sunset, Song Qiying would waltz right up to Lord Grim without hesitation. Strikers would not be able to demonstrate full potential in battle unless they were really up close.

What will he do?

Song Qiying carefully watched Lord Grim's every move.

"Don't forget to maintain the angle!" Song Qiying yelled. He noticed that after Lord Grim retreated perpendicularly to their two characters, the angle between them was shrinking. This would allow Lord Grim to switch fire more freely; they definitely shouldn't make this so easy for Lord Grim.

"You maintain it!" Zeng Xinran answered firmly.

Song Qiying was speechless. Although keeping the angle by one person was achievable, it was more flexible if both contributed! Zeng Xinran really wanted to be the primary attacker no matter what!

There was no time to argue in the midst of battle. Song Qiying felt helpless and could only do all the dirty work that the other guy didn't want a part of. He moved sideways to maintain the Lord Grim sandwich, while trying his best to close the distance and exert some pressure.

Lord Grim concentrated even more gunfire towards River Sunset.

"Chance!" Song Qiying called out.

"You don't say!" Under Zeng Xinran's control, Delillo sent out a Powerful Knee Strike. It wasn't aimed at dealing damage but rather to close the distance, and Delillo managed to forcibly propel himself into attack range.

"Here I come!" Zeng Xinran shouted loudly.

"Don't rush in!" Song Qiying saw this and shouted in return, but Delillo already used the Powerful Knee Strike. It was too late to cancel the skill; in any case, it wasn't like Zeng Xinran would care about anything Song Qiying said in this situation.

This is bad!

A flank attack didn't seem complicated, but it actually required balance and precision between the two partners. Delillo's advance was too hasty and brought about an imbalance; this was especially disadvantageous for Song Qiying's Striker, as they needed to be up close and personal before they could attack at all. This gave a very good chance for the opponent to launch a fierce counter-attack.

Song Qiying analyzed this correctly, but he knew he had no way to stop Zeng Xinran. He could only have River Sunset charge forward recklessly, but...

"Behind you!" Song Qiying shouted. Lord Grim used Shadow Clone Technique and teleported behind Delillo. Zeng Xinran threw a brick towards Lord Grim; he was so excited he got within attack range that he thought he was invincible. After hearing Song Qiying's warning, he realized something was wrong; but it was far too late to react. A spurt of blood bloomed out from Delillo's neck. Ye Xiu mercilessly had Lord Grim use Cut-Throat.

Exactly! This imbalance!

Delillo rushed in too quickly and disrupted the coordination with River Sunset. From the current distance, River Sunset could not throw out any attacks. Zeng Xinran was currently one on one against Ye Xiu, and after being ambushed from behind, lost all initiative. Song Qiying could only watch from afar. He had no way to intervene so he urged River Sunset to quickly close the distance.

But... would Ye Xiu have Lord Grim wait for River Sunset to arrive?

Of course not.

A Falling Flower Pam sent Delillo crashing into River Sunset. Lord Grim took this opportunity to retreat and increase the distance, once again starting to kite the two characters.

Chapter 1251: Do as Promised

As expected...

The situation did not stray from Song Qiying's expectations. Ever since Zeng Xinran took a risk in using Powerful Knee Strike to break the stability of the situation, Song Qiying had been expecting such a circumstance. Ye Xiu had given Delillo a beating, taking advantage of the fact that Song Qiying's Striker would still need a while to arrive, and had then beat a hasty retreat.

Zeng Xinran was flushed with anger and embarrassment. Even though he might've been facing a God, getting tricked so easily by a Shadow Clone was unacceptable. He had gotten too excited; calm down! Zeng Xinran took a deep breath.

Zeng Xinran immediately calmed down, but his partner, Song Qiying, who was always telling him to not rush, seemed to lose control. River Sunset charged recklessly at Lord Grim.

"Hey, slow down!" This time, it was Zeng Xinran who warned Song Qiying.

Song Qiying didn't know if he should cry or laugh. These things depended on the situation! Speeding up or slowing down, that was all about the appropriate pacing at the time. There was no such thing as always going slow and steady or fast and hard. His Striker had gotten this rare chance to close in on Lord Grim, one he hadn't had yet in this match. If he slowed down now, then wasn't that letting this opportunity escape? How could he slow down now? On the contrary, you should pull yourself together and go on the offensive. Your Brawler is still in attack range!

It was just unfortunate that Zeng Xinran was calming himself down. He calmly watched Lord Grim run away, calmly watched River Sunset charge, and calmly told Song Qiying to calm down.

"This is an opportunity!!" Song Qiying really didn't know what to say anymore. It wasn't like he could give this guy a lecture on how, precisely, to act in such a situation.

God! He was a pro player. Why was his Glory IQ so low? Wasn't his ability to read the situation just a little too low?

At Song Qiying's shout, Zeng Xinran finally reacted. This really wasn't a time to stop attacking! River Sunset had gotten this golden opportunity to finally close in. This was the closest they had gotten to Lord Grim. Why did he… stop?

Delillo hurriedly readjusted himself. Though he was now behind River Sunset, he had quite a few mid-ranged attacks. A brick was already flying out with deadly precision, but Ye Xiu wasn't dead. Lord Grim turned his body, dodging.

Soaring Tiger!

Song Qiying was glad that Zeng Xinran finally cleared his head. This attack was a little late, but it finally arrived, at least. As Lord Grim moved to dodge, River Sunset flew forwards with Soaring Tiger. This level 60 ultimate activated swiftly. River Sunset shot forwards feet first towards Lord Grim, arriving in front of the other in the blink of an eye.

　

This was an ultimate, an ultimate which Lord Grim's low leveled skills would have trouble facing off against. This attack came suddenly, furiously, right as Lord Grim moved to dodge the Brick. Song Qiying's timing was extremely precise.

It was just unfortunate that this skill was, in the end, a little too late. Zeng Xinran's self-calming had cost them the opportune moment. Their attempt at making up for it wasn't good enough. Lord Grim finished dodging the Brick and then sidestepped again, avoiding the Soaring Tiger, too.

However, River Sunset had finally come in front of Lord Grim. Yet this wasn't an alleyway with only two ways to run. If you spun 360 degrees, which way wasn't forwards? Lord Grim swerved away from River Sunset's direction and continued to run.

Still want to run?

River Sunset's Soaring Tiger hadn't ended, but he had finally managed to close in on Lord Grim. Lord Grim was finally within attack range, and how could Song Qiying let Lord Grim pull away again?

Fling!

River Sunset reached out towards Lord Grim with both his hands. Lord Grim hurriedly jumped backwards and River Sunset missed. However, he then bent his elbow, stepping forwards, fist flung out.

Straight Punch!

The punch following the Fling was headed towards Lord Grim's chest, but...

Sword Draw!

Lord Grim didn't dodge, but unsheathed his sword and countered.

　

Which was faster, Sword Draw or Straight Punch? No one could see clearly. All they knew was that River Sunset's fist hit Lord Grim's chest while a splash of blood was flicked into the air as the blade swept past.

　

River Sunset stumbled backwards. Sword Draw's momentum wasn't completely negligible. But Lord Grim? His sword had already been retracted and the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella was set in front of his chest. Utilizing the momentum from the Straight Punch, Lord Grim would be able to fly back a significant distance if he followed with an Aerial Cannon. Did Song Qiying miscalculate? Should he not have used Straight Punch?

　

No, that wasn't so.

If it was one versus one, then his choice of attack would simply be pushing away a target he had worked hard to close in on. However, this wasn't a one on one. Lord Grim, having pushed away, wanted to use this chance to run, but Zeng Xinran's Delillo had already arrived. He wasn't so stupid that he didn't know what he should do. Delillo had rushed forwards to block Lord Grim's escape route. His hands stretched out, throwing a Fling out at Lord Grim.

Falling Light Blade.

Ye Xiu suddenly activate this skill, forcing Lord Grim, who was still airborne, to turn. Delillo hit air, hurrying to follow up with another attack. Yet, Lord Grim had already turned around and knocked Delillo into bending over with a Knee Strike.

This was a Brawler skill, yet it was now used on the Brawler Delillo. Zeng Xinran was angered, but he wasn't given a chance to counterattack. After the Knee Strike, Lord Grim used Fling and picked him up, tossing him at River Sunset.

Zeng Xinran seemed like he had been bullied again, but his task was complete. He had successfully hindered Lord Grim, who had planned on fleeing with Aerial Cannon. River Sunset was already charging forth, dodging the tossed over Delillo and swinging his fists.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

Shockingly, Song Qiying activated this powerful skill. River Sunset punched and kicked, leaving afterimages in his wake, fiercely charging towards Lord Grim

But that was when the figure in his line of sight blurred and Lord Grim somehow vanished.

What?

Song Qiying was shocked. In the next moment, River Sunset's waist had been grabbed. He was raised up then thrown backwards, smashed onto the ground upside down. Ferocious Tiger Flurry's powerful strikes were immediately brought to as halt.

Song Qiying was befuddled. How did Lord Grim suddenly get behind him?

Shadow Clone Technique? There was no clone though!

Teleportation? It didn't seem like it. Lord Grim had blurred away as if he had used some sort of movement technique to get behind. However, there wasn't a single skill in any of the 24 classes that would let a character immediately get behind another character!

Yes, there was no such skill, which was why Lord Grim had actually used two skills in that moment.

Charge, Shining Cut.

These two low level skills, a Knight skill and an Assassin skill, were often used as movement skills despite being offensive skills. However, many people only realized this when the screen showed a slow motion playback.

This was because it had all happened too fast. These two skills had been used by Ye Xiu to move Lord Grim, but he had only moved two steps.

One step to River Sunset's side, then another behind.

Using two skills to achieve this movement in such a small area… What precise mechanics, what swift hand speed!

The entire audience was stunned, even the pro player stands were filled with shocked faces.

How high had his APM gone in that moment?

Many people had wandered to this thought. However, the screen didn't show the calculations for this burst of speed like it usually would. Could it be that he was so fast that the system couldn't process it anymore?

Even more shocked faces appeared. As for Lord Grim's retreat, no one cared about that anymore. Everyone still had their heads raised towards the screen, watching the continuous replay of Lord Grim completing the two steps with Charge and Shining Cut.

This was practically supernatural...

The entire venue sunk into silence. Even the Tyranny fans, who never liked Ye Xiu, were unable to offer any boos in that moment.

"What is this?" Discussion soon erupted amongst the pro players from Rookies to Gods, everyone was exchanging opinions.

"In reality, it's just a Z-Shake," Blue Rain's Huang Shaotian said.

"Just?" Yu Wenzhou smiled.

Huang Shaotian stopped speaking.

Of course he couldn't use "just". Managing to execute these two skills in two steps. If it was him...

"Don't forget, it isn't just unleashing the two skills and moving his character for him." Yu Wenzhou seemed to know that Huang Shaotian was comparing this to himself and reminded him. "There's also the mechanics required to switch the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's form."

Yes, one was a Knight's Charge, Priest class; one was an Assassin's Shining Cut, Nightwalker class. If the weapon wasn't switched, there was no way to execute the two skills.

Huang Shaotian's complexion went a little off. Could he do it? He suddenly didn't feel like pursuing such an answer.

"Z-Shake, hm…" Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi had also figured out the foundation of this technique.

"In the end, he really does still use the crudest style!" Wang Jiexi exclaimed. The Tiny Herb members around him were all looking at each other.

Z-Shake, a basic movement technique, but in such a space, using these two skills to accomplish it was… This was skill beyond supernatural talent.

The pro players were all wondering in their hearts if they could accomplish this or not.

As for the match?

Who would pursue the results of a match that not many people cared about in the first place? What everyone was interested in was if Ye Xiu would do any more shocking maneuvers.

The only ones who would care about the results were probably just those Tyranny fans who hated Ye Xiu. They hoped that Ye Xiu, who had said he'd fight one on two, would lose the match and lose face.

In the end, it really was as they had hoped for. Song Qiying and Zeng Xinran really did end up winning in this two on one.

Booing sounded, but it was very weak. This was because many people could tell that Ye Xiu was clearly not giving it his all in the latter half of the match. This allowed Song Qiying and Zeng Xinran to grasp the advantage and claim victory.

Yes, they had gasped the advantage later. That meant, in the first half, Ye Xiu had the advantage despite fighting one against two.

If he continued that way, then what would be the result? Everyone knew, including Song Qiying and Zeng Xinran.

This kind of victory was nothing to be proud of.

"Senior really did go easy on us." Song Qiying pointed this out directly, seeming to have a problem with it.　

"Pro players should always do as promised. I said I'd throw the match, so I had to!" Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1252: Hot-Blooded Dodgeball

Do as promised? He said he'd throw the match, so he threw the match?

As expected, the crowd once again erupted with boos, but Song Qiying's expression right now was a bit subtle. He reacted very quickly - his eyes swiveled to the player area just offstage, where Happy's players were gathered.

If talking about doing as promised, wasn't there a player from Happy that was the biggest joke in history?

Happy's Tang Rou, after failing to complete her promise of a 1v3, didn't follow through and quit Glory!

But when Ye Xiu said "do as promised," he promised to throw the match, and then threw the match…

Throwing a match truly wasn't anything pretty. Even on the All-Star stage when most people weren't putting in their full effort, it was rare for anyone to throw a match as obviously and bluntly as Ye Xiu had. He'd even used a "GG."

Do as promised, but he'd promised to throw a match. Ye Xiu's words, were they supposed to be ironic?

Aside from Song Qiying, it seemed that most people for now hadn't thought of Tang Rou. Right now, the Tyranny fans' aggro toward Ye Xiu was very stable. Even though the Rookie Challenge had entirely ended now, they were still targeting their fire to send Ye Xiu off the stage. This Day 1 of the All-Star Weekend, no matter how you looked at it, seemed to be designed for Tyranny fans. First was that strong commemoration of Tyranny's Captain Han Wenqing weathering ten years of Glory, which let the Tyranny fans shed a tear. And then, it became focused on the primary target of Tyranny fans' hatred, Ye Xiu, as all of the rookies lined up to challenge him.

Even though Ye Xiu had pulled off the unprecedented circumstances of "GG" and "1v2," it had to be said that this year's All-Star Weekend Day 1 was still quite exciting.

Typically, there were no formal press conferences planned for the All-Star Weekend. The reporters stationed by various media organizations had their own designated seating area, but only the media groups with partnerships had the chance to enter and directly interact with players. This included the Esports Channel that was in charge of the television broadcast, as well as the most authoritative Esports Home. But most of their time in the stadium was just spent watching. Only when there was a suitable opportunity would they search for players to exchange a few words. No one anticipated a formal interview at a setting like this, and no one would try to get one.

Today? The reporters were of course gathering the opinions of the players of the various teams, their opinions of the ten-year Han Wenqing, their opinions of the rookies lining up for their challenge, and their opinions of Ye Xiu, who was so fed up that he used a "GG."

The topics wouldn't be very serious. It was the All-Star Weekend, it was all in good fun. Even things like GG or throwing matches, only someone with a waterlogged brain would use that as ammunition for an attack. To be honest, the reporters quite welcomed these unexpected situations that Ye Xiu caused. They were a bit tired of writing the same thing about the respecting the old and loving the young when it came to the Rookie Challenge.

After a few performance events planned by the organizers, Day 1 of the All-Star Weekend officially came to a close. The pair of death rivals, Han Wenqing and Ye Xiu, became the stars of this day. Han Wenqing's ten years of persistence left behind strong emotions; Ye Xiu's seven consecutive rookie challenges left behind chaos.

Some older Glory players couldn't help but reminisce, this wasn't even the first time Ye Xiu had experienced all seven rookies wanting to challenge him.

But that time, Ye Xiu had honestly and straightforwardly played seven matches with those rookies. It had been nothing like the ridiculous scene today.

The older the ginger, the spicier it was. Ye Xiu alone demonstrated this point most vividly.

"You're really something…" As the pro players mingled after the conclusion of the event, a number of players came to jokingly complain to Ye Xiu in the backstage passageways.

Thrown among this crowd, Chen Guo really felt like a dazzled fan. Once upon a time, these figures were all high and mighty, but now, they were all gathered right beside her, and everyone was really very ordinary. Just from this setting, it was impossible to tell how fierce were the characters that these players controlled in the world of Glory.

Li Xun, the Void Assassin who loved one-hit kills, was currently complaining to Royal Style's Tian Sen about his toothache. It looked like Tian Sen gave him a phone number, recommending some dentist.

Chu Yunxiu, Misty Rain's captain and the idol of female players, was accusing Zhang Xinjie, originally from City X, of giving her a bad recommendation. The hot and sour rice noodles from a food street he had recommended to her didn't taste good at all.

"Too sour!" Chu Yunxiu said, baring her teeth as though she could still taste them.

"You probably put in too much vinegar!" said Zhang Xinjie, very serious.

"How much are you supposed to put in?" Chu Yunxiu asked.

"Seven-tenths of a spoon. Just use the little plastic spoon that comes with it," Zhang Xinjie said.

Spoon? Who used a spoon to add vinegar? And seven-tenths?

Chu Yunxiu bore her teeth again and directly abandoned Zhang Xinjie to look for her close friend Su Mucheng.

Miracle's Guo Shao and Tyranny's Song Qiying, those two youths somehow ended up together. Amidst the crowd of seniors, the two were holding a quiet discussion, occasionally shooting glances toward Happy's players, stopping at Ye Xiu. It looked like these two were currently studying how to knock over the mountain that was Ye Xiu.

Chen Guo discovered that only the discussions among rookies tended to revolve around Glory. The older players tended to talk about much more mundane topics.

301's Yang Cong and Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi were talking about recent housing prices.

Jiang Botao and Xu Bin were talking about European soccer.

Tang Hao was complaining to Zou Yuan about the weather in City N. He was originally in Hundred Blossoms, and City K was his home; only after transferring to Wind Howl did he have to move to the city they were in, City N. It had now been almost two years, but it looked like he still didn't much like his new city.

Such ordinary topics allowed Chen Guo to truly feel that these… were all very much real, living, breathing creatures.

In the long passageway, the players didn't rest. They directly walked outside of the stadium, and then naturally said their goodbyes to each other, all going to their own team vehicles to head to the hotels where they were staying. Some teams were staying at the same hotels, and so the players instantly started mixing together and hitching rides randomly, continuing the topics they hadn't finished chatting about.

Compared to normal matchdays, the atmosphere was much more relaxed between all of the players. Chen Guo could feel this clearly.

The All-Star Weekend was really a good event! Amidst it all, Chen Guo smiled.

The second day of the All-Star Weekend soon arrived. Compared to Day 1, Day 2's events were bit more enriching, and there was some interaction with the live audience. They would choose some audience members to participate in the events alongside the pro players.

The first event would involve pitting Glory characters against each other in mini-games. In these past years, the All-Star Weekend would use MODs specially developed by the Glory creators. It was common that afterwards, they would become available within the normal Glory game, enhancing and diversifying the content of the game.

And what was this year's mini-game? The All-Star Weekend had already made a public preview. First up was Hot-Blooded Dodgeball!

It was called dodgeball, but in reality, it didn't strictly follow the typical rules of dodgeball. From the information that had been officially released, this game was more like the folk game sandbag toss.

The rules were as follows: the participating teams would send three players onstage, and two teams would be pitted against each other at a time. Each team would take one turn defending and one turn attacking. The final victory was determined by how long the turn lasted. For this event, there would be eight participating teams, five of them professional, and the other three made from randomly-selected audience members.

The players from the five participating pro teams quickly gathered onstage. The audience saw that they were players from Samsara, Thunderclap, Tiny Herb, Miracle, and Happy.

These five teams were selected with some care. Samsara was the team with the vast lead, Thunderclap had demonstrated unexpectedly strong team performances, Tiny Herb hadn't lost a single group arena yet, and Happy and Miracle were the two new teams in the Alliance that were doing unexpectedly well. These five teams were all attention-grabbing teams.

There were only players from these five teams…

From Samsara was Vice-captain Jiang Botao leading Assassin Wu Qi and Blade Master Du Ming.

Thunderclap had Captain Xiao Shiqin himself on the roster, leading Elementalist Dai Yanqi and the Sharpshooter that transferred from Misty Rain, Lu Yining.

Tiny Herb had Gao Yingjie, Liu Xiaobie, and Zhou Yebai.

Miracle had Shen Jian, Guo Shao, and Battle Mage Jia Xing.

As for Happy, there was Wei Chen, Steamed Bun, and… the player who had yet to appear onstage this season, someone whose first appearance would be in the fun atmosphere of All-Stars: Luo Ji.

It was his first time on such a large stage, and Luo Ji was clearly a bit terrified. Even though he knew that this was just a game, but he couldn't help but be nervous. As he stood onstage, he had no idea what to do with his hands and feet.

"Pull yourself together, you have me here!" Steamed Bun said to him, patting his own chest.

Having teammates beside him did allow some of Luo Ji's nervousness to dissipate. For the first time ever, Luo Ji thought that having Steamed Bun next to him was pretty nice.

There weren't a lot of All-Star level players participating in this event. This was also a way of purposefully making this more lowkey. For one, it gave other pro players a chance to participate in the excitement, and for another, it saved the highest-level show of the All-Star Weekend for Day 3, with the All-Star Competition.

The pro players went onstage, and then it was time to select audience members, one two three four five six seven eight nine, nine lucky audience members were chosen. Each was asked which team they supported, which players they liked and so on, which took up a bit of time. Fortunately, all of them had at least some understanding of Glory.

Next, the lucky audience members were randomly sorted into three teams, and the system began to randomly assign teams against each other.

Even though it was a never-before-seen playing mechanism in Glory, the pro players had their base level of skill, so it was very unlikely that they would be defeated by some ordinary players. For a pro vs ordinary team matchup, the outcome was basically set. But there was one extra pro team, plus since the matchups were randomized, it wasn't guaranteed that three pro teams would face the audience teams.

Indeed, in the end two audience teams were paired against each other, and Tiny Herb was matched against the third. The other four pro teams were matched against each other, two and two.

"Hehe, looks like Samsara's win streak ends here." When interviewed by the host, Happy's Wei Chen saw their upcoming opponent and spoke with full confidence.

Happy's opponent: Team Samsara.

Chapter 1253: The Decider

Happy. Samsara.

One was a new team that had made their way through the Challenger League, the other was the two-time defending champion. At the start of the season, no one would have imagined that these two teams would become rivals - the opening match seemed to prove this point. Team Happy had lost to Team Samsara 0-10, a score that couldn't get any worse, and started their season with a stumble.

Afterwards, Happy became more and more terrifying. Starting from Round 9, they stopped losing, slaughtering their opponents with a record matching Samsara's.

Six 10-0s.

Even though the total point difference between the two teams was a large 34 points, if one only looked at Round 9 through Round 17, Happy had won even more points than Samsara.　　

Happy was completely in form now!

Everyone believed this. After all, Happy was a new team. New teams always needed an adjustment period. A rocky start was actually very logical. After getting past this difficult period of adaptation, Happy finally soared into the skies.

The problems that the outside world had helped analyze for Happy were now cleanly resolved.

For the issue of Fang Rui's class change, after finding his own path, his dirty Qi Master style was becoming more and more mature.

For the issue of the team's unfamiliarity with an unspecialized, Happy's players had adapted very well, far faster than people had expected. From the very start, people seemed to have disregarded how good Happy was at adapting to this new class.

The rookies Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Luo Ji, didn't need to be mentioned. When they first came into contact with Glory, Lord Grim quickly appeared by their side. Perhaps in their minds, Glory originally had 25 classes, not 24. And among these 25 was the unspecialized. From the very start, the unspecialized problem didn't exist for them.

As for Su Mucheng, as a pro player, an unspecialized hadn't been seen in many years, and she needed time to get familiar with this class. However, Su Mucheng was a player who understood Ye Xiu well, so compared to anyone else, she had an advantage in adapting to Ye Xiu's Lord Grim.

As for Fang Rui, he didn't have the same level of connection as Su Mucheng did with Ye Xiu, but Fang Rui just happened to be undergoing a class change. He coincidentally was also getting used to a new class. During his process of destruction into construction, he brought Lord Grim into his new system without any extra trouble, so he was able to fit in with Lord Grim much faster than the average pro player.

For the same reason, when Qiao Yifan got into contact with Lord Grim, he happened to be changing classes too, so his story was the same as Fang Rui's.

Wei Chen had ten years of Glory experience and An Wenyi was a healer, who had more of an observant role. As a result, getting familiar with Lord Grim was fast for them as well. Mo Fan was someone who had never coordinated with anyone before, so for him, he became familiar in another form of a destruction into construction process.

Everyone in Team Happy coincidentally had this and that advantage in familiarizing themselves with an unspecialized, so after practicing hard and accumulating experience in matches, the team took form very quickly. The more Happy played, the smoother everything became.

There was one point that could not be overlooked either. Happy's schedule at the start of the season had been quite the devil. Samsara, Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, these four powerhouses had matched against Happy in the first eight rounds. Happy's poor win record was partly because of this reason.

In any case, the current Happy was the most prominent team since the past nine rounds. Their current ranking was fifth… a strong contender for the playoffs.

Yes, a strong contender...

A team with three All-Stars.

A team placed fifth on the point rankings.　　

Saying they were a strong team wasn't unreasonable. No one felt like it was a notion difficult to accept.

If they were a strong team, then they had the qualifications to challenge Samsara.

However… on the All-Stars stage? In this fun competition? Happy wanted to end Samsara's win streak?

This had to be a joke!

How could anything here count?

The crowd started laughing. They regarded Wei Chen's serious words as a joke.　

Thinking of how Ye Xiu was in Happy, the home crowd obviously didn't bear much good will towards Happy. Amidst the laughter, there were quite a few boos thrown towards Wei Chen as well.

"Haha, it looks like the crowd's already feeling pressured in place of Samsara," Wei Chen laughed.　

The boos became even louder.

"It looks like they're really nervous!" Steamed Bun said in confusion. "Isn't this Tyranny's home stadium though? Why are they feeling afraid for Samsara?"

Afraid?

Tyranny's fans went into a frenzy. Sure enough, no one by Ye Xiu's side was a good person. Is he actually challenging us?　

The boos even drowned out the host's voice.　　

"DESTROY THEM!!" Someone even yelled out.

"Thanks!" Steamed Bun waved in the direction of that voice. "Relax, we'll definitely do it!"

"FUCK, I WAS SAYING DESTROY GUYS!!" Tyranny's fans were going crazy, but they looked at one another. How could they get these words through to them?

The host wasn't planning on just letting them continue playing around and started interviewing the next person.

"You plan on deciding it here?" Samsara's Jiang Botao moved towards Happy's three players and started chatting with them.

"Are you scared?" Wei Chen looked at him disdainfully.

"Hahaha," Jiang Botao laughed but didn't say anything. Next to him, Wu Qi and Du Ming walked up without any intentions of retreating. Even though this was All-Stars, a fun competition, if someone wanted to play for real, then they wouldn't back down. Samsara was the defending champions. Their title wasn't going to be snatched so easily with just a few words. Wei Chen's attitude made the two feel very displeased.

"There's no hurry." Wei Chen looked at those two. "We'll know the answer soon."

Wei Chen exuded extraordinary confidence. Samsara's three saw this confidence and felt a little doubtful. The fun mini-games were newly-created things that had never been revealed prior to the All-Stars Weekend. No one knew what they were, so where did the other side's unwavering confidence come from?

Could there be something in the game similar to this competition, and this guy happened to be a master at it?

The three guessed. Pro players were becoming more and more detached from the online game. To them, Glory was becoming more and more like a pure fighting game. Did the online game have something like this? The three weren't sure.

Sparks had started flying between Happy and Samsara, which was undoubtedly exciting for the viewers. One could never have too much drama. After the host interviewed each side, Hot-Blooded Dodgeball began. First up was Tiny Herb and the lucky audience team. The commentator on the broadcast took the information he had and introduced the mini-game in detail so that the viewers would have a better time watching. As for the host, he also had to explain the responsibilities of the players participating in this mini-game.

The rules were practically the same as normal dodgeball. In a confined area, one side would use a sandbag to attack, while the other side would defend. If a sandbag hit a character, the character would be knocked out of the field. But if the defender caught the sandbag, the defender would need to be hit an extra time to be knocked out. If an ally was already knocked out, the defender could also choose to revive the ally.

As for how to use a sandbag?

On stage, Tiny Herb and the lucky audience team loaded into the map and discovered that their characters had two new skills, Sandbag Toss and Sandbag Catch. After everyone tried them out, they quickly grasped how to use them.

The match officially started. Tiny Herb attacked, while the lucky audience team defended. If a sandbag hit, the target would be eliminated. It was equivalent to an instant kill. If viewed from a combat perspective, it vastly decreased the amount of time needed for a turn. As a result, after just a minute, the three lucky audience members were wiped out. The viewers could all see that Tiny Herb hadn't been too merciless and had held back.

Next, the lucky audience team attacked, while Tiny Herb defended. The three Tiny Herb players didn't catch any sandbag and only dodged. After dodging for around how long the last turn took, they let the other side hit them to end their turn. Because of the wide disparity in skill, everyone could see that in this mini-game, if the pro players played seriously, the audience team's turn to attack might never end.

With Tiny Herb's victory, the other contestants also got a better understanding of the mini-game.

The following match was between the two audience teams. Since the two teams were more evenly-matched, this confrontation was a lot more intense than the previous round. After lots of laughs, a winner was decided after the two turns.　　

Next was Happy versus Samsara. After drawing ballots, Samsara would be attacking first, while Happy would be defending.

After watching the first four teams fight, the on-stage players now had their own thoughts and ideas for this mini-game. The characters loaded into the map. The attacking Samsara stood at the corners of the map, forming an equilateral triangle, while Happy stood in the middle at the very center of the map. These positions were just their starting locations. After loading into the map, they could freely move around. In the match between the two audience teams, those six players ran around crazily until it was all a huge mess. The viewers weren't familiar with their characters and in fact, the players themselves weren't familiar with their own teammates, so enemies treating each other as allies and allies treating other as enemies had happened more than once.

This sort of situation probably wouldn't happen with these two pro teams.

When the match started, there was an indicator showing who first had the sandbag. Right now, it was in the hands of Du Ming's Blade Master, Moon-Luring Frost.

However, the sandbag wasn't thrown just like that. A sword light flashed, and Du Ming had Moon-Luring Frost open a path with Triple Slash.

The All-Star mini-games would never block anything the game originally had, so every single mini-game had this element in it: killing! It was always a method to win. But the problem was that in this mini-game, if a sandbag hit, the target would be instantly knocked out. Killing required calculating both damage dealt and health remaining, so it was more trouble than it was worth.

No one thought that Du Ming was going in with intentions to kill his opponent. Triple Slash was simply a way to close the distance. With less distance between them, it would be easier to hit the target. The logic was very simple.

Chapter 1254: Airborne Sandbag

Du Ming's target was the person who had looked down on them earlier, Wei Chen. Sword light flew, and Moon-Luring Frost rapidly closed the distance between him and Windward Formation. He raised his other hand and threw a sandbag.

The sandbag's speed and distance depended entirely on the player's skill. How could a pro player lack that? The sandbag was like a shadow as it shot towards Windward Formation.

Pu!

Hit!

Du Ming felt delighted. You arrogant bastard, I got rid of you in just three seconds. But before he could laugh, he looked closer and saw that Windward Formation hadn't been hit.　

A small flying dragon had flown in front of Windward Formation who knew when. His sandbag had hit this small flying dragon. It was undoubtedly Luo Ji who had summoned this small flying dragon. However, according to the mini-game's settings, the sandbag was a godly killing weapon. When the sandbag hit, the small flying dragon was instantly knocked outside of the battlefield just like a player character. 　

"Nice job," Wei Chen praised Luo Ji. Luo Ji didn't have time to be happy though, as his nervous heart was about to leap out of his throat. When the match started, Wei Chen immediately told him to summon a creature to block an attack. Such a heavy responsibility gave Luo Ji huge amounts of pressure. He feared that he wouldn't be able to control it properly or not accurately enough. If his block missed, wouldn't it be Wei Chen being knocked out of the field?

Fortunately, he succeeded, but he was more relieved than happy. Seeing that his small flying dragon had been knocked out, Luo Ji wanted to summon another one but when he checked his skills, he discovered that he couldn't use them. His character was Silenced.

Luo Ji immediately understood. A Summoner's creatures couldn't be used as an endless supply of shields in this mini-game. If a summon was hit by a sandbag, it would be locked and unable to be summoned again.

If I catch a sandbag, will I be able to use the summon again? Luo Ji thought to himself. But he also knew that in this mini-game, if he caught a sandbag, it didn't make sense to use it on getting the summon back.

The sandbag thrown at the small flying dragon dropped towards the ground. It wouldn't automatically return to the attacker's hands; the attacker had to pick it up himself. Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost was the closest to it. He hurried to grab it, but just before the sandbag hit the ground, a hand moved underneath the sandbag and caught it.

"Hahaha," Wei Chen laughed. Before a sandbag landed on the ground, it could be caught without question. As a result, Happy was able to pick one up, and the three players now had an extra life.

The rules stated that after catching a sandbag, within three seconds, the sandbag needed to be thrown away for an attacker to pick up. This was worthy of being exploited. Wei Chen looked at the other three's positions and found a gap, which was just behind Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost. He shouted "Catch" and Windward Formation chucked it.

Du Ming immediately had Moon-Luring Frost turn around. On the other hand, Wu Qi's Assassin, Cruel Silence, also rushed towards it to hurry and catch it. But when the two sprinted for it, they realized that there was no sandbag.　

"Whoops, sorry. I dropped it on the ground." Wei Chen laughed honestly. The sandbag had slipped out of Windward Formation's hands, falling straight down onto Windward Formation's feet.

The crowd erupted into thunderous boos. The viewers lashed out at Wei Chen's shamelessness one after the other. Wei Chen didn't care though. Happy's three characters had started moving away long before the sandbag hit the ground. For them, the farther they were away from the sandbags, the better.

Du Ming coughed blood as his Moon-Luring Frost turned around to pick up the sandbag. Wu Qi furiously had his Cruel Silence chase after him.

"Stay organized and maintain good positioning. Reduce their space and deal with them one by one," Jiang Botao yelled out. This mini-game looked easy, but in reality, there was a lot of strategy involved. The triangle starting position was a balanced way of positioning. How to move afterwards depended on the situation. Keeping up a constant stream of attacks was very important, so the three had to constantly be communicating. After Du Ming threw the sandbag, not only did the opponents play a dirty trick on them, even without that, just the small flying dragon blocking the sandbag and then forcing the attackers to run to pick it up was a serious interruption towards their offense. When throwing a sandbag, the path of the throw should be such that another attacker could catch the sandbag and continue attacking. This was the key to this mini-game for the attackers. Whether it was dodgeball, throwing sandbags, or this mini-game, this was always the strategy.

Seeing Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost pick up the sandbag, Jiang Botao immediately had his Empty Waves move in an attempt to form a link with Moon-Luring Frost's position. Who would have thought that before he could take more than a few steps, he would hear Du Ming curse loudly. When he turned around to look, he saw a Hexagram Prison trapping Moon-Luring Frost.　　

"You youngsters have got to open your eyes wider," Wei Chen sighed.　　

"Senior's methods are truly brilliant," Jiang Botao praised sincerely.

"Oh? You child, you really know how to talk!" Wei Chen laughed.

Jiang Botao also laughed, but his hands hadn't stopped moving.

Ice Wave Sword!

Ice crystals spread, quickly moving towards Happy's three characters. Ice element skills with a chance of lowering movement speed could undoubtedly be effective at crucial moments.

"We were having such a good chat and then you suddenly launch a sneak attack. Kids these days are truly too shameless," Wei Chen said as his Windward Formation dodged to the side.

"Senior, good joke." Jiang Botao wasn't affected by Wei Chen's trash talk. His Ice Wave Sword didn't hit, so he swung his sword again with a Fire Wave.　　

Fire blazed. Jiang Botao wanted to use this attack to restrict the opponent's movement options, but he didn't expect someone to just directly run through the fire waves and charge towards him.

Powerful Knee Strike!

Steamed Bun Invasion leaped up and his knee came crashing towards Empty Waves.

Sigh, a miscalculation!

Jiang Botao instantly realized that a purely offensive skill like Fire Wave Sword might be the least useful skills in this mini-game. With the threat of a one hit kill sandbag, who could care about this sort of damage? Happy's Steamed Bun decisively chose to ignore this damage and charged straight through these fire waves. This sort of scene was simply too rare. Jiang Botao wasn't able to react in time, and Empty Wave's Powerful Knee Strike slammed into him.

Wu Qi had understood Jiang Botao's intentions, and his Cruel Silence positioned himself with Empty Waves. They were just waiting for Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost to break free from Hexagram Prison. How could he have known Empty Waves would be sent flying away. For a moment, Wu Qi didn't know what to do. Everyone was still somewhat unfamiliar with this sort of mini-game.

"Hold them!" At this moment, Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost had finally broken from from Hexagram Prison. He shouted towards Wu Qi, telling him to form a pincer together.

Happy were doing their utmost to avoid the sandbag from Moon-Luring Frost. The three characters stopped grouping up and dispersed in different directions. Not only did they have to dodge Moon-Luring Frost, they needed to evade Cruel Silence as well. Jiang Botao saw Happy's movements and knew the other side also knew the key to this game. The attackers carrying sandbags were the most threatening characters, but the defenders could not just ignore the attackers without one. Sandbags could be passed around.

"Catch!" Du Ming shouted and tossed a sandbag into the air. Wei Chen, who was in front of Du Ming, had Windward Formation dodge, but how could he have known the sandbag would be thrown so off target...　　

This wasn't a direct attack, but an assist!

Jiang Botao's Empty Waves remained calm and collected and went into an extremely good position. Du Ming learned from Wei Chen's cheap trick and returned the favor with a shout of his own. The sandbag was instead passed to Empty Waves. From Jiang Botao's position to Moon-Luring Frost throw, it was hard to know what Samsara was planning, but in an instant, they suddenly sped up. After Empty Waves caught the sandbag, his hands didn't stop moving. He threw the sandbag, not at the opponent directly in front of him, but towards Concealed Light to the side of him.

Luo Ji turned pale with fright. He mashed his keys in a fluster and was able to dodge it, but when he turned around, he saw that Cruel Silence had unexpectedly used Shining Cut to instantly reach his rear. Cruel Silence extended his hands, catching Empty Wave's sandbag, and threw the sandbag.

Hit!

This time, it was a hit. Samsara's sudden acceleration had caught Luo Ji off guard. This sandbag struck Concealed Light squarely.

However, at the start of the match, Wei Chen's Windward Formation was able to catch a sandbag, giving Happy an extra life. As a result, this hit didn't knock Concealed Light off the stage. Samsara's offense wasn't over yet though. The instant Cruel Silence threw this sandbag, he rushed forward ferociously ready to pick up the sandbag.　　

If a sandbag successfully hit a character, the defenders would not be able to pick it up. Luo Ji could only have his Concealed Light run from that sandbag. However, how could a Summoner's movement speed compare to an Assassin's? By the time Cruel Silence snatched the sandbag, Concealed Light had only taken a few steps. Wu Qi showed no mercy. His Cruel Silence raised his arm, ready to throw the sandbag, when suddenly, a figure flashed in front of him, slamming a brick into Cruel Silence's face.

Wu Qi saw his screen instantly turn dark. This brick had blocked his view, and at this distance, how could he have any time to dodge? Pu! The brick struck Cruel Silence, making Wu Qi's heart thump. He had already been in a throwing animation. There was no time to cancel it, yet he still wanted to dodge the brick. In a fluster, that sandbag ended up being thrown, gently and without any force behind it, hitting nothing but air.

"I kindly accept this offering!" Wei Chen laughed. Windward Formation stepped forward to pick it up.

"Not happening!!" Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost rushed forward, but since he was behind Windward Formation, he wouldn't be able to reach it in time. Moon-Luring Frost leaped into the air, the tip of his sword trembling.

Curving Wind Form.

Moon-Luring Frost used the new Level 75 skill. Sword qi moved in reverse, pulling in the sandbag towards Moon-Luring Frost.

"Smart kid, looks like you're quite creative!" Wei Chen's Windward Formation saw his prize flying away and continued to trash talk as his Windward Formation pointed his Death's Hand into the air.

Chapter 1255: Point Blank

Soul Slice!

A purple light flashed from Death's Hand, sending out several slashes towards the airborne sandbag.

Du Ming was startled. He didn't dare wait for the sandbag to arrive and moved his Moon-Luring Frost forward hurriedly to grab it. Even if he couldn't get it, he definitely couldn't let someone from Happy catch it.

But no matter his fast his movement speed was, it couldn't compare to a skill's. Du Ming looked at Soul Slice's trajectory and made a prediction. Moon-Luring Frost headed directly towards Soul Slice's direction, but the Soul Slice unexpectedly missed the sandbag.

It didn't hit?

The sandbag pulled by Curving Wind Form's sword energy didn't pull the sandbag back very fast. For a pro player, hitting a target at such a speed shouldn't be anything difficult. However, Windward Formation's Soul Slice actually missed. Was it a mistake, or was it... intentional?　　

"Ah, is this mouse broken?" Du Ming heard Wei Chen complain. He hastily had Moon-Luring Frost turn around and saw a black shadow leap up faster than he could react. The sandbag disappeared into the air along with this black shadow.　

Du Ming had Moon-Luring Frost send out a slash in a fluster, but it missed. That black shadow's movements were quick and nimble. After snatching the sandbag, it ran towards Happy's Summoner, Concealed Light, who took the sandbag from the spirit cat's mouth.

From the system notification, everyone could see that this retrieval was considered effective. Happy had gained another life.

Du Ming, who had just fallen for the trick, was both furious and ashamed. Moon-Luring Frost raised his sword, ready to charge towards Windward Formation.　

"Calm down! It's just a minigame," Jiang Botao shouted.

Yes, it was just a minigame. It was supposed to be a casual minigame filled with laughs. But Wei Chen's confidence after Happy picked Samsara was truly quite infuriating. Samsara's three players wanted to give this old guy a slap to his face, but from the looks of it, the old guy's skill at this game was deeper than theirs. Who said young people were easier at adapting to new things? Right now, this old guy was relying on his experience and after just two rounds of observation, he had quickly found the trick to this minigame.

"Du Ming, directly attack them. Give the sandbag to me and Wu Qi," Jiang Botao decided. It looked like beating Happy purely in a contest of their understanding of this minigame wouldn't be easy. He decided that they should display Samsara's strength, using attacks to restrict them while using sandbags to kill.

"Okay!" Du Ming welcomed this decision and replied bluntly.

On Happy's side, Luo Ji's Concealed Light held onto the sandbag for three seconds before throwing it towards a location inconvenient for Samsara. In the meantime, the three from Happy began preparing themselves for Samsara's next wave of attacks. But this time, Samsara had clearly calmed down. Jiang Botao and Du Ming positioned themselves to restrict Happy, but they didn't hastily start attacking. They waited for Wu Qi's Assassin to pick up the sandbag before calmly searching for an opportunity.

"Pretend to attack Windward Formation!" Jiang Botao commanded. As expected, Samsara's ability to carry out orders was outstanding. Before he even finished his words, Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost moved towards Windward Formation with a Triple Slash. Cruel Silence circled around to the side with a sandbag in his hands. Their teamwork was quite steady. Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost rushed forward, but he didn't attack. He simply stood there in a defensive position, stopping Windward Formation from approaching.

Restricting the opponent's movement space meant limiting the opponent's ability to dodge. Forcefully breaking through was an unwise move in this minigame. The sandbag was an instant kill weapon. It wasn't possible for a defender to win a direct fight against an attacker.　

Sure enough, Wei Chen didn't make this unwise move. As soon as he saw Moon-Luring Frost block his path forward, he immediately turned. Cruel Silence had reached his side, but Wei Chen acted like he didn't see him.

Is he baiting us again? Jiang Botao observed Happy's movements. His Empty Waves was also shrinking their movement space, coordinating with Cruel Silence to continue pressuring Windward Formation.

However, these were all facades. From the very start, Jiang Botao had indicated that this was a fakeout, acting as cover for their true target. As for who this true target was, Jiang Botao still hadn't decided. Perhaps it was in fact Windward Formation. Everything depended on how Happy reacted to their pressure.

"Press forward!" Jiang Botao ordered again. Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost directly launched an attack at Windward Formation. As expected, as the defender, Wei Chen wasn't willing to get into a tangle with the attacker. Windward Formation retreated again.

"You punks, what are you doing, chasing relentlessly after this senior?" Wei Chen had Windward Formation dodge as he spouted trash talk.

"It's all because senior is too threatening!" Jiang Botao said.

"You baby, you really know how to talk! Hahaha!" Wei Chen once again praised Jiang Botao. Last time, Jiang Botao responded with a merciless attack. What about this time? This time, there was none. Jiang Botao suddenly turned diagonally. Empty Waves had originally been trying to block Windward Formation's retreat path, but this sudden turn completely changed his intent.

Ice Wave Sword!

This skill could not be ignored. An ice wave swept over murderously. Its target: Concealed Light.　　

"Good kid! So you were threatening the east to attack the west!" Wei Chen shouted. Windward Formation turned around to try and rescue Concealed Light, but Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost stopped him. He didn't attack. He simply cut off the path between Windward Formation and Concealed Light.

Cruel Silence suddenly sped up. He sent out a Shining Cut and activated Swift Movement. In an instant, the distance between himself and Concealed Light closed. Then, Shadow Clone Technique!

This instant movement Ninja skill was a skill practically every Night Walker class learned. For the final stretch of Cruel Silence's dash, he used this skill to instantly appear in front of Concealed Light. This sudden acceleration had caught Luo Ji unprepared last time, and this time was no different. He had just dodged Empty Wave's Ice Wave Sword and didn't expect an Assassin to suddenly appear before him in the blink of an eye with a sandback ready. At point blank, how could this sandbag be dodged? It was impossible!

Hit!

Cruel Silence's sandbag hit Concealed Light, instantly wiping out the extra life that they had just earned not long ago. As the sandbag fell, Luo Ji wanted Concealed Light to hurry and get away, but this time, Jiang Botao had predicted his intentions. In this sandbag minigame, whether the defenders caught it or the defenders were hit, the attacker's offense would be interrupted. Thus, just thinking about striking the target wasn't enough. Apart from hitting the target, the attackers needed to consider how to reach the next step in their offense. After hitting Concealed Light, the sandbag was caught in his hands before it fell to the ground. Concealed Light tried to run, but he was blocked by Empty Waves. By the time he tried moving in a different direction, he was too late. Cruel Silence once again threw the sandbag at point blank range. Concealed Light was hit once again and was cleanly knocked off the stage this time.

Fast. Everything had happened too fast. Wei Chen and Steamed Bun didn't have time to respond before Concealed Light was eliminated. Just this minigame alone show just terrifying the champion team's explosiveness was.

However, the offense from Samsara wasn't done yet. Two point blank sandbags and Cruel Silence caught both of them before they fell to the ground. Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost ran towards Windward Formation. Wei Chen immediately realized what he wanted to do, but facing this sort of charge, the defenders seemed powerless. They couldn't stop to fight with their opponents. Their only choice was to run away and dodge.

Windward Formation sprinted back, but Moon-Luring Frost pursued him faster, closing in with a Triple Slash. Cruel Silence then passed his sandbag to Moon-Luring Frost. Shadow Steps!

　　

Moon-Luring Frost didn't immediately throw his sandbag, instead using Shadow Steps. Five Moon-Luring Frosts instantly flickered into existence, each holding a sandbag. Without pausing, not giving Wei Chen any time to figure out which one was real, the five Moon-Luring Frosts threw their sandbags at the same time.

"That's too shameless!!" Wei Chen cried out in grief. The five sandbags flew at him, sealing off all of Windward Formation's escape options. Of the five, four were fake, but Wei Chen didn't know which one was real, so he could only pray.

Left!

Windward Formation stepped to the left. A sandbag hit him but disappeared.　　

Wei Chen let out a sigh of relief. However, it wasn't over yet. While he was figuring out if the sandbag that him was real or fake, Moon-Luring Frost acted again. A sword light flashed out, Sword Draw, aimed towards the previously thrown sandbag.

Du Ming obviously knew which of the sandbags was real. The Sword Draw didn't slice apart the sandbag. It carried the sandbag along with it towards Windward Formation.

"Punk… how crafty!" Wei Chen sighed. The sandbag was considered a throw too, and Windward Formation was eliminated.

The closely linked attacks knocked out two of Happy's players in the blink of an eye. The crowd was dumbstruck. Even Steamed Bun was having trouble keeping up.

"What's going on? How'd you guys suddenly disappear?" Steamed Bun was puzzled as he looked at the eliminated Windward Formation and Concealed Light.

"Chance!" Jiang Botao shouted. Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost shot forward. He picked up a sandbag and twisted his body, throwing the sandbag like a meteor towards Steamed Bun Invasion, who was looking away.

Pai!

The sandbag was stopped. A Brick had crashed into the sandbag, swatting it down. Du Ming was dumbfounded. He hadn't thought Steamed Bun would suddenly regain his senses and then throw a Brick that actually intercepted the meteor-like sandbag.　

"This is no fun!" Steamed Bun said. "Why don't we have a real fight?"

Chapter 1256: A Class Composition Fit for Dodgeball

"A real fight?" Jiang Botao laughed, "1v3 us? That's going to be very difficult!"

"Bring it on!" Steamed Bun yelled.

"Vice captain, he's stalling for time!" Du Ming saw that Jiang Botao seemed to want to play along with this guy, so he hastily gave him a reminder.

"This match is just for fun. Why worry so much? Let's just play with him! Could it be you think it'll take us a long time to beat him 3v1?" Jiang Botao asked.

"Of course not!" Du Ming's spirits rose.

"Let's go!" Wu Qi called out. His Cruel Silence rushed out.

"We're coming!" Jiang Botao said.

"I've been waiting for a long time now," Steamed Bun said calmly. For a moment, the Brawler Steamed Bun Invasion had the faint aura of a great scholar around him. Facing a 1v3, he didn't back down a single step and stood his ground proudly. But in the next moment, Steamed Bun Invasion was lying flat on the ground. He had turned into a corpse that was on his way out of the stage.

Everyone's mouths were wide open.

They couldn't understand. What was going on in Bao Rongxing's mind? Why would he disgrace himself? They just couldn't understand!

Is he stupid? Everyone thought so.

"Haha, what a pity, I lost!" Steamed Bun was very upset.

"DId you actually think you could win?" Luo Ji couldn't help but ask.

"Whether I lose or win, as long as I fight bravely, I'll never have any regrets," Steamed Bun said.

"Can someone take care of him?" Luo Ji seemed to be possessed by Mo Fan, his face expressionless.

"Alright, next up, it's our turn to attack. We're gonna fight fast and end this fast." Wei Chen said to his two juniors.　　

"Fight!" Steamed Bun shouted.

"..." Luo Ji.

The attackers and defenders switched roles. Happy on the offense, Samsara on the defense.

The opening was the same. It was just that this time, the ones standing at the corners of the triangle were Happy's three characters. The sandbag was in Windward Formation's hand.　

"If we keep catching sandbags endessly, won't this game go on forever?" Du Ming said.

"We just need to beat their time," Wu Qi siad.

"We can do it!" Jiang Botao said. Even though they didn't really care too much, it was still better to be the winner than the loser.

The match started. Jiang Botao immediately spun 360 degrees, observing Happy's movements.　　

The three from Happy were moving into offensive positions. Samsara also moved, while paying attention to Windward Formation's sandbag. Wei Chen was cunning. They had personally experienced it. With the sandbag in his hands, they felt like he definitely had a surprise waiting for them.

"Watch me!" Wei Chen suddenly roared and swung his arms.

Samsara immediately dodged, but the sandbag wasn't thrown towards them.

"This again!" Du Ming said. He turned around and saw the sandbag in Steamed Bun Invasion's hands. However, Steamed Bun Invasion wasn't in a good attacking position. Was he going to pass again?

Samsara moved, wary of Happy's next pass.

But there was no pass. The sandbag fell into Steamed Bun Invasion's hands, and then Happy's three characters gathered together.

What are they doing?

Jiang Botao couldn't understand. In this minigame, the attacking side carried more threat when they split apart and formed links with each other. If all three attackers crowded together, what was the difference between three people and one?

Could they be planning on charging at us together?

Just when they were thinking this, Windward Formation and Concealed Light started casting.

Concealed Light summoned creatures, while Windward Formation cast… Death's Door!　　

No one had ever heard of someone casting such a slow skill out in the open like this.

However, the threat of Death's Door was truly huge. Samsara couldn't ignore it. Jiang Botao's Empty Waves rushed forward. He swung his sword, sending out an Earth Wave Sword in an attempt to interrupt Windward Formation.

But then, Steamed Bun Invasion jumped out from the side, blocking this Earth Wave Sword.

The attack obviously dealt damage, but Steamed Bun Invasion didn't seem to care. He held the sandbag in his left hand and a Brick in his right hand as he sprinted madly towards Empty Waves.

Jiang Botao could only choose to run away. Who would dare to fight against someone who possessed the ultimate killing weapon, the sandbag?

But Windward Formation's Death's Hand had to be interrupted! Jiang Botao was being chased by Steamed Bun, so he had no chance to. He could only give the task to Du Ming and Wu Qi. However, by this time, Concealed Light had summoned quite a few creatures. His summons didn't rush out, instead providing cover for Windward Formation.

Jiang Botao suddenly realized the problem. At the same time, he also realized that in this minigame, some classes had advantages over others.

For example, Blade Masters and Assassins, two classes with powerful offensive capabilities, lost a lot of their threat in this minigame. No matter how strong your attacks were, how could they compare to an instant kill weapon?

The biggest threats in this minigame were control skills.

Warlocks were control experts, and Summoners who summoned creatures on the field were also very troublesome. His summons took up space, reducing the amount of room for the defenders to maneuver around, and this space was needed for defenders to dodge the sandbags.

A Warlock and a Summoner. Jiang Botao discovered that these two classes were most effective at exploiting the instant kill sandbags.

Not good!

Jiang Botao already had a bad feeling. Even though Du Ming's and Wu Qi's efforts forced Windward Formation to give up his Death's Door, it also lured the two into the summon's encirclement.　　

Kill kill kill!　

Sword and dagger danced in the air. Du Ming also realized that the situation was looking very bad, so he directly used the high-level skill, Formless Phantom Blade. Sword light quickly cut down the summons in a flurry. However, Concealed Light was constantly summoning more, not caring at all about his mana or his skill cooldowns because this wasn't a normal fight. As the attackers, they had instant kill weapons. As long as they had a single opening, they could instantly kill the opponent.

Using Formless Phantom Blade in this situation?

This decision was a bit careless!

A high-level skill like Formless Phantom Blade had a long ending lag, a large opening for the attackers to take advantage of. In this minigame, an opening like this could be fatal!

But the skill had already been used, and it was too late for Jiang Botao to warn him. He could only watch as Moon-Luring Frost slaughter the area around him and then when the final slash came out, Moon-Luring Frost became stuck in ending lag.　

Steamed Bun leaped out at this moment. Jiang Botao predicted this would happen, but there was nothing he could do to stop him. As for Wu Qi? Wu Qi was helpless too because Windward Formation was fighting him. A Warlock's control skills could not be ignored in this minigame.

Pai, the sandbag easily hit Moon-Luring Frost. Everyone could only watch helplessly.

Moon-Luring Frost was eliminated. Concealed Light's army of summons started swarming around Wu Qi's Cruel Silence. The sandbag that fell to the ground was also picked up by him and soon passed over to Steamed Bun Invasion.

Jiang Botoa clearly understood Happy's strategy now. A Warlock with control skills, a Summoner with summons, and a Brawler with the sandbag. All three characters were major threats, which could not be said for Samsara. He could throw out an Earth Wave Sword, but Steamed Bun could just directly take the attack. On the other hand, if a Warlock's Binding Curse or Control Curse came his way, he didn't dare eat it.

The threat that all three members of Happy possessed when attacking was something that Samsara's three couldn't achieve. If it was real fight like Steamed Bun said, Samsara might have the advantage, but in this minigame, Jiang Botao felt powerless when it was Happy's turn to attack.

Cruel Silence was trapped by the army of summons. Then, Windward Formation used a Control Curse to CC him. Jiang Botao was being chased by Steamed Bun and couldn't save him. As soon as Steamed Bun saw that a target had been CCed, Steamed Bun Invasion's sandbag was thrown. Cruel Silence was unable to move due to Windward Formation's Control Curse and the sandbag hit him square in the forehead.　

Two Samsara players had been eliminated. Happy's offense wasn't as fast and nimble as Samsara's, but it made the defending side feel completely powerless.

Jiang Botao checked the time. There was already no hope of winning.

"How about a real fight?" He laughed, learning from Steamed Bun last round.

"Sure!" Steamed Bun jumped out.

"Okay, Steamed Bun hand me the sandbag. Go!" Wei Chen said.

JIang Botao's heart thumped. Why did he feel like this arrangement didn't seem safe?

"Relax!" Wei Chen said, "I'll definitely sneak attack you."

Jiang Botao was speechless. The guy wasn't even trying to hide his intentions.

Steamed Bun Invasion charged forward and started fighting with Jiang Botao's Spellblade. Sure enough, Wei Chen kept his promise. Windward Formation was on the side, constantly harassing Jiang Botao. When an opportunity arrived where the attack couldn't be dodged, he threw the sandbag along with a skill.

"Okay, go die!" Wei Chen said. The sandbag hit, and Jiang Botao was eliminated.

In the end, Happy used less time, so they won.

"Samsara's win streak has finally ended!" Wei Chen exclaimed delightedly.

"Senior, you really…" Jiang Botao forced a smile. He was an expert at talking to others, but he didn't know what to say right now.

The first round of Hot-Blooded Dodgeball finished, and the four teams once again drew ballots for their next opponent. Just like Jiang Botao realized, in this minigame, Happy's class composition held an overwhelming advantage. The other pro teams, Tiny Herb and Miracle, couldn't compete. Happy won the next two rounds easily and ended up as the winners of Hot-Blooded Dodgeball.　　

"Champions!" Wei Chen declared loudly.

"Do we get a trophy?" Steamed Bun asked the host excitedly.

"This… I don't think so…" the host was sweating. It was just a minigame. A trophy?

"If there's no trophy, then a medal?" Steamed Bun asked.

"I don't think so either…"

"Prize?" Steamed Bun was still asking.

"Uh, that… Thank you to our nine audience members, and thank you to the fifteen players from our five pro teams for giving us a wonderful performance. Thank you!" The host took the lead and applauded, shooing away Happy down from the stage.

Chapter 1257: Things Remain, But The People Change

The Hot-Blooded Dodgeball competition came to a close. There were a lot of participants, and the elimination was turn-by-turn, so this one minigame replaced the three minigames of previous All-Stars. However, having just this one event would have been somewhat monotonous, so afterwards there was also a three-legged race event.

It could be seen from this that Tyranny, hosting this year's All-Stars, wanted to emphasize the subject of teamwork. Whether it was Hot-Blooded Dodgeball or Three-Legged Race, they all required exceptional teamwork and cooperation.

However, the famed All-Star pairings with which everyone was familiar still didn't appear in these minigames. Everyone knew that this excitement would be left until the final day. As they watched these fun events, the anticipation for Day 3 only grew.

After the Three-Legged Race was the Player vs Pro event, in which the hosting team would send out a pro player to accept challenges from the crowd. Tyranny sent out a player that had only just appeared in their roster last season, an older rookie, Qin Muyun.

This older rookie who fought alongside Tyranny's Four Heavenly Kings used to have a very faint presence. It wasn't until the playoffs that people realized that this player also had unusual battle ability. His presence was faint only because his use on the battlefield wasn't easily captured in summary statistics. This expert at positioning used his position to contain or restrict his opponents, which couldn't be recorded in statistics.

Qin Muyun took his place, Tyranny's Captain Han Wenqing went onstage to select the players. There were many Tyranny fans in the crowd, so of course this was a very exciting thing.

Qin Muyun's victories were of course guaranteed. But for the ordinary players that lost, their heads were filled with fog. During battle, they had all experienced an indescribable feeling of being bound. What was up with that? None of them understood. Qin Muyun's playstyle, which relied on positioning to launch offensives, was so high-level that it far surpassed what ordinary players could recognize. They might know that something like this was going on, but in real battle, they couldn't detect the intentions of each movement of Qin Muyun's Negative Nine Degrees.

"Such an outstanding player, how was he discovered so late?" Blue Rain's Captain Yu Wenzhou mused. He wasn't the only pro player with such thoughts; all of the teams were discussing Qin Muyun's performance. Even when fighting ordinary players, his style was fully apparent. For the pros, once they understood where Qin Muyun's talents lay, it was easier to grasp his plans on the field. But even though that was the case, if their attention wavered just a bit, they could still overlook him.

Suppression that relied on positioning - there was the feeling of some silent drowning. Qin Muyun had already earned a lot of attention, but his presence on the battlefield was still as faint as ever.

The lucky audience members happily walked onstage, lost, walked offstage in a daze, and Day 2 of the All-Star Weekend came to a close. The audience members left in satisfaction, and began to anticipate Day 3 of All-Stars, and the event that was the highlight of the weekend: the All-Star Competition.

What would the teams be? Which players would they see fight side-by-side? Which players would they see clash?

Any kind of dream team or dream confrontation could become reality in the All-Star Weekend. Carrying their hopes, everyone welcomed the arrival of Day 3 of All-Stars.

The atmosphere was extremely raucous; everyone was swept along by the excitement. The host was clearly aware of the crowd's mood, so he didn't try to tease everyone's appetite. One by one, the 24 All-Star players were introduced and welcomed onstage.

The excited crowd gave their cheers and shouts to all of the All-Stars. Of course, the ones who earned the loudest cheers were the players of Tyranny. When Captain Han Wenqing went onstage, the cheers were like the roaring of a tsunami wave. It was difficult to believe that this player had only been ranked 12th this year for All-Stars. The power of the home stadium made it seem like Han Wenqing was the number one superstar of Glory. From this it could be seen that although Han Wenqing's total popularity had decreased greatly, in Tyranny, he was still the immovable number one.

Opposite to everyone else was Ye Xiu. When he appeared, the Tyranny fans sent him not applause but merciless booing. This was the All-Star stage, not Tyranny's home game, so this sort of behavior was rather rude. But there was nothing that could be done. The hatred that Tyranny fans had toward Ye Xiu simply ran too deep. Last season, when there had been neither Ye Xiu nor Excellent Era, the Tyranny fans had really been a little lonely. No matter how strong Samsara was, even if they defeated Tyranny in the end, in the eyes of the fans they still weren't the biggest enemy. The archenemy was still Excellent Era, was still Ye Xiu.

Excellent Era was no longer here, but Ye Xiu had returned, so the hate was more focused. Tyranny's fans would never conceal their emotions. The setting didn't matter. If they saw Ye Xiu, they booed. This was law, iron law.

Among the 24 players, only Ye Xiu received such a brutal treatment. Although Su Mucheng was also from Excellent Era, the grudge that Tyranny had toward Excellent Era and Ye Xiu stemmed from the very beginning, with Excellent Era's three consecutive championship wins. Su Mucheng joined Excellent Era the year that Tyranny finally defeated Excellent Era, when their spirits were high. So, subtly, they didn't have much negative feeling toward Su Mucheng, since she had joined when Tyranny came to victory. All of the aggro was focused on Ye Xiu alone.

The other players all had their own feelings as they watched this person receive a completely different treatment than the rest of them.

This person had left the pro circle for a year and a half, and then he returned, and then he immediately stood on this stage that symbolized the very pinnacle of Glory players. Aside from Zhou Zekai, not a single player was more popular than him. This was indeed a powerful comeback.

Ye Xiu also looked at everyone on this stage. After leaving for a year and a half, the array of faces before him had gained some unfamiliar, and lost some familiar.

Of the opponents that had tangled with him for many years now, many of them had already left. Some were gone for good, others were currently sitting offstage.

Zhang Jiale, Lin Jingyan, Sun Zheping… And those that might be sitting in front of their televisions right now, Zhao Yang, Deng Fusheng…

Perhaps they would never stand on this most beautiful stage again. And what about himself? How much longer could he himself stand here?

Looking at Han Wenqing, Ye Xiu had mixed feelings. Standing on this stage now, there was now no longer a single player that had debuted in Season 2. But the two of them Season 1 debuts still stubbornly clung to their places here.

Him at number two. Han Wenqing at number twelve.

Not bad, Ye Xiu thought. But looking at the top ten All-Stars, the presence of the new generation was only growing stronger and stronger.

Zhou Zekai from Season 5 comfortably held the spot of number one, while Jiang Botao and Yu Feng from Season 6, along with Sun Xiang and Tang Hao from Season 7, were all in the top 10. Aside from them, there were three players from the famed Season 4 Golden Generation. Then, it was just Wang Jiexi from Season 3.

There weren't too many left from Season 3, either…

Ye Xiu counted, and realized that of the players from Season 3, aside from Wang Jiexi, there was only Yang Cong. And this time he was ranked 24th, barely catching the last train. Behind him, a crowd of newer players were eyeing this position. Perhaps as soon as next year, he would vanish from this leaderboard.

Things remain, but the people change…

Seeing all of these new young faces before him, Ye Xiu couldn't help but feel the vicissitudes of life. The onstage host was currently interviewing one by one the players that came onstage, and finally it was Ye Xiu's turn.

"God Ye Xiu made a strong comeback this year, coming onto this stage at second place. What are your current feelings?" The host was even more excited than Ye Xiu as he posed this question.

"Oh, I'm used to this," Ye Xiu said.

Don't even mention the crowd. Even some of the other All-Star players onstage booed at Ye Xiu.

The host also hesitated for a moment before continuing his questions. "Does God Ye Xiu have anyone he's looking forward to partnering with, or fighting against?"

Ye Xiu glanced at the other twenty-plus players, and continued to respond calmly. "I don't really care."

"Hahaha, God Ye Xiu is really… extremely calm!" the host said.

"Because I'm used to this!" Ye Xiu said.

His words came back to the same point… The host could only helplessly proceed to the next player.

The one after Ye Xiu was of course Zhou Zekai. The interviews proceeded in order according to the All-Star rankings.

"Little Zhou once again was voted to number one in the All-Star rankings. What are your current feelings?" The host didn't refer to Zhou Zekai as "God," but as "Little Zhou," evoking a feeling of familiarity.

"Does he even need to say? He's also used to this!" While Zhou Zekai was still pondering how to respond, Ye Xiu already helped him answer.

Zhou Zekai looked at Ye Xiu blankly, and in the end didn't say anything.

"Uh, this…" The host felt awkward. Maybe Zhou Zekai really was used to it, but only you would say it directly with that kind of attitude!

Zhou Zekai didn't look like he was about to say anything more, so the host could only continue to the next question, still the same one that had been repeated many times already: "Little Zhou, do you have any players you're looking forward to partnering with?"

"Partner with who? Samsara's sent four players here! Are you going to split them up?" Ye Xiu said.

"God Ye… can you… stop talking?" The host nobly suppressed the urge to blow up at him.

"Oh oh, you guys chat, you guys chat," said Ye Xiu.

Chat? What chat? Who could chat with Zhou Zekai? The host held the microphone and looked at Zhou Zekai. Seeing that after a very long pause he still didn't move his mouth, the host quickly repeated the question. "Have you thought it through? Who are you hoping to partner with?"

"Uh…" Zhou Zekai finally opened his mouth. "Our team… has four."

"Hahahaha!" Ye Xiu laughed like crazy. Gritting his teeth, the host ultimately restrained himself and didn't ask any more questions. Originally, the number two and number one should have had longer interviews, as befit their higher popularity. But now…

"Alright, now let us see the teams for this year's All-Star Competition," the host said, his face expressionless.

Chapter 1258: All-Star Team Division

The high point was finally here, and the entire stadium thrummed with excitement.

To be honest, the question of who would face off against each other wasn't especially interesting. After all, there were so many rounds of competition, and the confrontations between different teams could be seen in the normal League matches.

What was most important about All-Stars were the team rosters! Those players normally scattered among all the various teams would only have this once-a-year chance to fight alongside each other. The audience deeply loved to watch this sort of matchmaking.

Which people would be pushed together in this All-Star Competition? Everyone present lifted their heads to stare unblinking at the display screen in the stadium. The team divisions were only revealed right before the match; even the All-Stars themselves didn't know beforehand.

First, Team A.

Zhou Zekai, Sun Xiang, Jiang Botao, Lu Boyuan, four names appeared on the screen, followed by their account names.

It was Team Samsara. The All-Star team divisions would never separate members of the same team.

Samsara had four All-Stars, which was currently a unique distinction. No other team could match them in number of All-Stars. Blue Rain and Tiny Herb only had three each. Which team's players would be assigned to match Samsara's four?

Everyone's gazes turned to the right half of the display screen. Team B's roster was still empty.

The screen began to flash!

Several lines of player and account names tumbled and appeared before everyone's eyes. And everyone was utterly dumbstruck.

Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng.

!!!!

????

Tyranny's two, and Happy's two, combined into four to match Samsara's four. But the issue wasn't the player number, the issue was, Tyranny and Happy, how come they were paired together?

No one expected that this roster reveal would, instead of proceeding step by step, reach a high point right at the beginning. The live audience was stunned, and then there was an uproar.

Han Wenqing, Ye Xiu?

These two people would be fighting next to each other?

Countless people felt that their brains were about to short-circuit. Something that they felt would absolutely never happen for all eternity became reality at this All-Stars. In previous years, in order to maintain the competitiveness of the All-Star Competition, death-enemies like Han Wenqing and Ye Xiu, Tyranny and Excellent Era, would definitely be assigned to opposing teams. But this time, with Tyranny hosting this All-Star competition, they actually pulled Ye Xiu into their roster, making him stand beside Han Wenqing as a teammate.

This… this was truly a bold move!

But to many diehard Tyranny fans, this arrangement was unacceptable, and shouts of protest actually erupted in the stadium. The hosts, that was to say Team Tyranny, certainly had a hand in this arrangement, but Tyranny fans didn't want to blindly go along with this. Ye Xiu was the archnemesis, forever the archnemesis, how could they just change that?

Those that maintained this view were a few diehard fans. But more people felt that this arrangement seemed very interesting. What kind of awkward battle would result when these two opponents of ten years were standing beside each other? It seemed like many people were already beginning to anticipate, and the various emotions in the crowd were beginning to diffuse.

Afterwards, not many people paid attention when Blue Rain's Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian, and Lu Hanwen were assigned to Team A, while Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi, Xu Bin, and Gao Yingjie were sent to Team B. This arrangement was very ordinary; for many All-Stars now, these two teams would be split onto different teams. For one, these two teams had history between them, and for another, this allowed Team A and Team B to be relatively balanced in power. If both Blue Rain and Tiny Herb were sent to the same team, the balance would become very skewed. No matter what, A and B had to be around the same strength.

After Blue Rain and Tiny Herb, Wind Howl's Tang Hao and Liu Hao joined Team A, while Hundred Blossoms' Yu Feng and Zou Yuan joined Team B. This arrangement was again to increase the conflict. Tang Hao came from Hundred Blossoms, Liu Hao was former teammates with Ye Xiu. Their pasts now stood with Team B. And for Hundred Blossoms, Yu Feng was formerly in Blue Rain, and therefore was sent to Team B.

After seeing this arrangement, many people lamented that Happy's Fang Rui and Tyranny's Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan hadn't been voted onto All-Stars. Otherwise, this team division alone would be an even more complex mess in a boiling pot.

Zhang Jiale would be standing alongside Hundred Blossoms' revival of the Blood and Blossoms pairing. Fang Rui, newly changed to Qi Master, would reunite with his former Criminal Partner Lin Jingyan, the two of them taking their revenge against the Wind Howl that had abandoned them…

So many thrilling points to watch, but because these three players had failed to make it into All-Stars, this sight could not be witnessed. The audience could only sigh about how regrettable it was.

After the players of these two teams were assigned, Void's Ghost Duo Li Xuan and Wu Yuce were sent to Team A, while Misty Rain's Chu Yunxiu and Li Hua entered Team B.

Then, there were only two people left. Xiao Shiqin went to Team A, Yang Cong to Team B.

Looking at the final rosters of the two teams, the most exciting was still that moment at the beginning. Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing would be battling together? Even now, the crowd was still discussing this topic, ignoring all of the rest.

After the rosters were revealed, the 24 All-Stars had already split into two separate lines.

The exciting points to watch existed only in the hearts of the viewers. For the pros, in reality, they all agreed with Ye Xiu's answer to the interview question "who are you looking forward to partnering with": don't really care.

Two teams of 12 players. Following the normal match rules, it was just enough for every player to appear once. After the rosters were decided, Teams A and B separated to their respective temporary prep areas, which were specially prepared for this event. In this moment, they were two teams.

"Alright, now the teams are in their places. After letting them make some preparations, the All-Star Competition will begin in just a moment," the host shouted passionately.

"Coach Li, what kind of lineups do you think each team will arrange?" All-Star Weekend was always broadcast on television, and for the high-level confrontation that was the All-Star Competition, commentator Pan Lin and honored guest Li Yibo were also present for the live broadcast.

"Hm… Every year, there's always one crucial point in the team division, and that is… which team has the healer," said Li Yibo.

"Very true. For a few years in a row now, there's been only one healer voted into All-Stars, Zhang Xinjie."

"Correct. Team A is facing a situation where they don't have a healer, so for the team competition, they'll want to have a lineup with strong explosive power. Only then will they have a chance at suppressing Team B's healer advantage. For Team B, as long as they have a steady team that can thoroughly take advantage of their healer, then their chances of victory will certainly be higher than Team A's. As for the individual and group rounds, it'll just be the leftover players performing." Li Yibo said a whole lot, explosive and steady, but in the end he didn't name a single name. Naming names was very dangerous! He didn't want to be faceslapped because of an inaccurate prediction, and so he had to speak in very general terms for something like predicting lineup.

Li Yibo's answer was vague and crafty, and of course Pan Lin wouldn't try to break it. He simply said a "you're right," and then the two of them looked at the display screen together.

"Huh? Did some kind of argument break out over at Team B?" Pan Lin suddenly yelled. "Director, director."

The camera could zoom in and focus on Team B, but there were no microphones over there to pick up sound.

"Can anyone go over there to see what's going on?" Pan Lin called.

"Is it an argument between Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing?" Li Yibo studied the camera view. Seeing that the heart of the conflict appeared to be Ye Xiu, he instantly thought of this possibility. But when he looked closer, it didn't look like Han Wenqing was arguing with him, it looked like… everyone was targeting Ye Xiu.

"You want to save yourself the trouble and fight in an individual round? Too naive, stand aside," Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi was saying to Ye Xiu.

"This brother has sixteen consecutive individual wins! I'll give us a head start, get us a solid point, suppress their arrogance. This is such a logical and clever arrangement, how is this naive! Big-Eyed Wang, explain it to me!" Ye Xiu argued back.

Tiny Herb's other two players shrunk back. They of course knew their captain had this nickname, but how many people would dare to use it directly? They stole glances at their captain, wondering what his reaction would be.

Wang Jiexi didn't seem to have much of a reaction. He merely looked at everyone, and then said, "We'll vote. Those who agree with this guy playing an individual, raise your hands."

"What vote! Is your Tiny Herb governed by a voting system?" Ye Xiu said.

Everyone shrunk back again. The conflict between these two was a truly a battle between gods! Those like Xu Bin, Yu Feng, Zou Yuan, these players had all debuted much later. Although they were also All-Stars, in the face of this seniority and qualification, they instantly felt they were still shorter by a head. They didn't have the bravery to go and break up the fight. But even as everyone shrunk back, they stole glances at Han Wenqing, who did have the status to enter this battle of gods.

"What's all this fuss for!" But, surprisingly, the first one to interrupt and scold them was actually Chu Yunxiu.

"I'll go first for individual!" Chu Yunxiu shouted.

"There are three spots, what are you rushing for? I'll go first, you go second!" Ye Xiu said.

"Alright, agreed!" Chu Yunxiu gave a strong nod.

"And then Mucheng," Ye Xiu said, making sure to pick from his own team first.

"If all three of you went to the team competition, that would really be an excellent arrangement," said Wang Jiexi.

"And then leave the individual slots to you?" Ye Xiu said.

"Our Tiny Herb… has a very good group arena record." Wang Jiexi's fox tail was finally exposed. They talked and they talked, but in the end they were all just too lazy to perform in the most tiring team competition, and so they scurried toward the shorter and simpler individual battles. Ye Xiu just very plainly tried to snatch the desirable spots for himself, while Wang Jiexi wanted to stuff the team competition spots full, and then he could just smoothly enter the individual battles.

Ye Xiu stared at him, silent for a few seconds, and then turned his head to look at everyone else. "With that, isn't the lineup set? Everyone else go in the team competition, isn't that just enough?"

"Everyone else" would be Tyranny's two, Hundred Blossoms' two, Misty Rain's Li Hua, and 301's Yang Cong.

"Let's discuss the lineups!" Tyranny's Zhang Xinjie calmly opened his mouth, as though he hadn't heard any of the heated discussion just now.

Chapter 1259: A Member of the Strongest Team

"Hey hey, you, you're just completely ignoring us!" Ye Xiu, extremely dissatisfied, said to Zhang Xinjie.

"This is Tyranny," Zhang Xinjie said.

This is Tyranny.

There was a pause, but everyone quickly understood Zhang Xinjie's meaning. Even he might not necessarily enjoy this sort of showy battle, but this was Tyranny, this year's All-Stars was hosted by Tyranny, and as Tyranny's players, Zhang Xinjie and Han Wenqing could not undermine their own stage. They would have to do what they could to make this year's All-Stars brilliant and exciting. Ye Xiu and the others made their plan just to save effort, which the Tyranny players of course would not support.

"If only I were in Team A…" Ye Xiu sighed. Everyone cast him sidelong glances. Aren't you being too honest with your feelings? Are you purposely trying to undermine Tyranny?

No one was talking anymore. With the home team's players here, they had to give them face! But Ye Xiu? Would this guy let Tyranny save face? It'd be good enough if he didn't intentionally tear down this stage!

As they were all thinking this, Ye Xiu had already opened his mouth again. "Well, since that's the case, how about we have a more... tyrannical arrangement?"

Everyone continued to look at him. After he finished speaking, they all revealed expressions of excitement.

"So you did come here to tear down the stage," said Wang Jiexi.

"It's on purpose!" said Chu Yunxiu.

"This wouldn't be too good, would it?" Yu Feng was still doubtful.

"Have some confidence! What are you scared of!" said Ye Xiu.

Scared?

Of the entire Glory circle, these people here would be the last people scared of a stage like this! Everyone again fell silent and looked at Han Wenqing, looked at Zhang Xinjie. Would they agree with this plan of Ye Xiu's?"

"So be it!" Tyranny's Captain Han Wenqing slapped the table, closing the discussion.

All-Stars was just a show, so there weren't any strict time regulations. The judge came to Team A and Team B's preparation areas to confirm that both teams had made appropriate preparations. Then, with the passionate announcement of the live host, the All-Star Competition began.

"Now, we have the first battle of the individual competition. Will the first two players please come on stage?" As the host shouted, he was also looking to the left and right. The roster order of the two teams wouldn't be revealed beforehand so the suspense would last all the way to the end. Even the host could only wait for the results.

Team A, Lu Boyuan, Samsara's Grappler Lu Boyuan walked onstage. This meant that Samsara's four All-Star players would not all be working together in the team competition.

Team B? Yang Cong, 301's captain and an old general, would be taking the lead for Team B.

Lu Boyuan's account was Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, who, after Samsara obtained the character Flying Drops from Tiny Herb and taken all his equipment, was now the number one Grappler in Glory.

The original number one Grappler Flying Drops no longer existed. What about Flying Drop's original player, Li Yihui? After that summer's transfers, he had gone to the team that Yang Cong now led, 301 Degrees.

It was only after the host explained all this backstory that everyone realized that there was also this gimmick hiding in Team B. Yang Cong and Tiny Herb's Xu Bin were former teammates reunited!

In 301, Xu Bin had only been Yang Cong's assistant, but after transferring to Tiny Herb, thanks to the team's influence, his popularity was now even higher than Yang Cong's. In the All-Star voting, Yang Cong was at 24th, barely making it in, while Xu Bin was at 16th, a very stable position.

Yang Cong was a player from Season 3 and was now growing old, entering the twilight years of his career. He wouldn't have any new upgrades, and his professional career would probably just stop at his time in 301. But Xu Bin was a player from Season 6. He'd earned some attention and then entered the powerhouse Tiny Herb; he had nothing but a bright future ahead of him.

Even as the audience compared these two players and sighed, the battle onstage had already begun.

Victory or loss didn't matter too much at All-Stars. The battle also opened voice channel, available to players from both sides, so that even opponents could communicate.

But Lu Boyuan and Yang Cong evidently didn't have much to talk about. The two simply greeted each other, and then began to fight.

Lu Boyuan was also a player from Season 6, now at the pinnacle of his professional career. Originally smothered by the shining aura of Samsara's Zhou Zekai, he was able to earn a high amount of attention for himself after Samsara's first championship victory and his performance in those finals. From then on, he walked on the road to All-Stars.

But from the way things currently were, his position didn't seem to be that stable, especially after Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf's joining Samsara this season. Lu Boyuan, an All-Star level player, could only be considered the fourth player in the team.

Former Blue Rain player Yu Feng had chosen to leave for Hundred Blossoms in hopes of obtaining a higher position in the team. But Lu Boyuan? His position seemed to be even more awkward than Yu Feng's had been. What were his thoughts?

He didn't have any thoughts.

The meaning of that was that, for this sort of thing about which Yu Feng cared greatly, he didn't care at all.

It might seem like he didn't have much of a strong heart, but perhaps this was simply the personality of a natural-born Samsara player.

Lu Boyuan became a pro in Season 6. His teammate Zhou Zekai was only one year earlier, but at that time, the title of Great Gunner was already resounding throughout the Alliance. This player, who was silent offstage and yet performed explosively strong onstage, quickly sent Samsara from a mediocre, mid-tier team into the ranks of the strong teams.

Back then, they were already calling Samsara a one-man team. Back then, Zhou Zekai's light was already obscuring the entire team. And so Samsara's players like Lu Boyuan, from then until now, were very used to being outshone by this sort of light. Now that a Sun Xiang had appeared, pushing Lu Boyuan further down to fourth…

The fourth player, this was what the outside world said. But Lu Boyuan didn't have this thought in his heart, nor did any of the other players in Samsara. To the outside world, Samsara was Zhou Zekai and everyone else.

Correct. Aside from Zhou Zekai, the others were just "everyone else" even the newly-transferred Sun Xiang.

This sort of environment seemed like it'd invite disharmony. That unique character so easily crowded all of the others into that "everyone else."

But Samsara continued to walk along harmoniously. Because Samsara's unique person was Zhou Zekai, that quiet person. No matter how brilliantly the Great Gunner shone onstage, offstage Zhou Zekai was still such a humble, unassuming person. No matter how his position had changed in just these few years, no matter how many activities the sponsors or the team had him participate in, his personality was still just like this.

As teammates that had gotten along with each other for so many years, Lu Boyuan and the others understood Zhou Zekai's personality better than anyone else. Although he didn't speak much, he was a very easy-going person. Although he was the number one in Glory, he wasn't someone who very much liked receiving attention. Too much attention would only make him nervous and shy. Yet despite this personality, he'd become a star that thousands were watching, and even after he'd been a star for so many years, he still just had this kind of personality.

Regarding this point, Samsara's players admired him very much.

They often thought, if one day Zhou Zekai faced the camera and was able to suddenly make a complaint or crack a joke or something, what kind of earth-shaking moment would that be?

Samsara's internal affairs were just that harmonious. Zhou Zekai as the unique number one and the others as "everyone else" was only how the outside world understood it. But to Team Samsara themselves? They understood the true Zhou Zekai, and wouldn't be fooled by that onstage Great Gunner. Zhou Zekai hadn't pulled apart from them, and so, in their eyes, Zhou Zekai was also a part of that "everyone else" and Samsara didn't have any special members.

So, the fourth player in the team?

Lu Boyuan truly did not have that feeling.

Weren't they all the same? He always had that kind of feeling. This was the feeling that Samsara brought to every team member.

So even as the outside world analyzed what problems Sun Xiang's addition would incite within the team, Samsara was all peaceful winds and calm waves. In this harmonious team environment, their tolerance was really very high. If a newcomer really had some dissatisfaction, when they saw how even Zhou Zekai was so low-profile and silent, what kind of person would feel they had the status in this team to be cocky?

Samsara was very fortunate that they had a player like Zhou Zekai. Not just because of his strength, but because of his personality. And so they ultimately constructed the strongest team in the Alliance, of which Lu Boyuan was a member.

But in this match, he ultimately lost.

On one hand, this was All-Stars, Lu Boyuan fought quite casually. But more importantly, it was because Yang Cong played too intensely!

Up until now, Yang Cong had always attacked directly. Despite being an Assassin, he was an Assassin that walked in the light, on the straight road. But this time, he used Life-Risking Strike. This skill was one his Scene Killer had learned and added points to, but it had always just been a skill held in reserve as a surprise. Yet this time, he actually used it.

Life-Risking Strike, one-hit kill!

As soon as the Assassin used this skill, that meant that if you didn't die, I would…

"Captain Yang, you were too ruthless…" When Life-Risking Strike hit Chaotic Cloudy Mountain from the side, Lu Boyuan said this in surprise.

"Hehe…" Yang Cong chuckled. This was perhaps already his final performance on this All-Star stage. Let him end on a beautiful note! For Assassins, what people enjoyed the most was this kind of one-hit kill, right?

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain fell, Scene Killer emerged victorious.

The audience was in a daze, and then erupted into cheers.

One-hit kill, the audience loved it! Even neutral parties felt that this one attack was incredibly fulfilling. Plus, most of the audience, as Tyranny fans, were biased toward the Team B player Yang Cong, as their Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie were also in Team B.

But Team B also had a Ye Xiu…

"One bad apple really spoils the whole bunch!" some Tyranny fans thought, indignant. Far below on the floor of the stadium, Ye Xiu was strolling about in boredom.

Chapter 1260: The One Who Wants To Win, Cannot

"A beautiful Life-Risking Strike, a thrilling one-hit kill! Even more incredible, it was done by Yang Cong! This is really too rare, thank you for Yang Cong for your thrilling performance!!" The live host was shouting, and in the television broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo were also discussing this topic.

For Yang Cong to become an All-Star, he was no ordinary player. But on this stage that was resplendent with such stars, he seemed more like a passing guest. He hadn't left much of a mark in the Alliance, and even now there wasn't too much time given to him. This one use of Life-Risking Strike at this All-Stars would perhaps become an unforgettable moment of his professional career.

"Alright, right now Team B is in the lead 1-0!" As the host announced, the display screen updated with the current score.

"Next, will the second players of the two teams please come onstage?" Everyone's eyes swiveled from left to right, waiting to see which two players would stand up.

"First is Team A, this is - oh, another player from Samsara, their vice-captain, Jiang Botao!"

Jiang Botao walked onstage. Team B's player had also stood forward, Zou Yuan from Hundred Blossoms.

"This is a clash of vice-captains!" The host tried to let these matchups have more topics of discussion. Unfortunately, after these two vice-captains went onstage they didn't discuss much as they exchanged blows back and forth. Jiang Botao, who had already expressed how he didn't care much about the All-Star stage, played relatively relaxed. Zou Yuan, on the other hand, was different. Although this was his third time voted into All-Stars, this was the first time he'd earned recognition for his own merits, and not for this or that reason. He didn't want to disappoint those who had voted for him, and so even though this was just a show of a match, he didn't want to lose!

Sadly, things were just that fickle. Zou Yuan, who didn't want to lose, ultimately lost; Jiang Botao, who didn't care about the outcome and played very relaxed, actually won.

"Team A catches up with another point!" the host declared, and the scoreboard updated to reflect this. Zou Yuan returned to his teammates in disappointment, his mood so low that it gave Team B a shock.

"What's wrong? Do you have some grudge against Jiang Botao?" Ye Xiu asked.

"No?" Zou Yuan was caught off-guard.

"Then why do you look so unhappy?" Ye Xiu didn't understand.

"I… lost!" said Zou Yuan.

"Not like it's your first time," said Ye Xiu.

Everyone felt like they were going to be driven mad. This was supposed to be comforting? This wasn't very comforting, was it?

As Zou Yuan's teammate, Yu Feng understood him a bit better and quickly pulled Zou Yuan aside to comfort him. Everyone else shot disdainful gazes at Ye Xiu.

"Who's up next?" Ye Xiu ignored them, calling for the next player.

"It's my turn." For Team B, Misty Rain's Li Hua was playing in the next battle.

From Team A, the one who stood up was Wind Howl's vice-captain, Liu Hao.

"Haha, another confrontation between vice-captains." When the host said this, the stadium booed him for his dullness. These were all All-Stars! Practically all of them were either captain or vice-captain of their respective teams, so discussing a conflict between captains or between vice-captains or between captain and vice-captain wasn't rare at all. This host probably had nothing to say, and so he kept using this as a topic of discussion.

This thought was actually quite correct. The host truly had nothing he could say.

Liu Hao, Li Hua? This… This was another matchup where there wasn't any conflict to be discussed, not at all, not in the players' pasts, nor from the teams they were currently on, nor from any previous fights. Even in the team competitions, thanks to reasons like rotation, these people hadn't ever met, as though they were two parallel lines never intersecting…

When things had reached this point, it had to be said that the television broadcasters Pan Lin and Li Yibo were leaders in their profession for a reason. While the live host scrambled to find a topic and was booed by the audience, these two said with shock, "Whoa, this is actually the first time these two players are meeting on the official stage!"

From this it could be seen that looking at things from a different angle instantly revealed more points of interest.

Liu Hao and Li Hua, meeting for the first time, were both unfamiliar with each other. Not only was Liu Hao unfamiliar with Li Hua, he was unfamiliar with the All-Star stage as a whole. This was the first time he had reached this stage, this was something he had anticipated for so long, only to discover now that he could only show his face very briefly in the individual round.

Liu Hao very much wanted to prove himself, but… on this star-studded stage, he truly had no way of grabbing a larger role. The team competition was undoubtedly the event that drew the most attention. Compared to Team B, where people like Ye Xiu and Wang Jiexi and Chu Yunxiu were all too lazy and wanted to scurry into the individual matches, Liu Hao was anxious to play in the team competition! Because he knew clearly, the team competition rosters represented those with the strongest battle ability, the stars among the All-Stars. How he wanted to have that identity for himself!

Unfortunately, he did not…

Even if they counted the six people who had the highest All-Star vote count, he wouldn't make it in neither Team A nor Team B.

In Team A, the six people ultimately set to appear in the team round were Zhou Zekai, Sun Xiang, Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian, Tang Hao, and Xiao Shiqin…

Of the six people, aside from Yu Wenzhou ranked at 11th, the others were all tenth place and higher. Liu Hao had no place to try and challenge them for the right to play in the team competition.

Helpless, he could only accept the arrangement to play in the individual round. And now, facing Li Hua, Liu Hao's mind was completely blank. What kind of coincidence was this? Two teams would meet in at least two rounds of competition. Li Hua had entered the Alliance in Season 7, and it'd been several years now. Yet, somehow, they had never met?

Liu Hao felt that this was incredible. If he weren't standing here on this stage now, he never would have expected such a strange thing to happen to him.

He thought it was strange, Li Hua felt the same, so the two players progressed very carefully. After they met, they tested each other, tried to feel out the opponent, while mentally reviewing what research their team had done on this opponent. Afterward, Li Hua's Ninja Dark Forest vanished.

The Ninja's hidden movement began. It looked like Li Hua had already found the rhythm of the battle. Soon, when Dark Forest appeared again and launched an attack, the rhythm was extremely fast. What about Liu Hao? These few years he'd been wandering about and currying favor, and too much of his energy was spent on these things. He was also furiously thinking, but he couldn't think of any useful data. It could be summed up in one phrase: It's only when it comes time to apply knowledge that you regret not acquiring enough.

Liu Hao was filled with regret!

As a newcomer to the All-Star stage, he was like Zou Yuan, he wasn't as relaxed as everyone else. He desperately wanted to win, and he wanted to win beautifully, spectacularly, like Yang Cong in the first match. That Life-Risking Strike had been such a brilliant move!

Yet… Why did he have to meet this Li Hua?

This Ninja player who excelled at hidden movement had also been hidden to him throughout his professional career. Now he suddenly appeared in front of him, during his first All-Star appearance. Was his first show simply going to leave behind this mark of failure?

No… Not just failure, this was straight-up shameful! His Spellblade was beaten pathetically by Li Hua's Ninja, as though this wasn't a contest between evenly-matched heavyweights. At this moment, Liu Hao felt that he could already see countless audience members whispering amongst themselves, countless people staring dumbstruck, countless people thinking, Liu Hao's doing really poorly, is that all the skill he has?

This… is just too painful! What is this Li Hua doing! This is just All-Stars, why is he playing so diligently! Liu Hao suddenly forgot how much he had initially cared about this match, and began to be dissatisfied with Li Hua's investment.

This can't happen!

Liu Hao's heart was screaming, his Spellblade swung his sword, sending out killer shockwaves, but they revealed nothing. Dark Forest's ghostly silhouette had already appeared at his side.

Flickering Pursuit!

Dark Forest's afterimages filled the area, launching consecutive attacks toward Liu Hao's Spellblade. Liu Hao still couldn't get his bearings. He wildly slashed out with two attacks, but all he shredded were the images Dark Forest left behind in the air.

"Li Hua, old brother, how come you're playing so seriously?" Liu Hao managed to squeeze out a laugh, trying to make his words sound more relaxed.

"Ah?" Li Hua paused. "I'm… not really playing that seriously?"

Liu Hao was pissed!

Not playing seriously, you can say something like that? More importantly, you're not playing seriously and yet you can still beat me down like this, are you purposely trying to devastate me!

Liu Hao's little cosmos had been burning for who knew how long now, but the problem was, even though he used up so much energy, he found that he didn't have any sure-kill method. His chaotic and random attacks would only make him feel more powerless and pathetic; he also had no way of calming himself down to make careful observations or analysis. This was the chance for which he had waited so many years, but in the end, it was just going to be destroyed by someone who was invisible to him during his entire pro career! How could he be calm? No way!

He lost!

In the end, Liu Hao lost. The more someone wanted to win, the more they couldn't win. Last round it was Team B, this round it was Team A's turn. Liu Hao came pitifully offstage, feeling that the eyes of the entire stadium were upon him. When he returned to Team A, he didn't even lift his head. He wanted to explain something, but he also knew that those beside him were all Glory's top players. Find some technical excuse to brush it off? He should just save it!

On that note, the individual competition ended, with Team B in a 2 to 1 lead. But as soon as the two teams had tied at 1-1, everyone knew that victory would be determined in the team competition. The group arena wasn't important, this wasn't an Alliance match were points counted.

One by one, the players went onstage to play in the group arena. Team A's first player was Blue Rain's little general Lu Hanwen, while Team B sent Tiny Herb's Xu Bin. Lu Hanwen was young, energetic, and fearless, while Xu Bin had the title of Grind King, his rhythm like a slowly plodding old man. In this interesting confrontation, Xu Bin ultimately came out on top, defeating Lu Hanwen. Next from Team A was the number one Phantom Demon Li Xuan, who defeated Xu Bin. Then, Team B sent on their young player Gao Yingjie to send off Li Xuan. Team A's anchor was the other half of Void's Ghost Duo, Wu Yuce, who killed off Gao Yingjie without giving him much chance to perform.

With this, everyone could determine Team A's roster for the team competition. What about Team B? Which expert would have the responsibility of anchoring the group arena? The host looked toward Team B, the entire stadium looked toward Team B, and then they all rubbed their eyes.

Who's standing up?

That's… Zhang Xinjie?

Is he going to the bathroom? Preparing for the team competition, probably. No, wait, what's going on, he's walking toward the stage? What's going on here?

Team B's group arena anchor is the Cleric????

Chapter 1261: Forced Draw

Zhang Xinjie… playing in the group arena?

When everyone saw that Zhang Xinjie actually walked into the player booth, they had to accept this reality. But the live host? Even now, he still hadn't pulled himself together. He was still just staring blankly, completely forgetting to introduce Team B's player. To announce this person's name for the group arena, he… really wasn't used to it. It was even more unbelievable than Yang Cong's usage of Life-Risking Strike.

"Team B's third player in the group arena is… Zhang Xinjie?" Finally, the host made the announcement, but he still said it with a question mark. He still couldn't quite believe this.

Dead silence in the crowd, and then an explosion of noise. One player sitting in the diehard Tyranny fan section was staring in complete and utter shock, his mouth in the shape of an O, which only closed after a long while. His mood was slightly different from the shock of those around him. The instant he saw Zhang Xinjie come onstage, something whirred in his mind, and he thought of that winter two years ago, in Glory's tenth server. Just outside of the extremely low-level Frost Forest dungeon, that guy who controlled Lord Grim had said to this player: we don't need a Cleric.

And now, on the All-Star stage, the stage upon which the brightest stars of Glory shone, this phrase suddenly echoed in his ear again, floating back and forth nonstop: don't need a Cleric, don't need a Cleric, don't need a Cleric, don't need a Cleric…

Last time, the one who was "don't need a Cleric'd" was him. His Cleric was called Endless Night.

And this time, the one who was "don't need a Cleric'd" was Zhang Xinjie, the Cleric called Immovable Rock, the top healer in all of Glory.

Endless Night suddenly felt that he had no regrets in his life. On this All-Star stage, even Vice-captain Zhang was "don't need a Cleric'd." What the hell was he still bothered about?

His characted loaded in. Cleric Immovable Rock appeared on the group arena map, facing the half-health Ghostblade Carved Ghost.

If a Cleric really wanted to PK, they would have to rely on their powerful healing ability to maintain their health, and then use their few attacking methods to wear away the opponent.

In the Glory game, there was no shortage of Clerics who used this kind of method to PK. But in-game, both player skill and equipment quality was inferior. If Zhang Xinjie ran to the game to play in the Arena, no one would underestimate the battle ability of his Cleric.

However, if player skill and equipment quality were at the same level, a Cleric most certainly was not a bloody hurricane attacking class. This point could be seen from the Heavenly Domain challenge. Clerics and Paladins were very different from the other classes. It was clear that the Glory game had not designed these two classes to be powerful attackers. Those who stacked their points on the skill tree toward attacks were far from mainstream and hadn't earned any recognition in the pro circle. 24 teams, every team had a healer class, none of which was that kind of deviant.

Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock was even less so. This sort of strict player would never waver from the path.

How would this match be fought? The ruckus still hadn't died down, but many people were already wondering.

As for the televised broadcast, it was very quiet. Li Yibo was really depressed! His earlier predictions of the team lineups had been based on the difference of healer against no healer, but who would have thought, Team B had a healer but didn't use it, instead throwing him onto the group arena. This season, he had been truly attacked so much that he was in the perpetual mad state of "can't feel happy without being face-slapped."

Commentator Pan Lin was also silent for a long time. It wasn't until the characters onstage started moving that he said in a strained voice, "Let's watch this match, with Void's Wu Yuce, against… Zhang Xinjie…"

The characters met, and began fighting.

Those who dreamed that Zhang Xinjie had some sort of ultimate sure-kill method were quickly disappointed. Zhang Xinjie's 1v1 Cleric just used the same little tricks that were popular in the game. Change position to maintain distance, recover health during breaks, sparse attacks to wear away the opponent.

Many high-end Clerics in-game could enrage many people to death. Could Zhang Xinjie do it?

The crowd originally had a lot of excitement and anticipation, but gradually, all of it faded away. Because judging from the content of this match, this was truly dull to an unprecedented extent, duller than any other match of previous All-Star Weekends, duller than any match in any season of the League.

Everyone suddenly had a single thought: If Glory battles were all like this, then they should just shut down the League as early as possible.

Fortunately, that wasn't the case…

They watched as Zhang Xinjie controlled Immovable Rock, recovered his health like a robot, occasionally had his rhythm torn by Wu Yuce, but then tenaciously got it back, and then repeated the above process.

The refreshing feeling was gone. The interest was gone.

The players who had more in-game experience had all seen this situation before. It was just that Zhang Xinjie's controls were more precise, and Wu Yuce's attacks were more ferocious.

In terms of attacks, the Cleric really only had so many options. Even Zhang Xinjie couldn't make many changes. He just followed the most common thought processes seen in-game, and then displayed them with a higher level of skill and technique. Faced against a more powerful opponent, the result was… this match looked like it was going to drag on endlessly.

One minute…

Two minutes…

Five minutes…

Ten minutes…

Zhang Xinjie was still very methodically controlling, wearing away. At the start of the match, Carved Ghost had 52% health remaining. Now, 11% had been whittled away, leaving 41%. And that had taken a full ten minutes.

During these ten minutes, Immovable Rock's health had also dropped. This Cleric battle style couldn't be too careless or wasteful. If he used up all his mana, then he would just be fish meat on a plate. But even under Wu Yuce's powerful offensive, Zhang Xinjie didn't ignore everything to fill up his health. He had a set rhythm to maintain the balance of the situation. After ten minutes, Immovable Rock's health had dropped 20%...

And so everyone took another look. Carved Ghost had lost 11% after starting at 52%, wasn't that also a twenty percent decrease? These two guys, they were actually playing at such a precise balance? They were actually going to have to play all the way until the end to determine victory?

To do so… Judging from their current speed, wouldn't that require… forty more minutes?

Those that realized this point instantly paled. The organizers and the television broadcasters were even more panicked. This 1v1 was going to last an hour? That was much too far above the estimated time duration. Were they even going to play the team competition afterward?

Here they panicked, there they panicked, but the two people onstage weren't panicked.

Zhang Xinjie's controls were as methodical as ever. Wu Yuce? He was always a very persistent and persevering person, someone who never gave up easily. Otherwise, the current Void Ghost Duo wouldn't exist.

These two people were actually giving it their all. But it would be many dozen minutes before victory was determined, and with just these repetitive actions. It was truly difficult for anyone to continue watching.

What to do?

A wave of people went to the background, and then the smoking area became overcrowded, and then ambient noise became louder and louder as people started chatting. Lights flashed all over the the crowd like stars in the sky, as a result of countless people starting to play with their phones.

With the team competition finale, the audience couldn't bear to leave, but they honestly could not continue to watch this match.

"We can't let them drag on until the end!" The organizers finally made this decision, which was quickly sent to the stage. The judge entered the match through the system and forcibly declared the group arena a draw. There would be no extra time, it was just a draw! If they added extra time, then by the rules that meant that both sides would have a bit of health added and then face off. Wouldn't that just result in a confrontation between these two guys again? That absolutely could not happen.

The judge stopped the game very arbitrarily. After a pause, the live audience exploded with a surge of applause. Not to Zhang Xinjie, nor to Wu Yuce. This applause was sent to the one with an extremely weak presence in Glory matches, the judge. In this moment, he was the most lovable person in the audience's eyes.

Wu Yuce and Zhang Xinjie could only accept this reality. When the two players stepped out of the player booths, the crowd, with mixed feelings, sent applause to them as well. They could at least respect their seriousness, their perseverance, and their calm acceptance of the forced draw of the match.

After this boring period passed, it was now time for the highest point of this three-day event. And this time, Team B didn't have a healer either. Without a doubt, the two sides would be attacking each other ferociously. Looking at the players left to the team round, they were all the top attackers in the entire Alliance brought together now.

"Coach Li, could you analyze and compare the strengths of the two teams for us?" Pan Lin said.

"The two teams are both composed of the very best of the best. It wouldn't be unexpected for either side to win. However, this is a never-before-seen situation where neither side has a healer. Today's team competition will be the highest-level aggressive match in the entirety of Glory. These two teams have gathered the most powerful attackers in Glory!" Coach Li said.

"You're correct," Pan Lin agreed. The two continued to talk until the team competition finally gathered together onstage.

From Team A were Zhou Zekai, Sun Xiang, Huang Shaotian, Yu Wenzhou, and Tang Hao, with Xiao Shiqin as the sixth player.

From Team B were Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Han Wenqing, Chu Yunxiu, and Wang Jiexi, with Yu Feng as the sixth player.

The two teams were making their final preparations before the map. Team A had the two Master Tacticians Yu Wenzhou and Xiao Shiqin. Earlier, many people were uncomfortable with how Xiao Shiqin had dealt with Yu Wenzhou, but looking at their direct interactions now, there didn't seem to be any difficulties. The two were discussing nonstop, occasionally shooting glances at Team B. After several close-ups, the camera switched to Team B, and it could be seen that the two of them were likely discussing Team B's player Ye Xiu.

Team B's player Ye Xiu seemed very relaxed. This other Master Tactician didn't seem like he was making any arrangements for his team as a whole. He only said a sentence to Han Wenqing, standing beside him.

"When the battle begins, try to stay away from me. I fear that my attacks will automatically be drawn to your body," Ye Xiu said to Han Wenqing, very seriously.

Chapter 1262: Scatter

The team competition that was about to begin was the highlight of the three-day All-Stars Weekend. Everyone knew clearly that the result or the quality of this game may not be the finest, but it was definitely the most star-studded. Currently, there was no other event besides the All-Stars Weekend that allowed such a group of people to play together, whether it be alongside or against each other. This exhibition was well worth watching.'

Right now, the cheers in the crowd were directed more towards Team B, where Team Tyranny's players and characters were. However, even though this was Tyranny's home stadium, the hollering in support of Team A would not lose out much: many of the Glory Alliance's players with the most fans were all gathered on this All-Stars stage. Even though Team B had a slight home advantage, it was nowhere near enough to overwhelm Team A.

There was plenty of eye-candy prepared for this most important final match. The participating characters appeared one by one, and gave a little show for several minutes. However, no one was bored at the slightest; instead, this tease held back their energy. When the map finished loading and the match officially began, the crowd had entered a strange state of peace.

The map was specifically designed for the All-Stars match. There were mountains and rivers, trees and rocky outcrops, and street and buildings. It seemed to be an amalgamation of all the different maps used in Glory. In the very middle of the map, there was an arena made of limestone that looked thousands of years old. From an aerial view, it formed the Glory Alliance's logo as well as the number "10", to celebrate Season 10 of the Glory Alliance.

The players from both teams quickly spawned to much applause. Just seeing these famous characters form into teams was enough to get the viewers very excited.

Neither side seemed to want to beat about the bush. Since spawning, both teams charged towards the centre. Sending Zhang Xinjie to fight the group arena was a indication by team B that they wanted to fight Team A head on.

A fierce confrontation was originally the preferred strategy for Team A, who lacked a healer. But now, it was instead Team B who ditched their healer and took up this strategy. Could the players from Team A back off from a direct confrontation? Of course not! Who's afraid of who?

The match's pace was swift as soon as it commenced. Both sides rushed forward, past the scenery which became a blur in the background. Without a slow-moving healer, both sides' progress seemed very rapid. Finally, the opposition were within each other's sights.

There was no communication or command for formations, but the characters from both teams went into an arrangement that seemed to have been agreed on beforehand.

For Team A, the trio consisting of Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf, Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain and Tang Hao's Demon Subduer formed a straight line and stood in front. Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer followed behind by only a few units. Yu Wenzhou's Swoksaar brought up the rear and concealed himself behind his teammates.

For Team B, Han Wenqing's Desert Dust was the spearhead in front with Ye Xiu's Lord Grim trailing a few steps behind. After them, Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain, Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria and Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain formed a horizontal line at the back.

The two teams chose reversed formations. Team A's arrangement of three characters in front seemed to allow for more aggression. However, Team B were the first ones to start attacking. Even though there were three characters at the back for team B, they were all long ranged classes and team A entered their attack ranges first.

A maelstrom of cannon fire and magical energies erupted and rolled forward. The centre of the map where the Alliance's logo was located was immediately covered by bedazzling flashes of light.

Scatter!

The three Team A characters at the front suddenly changed directions as if it was pre-arranged. It looked like they were trying to go around the suppressive fire that was being laid down by Team B. But Team B would not let them off so easy. Their attacks closely followed the change in position, and they still managed to keep Team A out of attack range.

But as the three gave way, the second layer of Team A was suddenly at the forefront: Cloud Piercer!

Accelerate!

Cloud Piercer charged forward, guns blazing. He looked like a melee class character despite being a long-ranged Gunner class. Team A astonishingly used their three Gods at the front to draw their opponents' attention, all to allow Zhou Zekai to begin a solo assault. His attacks blanketed all the characters on Team B. The Sharpshooter's high attack speed was brought to the peak at this moment. Cloud Piercer grasped his dual pistols to begin launching his attacks, unleashing a countless flurry of bullets.

Blood splattered within Team B's formation. This wave of attacks came too quickly. It was fierce and covered a lot of ground.

But because the coverage of the attacks was wide, the bullets were spread out, so the damage output was reduced significantly. However, the higher-level skills of Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain and Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria had casting time. Even though being shot did not deal much damage, their casts would be interrupted. As both their attacks were stifled, Team B's long-range zoning seemed to have been extinguished for the moment. There was no way Dancing Rain's attacks alone could suppress the three Gods, Sun Xiang, Huang Shaotian and Tang Hao, at the same time.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf led with an ultimate skill to forcefully break into the opponents formation. In an instant, the Samsara fans went wild: this was the teamwork they were so used to seeing. After Sun Xiang joined Samsara, his duo play-style revolved around having him wreak havoc in the enemy's midst while Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer attacked from the outside. Countless teams were scattered by just this two, with their ability to bust apart an enemy team from inside and out. Even in the current situation with the best of the best as the opponents, it looked like Samsara's duo was still extremely potent..

Shattering the Lands!

After charging in with Dragon Breaks the Ranks, One Autumn Leaf followed up with another high-level skill. His body in mid-air and Evil Annihilation in his hands channeling magical battle spirit, he carried an air of invincibility about him as his spear shot down towards the enemy, like a God descending to smite mortals.

Scatter!

Team B suddenly scattered. Unlike the three-man scatter on Team A, all five players scattered and neatly formed a circle. And right in the middle of this circle was One Autumn Leaf…

One Autumn Leaf looked like he was descending from the heavens for one moment, but in the next, after Team B scattered, he suddenly looked like he was charging directly into the abyss.

Boom!

Shattering the Lands' magic created waves in the ground. At that moment, the ground within the skill's AoE folded up. However, not a single character was caught up in it. There were only skills in the AoE - not just from Shattering the Lands...

After dodging Shattering the Lands, the three ranged characters on Team B instantly followed up with a counter-attack. Everything happened quickly and precisely. Three ranged attacks landed on One Autumn Leaf who was still in the ending animation of his skill. There was zero chance to dodge. In fact, this hasty counter-attack was even coordinated. The three attacks were not simultaneous but chained, and they landed on One Autumn Leaf one after the other.

Although the damage wouldn't be increased, the status effects' duration was prolonged by chaining the attacks. In the short time frame where One Autumn Leaf was chain-stunned by the three attacks, Desert Dust and Lord Grim approached like the wind to flank him.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

Han Wenqing also led with a high-level skill. Desert Dust flew forward and One Autumn Leaf was greeted by his fist. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim couldn't display this sort of momentum, because even though they could be added to the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, they would be too low level. Thus, Ye Xiu did not choose to do so but instead charged next to One Autumn Leaf only with the intention of creating a pincer. He was also there to provide protection, since the rest of Team A wouldn't just watch and let One Autumn Leaf get surrounded and eliminated.

Zhou Zekai, the current teammate and duo partner of Sun Xiang, reacted the fastest. Cloud Piercer's attacks could also arrive the fastest. Random Firing!

Random Firing was a skill that sprayed bullets in all directions. However, under Zhou Zekai's tyrannical control, he forcefully turned the bullets into a very targeted stream. This stream of bullets flew accurately at the two characters on either side of One Autumn Leaf.

Dodge?

It was impossible to dodge this rain of bullets unless they abandoned their attack on One Autumn Leaf. However, Team B had no intentions of doing so. Han Wenqing allowed Desert Dust to continue his Ferocious Tiger Frenzy as if he didn't see the flurry of attacks from Cloud Piercer's direction. Although he and Ye Xiu were archrivals of many years, he seemed to have complete trust that Ye Xiu would deal with the current situation. Therefore, Han Wenqing simply ignored the attacks from Zhou Zekai and focused on his own attacks.

Swish!

The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella opened up and sheltered Lord Grim and Desert Dust from Cloud Piercer's hail of bullets.

"Put your back into it, get a good trade in!" Ye Xiu called.

Blocking with a shield could only negate status effects. It could not completely negate damage, which was dependant on the weight of the shield and other particular stats.

The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's weight was very light, but its attributes were still quite substantial. The Level 70 Myriad Manifestation Umbrella in shield form provided a 61% boost in defence as well as 34% damage absorption. These two abilities would take effect as soon as the shield met any attacks. But Glory's top Gunner, Cloud Piercer, obviously wouldn't stop trying to punch through Lord Grim's defences just because of these two abilities.

Lord Grim's health was still dropping. This kind of defence was just an exchange. Lord Grim's health for One Autumn Leaf's health...

The two characters who had an unbreakable bond with Ye Xiu were currently locked in such an exchange. One of the damage dealers happened to be Ye Xiu's biggest rival of all time, Han Wenqing. This scene could only be described as somewhat ironic. Team A, however, didn't just consist of Zhou Zekai. Huang Shaotian, the biggest opportunistic player of Glory, saw a great chance. Troubling Rain quickly appeared in front of the shield form Myriad Manifestation Umbrella. Right now, the Umbrella shield was completely blocking Lord Grim's field of view. Xe Xiu couldn't do much about this. If he stuck his head out to look, Zhou Zekai's marksmanship would deliver a faceful of bullets.

Troubling Rain used the cover provided by the shield form Myriad Manifestation Umbrella to deliver some pain!

Chapter 1263: Small Details and Techniques

Troubling Rain instantly got within melee range using the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's shield form as cover.

"Careful!" Huang Shaotian heard Yu Wenzhou's voice. Yu Wenzhou's Swoksaar stood rather far away. From his point of view, he suddenly realized that Huang Shaotian being captured was an opportunity, but also a trap.

Huang Shaotian quickly controlled Troubling Rain to move sideways upon hearing Yu Wenzhou's warning. Since he had already gotten this far, he might as well continue attacking rather than retreat. He only needed to be careful of whatever was hidden behind the umbrella. After all, this was just a Blind Shield playstyle. If he took the initiative and moved first, how could he not dodge it?

He couldn't dodge it!

Troubling Rain had barely taken half a step when the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella closed up. Huang Shaotian didn't even have time to see the character behind the umbrella before his screen was filled by a blinding light. This attack couldn't get any closer. There was absolutely nothing he could do that could dodge an attack which was close enough to singe his eyebrows...

Laser Rifle!

Only the Best Partners Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu could achieve this kind of precision. Ye Xiu used the Blind Shield playstyle to hide Su Mucheng's long ranged attack rather than his own.

"You want to ambush me? How naive!" Ye Xiu laughed, as he watched Troubling Rain tumble away from the Laser Rifle.

"Just fight, stop talking so much trash!" Huang Shaotian yelled.

The whole stadium collectively shared a sweatdrop. Bro, you're the one saying this? Are you trying to say that you're the strong and silent type?

Huang Shaotian's ambush failed. Zhou Zekai also sacrificed dealing damage to coordinate with the ambush. Even though there was no friendly fire, shots didn't just pass through allies. Zhou Zekai couldn't have Cloud Piercer move around Troubling Rain, because that might have lead Ye Xiu to turn and reveal Huang Shaotian's position...

Huang Shaotian's ambush was ultimately fruitless. This moment was over in the blink of an eye, but it contained so many small details. Right now, the guest commentator Li Yibo, conducting the live TV broadcast, wanted to share his analysis with everyone. But who could spare the effort to listen to his explanation? The match had long left this moment behind.

The players on Team B couldn't idly watch and let Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing trade health by tanking the enemy's attacks. The moment Su Mucheng foiled Huang Shaotian's ambush, Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain had already cast Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire. It engulfed Lord Grim, One Autumn Leaf, and Desert Dust together. Tang Hao attempted to interrupt her cast, but he was intercepted by Wang Jiexi. Currently, Vaccaria and Demon Subduer were locked in a skirmish.

The viewers' eyes were in a blur. They did not know where to look. Out of the ten players on the field, it looked like Yu Wenzhou was the only one who had some free time. However, his presence couldn't be ignored.

Yu Wenzhou may have trouble keeping up with the pace of this explosive battle because of his crippled hand speed. However, he obviously had his own, slower style of play which still secured him a place as a God in the Alliance. In this kind of flashy battle, Yu Wenzhou wasn't at all useless. Rather, his crowd control skills as a Warlock was indispensable to his team and extremely disruptive to his opponents. In this game with no healer, where the fight was blood for blood, one successfully landed control skill might just cripple a character entirely.

On the other hand, Team B's five on the field plus Yu Feng as a sixth were all top damage dealers. As for crowd control, they could only rely on their observation and mechanics and share the burden. They couldn't compare to Yu Wenzhou, who could focus on observing the entire battlefield and act accordingly.

Now, Team A's strategy was pretty much on the tables. From the start, they wanted to give Yu Wenzhou plenty of space to let his Warlock control the battle. Thus, the other four characters had to handle more of the head-on fighting. However, Huang Shaotian was one of the four. This so-called expert opportunity seizer was different from a core attacker. In Blue Rain, he seldom filled the role of the spearhead attacker. It used to be Yu Feng, and now, that position was passed to the fourteen year old Lu Hanwen, not Huang Shaotian.

This didn't mean Huang Shaotian was very bad at head-on type attacks. It was just that to him, being a head-on attacker simply did not fully display his talents and capabilities. He needed a certain amount of cover and waited for an opportunity before acting

Huang Shaotian didn't manage to seize this opening. However, the match had only just begun. Being able to create this opportunity for Huang Shaotian was already remarkable. This was because he had even fiercer teammates, who could provide cover for him.

Sun Xiang, Zhou Zekai!

This duo that had only existed for half a season at Samsara could probably be called the duo with the strongest offensive capabilities within the current Glory Alliance. Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf charged in and got himself surrounded. At first, this move seemed somewhat rash. However, with the ranged support from Zhou Zekai on the outside of the encirclement, Team B's flank did not have an easy time. Even though Huang Shaotian missed his chance to sneak up, the outstanding duo's skill was fully demonstrated. Team A didn't manage to get an advantage, but the battlefield was set for Yu Wenzhou's Warlock so that no one could suppress him.

Swoksaar began casting his curse. The spell would spell trouble for Team B if no one interrupted it. Su Mucheng quickly pressed forward, and Dancing Rain's cannon aimed at Swoksaar. However, Troubling Rain's silhouette quickly darted into her field of view and blocked her line of sight with Swoksaar.

An annoying screen tactic. This wouldn't stop the attack entirely, but rather bought a few moments for the ally behind him to finish his curse. This sort of tactic was what the opportunist Huang Shaotian was particularly adept at. His little obstruction stopped Dancing Rain from attacking, giving Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer time to close the distance between them. As he ran, he attacked continuously, pressing down on her with wild firepower.

The instant Zhou Zekai switched targets, a shadow flickered out from within Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire.

"Old Ye!" It was as if Huang Shaotian's mouth would itch if he stopped talking. Sword light flew out from a Sword Draw.

Miss!

His attack was aimed according to where he thought his opponent would move to. The attack missed, and it didn't even affect Ye Xiu's rhythm. He slipped beneath the sword light from Sword Draw with a Slide Kick. The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella assumed its gun form mid-slide and aimed towards Swoksaar. A gunshot rang out.

Bang!

As the bullet flied out, Yu Wenzhou sighed helplessly. His hand speed might be slow, but his judgement and observation were top notch. He immediately knew that this bullet would arrive before his casting finished.

Yu Wenzhou cancelled the skill and moved aside to dodge. When he looked again, Lord Grim was almost in front of him..

So fast!

An unspecialized's swiftness in closing short distances was now well renowned within all of Glory. Ye Xiu had already demonstrated how troublesome this technique was in many matches. Chaining together two skills would make him seem like he was almost teleporting, as shown in the Rookie Challenge matches in day one of the All-Stars weekend. It was an astonishing sight to see.

And now, Lord Grim was able to instantly close in on Swoksaar, when he was still inside the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire just moments before. No melee class had movement skills this strong. On top of that, the unspecialized even had ranged attacking methods, allowing him to switch targets while moving. The opponent was hard-pressed to get away.

But just before Lord Grim was right next to Swoksaar, he came to a sudden halt.

Boom!

A burst of Shadow Flames danced a step in front of Lord Grim. Clearly, the sudden halt by Lord Grim was to avoid being engulfed in the Shadow Flames.

"How scary, you almost blew me up," said Ye Xiu.

"Didn't I miss though?" Smiled Yu Wenzhou. His crippled hands would definitely put him at a disadvantage if a melee character got close. And right now, the one who came marching was none other than Lord Grim, who attacked like a hurricane. Lord Grim would be able to bury him right there. But even though Yu Wenzhou was in this predicament, he did not panic in the slightest. He held an instant cast spell like Shadow Flames and cast it at the last second. This was the most dangerous option for him, but it was also the most difficult for his opponent to deal with. In the last moments of a charge, when the target was within arm's reach, anyone's guard would drop to some extent; the player would probably be thinking about what attack to use next. Yu Wenzhou's sudden attack at this moment was very tricky to guard against.

"I wouldn't be afraid even if I was hit by this skill," Ye Xiu said. Shadow Flames inflicted a status effect, whereby the target would take damage over time. Caster classes found this skills particularly troublesome, as each tick of damage would interrupt their casting. However, an unspecialized at melee range could use an array of instant cast skills. Shadow Flames' interruptions were irrelevant. The damage alone could be tolerated. However, Ye Xiu still had Lord Grim dodge, since he couldn't tell what curse Swoksaar had thrown out.

Another instant filled with countless small details.

Just a slight pause was enough to turn the tables. Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain was already behind Lord Grim. Ye Xiu obviously couldn't just attack Swoksaar with reckless abandon. However, fighting Huang Shaotian with Yu Wenzhou right there would be very dangerous. His hand speed might be slow, but he was still extremely proficient at grasping opportunities. Ye Xiu wouldn't give him a chance to stir up trouble like that.

Lord Grim, who had just managed to get right next to Swoksaar, didn't attack even once. Instead, he quickly moved away.

Lord Grim shifted horizontally to dodge Troubling Rain's lunging sword, then turned tail and ran.

"Don't run!" Huang Shaotian yelled while chasing after him closely. On the other side, Zhou Zekai saw the situation and quickly turned to form a pincer with Huang Shaotian. However, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim dodge crazily. Various movement type skills were thrown out and comboed, to the point where even Huang Shaotian and Zhou Zekai combined couldn't suppress him momentarily.

The crowd was stunned.

Right now, Teams A and B each had a character that was the main attack target, and they happened to be One Autumn Leaf and Lord Grim. It seemed like Ye Xiu really owned characters with some interesting history.

How about the current owners of these characters? Their responses were the opposite of each other. One Autumn Leaf stood steadfast under Sun Xiang's control and welcomed the attacks head on; Lord Grim assumed deft poses and dodged attack after attack under Ye Xiu's control.

Chapter 1264: Unending Choices

The two teams, A and B, had each relied on a single person to pin their opponents in some form. An unrelenting offense was definitely a better way to disrupt an opponent then hiding around and dodging attacks. After all, if you faced your opponents head on like that, it wouldn't just be a one way beat down. When engaging your opponent, you'd still be a threat. If the other wavered even slightly, there was the chance that you could counter and crush them. As for dodging around, that made you passive and it would become harder to stick to an opponent and disrupt them. Your opponents could easily switch targets and ignore a troublemaker who ran around.

But the problem was that the character who was currently executing this pin was Lord Grim.

Unspecialized Lord Grim not only had ranged attacks, but also those methods of unexpectedly increasing his movement speed. Whenever he began to move, Team A's members would always go on high alert. No other class was such a comprehensive threat, to the point where Team A was currently using two top Gods, Huang Shaotian and Zhou Zekai to suppress him.

But even the combination of these two top Gods was having trouble dealing with the special class backed by Ye Xiu's cunning.

The disruption Sun Xiang was achieving was costing him blood! But for Ye Xiu? He ran, leaving dust in his wake, luring away two of Team A's most powerful characters with not a scratch. If this continued, then what would be the point of Sun Xiang's disruption? It was practically like they were offering him up to Team B to beat up.

"Cover me!" Yu Wenzhou called out. Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain immediately sheathed his sword and returned to his position, standing guard at Swoksaar's side. Zhou Zekai also changed his pace in accordance. Cloud Piercer began to move faster. As a Sharpshooter, he didn't keep his distance from his opponent, but instead pulled closer to Lord Grim, clearly hoping to strengthen the effects of his firepower to suppress him. If needed, he'd probably pull even closer and engage with Gun Fu.

Swoksaar began to cast, and it seemed like he planned on finishing this cast no matter the cost. He was even using Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain as a meat shield.

Ye Xiu wasn't able to go and interrupt, what with Huang Shaotian lying in wait and Zhou Zekai advancing on him. If he persisted in trying to interrupt, he would definitely be completely trapped by these two.

　

It was just that, with three of Team A's characters focused on Lord Grim, two of Team B's characters became free to act. Su Mucheng and Chu Yunxiu, originally having been giving long-ranged support, turned their attacks this way upon seeing Ye Xiu stuck between a rock and a hard place.

Dancing Rain stepped forward in front of Windy Rain and whipped out a Gatling Gun, wildly spraying bullets as she covered for Windy Rain's spell.

　

Dancing Rain's bullets arrived, and no matter how amazing Huang Shaotian's mechanics were, he couldn't use his swordsmanship to cut down every bullet. However, if the bullets flew past him, even if just one hit, then it would interrupt Swoksaar's cast.

Thus, Troubling Rain shielded Swoksaar like a knight, taking a sturdy stance in front of the other. He dealt with what bullets he could, and if he couldn't, then he would block them with his body.

Thud thud thud!

Flowers of blood bloomed one by one on Troubling Rain's body, making him look exceptionally heroic. However… Gatling Gun was a still a low level skill. Troubling Rain did look heroic, shielding Swoksaar with his body, and there was enough blood to set the scene, but in terms of actual damage, it wasn't even worth mentioning. To make sure the cast was finished, this was completely worth it.

However, being constantly hit by bullets, Troubling Rain's movements couldn't be smoothly controlled. There was still some level of stun from being hit by a bullet. With the consecutive hits, the small stuns linked up and the victim definitely wouldn't be able to move smoothly any longer. Thus, Windy Rain's spell was purposefully released just as Troubling Rain was most difficult to control. A Piercing Lightning shot forth.

　

"Oh shit!" A silent stutter of the heart wasn't Huang Shaotian's style. He had to yell out directly. Windy Rain had hid behind Dancing Rain and suddenly struck with this skill, at such a time...

How could he block it? He couldn't!

Piercing Lightning prepared to fly straight through the miniscule opening that Troubling Rain left under the effects of the consecutive attacks. Swoksaar had little choice but to cancel the cast he was executing.

Team A's plan seemed to have failed, but that was when Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf suddenly broke through his pin.

Was Han Wenqing unable to suppress Sun Xiang without support?

Of course not.

Han Wenqing's attacks weren't just thrown with reckless abandon. He would cooperate with the support he was getting to perfect his offense. However, Su Mucheng and Chu Yunxiu had suddenly pulled their support away just now. One Autumn Leaf, who was fighting several on his own, immediately found an opening. Sun Xiang had grasped that opportunity and broken out through that opening.

Was it a misconderation of Su Mucheng and Chu Yunxiu's?

Evidently not.

This was yet another choice. To interrupt the Warlock's cast or to continue their support. They didn't split up and each take one choice because they knew that they wouldn't accomplish anything then. Thus, the two decided to interrupt the Warlock's skill. After all, a Warlock's CC would be crucial to changing the tides of battle.

Thus, the Warlock's skill had been interrupted, but Sun Xiang had escaped. He didn't, as people expected, immediately begin to counterattack Desert Dust, but instead chose to retreat. When Han Wenqing pursued him, he avoided the other and charged at Su Mucheng and Chu Yunxiu's characters.

　

These two characters were definitely not good with close combat, but if the two moved, Team B's formation would be disrupted. Team A had set trap after trap, considering all the details, and managed to back all the members of Team B into a difficult place.

What should they do?

No matter how difficult, they had to choose a choice of action immediately. Decisiveness was also one of the crucial characteristics a top level player possessed.

　

Dancing Rain raised her cannon and began to attack!

She didn't dodge and instead launched a direct offense at One Autumn Leaf while Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain pulled away. These two female pros chose the third option out of to retreat or not to retreat. One retreated while the other didn't. It seemed like a wishy washy decision, but it would allow them to retain their positioning with one person stalling so that One Autumn Leaf would disrupt their formation too much.

　

It was a very clever and daring decision, and the two did well in deciding who would play what role. But they neglected to consider the players themselves. When One Autumn Leaf charged towards her and Su Mucheng hurriedly raised her cannon to attack, what lay in her heart was reluctance.

Because that was One Autumn Leaf.

　

Though it was just a character, it meant much more than that to Su Mucheng.

She had never considered that, one day, she would cross cannon against spear with this character. She knew that she had to maintain a professional attitude, but attitude wasn't the same as feelings...

Su Mucheng felt very conflicted, causing her mechanics to falter somewhat. One Autumn Leaf wasn't disrupted all that much, charging forth fearlessly. Chu Yunxiu startled. This was different from what they had anticipated. She wasn't ready to provide support for her yet!

A mistake!

Su Mucheng had realized her mistake just now, too, but there was no chance to make an attempt at saving the situation. One Autumn Leaf had arrived, glittering sparks of light drifting around him like broken stardust.

This was...

　

Su Mucheng and Sun Xiang had both noticed the abnormality in their field of view. This definitely wasn't something either of them could produce. This was...

From the air, a broom swiftly descended.

　

Vaccaria, Broom Tornado activated, swung his Stardust Extermination.

Chapter 1265: The So-Called Magician

Wang Jiexi!

Don't mention the players on the field, even the audience who had the omniscient view felt that Vaccaria's sudden violent arrival was shocking and bizarre. Truly, every single confrontation on field was a dazzling blur, from the cover of Ye Xiu's Lord Grim to his charging out from a Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire. Even the slightest change could affect everything. The players of the two teams one by one entered a chaotic exchange of attacking and defending.

The nonstop changes were dizzying for the audience to watch, and in the process of this, Wang Jiexi and Tang Hao were the two players that hadn't entered the chaotic brawl. And so, the presence of these two players was overlooked to some extent. The ones more absorbed in the fight almost forgot that these two players were still fighting, until now, when Vaccaria suddenly plunged from the sky, with an arcing trajectory that seemed to trail stardust, and a Broom Tornado came down fiercely upon One Autumn Leaf's back.

Vaccaria had arrived!

Only now did everyone remember this person's existence, and they thought of the opponent he had been tangled with just earlier.

The live audience was fortunate, as the immersive projection system made a huge difference in watching the battle live versus watching the television broadcast. They had a full aerial view of the entire battle. But this time, even they had forgotten to pay attention to that area, until now.

The audience turned their views, the television broadcast cut to a different camera, the target: Demon Subduer.

And so, in the eyes of the audience, in the camera view of the broadcast, Demon Subduer, the number one Brawler of Glory, a character that had reached the peak thanks to Tang Hao's upgrade, was currently pathetically collapsed on the ground.

What in the world had happened?

Everyone was engulfed by curiosity to the extreme, and the pain of the television broadcasters was great, for the current battle was progressing quite ferociously, and there was no way for them to cut back and show a replay.

"Show it in a small screen!" one of the senior workers shouted.

Thus, those that were watching the broadcast could now see in the lower corner of their screen a smaller display, replaying the events that had just occurred for everyone to see.

No viewer objected to this, because they too were intensely curious as to what had transpired between Wang Jiexi and Tang Hao.

As for the live viewers? They couldn't see a replay with the projection system, but the display screens didn't interfere with what was currently going on as they too showed the replay for everyone.

Everyone watched… In reality, it wasn't very long, it was just from when Lord Grim helped cover Desert Dust to when Vaccaria sent One Autumn Leaf flying. This entire process hadn't taken very long.

And during that chaotic pile of fighting, what happened between Wang Jiexi and Tang Hao was actually very simple. It could be summarized in one sentence: Tang Hao was completely crushed by Wang Jiexi.

Although this sentence was short, the amount of information it contained was truly shocking.

Early on, everyone had acknowledged that Tang Hao was standing at the summit, someone who wouldn't lose to any God at the summit, past or present. But just now, in that brief period of time, he had been crushed.

Crushed meant that he had utterly no ability to defend or parry. Something like that absolutely should not occur to a top God.

The television broadcast didn't just immediately move on after replaying it once; they continued to use the small window to display it a second time. The live screens also didn't just replay it once, they even used split-screen to replay it again and again from different angles.

This wasn't Tiny Herb's home stadium, but period of silence, the live crowd exploded with home stadium-like cheers. And this was just for a mere replay, a replay of something that had already happened.

"This is…" In the broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo had given up on their commentary of the match, and were instead searching for something to say about this past.

"This is the true Magician!" Li Yibo reached this conclusion.

Indeed, the unimaginable playstyle, the trajectories impossible to capture, the rhythms and changes like magic, these were the techniques used by Wang Jiexi in the past that earned him the title of Magician, and these were the techniques that he sacrificed for the sake of Team Tiny Herb.

Now, it could be seen that Wang Jiexi had not forgotten these techniques entirely. In this All-Star Competition, in this competition where he didn't have to take up many responsibilities at all, he very casually displayed this style. And so, Tang Hao, this Season 7 debutant, someone who had never experienced the Magician style firsthand, a young player who had only seen the style in old recordings and data, was beaten down by it until he couldn't tell which way was north anymore.

People understood this point, and everyone was very clear, this wasn't a difference in skill. Tang Hao simply met something that he had never experienced before. It was just like all those players who, upon encountering Lord Grim for the first time, were thrown into confusion. In a 1v1, quite a few people had been wiped out by Ye Xiu. As of now, Tang Hao had yet to meet Lord Grim, and if he did meet him, he probably wouldn't be as helpless as many of those at the beginning of the season, since half a season had already passed, after all. However, he met Wang Jiexi here, the Magician Wang Jiexi, and although he had seen him before, he hadn't studied this style closely, because everyone knew that Wang Jiexi didn't play like this anymore. But who would have expected that in this All-Star competition, this guy suddenly revived his Magician playstyle!

Although the audience had some understanding of Tang Hao's encounter, they felt overall that this explosion of something that had been hidden for a long time was extremely refreshing. In an instant, Wang Jiexi became the star of the stage, and everyone began to pay attention to his performance.

And Tang Hao?

Of course, he was clear on why he would be beaten to this miserable extent, but with his personality, how could such a reason be acceptable enough to stabilize his heart? The instant that Demon Subduer was ultimately knocked onto the ground in a pitiful state, Tang Hao's rage was at its peak. He furiously controlled Demon Subduer to leap to his feet, turned his camera view, and saw on the other end that One Autumn Leaf had been violently hit just like him. Sun Xiang had entered the Alliance in Season 7 just like Tang Hao. The two could be said to be the brightest stars of the new generation, and at the same time were two people who had never personally experienced the Magician playstyle. The end result was unsurprising. After Vaccaria plummeted from the sky and sent One Autumn Leaf flying with a Broom Tornado, those traces of stardust continued to swirl around One Autumn Leaf's body, and very quickly, One Autumn Leaf was also sent awkwardly tumbling along the ground.

Two of Team A's Gods being knocked over like this one after another of course had a large impact on the current situation. Zhou Zekai hurriedly controlled Cloud Piercer to turn his fire, the bullets flying crazily toward Vaccaria, but they only struck the residual traces left by Stardust Extermination.

Zhou Zekai, a player from Season 5. In Season 5, Tiny Herb won the championship. At that time, Wang Jiexi had already completely shed his old style, so even Zhou Zekai hadn't personally experienced it. But he was at least closer to that era and had seen and heard more, so when Vaccaria turned and rushed toward him, Cloud Piercer wasn't instantly wiped out like Demon Subduer and One Autumn Leaf had been. Wang Jiexi's storm-like sweeping of Team A was interrupted here.

However, Zhou Zekai's situation wasn't looking too good either, as he too lacked the experience to counter this style. He could only rely on his own instincts and skill to deal with Wang Jiexi, but he couldn't change the current situation.

"Damn, Old Wang, you could just carry this battle by yourself!" Ye Xiu exclaimed. It seemed like a very ordinary statement of mocking and surprise, but those who were paying attention suddenly realized: even the viewers who had the omniscient view had overlooked Wang Jiexi crushing Tang Hao due to the intensity of the match. Ye Xiu, this man, who was currently very busy on the battlefield, had actually managed to notice all of this?

The legend of the expert with eyes that could watch six directions at once, it was actually true!

"Stop talking nonsense!" Wang Jiexi replied coldly.

His saying this was of course a thousand times more powerful than anything Huang Shaotian could say. Would Team B miss seizing this opportunity before them?

Tang Hao was still trying to take revenge on Wang Jiexi, but he was cut off by Han Wenqing's Desert Dust. After Vaccaria pulled away Cloud Piercer's firepower and reduced the pressure, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was using all of his varied rapid-movement skills even as he complained about Wang Jiexi. One Autumn Leaf hadn't even managed to stand up when Lord Grim had already arrived in front of him and sent ferocious attacks toward this character who currently had the lowest health on the field. At the same time, echoing Lord Grim's attacks was the one who knew Ye Xiu best, Su Mucheng. Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain was also casting spells at this moment, covering Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng's offensive, sending continuous map-affecting spells toward that duo from Blue Rain.

"Countless changes in an instant," this was the only way the situation could be described. In the blink of an eye, many people had already exchanged opponents. The only change that hadn't changed was that Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf was suffering the fiercest attacks on the battlefield. And this time, it was no longer because he was forced to do this for the sake of charging forward, it was because he had become the primary target of Team B. In a situation without a healer, with the skill of these players and the strength of their characters, the damage output was truly ferocious. But Sun Xiang's luck was fairly good, as the two people who were currently attacking him happened to be the two characters who were relatively weaker according to the statistics.

Lord Grim was probably the only All-Star character whose weapon had yet to reach Level 75, and was also the one with the least Silver equipment.

Dancing Rain's weapon was Level 75, but the upgrades of her other equipment were lacking compared to the all of the other All-Stars who'd been upgrading continuously for a year now. Sun Xiang struggled, but he was still able to keep One Autumn Leaf alive.

"What a shame, your damage output's a little weak!" After Yu Wenzhou was finally able to contain Misty Rain, Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain broke through Windy Rain's blockade. He and his noise charged to Lord Grim's side.

"So damn noisy, I'll just leave this to you!" Ye Xiu shouted.

It was very clear to whom the first part of that statement was directed. Even people who didn't know the context could probably figure it out. But the second half? Leave it to you? Who was "you"?

The audience didn't understand, the commentator and honored guest were confused. But at this moment, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim suddenly escaped from his current situation, flying like the wind toward Yu Wenzhou's Swoksaar. Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria also drew a bizarre path in the air, one that even the Great Gunner's bullets had no way of chasing, as he flew toward the target: Swoksaar.

Aside from this, Dancing Rain's cannonfire and Windy Rain's spells were also targeting Swoksaar.

There seemed to be only one option left for Team B's "you."

Han Wenqing.

Desert Dust.

Another Ferocious Tiger Flurry.

Chapter 1266: The True Assassin

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

Fierce, fast; accurate, steady.

The first punch knocked askew Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf. The second punch forced Huang Shaotian to stop his Troubling Rain and parry instead of rescuing Swoksaar. The third punch forced Demon Subduer, chasing up from behind Desert Dust, to dodge and retreat.

Only Han Wenqing could play such a shrewd and precise Ferocious Tiger Flurry, forcing these three top Gods to instantly stop and defend, parry, dodge.

It interfered with what they had each been planning to do. Even though it was just an instant, it was enough for Team B.

Yu Wenzhou, the one with the title of "crippled hands" in this professional circle. And now, he had to face Lord Grim, the unspecialized with an incomparably rapid attack rhythm, the Magician, whose unpredictable changes were incredibly difficult to grasp, as well as the Launcher and the Elementalist, the mightiest AoE attackers…

He didn't panic, he still maintained his calm, but calm was not a panacea. Although he swiftly and clearly judged the situation on the field, this didn't necessarily mean that he had a way of solving it.

By this point, Team B's strategic planning was entirely clear. Ye Xiu was Team B's metronome. Every step he took directed Team B's attack direction and rhythm changes as a whole. And Wang Jiexi was the one who ultimately set the scene. He used his long-sealed Magician playstyle to instantly throw Team A into chaos, creating many gaps in their team coordination. At this time, Team A was full of openings to attack. If these couldn't be seized, then these people wouldn't be called the top Gods at the summit of Glory.

So at the end, the firepower transferred to Yu Wenzhou. Four attackers, two close-range, two long-range, against a Warlock, a Warlock who in terms of hand speed had absolutely no way of keeping up with anyone on the battlefield.

"You guys are too cruel…" All Yu Wenzhou could do, perhaps, was smile bitterly and raise a slight objection to these fierce players.

Han Wenqing couldn't hold off those three people forever, but just this slight delay helped his four teammates gain the opportunity to focus on one target. What kind of fury could they unleash? Adding onto the fact that Yu Wenzhou's defensive ability was a bit weak, Swoksaar's fall would only take a matter of seconds.

Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain was the first to break free of Desert Dust's interference.

Rescue!

This was his instinctive judgment and reaction to seeing Swoksaar suffering from that powerful offensive. Troubling Rain had already stepped forward, but at this moment, Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer suddenly turned fire, sending bullets toward Desert Dust.

Troubling Rain's steps suddenly stopped.

A trade!

He instantly understood Zhou Zekai's intentions. In a situation without a healer, saving Swoksaar now was already basically impossible. It would be better to focus his attacks onto Desert Dust. Whether they could besiege their opponent enough to save their own teammate, or complete the trade, both were acceptable outcomes.

Huang Shaotian immediately halted his instinctive reaction. The fact that Swoksaar was surrounded didn't cause him in the slightest to impulsively charge in. After all, he was the most brutal opportunist in Glory. From a certain standpoint, he was in reality very cold, ruthless, and tenacious, because only like someone like that could he seize the deadliest opportunities.

His sword light flashed toward Desert Dust. Team A's players instantly completed a surrounding formation toward Desert Dust. A 1v3 was impossible on this sort of beautiful stage; Han Wenqing had already performed to the best of his ability, and now, he was being counterattacked to the strongest possible degree.

But Tyranny's captain would never back down from any challenge.

One against four? So what.

Even if facing a hundred thousand enemies, he would not bend!

Desert Dust did not dodge or hide; he retaliated, he attacked.

Team B's four players didn't reveal any intent of rescuing him. This was the rhythm of completing a trade. But would this trade be successful?

A dazzling display of attacks roared forth, Swoksaar's and Desert Dust's health bars plummeted down, but which was faster? The viewers couldn't tell at first, but in an instant, the exchange was just about complete. Swoksaar's health was dropping faster!

There was nothing they could do about that.

Yu Wenzhou himself was already inferior in terms of controls, and the Warlock class had low defense and low health, as well as poor survivability against close-range attackers. This sort of situation was much more difficult for him to face. For Han Wenqing, on the other hand, the Striker class was a powerful close-range attacker, and Reinforced Iron Bones once activated could greatly increase defense. If it had to be called a little unfair, that would be the fault of Han Wenqing's stubbornness. In a situation like this, many other players would probably be a bit more flexible, more compromising.

Team B took the initiative, and their attack rhythms were faster by just that step. Team A had to be complimented for their ability to keep up so well that the speeds were difficult to distinguish. Plus, in terms of damage output, Team B had four people and had the advantage in that respect as well.

But ultimately, Swoksaar still fell first. Team A's attacks instantly became even more crazily fierce.

Fall!

The final attack landed, but a white light flashed upon Desert Dust's body. He didn't fall!

"Damn couldn't you take it a little easier do you think I'm Zhang Xinjie!!!" Ye Xiu shouted. This flash of white light had of course come from Lord Grim's instant-healing Cure skill, but like he said, he wasn't Zhang Xinjie, Lord Grim didn't have as powerful and specialized a healing ability as Immovable Rock, and he couldn't instantly bring up Desert Dust's health very far. Preventing Desert Dust from falling with that final attack was already the limit of what he could do.

The four from Team B who had taken care of Swoksaar now came to rescue. Lord Grim healed, and Vaccaria, Dancing Rain, and Windy Rain, those three powerful characters, were already firing.

Retreat for now, or force the kill?

Team A once again faced a difficult decision. Team B had surrounded them and were attacking ferociously. If they didn't retreat, this was the rhythm of everyone falling.

And so Team A chose to retreat, as after all this was a battle with no healer. Sacrificing too much health to kill a target wasn't worth it, and the remaining attacking party at low health could be swiftly defeated. Even though Team B had Lord Grim, the unspecialized's healing ability was truly just a drop in the bucket. There was no way for him to heal Desert Dust to any significant point, and under a powerful barrage of attacks, he likely couldn't even complete another life-saving heal at a critical point.

Team A's characters retreated and scattered, but these were only three characters. Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer was a Sharpshooter and had been attacking from a long-ranged position. Team B had shifted targets to save Han Wenqing from the encirclement, but their attack range couldn't catch Cloud Piercer's position. It seemed that Zhou Zekai wanted to keep attacking to deal with Han Wenqing once and for all, and that was exactly what he was doing.

And just as Cloud Piercer prepared to continue his fierce shooting, Lord Grim flashed before him.

In the end, Team B didn't let Team A squeeze through this gap. Zhou Zekai didn't have the chance to fire before he was interrupted. The rest of them immediately gave Ye Xiu a helping hand, and Cloud Piercer seemed to have become Team B's next target.

But no one, including his own teammates on Team A, expected what happened next: Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain, just after escaping from Team B, immediately turned around and charged back.

Shadow Steps!

Troubling Rain instantly split into seven images, opening the path with Triple Slash, numerous silhouettes darted forward, target: Desert Dust!

The cheers of the crowd seemed to have fallen silent…

Team B killed Swoksaar and returned to save Desert Dust. One wave of high excitement had just barely passed and they were already regrouping and preparing for the next offensive. Everyone's hearts had just barely relaxed from the nervousness when, all of a sudden, Huang Shaotian shot forward like a cold arrow.

This opportunity seized was truly… too fierce…

The silhouettes flashed, Troubling Rain's sword finally pierced through Desert Dust. That tyrannical King of Fighting, who never backed down in the face of hundreds of thousands of enemies, didn't fall under the powerful encirclement of four enemies, but fell under the cold blade of an assassin.

Huang Shaotian, Troubling Rain. Even though he wasn't of the Assassin class, he was a true assassin.

"Holy fuck!"

The viewers felt their hearts go cold, and all sorts of swears came out in the live stadium. Some were from the sheer shock of this sudden attack, some were from unhappiness at Desert Dust's fall as a result of it. This, after all, was Tyranny's home stadium, and Desert Dust was the highest God in their hearts.

But no matter what, once he fell, there was no way he would be revived. In an instant, the two teams were now equal again. It looked like the players also needed time to process all that had happened just now. Eight characters carefully moved position, facing each other, but for now none of them launched a new offensive. And so Ye Xiu, with nothing else to do, gave the four characters of Team B some Heals to let them slowly recover their health.

"Damn, are you brave enough not to use healing? Even if your stupid skills help heal they can't heal that much unless you instantly use them at a key moment, do you think that's useful at all do you do you? How much damage do you think one slash of my sword can do? It can completely ignore whatever healing you try to do did you know that? Can't you focus on attacking and not do these sort of stupid complicated cheap tricks that destroy the quality of the match and bring down the standard level of this showdown?" Huang Shaotian hollered.

In the live audience, in front of the televisions, countless people's mouths twitched.

This guy's chattiness was a huge obstacle affecting his popularity! That unexpected attack had shaken countless hearts. How many people were still engrossed in that sudden moment! The television broadcast had again split the screen for replay, and the display screens in the stadium gave the same treatment they had for Wang Jiexi's earlier performance - multi-angle replay.

But just at this moment, Huang Shaotian's own passionate voice was dubbed over, and it was all some nonsense. Everyone was thrown out of the moment okay? Everyone's moods weren't the same anymore, okay? The television broadcast will turn off your replay, okay? Can't you be cool for a bit longer, okay, okay?

No one had the strength to complain anymore. Someone like this, why did he have to have a bad habit like this? Was there truly no perfect existence in this world?

Two teams, eight people, waiting there as though they had arranged a meeting. But, in the closest player exchange area, the sixth players of the two teams had already loaded in.

Team A, Xiao Shiqin, Life Extinguisher.

Team B, Yu Feng, Blossoming Chaos.

Chapter 1267: Season 7’s Two Rookies

No matter how little an unspecialized healed, health was health. Letting Lord Grim continue healing non-stop would still recover a good amount of health. As a result, if the two sides just stared at each other, Team B would hold the advantage because they were more than willing to just wait and let Lord Grim slowly heal them. But Team A? There had to be a breaking point.

However, the first to attack was still Team B. It seemed like Team B wasn't planning on drawing support from Lord Grim's healing capabilities to gain the upper hand. They only stopped because their rhythm had taken a pause. With neither side possessing a dedicated healer, the two teams strived to deal the most damage in as short of a time as possible, so when they didn't hold back their usage of skills. They wouldn't try to maintain a constant cycle of skills like in a prolonged battle. After experiencing this intense wave of attacks, the skill cooldowns on both sides became somewhat imbalanced. What seemed to be a break was, in reality, time for their skills to come off cooldown.

At this moment, the unspecialized Lord Grim, this annoying existence, once again stood out.

In terms of DPS, Lord Grim might be the weakest among everyone. His equipment wasn't great, and his skills were all low-level skills. However, the issue of an imbalanced skill cycle didn't matter for him. The vast majority of low-level skills had short cooldowns, and he had so many of them too. He didn't need to care about waiting for skills to come off cooldown.　　

While the others were waiting for their cooldowns, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was as lively as ever. He healed Team B, while also sending a few attacks towards Team A. He was awfully busy.　　

Team A all felt annoyed, especially Sun Xiang. His One Autumn Leaf currently had the lowest amount of health on the field. Previously, if Lord Grim and Dancing Rain had a higher DPS, or if Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain hadn't rescued him in time, he might have already fallen. His team didn't have a healer either. Since his character didn't have any special equipment, the automatic health recovery could be ignored. Thus, One Autumn Leaf's health remained critically low.

As a result, Ye Xiu's harassment was mainly focused on him. Whenever Ye Xiu fired a few shots or pretended like he was going to charge in for the kill, Sun Xiang always tensed up.

It might seem like his character was still on the field, but from a certain perspective, he could be considered as dead. Anyone could see that Team B could easily end him with a single wave of attacks. If it was that obvious to even the viewers, then the competitors would obviously try to exploit it. One Autumn Leaf used to be Team A's front-line attackers, but now he had been shifted to the team's rear. Team B just had to have someone like Lord Grim, who could spam skills endlessly to harass One Autumn Leaf.

This was simply forcing Team A to hurry and act! It would obviously be advantageous for Team B to stall, no?

　

No one could understand. On the broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo were even more reserved and cautious. They didn't dare make any hasty conclusions.

　

Team A couldn't just keep bleeding. Even if One Autumn Leaf was nearly dead, he could still be used. If they let Ye Xiu's Lord Grim keep harassing him, the entire team would be dragged down trying to protect One Autumn Leaf. They might as well try and attack. In any case, Team A and Team B were in similar situations. Team B's skill cooldowns hadn't completely refreshed yet either, so it wasn't like Team B was any stronger than them right now.

Team A was just about to pick the impossibly annoying Lord Grim as their target, when Team B suddenly launched their attack.

Team B was clearly forcing Team A to hurry and act, but by the time Team A was ready to move, Team B was one step ahead of them. This this this… are they just playing around?

　

The viewers felt like this sort of playing was a bit ridiculous, but they didn't know the destruction that Team B had done to Team A's rhythm. Huang Shaotian's assassination on Desert Smoke had succeeded, leading to the two teams separating to readjust themselves. Team B received Lord Grim's better than nothing heals, but Team A? They received Lord Grim's annoying harassment. Unable to wait any longer to fully carry out their goals, Team A was forced to fight again. However, it was Team B who took the initiative and attacked first.

　

Even though this brief fight wasn't as intense as before, it was still filled with countless details. At first glance, these details couldn't be seen, but soon the effects surged forth onto the field.

Sun Xiang couldn't play as boldly as before, so One Autumn Leaf's original role in Team A was lost. In the end, Sun Xiang's role fell to Tang Hao, the rookie in the same generation, a God whose sudden rise sharply differed from Sun Xiang's slow ascent.　

When Sun Xiang joined the Alliance, he was a talented rookie who had received much attention. He had obtained numerous opportunities in Team Conquering Clouds, allowing his talent to shine. Afterwards, he joined the powerhouse Team Excellent Era and directly inherited the Battle God One Autumn Leaf after Ye Xiu's retirement. As if loved by the heavens, he didn't even hit a Rookie's Block. Everything seemed to be smooth sailing for him. But then, Team Excellent Era encountered a shocking setback and was relegated, the greatest miracle in all of Glory history. It was even more miraculous than Happy beating them in the Challenger League.

Sun Xiang had started high but left low. Fortunately, he wasn't dispirited by the setback. Excellent Era disbanded and Samsara, the champions, threw him an olive branch. From this point, Sun Xiang was also a very lucky person. When Sun Xiang came to Samsara, he seemed to have matured a lot after his setback at Excellent Era. The Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang duo became the most terrifying offensive force in the Alliance.

As for Tang Hao? His journey was the opposite of Sun Xiang's.

His first season in the Alliance was no different from ordinary rookies. He experienced all of the bitterness and hardship felt by rookies, surviving his first rookie year. Then, their captain Zhang Jiale unexpectedly retired, and the team suddenly turned into a fly without a head. All of a sudden, the other rookie of the same generation, Zou Yuan, was pushed onto the stage and directly inherited the number one character, Hundred Blossom's core, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Zou Yuan's fate was worthy of being envied, but no one would have thought that the one to stand out from Hundred Blossoms wasn't Zou Yuan, but Tang Hao.

Th junior succeeds the senior!

This was the declaration that Tang Hao had made in that year's All-Star Weekend. It was also the true feelings in his heart. He didn't have the same luck or opportunities as Sun Xiang or Zou Yuan. Everything he obtained came from his own hard work, fist by fist.

For the junior to succeed the senior, the number one Brawler, Lin Jingyan, wasn't the only one he had to surpass. That season, Team Hundred Blossoms still had their core character, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, but who was their true core? It was Tang Hao and his Brawler Delilo, a character who had just been a substitute character in the team.

Tang Hao was proud because everything he had accomplished was worthy of being proud of. No one had doted on him, and the team hadn't provided him any resources or support, yet despite these circumstances, Tang Hao pushed his way from an unremarkable rookie to the team's core on his own. And today, he was the leader of Team Wind Howl, the number 8 most popular All-Star.

Was Tang Hao satisfied?

Of course not?

He wanted to become the MVP in the Alliance. He wanted the championship cup that everyone yearned for. Everyone standing on this stage were all potential obstacles to this goal. All of them were targets to succeed.

But just a moment ago, he had unexpectedly been crushed by Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria in an instant.

He had truly been unable to defend against Vaccaria's attacks. The so-called Magician was actually this freakish? Just a while back, from the data he had looked at, Tang Hao felt that it was a pity Wang Jiexi no longer played with this style. When Wind Howl fought against Tiny Herb, he had even provoked Wang Jiexi when they met in the group arena.

Wang Jiexi obviously ignored him. Tang Hao gradually pushed this playstyle of the past to the back of his mind. Who would have thought that in this widely-watched All-Stars stage, Wang Jiexi would suddenly use it and with a sharpened blade too. Or to be more precise, it wasn't a blade but a broom… a broom didn't sound as scary as a blade though.

Shock, humiliation,a shred of fear, and… excitement caused him to tremble.

The junior succeeds the senior!　

Tang Hao's gaze locked onto Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria. He was ready to payback the humiliation he received many folds. Magician? He had been caught off guard last time, but this time, he could definitely do it.　

Come!

Tang Hao was waiting impatiently for Team B to attack. The only person in his line of sight was Vaccaria.　

Vaccaria sat on his broom. Vaccaria floated in the air. Vaccaria flew at an extremely low altitude. Vaccaria was coming!　

What? He's not coming at me?

"Where do you think you're going!" Tang Hao shouted and immediately had Demon Subduer move forward to intercept him.　　

"And where do you think you're going?" A voice rung in his ears like a clap of thunder.

That sound is too close. An enemy?

Of course it was an enemy.

Lord Grim suddenly charged towards Demon Subduer, but he was actually ignored. Demon Subduer continued to move in a different direction.

"Young people these days are too arrogant!" Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim attacked madly.

Shit!

Tang Hao messed up again. His mind had been completely preoccupied with Vaccaria and that strange Magician playstyle. He had tunneled so hard on Vaccaria that he hadn't even noticed Lord Grim calling out to him.

By the time he regained his senses, he was already up in the air. Lord Grim's skills battered him endlessly. He… was crushed again.

　　

Tang Hao collapsed at the first blow. The players on both teams were all astonished, but since an opportunity had appeared in front of them, Team B wasn't going to let it pass.

　　

Team A's offense had been led by Tang Hao, but Tang Hao was instantly blown away. The implications were too obvious.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

But at this moment, One Autumn Leaf, with his critically low health, charged forward bravely towards Lord Grim.　

　

He wasn't of much use anymore. He couldn't fight too fiercely. Perhaps waiting for an one-shot opening like Huang Shaotian had done wasn't a bad choice. But right now, Tang Hao was being beaten up. Huang Shaotian and Zhou Zekai were being suppressed. The two had no choice but to go out and rescue Tang Hao like tinkermen, but before they could act, Sun Xiang made up his mind and acted first.

He couldn't do much right now. If he could sacrifice himself to save Tang Hao, that would be a worthy trade.

Chapter 1268: This Isn’t What You’re Good At

One Autumn Leaf, the character personally raised by Ye Xiu and brought into the Alliance, the character that became Excellent Era's foundation and earned the title of "Battle God"... This character suddenly and viciously cut into Ye Xiu's field of view.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks, what a familiar skill, how long has it been since I've last used it?

For the briefest of moments, Ye Xiu couldn't avoid feeling a pang of melancholy, but it was only for a moment. Right afterwards, Lord Grim dodged Dragon Breaks the Ranks, and didn't hesitate at all before attacking the character he was the most familiar with. How many times had he encountered One Autumn Leaf as an enemy after leaving Excellent Era? Ye Xiu couldn't be bothered to keep track anymore.

When Sun Xiang controlled One Autumn Leaf to charge at Lord Grim, he had hardened his heart to die while doing so. He believed that in order to swiftly deal with him, his opponent would definitely let go of Tang Hao's Demon Subduer, if only for a moment.

When Lord Grim's attacks arrived, he did his best to parry the strikes, hoping to use the opportunity to create more space. But after this valiant effort, what he met was not just the assault of Lord Grim, but instead the attacks of anyone who was in range from Team B, none of whom missed this opportunity. Dancing Rain, Windy Rain, and Vaccaria all attacked him.

Was it worth it?

Sun Xiang thought to himself, One Autumn Leaf only had so much health left. A few casual attacks would be able to finish him off, was there a need for such exaggerated fanfare? Especially Wang Jiexi, who had turned around and changed his movement just to charge at him, were they trying to KS each other or something?

Dancing Rain and Windy Rain's attacks were both long-ranged, and Sun Xiang had no way of retaliating against the two. But Vaccaria had surprisingly charged towards him, so Sun Xiang had One Autumn Leaf welcome him instead.

But Vaccaria's body suddenly dipped down and changed directions, flying towards One Autumn Leaf at a low altitude. This situation!

Sun Xiang hurriedly changed his camera angle, and saw that Vaccaria, who had just brushed past him, was actually charging towards Demon Subduer.

This guy switched targets… way too fast, right?

As he stared agape, One Autumn Leaf had already received a fatal blow, becoming the third character to fall in this team competition.

As a result, in terms of numbers, Team A was finally at a clear disadvantage. With the situation being a 3v4, and none of Team B's 4 characters being in great danger of dying, the advantage in numbers became very obvious.

To make matters worse, Sun Xiang letting One Autumn Leaf make a valiant last stand was in order to give Tang Hao an opportunity to seize the initiative, but it seemed as if the results were very debatable.

Tang Hao had really been beaten dizzy.

After facing Wang Jiexi's fierce barrage of attacks, all he could think of was the Magician's playstyle. Right afterwards, Ye Xiu's unspecialized, Lord Grim had charged up and focused another flurry of attacks on him. In order to save him, Sun Xiang sacrificed the life of One Autumn Leaf, resetting the battlefield, but as soon as that happened, the unspecialized Lord Grim was swapped out for the Magician again.

With these two opponents irregularly swapping in and out in front of him, Tang Hao felt a head-splitting migraine coming on.

Was this a 1v1?

No, in Tang Hao's eyes, this already felt like a 1v2, for the two opponents would change in the blink of an eye. At one moment, it was the unspecialized, at another moment, it was the Magician. One of them was so fast that it was dazzling, while the other had unimaginable variations in his playstyle.

Who are these people?

Tang Hao, the junior who had succeeded the senior, suddenly felt completely perplexed.

Once again, faced against Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria, Tang Hao played very poorly. Originally, he had been psychologically prepared to go up against the Magician once more, but this preparation had been shattered beforehand by Ye Xiu's Lord Grim.

"This fellow is already a mess," Huang Shaotian said to Zhou Zekai.

"Yeah..." Zhou Zekai indicated his agreement.

Tang Hao may have been somewhat helpless against Wang Jiexi's Magician playstyle, but after being beaten by it once, he shouldn't have been beaten so soundly the second time. If the Magician playstyle was so tyrannical that it could oppress God-level players, would Wang Jiexi still need to change his playstyle? He could just single-handedly slaughter his way to a championship title. Evidently, by relying on these bursts of attacks, Ye Xiu and Wang Jiexi both explosively fought Tang Hao one after the other, and eventually shattered his fighting spirit.

"Should we still save him?" Huang Shaotian asked.

"..." His question only earned Zhou Zekai's silence.

Huang Shaotian suddenly had a headache. What could he do? At the end of the day, the guy next to him just had to be this taciturn person. In terms of communication through words, it seemed as if they could only go this far!

"Let's go take down Ye Xiu!" Huang Shaotian shouted, as Troubling Rain's sword swept towards Lord Grim. He was already too lazy to waste time on Tang Hao's predicament, that would just be too passive. Their team was already at a clear disadvantage, and if they were to be lead by the nose by Team A the whole time, they would just be whittled down one-by-one till the end. At this time, they could only respond by taking daring risks and erupting with full force against the enemy.

Troubling Rain's sword was flourished, but even faster was Cloud Piercer's bullets. It seemed as if by the time his sword flashed, the sound of Cloud Piercer's bullet had also rung out.

The character that the bullet flew towards was indeed Lord Grim.

"Good kid, you thought the exact same thing as me! Let's kill him!" Huang Shaotian shouted.

"..." Unfortunately, Zhou Zekai had never wanted to have any verbal communication with his team, but the coordination of his skills was always outstanding. Troubling Rain effortlessly dashed over to Lord Grim's side. Su Mucheng and Chu Yunxiu attempted to intercept him, but Zhou Zekai had Cloud Piercer's bullets arrive at the most appropriate place at the most appropriate time, causing their attacks to have no effect on Huang Shaotian.

"..."

"I really couldn't tell that you were such an expert in providing covering fire as well!" Huang Shaotian loudly praised before shouting, "Old Ye, watch my sword!"

Sword light flashed downwards, carrying a cold killing intent.

His relationship with Ye Xiu was quite good, but that was only off-stage, what about during matches? He would definitely try to kill Ye Xiu as fast as possible, with no other emotions involved. He was already irritated by Ye Xiu showing off in the individual competition, but it was uncertain whether he could take revenge by winning this team competition. The situation on Tang Hao's side was already hopeless, and Zhou Zekai… he had already successfully covered Huang Shaotian from the attacks of three characters, showing off his abilities to the maximum, could anything more be expected of him? He only hoped that the kid would be able to completely follow the tempo of his attacks next!

In the midst of a rain of bullets, a sword light shone through!

Zhou Zekai coordinated with Huang Shaotian, focusing their attacks on Lord Grim. Wang Jiexi was dealing with Tang Hao, and even though Tang Hao's condition wasn't good, in a 1v1, it was unlikely that he'd be beaten down in a matter of seconds or minutes. Even as he cut a sorry figure, Tang Hao still retained a last trace of clear-headedness, helping him continue to fight back.

Aside from them, there was Su Mucheng and Chu Yunxiu left. The two of them were long-ranged attackers, and when cooperating with Ye Xiu, it was a 3v2 scenario. Originally, the two of them had assisted Ye Xiu in counterattacking Troubling Rain, but now, Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer had severely restricted them. The majority of the attacks were aimed at Lord Grim, but once in a while, some attacks would be directed towards the two of them, causing a great amount of trouble for them each time. If it wasn't interrupting their attacks, it was disturbing their coordination. Between the two of them, Chu Yunxiu had a harder time. Most of her spells had a cast time, and under Cloud Piercer's unpredictable harassment, there was surprisingly not a single big spell that could be casted, causing her to be helplessly suppressed.

"This guy is truly terrifying..." Chu Yunxiu said to Su Mucheng.

"Yeah..." Su Mucheng had no way of disagreeing. Zhou Zekai's mechanical skills had already surpassed that of most other players.

"Not bad not bad, very well done hahaha, this is the tempo of victory!" Huang Shaotian shouted as he hacked away with his sword.

If this continued, victory or defeat would be hard to determine. If these two could be as fast as Wang Jiexi, first getting rid of Lord Grim, then turning their fire towards Vaccaria, what would the situation be like? Everyone was currently considering this possibility.

"The tempo of victory?" At this moment, Ye Xiu laughed and said, "How come I can't see it at all?"

The Myraid Manifestations Umbrella shook and a Sky Strike flew out!

Huang Shaotian didn't back down, and Troubling Rain simply used a Falling Phoenix Slash to knock down the Sky Strike.

Lord Grim's body conveniently crouched down, and when Falling Phoenix Strike's power had been expended, he straightened up and sent out a Knee Attack.

Troubling Rain had already taken a step back, and his sword flashed as he executed Headwind Strike.

Under Huang Shaotian's control, this Headwind Strike's sword arc had extended half a body unit, creating a dense cluster of sword energy.

At this moment, Zhou Zekai suddenly made a sound. "Ah!"

"What did you say "ah" for?" Huang Shaotian was very excited, surprisingly, this person actually still knew how to speak.

"Uh..." Zhou Zekai hesitated and couldn't say what he wanted to, but the Myraid Manifestations Umbrella in Lord Grim's hand had already opened up, completely blocking all the sword arcs from Headwind Strike. Once the attack was blocked, the umbrella was folded back, but it didn't fold inwards. Instead, it folded outwards, directly turning into a spear before striking out.

Hit!

The distance between them was too narrow, and this Dragon Tooth was just too fast, leaving Huang Shaotian with no opportunity to dodge.

Dragon Tooth had a stun effect, so after being hit by Dragon Tooth, the next few combo hits would be unavoidable. Zhou Zekai frantically intensified his attacks to suppress Lord Grim, but at this moment, Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain had finished the cast for a high-level spell, and together with Dancing Rain's attacks, they blotted out the sky as they attacked Troubling Rain.

Zhou Zekai managed to stop Lord Grim's attack, but he had absolutely no way of controlling the other two on the field. He wasn't Nezha, the god with three heads and six arms.

Huang Shaotian immediately figured out that when Zhou Zekai said "ah", it was possible that he had already noticed a problem, and the problem was, in all likelihood, Huang Shaotian's problem, but... he was completely unaware of the situation.

"Grasping the tempo of attacks is still something that I do best, Huang Shao!" A voice filled with laughter travelled over as a violent sword light slammed down. Within the swordsman classes, only the Berserker could possess such a reckless momentum.

Hundred Blossom's Yu Feng, Berserker Blooming Chaos, entered the field.

On the other side, the click clack sounds of machinery rang out. Xiao Shiqin's Mechanic, Life Extinguisher had also finally reached the battlefield.

At the same time, Huang Shaotian finally realized the subtle meaning in Yu Feng's words, because back in Blue Rain, the person who was the arrowhead of the formation and who lead the team's tempo was Yu Feng. And Huang Shaotian, the true core of Blue Rain, instead drifted away from the formation, waiting to seize an opportunity.

To put it another way, Huang Shaotian's speciality was seizing opportunities and coordinating with others, and not having other people follow his attacking tempo. In this way, he was very different from most other core players.

So just now, it was clear that there was a slight error in his judgement. When he attacked, it could be that his timing was slightly off, or his positioning was slightly off, but in short, it interfered with Zhou Zekai, messing up their perfect attacking tempo. As a result, Huang Shaotian was immediately counterattacked by Ye Xiu, and shortly after, Zhou Zekai's suppression over the two ranged players had been broken.

"This... really something that I'm not good at. It's a shame that you're also my opponent now." Huang Shaotian said to Yu Feng.

Chapter 1269: Personal Grudge

"Haha, and you have the face to celebrate about your tempo!" That was when Ye Xiu cut in.

Huang Shaotian was enraged, immediately remembering how when he had cheered "this is the tempo of victory", that guy had spoken up with a seemly random "can't tell". It was clear that Ye Xiu understood Huang Shaotian's playstyle and predicted that his and Zhou Zekai's partnership would eventually go wrong, so he didn't rush things. In the end, Huang Shaotian had messed up the tempo practically the moment after he yelled about the tempo of victory. Even Zhou Zekai had voiced a "huh?" in response to him. It was obvious how much his judgement had failed him.

What tempo of victory? This was the tempo of slapping himself in the face!

"Everyone stop moving! It's time to settle a personal grudge, 1v1 me!!!" Huang Shaotian suddenly roared.

Everyone was stunned. The characters turned their view, like they were looking around at each other.

Then, Dancing Rain unhitched her cannon from her shoulder, Windy Rain lowered his raised staff, and Cloud Piercer sheathed his revolves back in the holsters inside his trench coat. Yu Feng, who had finally arrived, looked around for a while before stabbing his sword into the ground. Even the others in Team B had stopped. He was Huang Shaotian's old teammate too, so he had to give him face.

This time, it was the audience that had their eyes wide in shock.

What the hell was this?

This was the team competition! But everyone really did stop and let these two duel each other. This, this… they were so… not serious! This All-Stars competition was the most unorthodox ever; a Cleric had gone to the group arena, now they were having a one on one duel in the team competition… What… What kind of team competition was this?

But… it really was interesting!

Silence enveloped the stadium for a moment before excitement erupted through the crowd. This All-Stars Competition was really something. So what if it wasn't strict and serious? There were ten of those each week, and sometimes, people just wanted to see such an unorthodox match!

All the characters had stopped over here. As for the other side, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher had just arrived and originally wanted to go and help Tang Hao. After looking at what was happening here, he wasn't sure what to do anymore.

"What about them? Are we going to let them duel one on one as well?" Xiao Shiqin asked. Wang Jiexi and Tang Hao were still entangled in a fierce battle!

No one paid him any attention. The other characters over here had formed a circle around Lord Grim and Troubling Rain, turning into spectators.

Xiao Shiqin looked around in shock before his Life Extinguisher eventually ran over to stand in the circle with his Mechanical Box.

"You sure this is what you want? After you die, your team will be down two people," Ye Xiu warned the other.

"Bah! You're the one that's gonna die," Huang Shaotian replied.

"What? With the tempo that you're going at?" Ye Xiu struck.

"Fuck off, fuck off, fuck off!" It hit Huang Shaotian's weak point.

"Fine!" Ye Xiu had Lord Grim take a step forwards.

Huang Shaotian took a deep breath, sending a kill emoji as Troubling Rain hiked up Ice Rain, preparing to turn and charge forwards

"Wait!" Ye Xiu suddenly yelled.

"What?!" Huang Shaotian raged. He had just hyped himself up just now.

"Referee, can you hear me, referee?" Ye Xiu called out.

After a moment of silence, a system message popped up in the global channel. "What?"

The audience burst into laughter. This was a system message! They couldn't believe that the referee would send a system message filled with such emotion. How interesting.

"Can I request that the voice function be turned off temporarily?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Go die!" Huang Shaotian yelled, He didn't show any more mercy. Troubling Rain whipped forth sword-light, starting with a Sword Draw.

Ye Xiu didn't back down, using a Slide Kick to slide under the sword-light before launching an offensive.

However, Troubling Rain had already jumped up with a Falling Light Blade, stabbing down towards the sliding Lord Grim.

Lord Grim was reclined, yet the Myriad Manifestations had already changed to spear form, stabbing up at Troubling Rain with Dragon Tooth. Spears were longer than swords. No matter how you looked at it, it was Troubling Rain who would be hit first.

However, Huang Shaotian was truly worthy of being called a top expert. Faced with this situation, he sent his sword straight at the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, the two attacks becoming a parry.

Clang!

The two Silver weapons clashed and Troubling Rain landed behind from there, sword-light flickering once more with an Immortal Guides the Way.

This skill was a knockback attack, but Lord Grim was lying flat on the ground. He obviously couldn't be knocked into the ground, so under these circumstances, knockbacks would cause a small stun. Ye Xiu knew this and Lord Grim rolled to the side. Immortals Guide the Way's sword-light slashed down, sending chunks of earth flying. Lord Grim rolled to a stand, a grenade already thrown. Troubling Rain raised his returning sword-light and with a boom, the grenade exploded into light and fire between them.

Everyone watched them anxiously, not wanting to miss even a moment. Neither of them had much health left. Just once chance would be enough for either of them to claim victory. A pro player's offensive didn't just end with one attack. When one skill hit, there would be many more follow-ups to maximize damage. Currently, the two played extremely cautiously, knowing that a single hit could mean the end.

The smoke from the grenade hadn't even dispersed when Lord Grim snatched the initiative to attack. Shadow Cloak streaked out of the smoke like a ghost, but Huang Shaotian was well acquainted with Ye Xiu's antics. Naturally, he would move to counter it. The instant the Grenade exploded, he was already jumping back to make Troubling Rain dodge.

　

The Shadow Cloak hit thin air and Huang Shaotian couldn't help but feel triumphant for a moment. He was about to speak, when the earth beneath his feet loosened.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Lord Grim suddenly leaped out from the earth, causing many to cry out in surprise.

Huang Shaotian's amazing reaction speed was clearly reflected by this event. This strike was not at all within his expectations. But through his fast reaction speed and immense hand speed, Troubling Rain still managed a backwards jump to dodge, and even send out a slash with his sword as well. Unfortunately, activating a skill in such a short time was impossible, so this was only a normal attack. Lord Grim jumped up with the Underground Tunneling Technique, knocking the slash aside. His other hand swung up, sending a strike at Troubling Rain's face.

Sand Toss!

The blind this skill dealt was very annoying. Huang Shaotian hurriedly turned his character's head part way, but he knew that the other would try to grasp this chance while he was looking away. His sword was already slashing down, activating Triple Slash and sending his character into motion.

The Sand Toss didn't manage to blind Troubling Rain, and Triple Slash didn't move him too far. Huang Shaotian's Triple Slash was a two step movement in a small area. Under the flickering of the sword-light, Troubling Rain used it to arrive behind Lord Grim with the first two slashes and then sent out the final slash.

　

Lord Grim didn't bother to turn. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella already on his shoulder. With a whoosh, the umbrella was opened and the slash landed on the shield.

However, shields wouldn't completely block the damage. With the slash colliding with the shield, Huang Shaotian felt that he had gotten a small advantage.

Was he going to go on the offensive?

That was the thought that suddenly surfaced in Huang Shaotian's mind. Lord Grim didn't have as much health as him. After all, he had been subject to Zhou Zekai and Huang Shaotian's combined offensive before, almost entirely relying on his shield to reduce damage. If he had been fiercer and had managed to bring his DPS high enough, then he and Zhou Zekai might have been able to kill him.

Just as the thought flashed by, still in the ending lag of Triple Slash, Lord Grim jumped back without even putting the umbrella away.

"You're such a crafty bastard!" Huang Shaotian cursed. With that jump, the umbrella shield was practically on top of him. Troubling Rain didn't have any space to move anymore! He had to be careful of the unspecialized quick offensive after the umbrella was closed.

Wait, something's wrong!

　

How come...

Huang Shaotian suddenly realized, shocked, that his Troubling Rain… was Dizzy!

　

What the bloody hell? Huang Shaotian abrupted came to a conclusion.

"Shield Attack, huh…" Someone in the circle of spectators said. Everyone turned to look; it was Vaccaria.

"How come you've come over?" As Xiao Shiqin asked his, he turned Life Extinguisher's view.

"I'm done with the battle," Wang Jiexi replied.

As expected, over there, Tang Hao's Demon Subduer had vanished, clearly having been killed.

As for the duel over here? The outcome was set. Huang Shaotian had only trashtalk left, his words filled with rage and dissatisfaction.

Jumping backwards with an umbrella hitched on his shoulder, was he trying to take up Troubling Rain's room to attack? Of course it wasn't that nice. This was a fucking Shield Attack, a Knight's Shield Attack that would apply a Dizzy effect!

Huang Shaotian hadn't realized at first because, one, Shield Attack wasn't a low level skill, and two, with that thing open, he had thought of it as an umbrella. He knew it had the effects of a shield, but he hadn't taken it as a proper shield. In addition, it was a backwards jump after settling the umbrella on his shoulder. Who could have expected Shield Attack to be hidden in there?

After making Troubling Rain dizzy, Lord Grim steadily poised himself to strike before giving Troubling Rain a beating. Without much health left, Troubling Rain finally fell amidst Huang Shaotian's cursing.

Now, Team A only had two people left, Zhou Zekai and Xiao Shiqin, who had only arrived and done nothing but spectated.

As for Team B? They weren't that healthy, but all five were still alive. There was little suspense to the results of the match now. After Wang Jiexi had dealt with Tang Hao, Wang Jiexi had chosen a position to spectate that Xiao Shiqin understood immediately. Wang Jiexi was in a position where he could immediately coordinate with Ye Xiu and form a pincer attack on his Mechanic.

"So, that's it then?" Xiao Shiqin looked around, saying.

"What on earth did we even come here for?" Yu Feng asked Xiao Shiqin. They had arrived, then watched the two duel and then… there wasn't any more to it.

"What about you two duel too?" The others suggested teasingly.

"Nah!" Xiao Shiqin clearly had little interest.

"Yeah, let's not." Yu Feng didn't seem willing either.

"Then let's finish this!" Wang Jiexi said as Vaccaria swung his broom towards Life Extinguisher. Xiao Shiqin responded instinctively, immediately dodging and counterattacking. Then it was a two on five and after a short battle, Team B won without pressure.

Both the audience at the venue and those watching the broadcast were still thinking back to the All-Stars Competition after it ended. The final two on five wasn't interesting, but before that, there was so much to see.

The TV broadcast team was left in a rather awkward position though. In the end, the Team Competition, the climax of the All-Stars Competition, had lasted not even five minutes.

"Only five minutes?" The audience, who only noticed this afterhand, were amazed. These five minutes had really been filled with too much content!

Chapter 1270: The Most Experienced Player

This concluded the official events of the All-Star Weekend. Although the audience felt that it was very fulfilling, when they checked the time, they suddenly felt like they hadn't gotten enough. Wasn't it kind of a shame that the high point of the three day event ended that quickly?

But the winners had already been determined, and the players of Teams A and B had already walked out of the player booths. They didn't go offstage, but mingled amongst each other. For this sort of performative match, most people didn't care too much about victory. Otherwise, how would there be that scenario of everyone crowding around to watch two people 1v1 each other.

But only most people didn't care. There were always people who did care, very much.

Tang Hao…

When he came out of the player booth, his face was pale. In the Rookie Challenge of Season 8 All-Star Weekend, Tang Hao defeated Lin Jingyan. This battle could be considered the battle that established him as a God, cementing his position as a top player. But in this All-Star Weekend, in the team competition, he had been beaten down so pathetically.

The images of the battle flashed through his mind. In front of him, the God-level players of all the other teams were all relaxed and chatting with each other, but Tang Hao just couldn't relax.

It wasn't that he couldn't accept a loss. But how come his loss was so ugly, so pathetic? The cheers of the crowd seemed like mocking laughter to Tang Hao.

The players didn't immediately come offstage, but a reporter from the esports channels carried his camera and flew toward the stage. This team competition ended too quickly, far out of their expectations, entirely disrupting their planned program schedule. They'd purposely left an extra large block of time empty for the All-Star event, since they didn't want time restrictions to disrupt the broadcast of this once-a-year special event. But in the end, the team competition was over in five minutes. Fortunately in the last battle of the group arena, Zhang Xinjie with that Cleric PK had used up a good deal of time, otherwise this All-Star Competition would have ended even earlier.

Sending a reporter onstage now was so that they could do some live interviews, use up a bit more of the broadcast time.

These interviews hadn't been planned in advance, but these God-level players were used to being chased by reporters for interviews. Today's competition hadn't posed much of a burden, anyway, so most of them weren't in any low spirits. The reporter that rushed onstage immediately saw Zhang Xinjie and Wu Yuce discussing something together, and he headed toward them first.

"Hello, vice-captains!" the reporter greeted.

These two paused in their conversation and looked at him.

"Are you discussing that group arena battle from just earlier?" the reporter asked.

"Yes," Zhang Xinjie nodded.

"What do you two think?"

"If it hadn't been stopped, I should have had a slight health advantage at the end and I should have won," said Zhang Xinjie.

"That's only in your planned, ideal conditions," Wu Yuce immediately retorted. It looked like the two of them had been discussing the question of who would have won that battle.

"The plans would have become reality," Zhang Xinjie said.

"You never know what will happen in a battle," said Wu Yuce.

"I'd try my hardest to minimize the unexpected," said Zhang Xinjie.

"Hard to say." Wu Yuce shook his head.

"Perhaps we should give it another try," Zhang Xinjie said.

"Forget it… I'm not too interested in that kind of battle," Wu Yuce said. He'd already avoided having to play out such a dull battle, of course he didn't want to repeat it. After all, it would never happen again.

Zhang Xinjie didn't press either. He only shook his head in regret, seeming quite unsatisfied with his inability to verify the result.

To the side, the reporter didn't interject. He simply recorded all of this to the camera as is. Let everyone experience the unaltered interactions of the Gods after a match. Seeing that these two didn't have any more to say, the reporter began to search for a new target. Those who had had strong performances in the match would of course attract him more easily.

Wang Jiexi!

The reporter's eyes brightened. Wang Jiexi seemed to be giving a lesson to Tiny Herb player Gao Yingjie, and the reporter immediately rushed forward.

"Use your best, most comfortable, most familiar method to perform, that's enough," said Wang Jiexi.

"But Captain, what you've been using all this time, is that your best, most comfortable, most familiar method?" Gao Yingjie suddenly asked.

Wang Jiexi was silent for a while, and then he shook his head. "That is why I hope that you can. Have more confidence, don't be easily shaken. You're more suited to this team than I am. Believe in yourself!"

Seeing Gao Yingjie nod, the reporter took this chance to interject.

"Hello, both of you," he greeted.

"Captain Wang's performance in this team battle really gave us quite a shock! We never would have expected you to suddenly revive your old style. Are you planning to go back to your style again?" the reporter asked.

"Of course not," Wang Jiexi smiled, and then looked at the stage and player booths behind him. "It's good enough to be able to relax here."

"Maybe if Tiny Herb had the Magician, they could earn even better results?" the reporter said.

Wang Jiexi continued to smile, but he didn't say anything. The reporter knew that he was rejecting this view, he just didn't say so out loud. The Magician Wang Jiexi hadn't won anything for Tiny Herb, but after he changed, Tiny Herb had obtained two championships. The person in front of him knew a hundred times better than him what style suited Tiny Herb better, and his own opinion was just himself trying to be smart. As he thought about this, the reporter looked at Gao Yingjie, and asked, "Then what about Little Gao? Will we have a chance to see him become a magician?" This time, the reporter was asking with a joking tone.

"Maybe! If it's on this stage." Gao Yingjie was now better at dealing with the media, and he answered the question quite well. He hadn't rejected the possibility entirely, but he said "on this stage." Yes, on the All-Star stage, what wasn't possible?

After obtaining another conversation, the reporter turned his head, saw Ye Xiu not too far away, and quickly rushed up to him. This God's performance was also very strong, and he rarely accepted interviews. Even though he didn't reject them completely after his return, he was still very low-key. Whatever he could avoid, he would try to avoid, and it was no easy feat to obtain a live interview.

"God Ye Xiu!" The reporter saw that Ye Xiu wasn't talking to anyone right now, and charged forward.

"Hm?" Ye Xiu looked at the reporter.

"The team competition was incredibly exciting. Was it your plan to leave the Cleric out of the team competition?" the reporter asked. This is what they had guessed offstage, because earlier they'd seen that argument at Team B, with Ye Xiu apparently at the center. They didn't know that was Team B trying to pick the most energy-saving arrangement, but looking at the final line-up, they thought that it was possibly Ye Xiu's idea to put the Cleric in the group arena, causing everyone to oppose him.

"Of course not!" But Ye Xiu answered with this. "I just gave a random suggestion."

"Hahaha…" The reporter laughed dryly. When Ye Xiu said "of course not," he had actually thought there were some other hidden factors at play, but in the end, it really was just this.

"Why would you propose such a suggestion?" the reporter then asked.

"Obviously so we could have a more exciting and aggressive battle!" Ye Xiu said, very seriously.

Instantly, the nearby Team B players who heard this all looked at him.

This guy, he could really talk! When they'd made this plan, everyone liked this arrangement only because it would allow the match to finish faster!

"Haha, the battle really was very exciting. There were a lot of highlights!" the reporter said.

"Well, of course. After all, everyone here is an outstanding player," Ye Xiu said.

"And you? How would you evaluate yourself?"

"Me? I'm probably the most experienced player here in this circle, right?" Ye Xiu said.

The interview was broadcast on television, but it was also shown on the display screens in the stadium. Tyranny fans obviously had no kind feelings toward Ye Xiu, but they did have to have a reason to boo him. They couldn't find any points to complain about with his earlier, very standard answers to the reporter's questions. But with these words, Tyranny's fans were instantly upset.

You're the most experienced player? At least add a "one of the" okay! Over there is our Captain Han! A player from the first generation just like you! No, technically, he's even more experienced than you! You still have a year and half gap in the middle!

The stadium came alive with boos, which prompted the reporter. Looking at the players around him, quite a few people were looking this way after hearing this answer. The reporter immediately asked, "Then what about Tyranny's Captain Han Wenqing?"

"Old Han? He can't compete with me!" Ye Xiu said, brimming with confidence.

The booing increased. Even the gathered Gods had "you jerk can't you stop bragging" expressions as they continued to watch.

"Why is that? You're both players from the first generation, and Captain Han Wenqing…"

"Has he played in the Challenger League?" Ye Xiu directly interrupted the reporter with his explanation.

Silence.

Played in the Challenger League? Fuck, you're counting that a experience? Everyone was shocked, but if they were really talking from this standpoint, then indeed, Han Wenqing's experience was slightly inferior. But everyone was glad not to have that sort of experience. Playing in the Challenger League, that absolutely wasn't a joyful experience for a top-tier God, but this guy actually made treasure out of this trash, counting this as part of his accumulated experience. Is there anyone else like you shamelessly increasing their own level like this?

BOOOO!

This time, it wasn't just the Tyranny fans. The rest of the audience, even some of the players offstage, the Gods onstage, they were all booing Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu smiled bitterly, waving his hand as he said to the reporter, "They're just jealous."

Jealous your ass! The reporter felt unwell, and even the cameraman had shaken unstably. The reporter chuckled awkwardly. He felt like his head had crashed, and he couldn't think of what direction to go next with the interview.

Fortunately, from the shock Ye Xiu had provoked, he'd picked out a target.

Han Wenqing, the captain of Team Tyranny Han Wenqing, the boss of this area, the one who "lost to" Ye Xiu in experience because he hadn't played in the Challenger League.

"Captain Han, regarding Ye Xiu's words just now… Do you object?" the reporter asked, rather directly. After all, the two of them had been death enemies for ten years.

"His accomplishments in the Challenger League are indeed worthy of pride," said Han Wenqing.

Chapter 1271: All-Star Armory

Han Wenqing's answer surprised the reporters somewhat. These bitter enemies of ten years had never yielded to each other on stage, but their relationship off-stage wasn't quite what the reporters had imagined it to be.

The mutual respect between heroes? The reporters weren't too interested in such a dry topic, but when Han Wenqing said that Ye Xiu's results in the Challenger League were worthy of pride, thinking about it a little, he was right. Leading a team full of players who had been scraped together from god-knows-where at the last minute, he had defeated Excellent Era and emerged victorious from the Challenger League. Why wouldn't such miraculous results be something to be proud of?

In that case, to say it was a fruitful experience was in fact completely correct?

The reporters thought about it and suddenly realized that Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing seemed to resonate on some kind of level, could it be because they were both practical and realistic people?

Practical and realistic?

When this phrase popped up in their minds, the reporters all shuddered. Calling Han Wenqing practical and realistic was fine, but Ye Xiu? The reporters refused to entertain this notion any further, they were completely unwilling to accept such an idea.

The All Star Weekend was hosted at Tyranny's stadium, but in the All-Star Competition on the last day, Tyranny's two players didn't have too prominent a role. Zhang Xinjie's Cleric was sent off to fight in the group arena, while Han Wenqing was the second to be eliminated from the team competition. As such, the fans of Team Tyranny, who were onsite, were a little dissatisfied. In the All-Star Weekend, most of the time, everyone would do their best to bolster the reputation of the host team's players, letting them perform more beautifully and becoming the MVP of the All-Star Competition. But this time, the title of All-Star Competition MVP was instead stolen away by Wang Jiexi. The Magician style that he showed off during the competition had defeated Tang Hao and Sun Xiang in quick succession, and he was unquestionably the most brilliant star in the competition.

In sharp contrast to his beautiful performance was Tang Hao's miserable one. Evidently, in this All-Star Competition, it was impossible for everyone to be happy and satisfied. Even so, the curtains finally fell on this event.

The teams each regrouped and went home, and the media wantonly reported on the various magnificent scenes produced over these three days. But to the pro players, these three days were simply not worth focusing on, because this event and the true goal that they were pursuing were completely unrelated.

As everyone returned home, each team immediately started preparing for Round 18 of the regular season.

In Round 18, the intense matches of strong teams facing each other were everywhere.

The home and away teams respectively were as such; Team Tiny Herb against Team Misty Rain, Team Blue Rain against Team Void, Team Tyranny against Team Hundred Blossoms, Team Samsara against Team Thunderclap, and finally Team Happy against Team Wind Howl.

This kind of round presented a truly difficult decision for the broadcasters, and after weighing their decisions over and over again, they finally decided to show the match between Team Samsara and Team Thunderclap. Thunderclap's performance in the team competitions this season had been discussed with great enthusiasm, but Samsara? They were far too strong, making everyone somewhat numb to their formidable strength. Team Samsara had won every single one of their 17 rounds, an achievement even more exceptional than Team Thunderclap's.

Team Thunderclap's consecutive victories in the team competition were unfortunately halted in Round 16 by Team Happy. Even so, people didn't lose faith in Thunderclap because of this. When this team that relied on precise execution of their strategies met Samsara's lineup with 4 All-Stars, what kind of a battle would ensue? This match was thus selected to be the one broadcasted live, as it would evidently attract more than enough viewers.

The players were busily preparing for their upcoming matches and the television stations were busy selecting which match to broadcast, but the big team's managements were currently collating the opinions of the team members, carefully considering whether or not any adjustments needed to be made in the winter transfer window. What about the Alliance? After this All-Star weekend, they had released a new list: the All-Star Armory.

No matter whether it was in-game or in the pro scene, of all the equipment on a character, the one that drew the most attention was without a doubt the weapon. And now, the Alliance had compiled a list of all the weapons of each character in the pro circle, letting players vote in order to decide on this "All-Star Armory".

To those in the know, this was probably in order to do a survey before making products based on these weapons, but no matter what, the players were undoubtedly excited about this. The moment the list came out, the votes poured in non-stop, and the Alliance made a new rule: the Armory rankings would reset every month, and the results would be tallied at the end of the year.

After a few days, the All-Star Armory had already seen some clear distinctions in its rankings. The weapon in first place was the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella of Team Happy's Lord Grim.

The Silver lettering showed that this was a piece of self-made equipment, but having a Level 70 weapon on the list was exceedingly irksome. Glory's update had been around for a year already, and weapons were always the number one priority of equipment research. To this date, the number of self-made weapons that hadn't reached level 75 was exceedingly small, not to mention the number one rank in the All-Star Armory.

It couldn't be helped; the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella's novelty was far too eye-catching. In the All-Star voting, Ye Xiu was ranked lower than Zhou Zekai, but in this Armory, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had outranked Cloud Piercer's Wildfire and Shattered Frost by a few ranks.

This result had made many people exceptionally gloomy.

It was just as those in the know had said, this All-Star Armory could be said to be a survey of the players' interest in weapon-based merchandise, but now, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella's popularity had far exceeded that of other weapons, making the merchandise manufacturers very jittery.

Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, it wouldn't be enough to just make an umbrella and call it a day. The biggest characteristic of the weapon was its transformations, if it didn't transform, how could this weapon be popular?

This kind of thing that could transform, dismantle, and reform could be created in-game by ignoring some of the rules of science here and there. But to make it a real piece of merchandise and fully replicate its transforming ability, how much meticulous design and planning would be required? How complicated would the assembly of such a product be? How long would it take to manufacture? Finally, how much would it cost to make?

A high cost of production would mean a high price tag. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella would have a price tag far more demonic than other merchandise, and it was so demonic that those professionals who understood the market for merchandise all felt that this was too crazy.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could not be fully replicated, but not fully replicating it would definitely impact sales, making many people feel very regretful.

This Ye Xiu, why was he always such a pain? In the past, he hadn't allowed Excellent Era to make too much of a profit off of merchandise based on him. Now, he had easily created an extremely popular and famous weapon, but at the end of the day, it was unreplicatable. This guy, was he deliberately suffocating these businesses? All of those in the business who had known Ye Xiu in the past were now bitterly complaining inside. But no matter what, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was extremely popular. Making two or three of the forms was something worth trying out, and so the producers of this weapon merchandise took the initiative to get in touch with Happy.

These matters were all handled by Chen Guo. Over the past half a year, she had gotten familiar with managing the team, allowing Ye Xiu to single-mindedly focus on the competitive aspect, so he wouldn't have to expend too much effort on other things. At present, aside from these collaborations, the winter transfer window opening was also something that would create a lot of work for the teams.

Team Happy's line of thinking during this transfer window was very simple; don't buy and dont' sell. In effect, they wouldn't take part. But while not buying would allow them to avoid a few disturbances, not selling couldn't stop other teams from making inquiries.

With the impressive results that Happy had, their value of their members had also seen a significant increase. On top of that, they were a grassroots team new to the Alliance. After half a year of interaction, everyone knew that Happy's financial prowess wasn't anything impressive, and that their conditions were a little more arduous. As such, in a lot of people's eyes, Happy was like a poor child holding a brick of gold. While they couldn't snatch the entire thing away, they could spend some money to take at a least a chunk of it, right?

Qiao Yifan, Steamed Bun, Mo Fan and even Ye Xiu had all been given offers by various people. But at the end of the day, the buyers all ran into a wall and had no choice but to turn back. Chen Guo didn't show the slightest intention of letting go of any of their players, making everyone unable to see a hope in negotiating a deal.

Very quickly, on the 10th of January, Round 18 would begin. In the past ten days, there were some teams that had closed some deals, but the winter transfer window was always a small event. A transfer in core players, like in season eight, where Excellent Era managed to dig out Sun Xiang, was very rare.

In this season, some teams had stable results, while others were more unstable, but seemingly no team had a big enough conflict between their core players and normal players that they needed to use the winter transfer window to resolve it. The teams with the greatest rumors of making a transfer were Team Misty Rain and Team Wind Howl. Team Misty Rain's new playstyle this season had not created any breakthroughs for them thus far, and with 86 points, they sat at tenth place in the rankings, which was their worst results in the past few years. In a situation where their playstyle had yet to bear fruit after half a season, many people guessed that Team Misty Rain would make some adjustments to their roster.

As for Team Wind Howl, they had accumulated 112 points and sat at sixth place, which was a seemingly decent result, but it fell short of their expectations. They were a team that was aiming for the championship title, but this season, they had lost most of their matches against strong teams, causing them to begin to doubt themselves somewhat.

Upon Fang Rui's departure, the position of second-in-command had fallen to Liu Hao, who had willingly transferred in, which had somewhat disrupted the structure of Wind Howl's core. The Criminal Duo of a Brawler and Thief was what they had relied on for many years, and after Fang Rui's departure, they hadn't given up on their Thief, instead spending money to invite Team Blue Rain's Thief Player, Lin Feng, giving him the All-Star character, Doubtful Demon.

But at the end of the day, Liu Hao's Spellblade had taken a higher position, even snatching a place in the All-Star rankings, making his standing in the team very clear. And Lin Feng? He held an All-Star account in his hands, but was still far from making the list of All-Stars. In comparison with Hundred Blossoms, Zou Yuan had relied purely on the fans attachment to his account, but he still managed to send himself and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms into All-Stars. It was evident that Lin Feng's performance was not particularly outstanding, although Doubful Demon's standing was far inferior to that of Dazzling Hundred Blossom's.

Would Team Wind Howl make any adjustments to their roster? Everyone was making their own conjectures, and some fans even appealed for them to ask Fang Rui to come back. But this kind of idea could only be a fanboy's wishful thinking. Fang Rui went to Team Happy, even going so far as to put in the effort to change classes. Now, when his class change had finally begun to show results, and when Happy was still a step higher than Wind Howl in rank, they wanted him to go back to Wind Howl and revert to playing a Thief? These people, they were probably counting on Fang Rui to have some kind of undying love for Wind Howl...

Would such a situation occur?

Surprisingly, there were really reporters who went online to ask Fang Rui this question.

"I will go back," Fang Rui replied.

The reporter was completely stunned, then ecstatic, this news was truly too explosive. Fang Rui, he was actually willing to return to Wind Howl?

"On the 10th of January, I will return," Fang Rui even gave a concrete timing afterwards.

When the reporter looked at it, he suddenly understood, Fang Rui would return, but as an opponent, although…

"Great Fang Rui, the 10th of January is Happy's home game!" the reporter reminded him.

"Is it? How stupid of me, what a waste of my beautiful lines! After playing at All-Stars, I can't even count now!" Fang Rui shouted.

Chapter 1272: Meeting Force With Force

January 10 finally arrived. Neither Misty Rain nor Wind Howl made any transfers before this day. Wind Howl's original team travelled to City H one day ahead of time to warm up and get used to the set-up. Wind Howl's vice-captain Liu Hao received a good welcome from City H. It could be seen that the Excellent Era fans were still supportive of this former Excellent Era player. In the pre-match interview, Liu Hao expressed his deepest condolences towards Excellent Era's disbandment and wished New Excellent Era good luck. He also talked about New Excellent Era's current situation in the Challenger League very precisely and clearly, immediately touching the feelings of many Excellent Era fans.

As for the upcoming match, Liu Hao didn't talk too much about it. Wind Howl's captain, Tang Hao, didn't accept the pre-match interview. After the All-Stars Weekend, there were rumors that Tang Hao was feeling down because of his performance at All-Stars. These rumors were rather surprising. Who would have thought that this God would actually care so much about All-Stars? 　　

"Our captain? His condition is great. He didn't accept the interview because he wants to fully focus on this match. Wind Howl has performed well in our previous two matches. We want this momentum to continue! Happy's performance this season has already told us that they aren't a weak team, so we also need to prepare for them seriously," Liu Hao said about Tang Hao.

Wind Howl's Liu Hao and Guo Yang originated from City H, but they didn't have too much to do with Happy. When Happy beat Excellent Era in the Challenger League, the two of them had already left Excellent Era.　　

However, Wind Howl and Happy were only 5 points apart on the rankings. After this match, the placings might change. Fang Rui, a former Wind Howl player, was another focus point in this match. Many people wanted to see Fang Rui take revenge. After all, his departure from Wind Howl had been quite sad. Everyone saw that Wind Howl had let go of Fang Rui to construct a new team.

Tonight, Happy's home ground, the Xiaoshan Stadium, was a full-house. Happy's outstanding record had conquered more and more City H Glory players. Just by looking at the number of seats filled, you wouldn't be able to tell that Happy was a new team in the Alliance. Skill was what mattered in competition. This logic wasn't wrong.

The match was about to begin. First up was the individual competition. Happy's home crowd immediately roared with all their strength, "SEVENTEEN!"

17!

If Ye Xiu won this individual round, his win streak would be at 17. He had always been the first to go up in the individual competition, so before the lineup even came out, Happy's fans were already cheering.

Happy's fans didn't shout for nothing. Ye Xiu stood up from his seat and waved his hands towards the crowd. Amidst the energetic cheers and applause, he went onto the stage.

Ye Xiu had always been a symbol in this city's Glory community. After his return, his overwhelming record-breaking win streak and the unmasking of his mysteriousness amassed countless fans. The majority of these fans were on the older side. Among them, quite a few had already left the Glory scene, but Ye Xiu's return aroused their former passion and nostalgia for the game. In the Glory game, many old accounts that hadn't logged in for a long time started playing again.

Ye Xiu was the symbol of that generation. That generation's players couldn't feel the same passion from chasing the new Gods like Zhou Zekai, Sun Xiang, and Tang Hao. But now, their passion had been reignited on the stage.

Ye Xiu walked onto the stage. Who would Team Wind Howl send out as their first player?

The current consensus by numerous analysts was that Ye Xiu's fixed ordering in the individual competition was a way to gain the upper hand in the morale battle.

Ye Xiu always appeared first. He never hid. Then, how could the opponents respond?

Send out a strong player to fight? If that player lost, the team's morale would take a hit. If the team sent out a weak player, it would be like Tian Ji's horse race, but breaking the team's momentum right at the start of the match might not achieve such ideal effects.

As a result, Happy's move was difficult to deal with. We're going to put our strongest player up first and we'll wait for you to beat him. Do you dare? Ye Xiu's win streak seemed to be taunting them.　　

A weak team wouldn't dare to take up this challenge and usually just threw away this round. But some teams really would try to fight this morale battle. After all, if they really could beat Ye Xiu, it would be a huge blow to Happy's morale and a huge boost to their own team's morale. Happy's move was a double-edged sword. However, Ye Xiu was confident in waving this double-edged sword around. In the past 16 rounds, he had only injured and never been injured.

What will Wind Howl do?

This ambitions of this team were very high. The ambitions of this team's captain were very high. The ambitions of this team's rookies were very high. It was unlikely for them to throw away the first match. Who would they send up? Their captain Tang Hao? Would they send their core player to fight Ye Xiu and give up on the group arena? Speaking of which, no team had made this arrangement yet. Would Wind Howl do it?

Some looked towards Wind Howl's seats. Some stared at the screen. On Wind Howl's lineup display, the name of their first player slowly flipped into view.

Tang Hao!

They really sent out Tang Hao. Sure enough, Wind Howl was the first to take the gamble*, directly bringing out their captain and core player to fight against Ye Xiu.

Wind Howl's loyal fans, who came all this way to support their team, cheered for their team's aggressiveness and pride. However, their shouts were quickly drowned out by the boos and laughs by the home crowd.

If we aren't remembering wrong, didn't your captain Tang Hao just get destroyed by our captain at All-Stars?

Happy's fans had the lung power. Even though All-Stars was just a showmatch, who cared? Just find an example and spout it as the truth.

What could Wind Howl do? Explain patiently that All-Stars didn't count? Perhaps that might work in a forum, but in this stadium's atmosphere, words alone didn't hold enough power. They could only feign ignorance. However, Happy's taunts were quite painful to listen to.

The one in the most pain would be Tang Hao, though. At All-Stars, even though the public didn't care, he definitely did care. Now, because of the taunts from Happy, he cared even more. His two fists were clenched tightly. These two hands had helped him win everything, taking down all those voices he didn't want to hear. This time, he had decided to use this two hands again, to silence the Happy fans.

"Victory will be Wind Howl's!"

As soon as the match began, Tang Hao immediately declared that he would win, and Demon Subduer rushed straight towards the center. At All-Stars, no one had moved strategically, so Tang Hao didn't either. What's more, when Ye Xiu chose 1v1 stages, he never picked anything complicated. His maps were always the simple and direct.

The two characters met decisively at the center of the map. Lord Grim had a longer range. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella's gun form turned into a Gatling Gun and sprayed a rain of bullets. Tang Hao didn't retreat. Demon Subduer tore right through the bullet rain. It was just a Gatling Gun; it wasn't enough to hold him back.

Gatling Gun finished firing in the blink of an eye, and Demon Subduer had forcibly pulled the distance closer. Lord Grim still had plenty of skills though. His character retreated, while firing Anti-Tank Missiles. Three missiles formed a triangle, shooting out from the gun in parallel like a fan.

However, these still couldn't stop Demon Subduer's rush. Demon Subduer weaved between two missiles precisely and swiftly. This little technique was nothing in front of top Gods.

And at this moment, Lord Grim had finally entered Demon Subduer's attack range. Demon Subduer raised his hands and threw a handful of sand. You could take the hit, but you had to turn your gaze away from it. However, Lord Grim had an umbrella in his hands. With a whoosh, it opened and blocked the sand.

This response was within Tang Hao's expectations. The purpose of a direct Sand Toss was for that instant where the opponent's sight was no longer on him. Whether it was turning around or blocking with a shield, the outcome was the same. Demon Subduer threw the Paralysis Needle he had prepared. If the needle hit a target, it would paralyze the target. Brawlers were filled with these dirty little tricks.

Paralysis Needle was thrown practically the instant Lord Grim's umbrella opened. Tang Hao was banking on Ye Xiu closing his umbrella after blocking the Sand Toss. In that case, the Paralysis Needle couldn't be dodged and it would strike Lord Grim.

But after the Sand Toss was blocked, Lord Grim didn't retract his umbrella. His umbrella stayed wide open. The precisely timed Paralysis Needle stabbed the umbrella canopy and fell down without even making a sound.

Tang Hao was gloomy. Seeing that the umbrella wasn't going to be closed any time soon, he might as well use it as a cover. Demon Subduer rushed forward, holding a Brick in his hands. The Brick would be thrown as soon as he reached him.

Lord Grim didn't retract his umbrella, but he rushed forward as well.

Charge! A Knight skill. The shield was a Knight equipment, and it didn't stop this skill from being used. Using Charge with a shield would carry the same momentum, but it lacked the damage. Tang Hao didn't dare disregard it. A Shield Charge dealt no damage, but shields had Shield Attack. At All-Stars, Ye Xiu had used this trick and even Huang Shaotian fell for it. Tang Hao remembered that scene and didn't dare borrow the shield as a cover anymore. He hastily shifted diagonally and pulled the distance between them a bit. He raised his arms and threw a Brick.

But in this instant, Tang Hao clearly saw that the Lord Grim behind the umbrella was looking towards the side, staring right at him.

My opponent knows!

By the time Tang Hao realized this, the Brick had already been thrown by Demon Subduer. Then, he saw Lord Grim draw his sword from the umbrella handle with a Sword Draw. A sword light flashed out in front of him. Dodge? Demon Subduer had just stepped towards him. Which way should he dodge?

Forward? Backwards? Left? Right?

The sword light covered all of his options!

Hit!

Demon Subduer's blood sprayed into the air.

Chapter 1273: Completely Crushed

The attack landed in such a simple manner.

Splattering blood and cutting down Tang Hao's rising spirit.

Demon Subduer's Brick was easily dodged, while he himself took a hit. How could Ye Xiu only attack just once? After Sword Draw, the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's shield form retracted, and its numerous other forms were displayed as all sorts of skills struck Demon Subduer.

Unspecialized characters fight fast!

Unwittingly, the crowd had started gasping at Lord Grim's combo. Even though they had no idea what exactly Ye Xiu was doing in his combo game, they could see Demon Subduer being hit by a bunch of different low-leveled skills. From this, they knew that Lord Grim's combo had started.

So far, 16 players had lost to these swift attacks. Among these players included nervous rookies, talented rookies, matchups tactically chosen to be thrown away, and strong players who wanted to give him a try. There were also former Gods like Zhang Jiale and Sun Zheping.

However, it was the first time Ye Xiu had encountered a team's core player.

And what was the outcome?

The people carrying hopes for Tang Hao were quickly disappointed.　　

He… was no different from anyone else!

Victory belongs to Wind Howl?　

Tang Hao's declaration before the match now just seemed like empty words. The powerlessness he was showing right now indicated that he was being completely overwhelmed.

What's going on? This isn't All-Stars.　

Quite a few people wondered. They felt like this wasn't Tang Hao's true strength.

Tang Hao also thought that this wasn't his true strength, but the problem was that he wasn't able to display it.

After Ye Xiu took first blood, Tang Hao had felt a bit defeated. His fighting spirit and willpower had taken a small blow, but they were still there. He was waiting for an opportunity to counterattack, waiting for an opening.

But… there were no openings.

It was just four words, but what level of fundamentals did that require?

No matter how haughty Tang Hao was. No matter how confident he was that he could beat anyone. He didn't dare believe that he could play on stage without exposing any openings.

No one could do it. At least that was what Tang Hao thought up until today. But right now, facing this opponent, he couldn't find even the slightest opening.　　

How is this possible?

Am I just not perceptive enough?

Tang Hao didn't believe a person couldn't have any openings, so he started doubting his observational abilities. His confidence had already started to waver.

Tang Hao didn't know whether this doubt had sprouted starting from today, or from that day at All-Stars. He only knew that he didn't want to lose, yet he couldn't find any ways to win.

Keep fighting like this?　　

Seeing Demon Subduer's health dropping, Tang Hao started to panic.　　

What if I really can't find any openings? Could I be taken out in one go by a near full health Ye Xiu? In Ye Xiu's sixteen victories, no one had lost this miserably, no? Could it be that I'm worse than even them?

"Impossible!!!" Tang Hao roared. No one could hear him though. Voice communication was only enabled at All-Stars. In regular season matches, the competitive rules were back to normal.

With this roar, Tang Hao sprung forward. He ignored Lord Grim's next attack, activating Reinforce Iron Bones, and forced his way over!

Instant defeat.

Tang Hao's choice wasn't some sort of magical road out; it looked more like a trapped beast's final struggle. Ye Xiu saw a hundred different ways to deal with it. He simply chose one of them and knocked down Demon Subduer.

The crowd erupted into loud boos. Tang Hao's struggle looked like there was zero brain behind it. You want to break through an unspecialized's combo like that?

"Too naive!" Happy's fans shouted loudly.

The sound couldn't reach Tang Hao's ears, but he knew better than anyone else what he was doing.

If once isn't enough, then again!

Tang Hao rushed forward again like a brute, continue to charge at him without any thought.　　

You look as if you've got a hundred ways to deal with me? Fine, then I'll try them out one by one. Let's see just how many you've got.

Tang Hao continued to go for it, but the crowd's laughter was gradually dying down.

Tang Hao's playing looked pathetic, so much so that it didn't look like he deserved his God status. However, when there was no way out, being able to lower oneself and daring to try such humiliating choices showed just how pure Tang Hao's pursuit for victory was. Many people thought his All-Stars performance was disgraceful, but right now, his actions showed he didn't care about that.

He wasn't playing for honor, he was playing to win.

Unfortunately, victory wasn't as simple as just letting go of everything. No one knew just how many ways Ye Xiu had to deal with this situation, but everyone could see how Tang Hao's countless attempts ended with him being beaten back. The crowd stopped laughing. Ye Xiu didn't let up at all.

Tang Hao might have the energy to keep trying, but Demon Subduer didn't have unlimited health.　

Again and again, he was unable to break through Lord Grim's offense. All he faced was an even stronger retaliation. Finally, Demon Subduer's health fell to zero.

I lost!

But he wasn't as humiliated or embarrassed as he'd been at All-Stars.　　

Wang Jiexi's Magician playstyle had been too abrupt and too unexpected. Tang Hao had been caught unprepared. He was probably more resentful about being cheated by this sort of surprise move. But right now, he wasn't facing anything surprising. He wasn't caught off guard. He was being completely suppressed in a real fight. It was because his opponent was better than him.

So there was someone this skilled?

When Demon Subduer fell, Tang Hao didn't feel humiliated, but rather humbled.

"I'll win next time!" He was still as stubborn as ever. He seemed to have forgotten that his declaration of victory had been shut down.

"We'll see next time," Ye Xiu replied.

The crowd let out a sigh of relief.

Sigh of relief? Why did they let out a sigh of relief? Everyone suddenly started feeling a bit strange. Tang Hao was just thrashing around without any brain. How could he win like that? Why were they worried for Ye Xiu?　

When Ye Xiu came down from the stage, the crowd clapped and cheered, but there was a trace of hesitation mixed in.　　

As for Tang Hao? He was the loser, and one who lost miserably, but his steps were firm. Everyone looked at him with complicated feelings. They couldn't say why though.

Ye Xiu walked down from the stage and returned to his seat.

"Beautiful playing! You really taught that guy a lesson!" Chen Guo went over to Ye Xiu and praised him. She didn't like Tang Hao. Watching Tang Hao get destroyed by Ye Xiu felt amazing.

"It was well done," Fang Rui nodded. "But it wasn't easy, no?"　　

"What?" Chen Guo was puzzled. When she looked at Ye Xiu, she discovered that he didn't look too happy about his win. Even though Ye Xiu wasn't the type to show his emotions easily, his expression wasn't very relaxed despite winning. Chen Guo realized her perspective of the match was too shallow. She looked at Su Mucheng, and from Su Mucheng's gaze towards Ye Xiu, she could see… worry.

"It wasn't easy," Ye Xiu said.　　

"Why?" Chen Guo asked.

"Boss… do you really think completely suppressing a player of Tang Hao's caliber is easy?" Fang Rui said.

"Ah?"

"The reason he could do it was because he was going all out the entire time! That's very exhausting," Fang Rui said.　

Chen Guo now understood that Ye Xiu had used up much more energy than normal to achieve such a beautiful win. Beat Tang Hao? It wasn't just that. He had completely suppressed him.

"Why did he have to do that?" Chen Guo was feeling worried. Isn't a win just good enough? Why did he have to pay such a price to win so thoroughly? Was that necessary? Chen Guo felt distressed.

"Why? Because I didn't want to lose!" Ye Xiu said.

Not lose?

Chen Guo was stumped. Ye Xiu meant that if he hadn't completely suppressed Tang Hao, if Tang Hao had an opportunity to counterattack, he might have lost to Tang Hao?

Chen Guo looked at Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, everyone.　

Everyone was quiet. No one called Ye Xiu's words into question.

Chen Guo couldn't say anything else.

"You… rest well!" She could only say these words.

The match continued. Even though she was worried about Ye Xiu, the match was going well. In the individual competition, Happy sent out Mo Fan and Su Mucheng, who won their matches, making the score 3-0.

The entire crowd had forgotten the weird feeling felt from the first individual round and started chanting 10-0. The points in the individual competition were the most scattered, so these points were often the biggest barriers to a 10-0. However, Happy had swept the individual competition and were on their way to 10-0! So far, whenever Happy won every round in the individual competition, they had always gotten a 10-0!

Hearing the crowd's cheers, Chen Guo unexpectedly didn't share the same excitement as the crowd. She didn't forget the exhaustion Ye Xiu felt after the first round and suddenly felt a bad premonition.

The group arena began. Happy's first player was Fang Rui and his Qi Master, Boundless Sea.

The entire crowd applauded.

Even though Fang Rui had switched to a Qi Master, he was as dirty as ever. His playstyle might not be well-liked and might be spurned by the Qi Master community, but among Happy's supporters, a lot of people still admired him. For a newly joined team, everyone cared more about winning. As for a good win record and beautiful playing, those goals could be left for those powerhouses who were consistently solid! Happy's fan base was more practical. Victory was greater than anything else.

A dirty win was still a win, no?

Amidst the cheers, Fang Rui went onto the stage and into the player booth. His opponent was Team Wind Howl's Zhao Yuzhe.　　

"Senior, it seems like you're doing well at Happy!" At the start of the match, Zhao Yuzhe took the initiative to message Fang Rui.

Chapter 1274: Familiar People

"hehehehehehehe"

The response that Zhao Yuzhe received was seven consecutive "hes." Coming from the master of playing dirty, this sent a chill down everyone's spines. They instantly felt that not only would Zhao Yuzhe lose, he would lose miserably.

"What is senior laughing about?" After Fang Rui's seven "hes," Zhao Yuzhe's reaction was fairly calm. He wouldn't feel any chill from Fang Rui's dirty playing. From the very start, he had never thought highly of this senior. But for a Thief to play dirty, that was excusable, as this class relied on playing dirty to reach full potential. But now that he had switched to Qi Master, yet he was still this dirty, that wasn't because of the class, that was because of the person himself. This person was dirty, so whatever class he played was dirty.

"I'm laughing at you!" Fang Rui answered.

"Laughing at me about what?" Zhao Yuzhe asked.

"Laughing that you still have the time to chat. I'm already behind you right now, don't you know?" said Fang Rui.

"Haha, senior is as funny as always." Zhao Yuzhe of course wouldn't be tricked by something like this. Although he was chatting with Fang Rui in the channel, he was very careful with his character's controls. He was rotating his camera often, doing his best not to leave any blind spots.

As long as you closely watched the opponent's movements, then there was nothing to fear from dirty playing. That was what Zhao Yuzhe believed. Back when they were teammates, during practice matches within the team, his win rate against Fang Rui had been relatively high.

The group arena map was Forest Corridor, a relatively complex map for 1v1 matches, suitable for the dirty playstyle. But for an Elementalist, a class that required casting to launch attacks, extra cover wasn't a bad thing.

Neither character charged directly towards the center. Both were steadily approaching using all sorts of cover. The crowd was also gradually affected by this kind of atmosphere. The shouts became quieter, quieter, until it was almost completely silent, and then, the two characters met!

Boom!

Zhao Yuzhe was the first to attack. Elementalist Beautiful Light waved his staff and launched a Fireball. This sort of low-level spell could be cast almost instantaneously for a pro character. For an Elementalist's equipment, cast speed was one of the most important attributes to boost.

Boundless Sea, who had been trying to take a roundabout path to flank him, had actually been directly seen through by Zhao Yuzhe. The stadium was filled with sighs of regret. Boundless Sea rolled and dodged, and with a flip of his palm, he pushed out a Qi Bullet.

He sure has a few tricks, huh?

The light of the Qi Bullet directly covered Zhao Yuzhe's view. He laughed coldly and cleanly used a Teleport.

Using this sort of skill to dodge a Qi Bullet was indeed a bit wasteful, but Zhao Yuzhe was clear that Fang Rui only used the Qi Bullet as a cover. The true attack would come after. A Teleport would allow him to avoid both the interference of the Qi Bullet and the follow-up attack, wasn't that convenient?

Beautiful Light raised his staff, preparing to fire another spell, but he suddenly saw the air around him rippling in an unusual pattern.

Qi Blade!

Pu!

Zhao Yuzhe had no time to react, and Beautiful Light's cast was brutally cut short by this attack. But what really shocked Zhao Yuzhe was the sheer accuracy of this attack. Had the opponent predicted early on that he would come to this position? And if that was the case… how could a Qi Blade be the only attack?

Of course it wasn't!

With that Thief posture that looked particularly ugly on a Qi Master, Boundless Sea flew toward him. In the midst of his leaping, he slapped his palms against the ground, using a Landmine Quake after that Qi Blade.

The Qi spread rapidly along the ground. Beautiful Light, having just been hit by that Qi Blade, didn't have the chance to escape the range. He was shaken by the Qi, and sent staggering and falling over. Boundless Sea activated Qi Flowing Cloud, instantly arriving in front of Beautiful Light, Pulse Break: Break Intelligence, Flash Burst, then a Qigong Blast, and at the very end there was even a Sky Piercing Strike!

The Qi Master's fierce attacks surged toward him, instantly landing on Beautiful Light's body. The rippling Qi energy lifted his robe, and Beautiful Light looked like a giant balloon as he floated upward. No blood spilled, but his slipping health let everyone know that even if these weren't bloody attacks, the damage they brought was no inferior to any hacking and slashing attack.

"How about it? A pleasant surprise?" Fang Rui began his trash talk attack in the channel.

Surprise, sure. But pleasant? Zhao Yuzhe of course didn't feel that at all.

"Don't just think that you understand me well! Teammates are mutual, I'm no stranger to your fighting either. The only difference is that, as your senior, I was kinder," Fang Rui said.

As your senior I was kinder?

What did that mean? That in their previous practice fights, he hadn't been using his full strength?

No! How was that possible!!

Zhao Yuzhe didn't believe it. He instantly adjusted Beautiful Light's condition, prepared to launch a counterattack, but… where was Boundless Sea?

The target had vanished.

Zhao Yuzhe was shaken. He immediately used an Electric Ring, creating a coil of lightning around him. No matter from which angle the opponent wanted to approach, he would first be zapped by this lightning. Even though this low-level skill didn't cause much damage, it could serve as some protection.

"Electric Ring? Aren't you forgetting something?" Boundless Sea had vanished from Zhao Yuzhe's sight, but Fang Rui's messages were still constantly appearing in the match channel before his eyes.

"I'm… not a Thief anymore!" Fang Rui said. Boundless Sea suddenly appeared, but he was… above Beautiful Light.

Thieves had the most fearsome tool at their disposal for launching close-range sneak attacks: Stealth. Electric Ring? It was undoubtedly a useful countermeasure towards Stealth. When Zhao Yuzhe couldn't find Boundless Sea, he instantly activated Electric Ring, because… he thought that Boundless Sea would use Stealth to quietly get in close range? Had he subconsciously treated Fang Rui as the King of Thieves like when he had been in Wind Howl?

But he was no longer a Thief. He could no longer use Stealth or such techniques to sneakily come into close range.

Where was Boundless Sea?

Zhao Yuzhe spun around in a full 360-degree circle several times, finally stopping at that fallen willow tree in the 2 o'clock direction.

He'd overlooked something?

Zhao Yuzhe suddenly raised his camera view and saw above his head the near-invisible, silent glittering.

Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

The level 55 Qi Master Awakening skill. Qi was pushed through the whole body, and what was blasted out was no longer just Qi, but the Qi Master himself as well.

Boundless Sea, like a heavy bomb, fell from the sky. Qi collected around his whole body, thick and radiant, slicing through the air like a rainbow, falling straight down and crashing into Beautiful Light.

Boom!

The Qi around Boundless Sea exploded when he hit Beautiful Light. It wasn't as bright as the surging fireworks of a Launcher's cannonfire, nor was it as elegant as the light of an Elementalist's spells. Even the light of the rainbow around his body faded in that instant of impact. But because this was the case, the damage caused by this attack was incredibly apparent.

The surrounding plants, the rocks, the mud, were all bent out of shape from the pressure of the Qi, some directly breaking. As for Beautiful Light, the direct target of this attack, even less needed to be said. Spirit Rainbow Blast was an attack that could be charged up, and while Fang Rui was chattering away at Fang Rui, the audience could see clearly that Boundless Sea had gotten into position early and begun charging.

"I'm not done yet!" Fang Rui yelled. Spirit Rainbow Blast was only a starting attack; more would follow. But compared to most combos, which would save the powerful attack for the end, Fang Rui used a powerful attack to blast the opponent first. Afterward, if there was an opening he'd continue, otherwise even just one powerful attack was worth it.

Zhao Yuzhe had clearly been thrown off by the powerful attack. This was a good chance for Fang Rui to seize the opening, and he didn't hesitate as he blasted another series of Qi Master attacks, which appeared gentle, but hit so hard that Zhao Yuzhe even felt pain on his real body.

How did things end up like this?

Zhao Yuzhe didn't understand. He hadn't dared to say his victory was guaranteed, but he had originally had a lot of confidence. But why? Why was he battered so harshly that he had no way of parrying? He couldn't predict the opponent's movements, but his own choice of position, his reactions, all seemed to be within Fang Rui's calculations.

Was it really like Fang Rui had said? Fang Rui understood him extremely well, but he had never taken advantage of this point before?

How could that be possible?

Zhao Yuzhe didn't believe it. He wasn't convinced. Beautiful Light stood up again, rushed forward… and in the end, lost the match brutally.

"You actually hid your strength even from your teammates?" In the last moment before he fell, Zhao Yuzhe shouted, full of venom.

"Hehe, dirty, no?" This was Fang Rui's answer.

In the first battle of the group arena, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea used only ten percent of his health to defeat Zhao Yuzhe's Beautiful Light. The crowd was filled with joking and laughter, and they threw all sorts of ridicule at Zhao Yuzhe as he walked out of the competitor booth.

"Is Fang Rui really so evil to actually hide his true strength even from his teammates?" But some people were still wondering about this question, including Chen Guo.

"Of course not. That kid just doesn't understand," said Ye Xiu.

"What doesn't he understand?" Chen Guo said.

"He doesn't understand that understanding your teammate and understanding your opponent are two different things. Before, Fang Rui treated him as a teammate, and now, he treated him as an opponent. As for him… he probably only knows how to understand people from the position of an opponent!" Ye Xiu said.

"Oh…" Chen Guo nodded, beginning to understand.

At this time, Wind Howl's second player of the group arena stood up.

Lin Feng.

Lin Feng, a transfer from Blue Rain to Wind Howl. Immediately upon his arrival, he obtained the top Thief character, Doubtful Demon. Lin Feng's luck was quite good. But he hadn't grasped this opportunity very well, and on the final All-Star rankings this year, there was no Thief representative.

And now, Lin Feng was challenging Doubtful Demon's old owner. He, who hadn't completed the inheritance of this character very well, what kind of answer would he give in this battle?

"Hahaha, my luck today is really good! First it's my familiar old teammate, and now it's my familiar old character. I can already hear the cheers of victory." When the battle started, Fang Rui was already beginning his trash talk. But, his old teammate, and the character he'd fought with for so many years, for them to suddenly become opponents, this… was this really good luck that could make the heart happy? No one would believe this.

Chapter 1275: The Battle Thief

The second battle of the group arena began, and neither character took the conventional path. Fang Rui's Qi Master continued to play dirty, while Lin Feng's Thief directly charged forward. Indeed, a Thief charged forward. In most people's eyes, this was not the conventional thing to do. However, this was the speciality of Lin Feng's thief. His playstyle was the less commonly seen style for Thieves, the so-called Battle Thief playstyle.

Wind Howl's style, after taking in Tang Hao and discovering the potential of rookie Zhao Yuzhe, had changed greatly. Under the powerful push of these two players, the dirty playstyle that had existed in this team for a long time suddenly became more and more unsuitable. Because of this, even the one called the master of playing dirty, Fang Rui, had been forced to leave.

Wind Howl hadn't given up on their All-Star Thief character Doubtful Demon because of this, but clearly they weren't going to find another dirty-playing Thief player here, otherwise what was the point in having Fang Rui leave? If talking about playing dirty, Fang Rui was already called the master.

And so they took in Lin Feng from Blue Rain, a rare Battle Thief player in the pro circle. Wind Howl hoped to change the Thief's style to let this All-Star character continue to demonstrate its power. But after half a season, Doubtful Demon vanished from the ranks of the All-Stars, proving that his ability hadn't been displayed as effectively as they'd hoped. When the winter transfer window opened, Lin Feng and Doubtful Demon were surrounded by many rumors. At this time, if he still wanted to stay in the team, he had to prove himself. If he could defeat the opponent in front of him now, Doubtful Demon's former owner, who was expelled for not fitting with Wind Howl's new style, that would be the best proof that Wind Howl's choice was worth it.

And Wind Howl chose Lin Feng exactly because his Thief style wasn't like others. So, when facing Fang Rui, he charged forward even more determined than usual. He wanted to more clearly display the new Battle Thief style of Doubtful Demon under his hand.

The so-called Battle Thief involved a focus on the Thief's direct attacking skills, supplemented by the trapping skills, resulting in instantaneous explosions of high damage output. As of now, it was a rare playstyle in both the professional circle and in-game. And Lin Feng could already be considered the leader of this style. In Blue Rain, although he wasn't a first-string player, he still had stable chances to appear onstage, and his performances deserved praise. But when he arrived at Wind Howl and obtained the number one Thief, when he had to bear higher hopes from the team, he seemed to have lost himself a bit.

I have to prove myself!

Lin Feng controlled Doubtful Demon to move toward the center of the map. When he found no trace of Boundless Sea, he knew that the opponent was playing dirty again, and would appear from who-knows-where. After watching the previous battle, Lin Feng's camera observed not just the four directions around him but also the high points from which attacks could be fired. He carefully controlled Doubtful Demon to move around, searching for a position where he wouldn't have to defend from too many directions.

"A Doubtful Demon that's instantly discovered, what an eyesore!" In the match channel, a message from Fang Rui suddenly popped up.

Is he here?

Lin Feng hurriedly turned his view, left and right, in front and behind, above, but he didn't discover anything.

"Your Shadow Trap at position 124, 119, thought I wouldn't see it?" Fang Rui said.

Lin Feng's heart grew cold. When he'd had Doubtful Demon place down that trap, he'd been especially careful to observe his surroundings. But this Boundless Sea had still been hiding somewhere and managed to discover it? A trap that had been discovered had no purpose anymore…

But the audience was even more shocked.

Because they, with the omniscient view, knew clearly that Boundless Sea right now was already quietly watching Doubtful Demon. But, when Doubtful Demon had placed that Shadow Trap, Boundless Sea was still taking the roundabout path. He hadn't seen it at all.

This was a guess! But he'd guessed so accurately.

Fang Rui understood the map, understood the Thief class, and it looked like he understood Lin Feng as well…

If the trap had been seen by the opponent, then the intention was also seen through, thought Lin Feng. He could only make adjustments. But more importantly, where was Boundless Sea right now? He still hadn't discovered him, but to have seen Doubtful Demon planting that trap…

Over there!

The slight rustling of the grass didn't escape Lin Feng's notice. Doubtful Demon used an Assassin's Shining Cut to fly forward through the grass, but when the character arrived, he didn't see Boundless Sea.

"Too gullible! Battle Thieves are just that simple-minded!" As Fang Rui mocked him with a somewhat personal attack, Boundless Sea shot an attack from the side of the road and Sky Piercing Strike instantly enveloped Doubtful Demon.

But, nothing happened!

He hadn't suffered damage, nor had he been jostled by the rippling Qi energy. Doubtful Demon turned and charged toward Boundless Sea, as though the Sky Piercing Strike simply didn't exist.

"Maxed out Escape?" Fang Rui commented.

Escape, a Thief skill. It granted a certain probability to completely nullify the effects of the opponent's next attack, and at max level this probability reached 100%. For professional players, if this skill was to be leveled up, it would be leveled up to the maximum, because only then could it be reliably used in a match. A probability under 100% was an opening.

In Fang Rui's hands, Doubtful Demon hadn't learned this skill. But now that Lin Feng had changed Doubtful Demon to a Battle Thief, he had clearly added the points to this skill to max it out.

Before the Sky Piercing Strike landed, Doubtful Demon had already activated Escape, so this attack was forcibly negated, and now Lin Feng cleanly rushed to attack.

"An expected choice!" Fang Rui was still nagging, but Boundless Sea had already easily avoided Doubtful Demon. He'd expected Doubtful Demon's skill choice, and so he'd had ample preparation for this current situation.

Boundless Sea, who'd activated Qi Flowing Cloud to easily avoid Doubtful Demon's attack, pushed out his palm to send the Qi that had gathered flying toward Doubtful Demon.

Flash Burst!

Directly using such a powerful attack was a common technique of Fang Rui's dirty playing Qi Master, very different from the classical Qi Master style. Most Qi Masters played in a very standard way, using small attacks for a bit of damage and containment, and once they'd grasped the rhythm, they'd unleash a powerful attack.

And for Fang Rui, he used his dirty playing to create the opportunity to use such a powerful attack.

Dirty tactics, dirty movement, dirty attack timing.

This Flash Burst was the result of combining all of the previous dirty playing methods. Under countless exclamations from the crowd of "too dirty," this palm hit Doubtful Demon.

The Qi spread around Doubtful Demon damaged him like crazy. Evidently, Fang Rui didn't hold back even as he attacked this character that had been with him for five years. One brutal blow after another landed, and it seemed that the dirty Boundless Sea wasn't dirty at all right now, as he used standard Qi Master attacks and techniques to teach Doubtful Demon a direct and harsh lesson. But the instant that this flurry of attacks ended, Boundless Sea immediately scurried away again, in his usual dirty playing fashion.

After adjusting himself, Lin Feng once again lost all trace of Boundless Sea, but this time he wasn't as calm as he was before. Doubtful Demon moved around quickly, changing his position often. As he searched for Boundless Sea, he ensured that he wouldn't be exposed in one position for too long.

And so he quickly found Boundless Sea. Or, more accurately, Fang Rui voluntarily made Boundless Sea appear in front of him.

A sudden, completely unexpected appearance, it would stun anyone. But coming from Fang Rui, the stadium was once again filled with shouts of "too dirty!"

Yes, a very dirty appearance, so dirty that Lin Feng was completely unprepared.

Countercurrent!

Boundless Sea used the lowest level knock-up attack, the most long-ranged knock-up skill among all classes.

Doubtful Demon was unwillingly sent into the air by the Qi waves that Boundless Sea sent out, and naturally he became a perfect target for midair attacks. The skills to escape these attacks wouldn't have very short cooldowns, and they hadn't restored yet, so Lin Feng could only himself search for ways to escape the opponent's attacks… But Fang Rui was truly too familiar with Thieves, even if this was a Battle Thief.

Lin Feng struggled to steady his heart as he carefully observed, and finally, he discovered that Boundless Sea had already completely finished his series of attacks.

Lin Feng's heart sank into helplessness.

Fang Rui was the previous user of Doubtful Demon, the one whom he had replaced in Wind Howl. If he could win this match, then for Lin Feng it would be a powerful way to cement his place in the team. But who knew that Lin Feng suffered so much psychological pressure from Fang Rui? Lin Feng wasn't Tang Hao, nor was he Zhao Yuzhe. The person he was facing now was, to him, the king amongst them Thieves!

Lin Feng was a player from Season 7. He'd ultimately chosen to become an unusual type of Thief, a Battle Thief.

He had never explained to anyone his reason for choosing Battle Thief.

In reality, he chose to play as a Battle Thief only because he felt that he needed to open a different path. He felt that, in the standard Thief style, Fang Rui had already achieved the ultimate level, and he himself had no way of surpassing that. But even though he had taken an uncommon path with his Thief, he still hadn't been able to reach a position to rival Fang Rui.

And now, Fang Rui changed classes to Qi Master. He was no longer that King amongst Thieves, and because of this Lin Feng could relax significantly. But after being completely smothered by Fang Rui twice now, Lin Feng had no way of relaxing. He discovered that even though Fang Rui was no longer the King of Thieves, he could still deal with any Thief player with ease, no matter whether it was a dirty-playing, trap-laying Thief, or a Battle Thief like him…

There was no way to win. After recognizing this point, Lin Feng lost all his fighting spirit. This wasn't an on-the-spot realization, but a conclusion he'd reached years before when comparing himself to this King of Thieves. And now, even if Fang Rui had changed classes, this conclusion hadn't changed.

"Doubtful Demon turned into this because of you, it's really too ugly." As Fang Rui sent a final message, Boundless Sea sent a final attack. Lin Feng, this Battle Thief player, couldn't reach the height of a king, but Wind Howl didn't need a dirty playing Thief. And thus this king character among Thieves finally fell.

Chapter 1276: Behind You

Happy progressed one level further in the group arena. It seemed that Fang Rui had achieved these two victories very easily, so easily that it was almost scary. After two battles, Boundless Sea had only lost 17% of his health!

This… was the pace to a 1v3!

The crowd took a while to process this, but when Wind Howl's Lin Feng exited the player booth and left the stage with his head lowered, the crowd finally recovered and suddenly exploded with cheers.

He still had 83% health left, and Wind Howl's core God Tang Hao had already appeared in the individual competition. There was a big chance for a 1v3 in this group arena today!

The crowd looked toward Wind Howl's player area. Who would be Wind Howl's group arena anchor?

After several moments, the shouting in the stadium seemed to quiet down a bit, as Wind Howl's anchor stood up: Liu Hao.

Liu Hao had entered the All-Stars this season, meaning that his popularity wasn't bad. More importantly, this was City H, and one year prior this was still Liu Hao's home stadium. Much of the crowd today had come here in the past and watched his matches in person. Seeing Liu Hao come onstage, everyone hesitated. Yesterday's teammate becoming today's opponent, this was what players had to face. Yesterday's idol becoming today's obstacle, this was what fans had to face.

At this sort of time, the crowd's mood would become very complex, and the hopes for a 1v3 were pulled back. This was the cruelty of the professional league, occasionally leaping out to bite.

Liu Hao's steps were firm as he walked toward the stage, and he even paid tribute to the crowd, waving his hand toward them. As an away team player, this was practically asking for contempt, but Liu Hao evidently knew that his relationship with this crowd was different. His attitude actually won over quite a bit of the crowd. Toward this away team player, the home crowd actually gave him some applause.

But Liu Hao was nowhere near as confident as he appeared.

They'd already lost two players, and they'd only taken down 17% of the opponent's health. If Wind Howl wanted to win, he would have to accomplish a 1v3…

Liu Hao didn't have such dreams. In his view, this was already a group arena that Wind Howl had no way of winning. To him, what he absolutely needed to do was defeat Fang Rui, at least prevent the other side from completing a 1v3. Otherwise, it would simply be far too embarrassing for both him and Wind Howl as a whole.

But this opponent still had 83% health…

Liu Hao's mood was a bit heavy. As soon as he entered the player booth, that air of confidence and elegance he'd projected for the crowd instantly vanished. He carefully examined the state of the keyboard, mouse, and other such things, before finally logging on.

The third battle of the group arena began. Happy still had Fang Rui, but Wind Howl was already on their third and final player.

"Now that I'm here, if I don't 1v3, everyone will be so disappointed!" When the battle began, Fang Rui already boldly expressed this.

"Haha, what a nice imagination!" Liu Hao replied.

"But you're even more screwed. You'll have to 1v3 if you want to win this group arena, right?" Fang Rui said.

Liu Hao couldn't say anything. Just now, he had wanted to use his words to draw the crowd's attention to the question of whether or not Fang Rui could 1v3. With this, if he won and blocked Fang Rui's 1v3, he could be put in the role of a victor. Wind Howl would still lose the group arena, but everyone would put the blame on the first two players for not doing well, and he, who stopped Fang Rui's 1v3, would still have a bit of the air of a hero.

But who would've expected Fang Rui to be so quick with his words? With one sentence, he exposed the truth of the difficult situation he was in.

Just defeat Fang Rui? That was far from enough. Right now, he was the one who actually bore the heavy responsibility of completing a 1v3. Liu Hao's plan of diverting the crowd's attention hadn't even been implemented before Fang Rui shattered it.

"How about it? 1v3, have any confidence? I can say that I sure do!" Fang Rui was still chatting away. Not only had Liu Hao's goal of redirection failed, Fang Rui was forcing everyone's attention onto this issue of 1v3 like crazy. He had confidence? Of course he did, 83% challenging 100%, any player in this position would be extremely motivated. But Liu Hao? 100% against 283%? His heart was broken.

"1v3? In your dreams!" Liu Hao was helpless. He could only continue to present himself as someone who would stop a 1v3, and not someone who had to carry out a 1v3.

"Hehe, I should say in YOUR dreams! Or is it that you don't even have these dreams? If that's the case, I say, stop wasting time and just GG!" Fang Rui said.

Now that their conversation had reached this point, it was practically grinding away Liu Hao's spine. This was Happy's home stadium, but there were a number of diehard Wind Howl fans following along with the team. They couldn't bear to see such mockery anymore. In such a situation, they could understand if Liu Hao lost the match, but ultimately everyone still had a sliver of hope for a miracle. Seeing Fang Rui's attack now, Wind Howl's fans instantly exploded. They hoped that their vice-captain Liu Hao, upon whom the team had heavily relied this season, would fight back back for them, initiate a powerful counterattack 1v3 in this Happy stadium, and humiliate the opponents.

"1v3!!!" Wind Howl's diehard fans became fired up, cheering and yelling encouragement for their vice-captain. But instantly, their shouts overlapped with the "1v3" shouts from the Happy fans. Wind Howl's shouts were a bit more vigorous and exuberant, as they wished so desperately to see this humiliation. But with their shouts, Happy's fans couldn't sit still. The battle was already at this point and they still wanted to see a 1v3? Ridiculous! And so, Happy's shouts of "1v3" reached a new peak, attacking the Wind Howl fans. There were more of them, and so they quickly smothered the away team fans. But Wind Howl refused to yield. Even if their sound was drowned out, it wouldn't stop them from continuing to shout.

This was their trust and hope in Liu Hao and Wind Howl!

Liu Hao, sitting in the player booth, had no idea. If he did know, he probably wouldn't be moved, he would probably start crying from the the motivation of these fans.

1v3? Can't everyone be logical here? How was he supposed to 1v3 under these conditions? The opponent's first player still had 83% health!

Liu Hao didn't know, and so he didn't think that much right now. He only prepared to defeat Fang Rui, at least stop Happy from 1v3ing, and then he would definitely be understood by the fans. He had no idea that, because of Fang Rui's trash talk, Wind Howl's fans had already expressed even higher expectations for him.

As the two of them bickered through the chat, they were already approaching. Fang Rui continued to play dirty, and there was no sign of Boundless Sea. After watching two matches, Liu Hao had already grasped a few key points of Fang Rui's usage of this map. Right now, he paid close attention as he moved his character, choosing positions carefully. For now, he hadn't found Boundless Sea, but Fang Rui also couldn't find a good chance to attack. The two were at a stalemate.

"What's wrong, still not attacking? Can't find an opportunity? If you continue to hide like this, watch out for a yellow card!" Liu Hao also began a trash talk offensive.

"I'm right behind you!" Fang Rui said.

"Haha." Liu Hao wasn't that naive.

"I really am right behind you!" Fang Rui still said.

"..."

"Behind you!"

"Behind you!"

Fang Rui suddenly channeled Huang Shaotian and actually continued to spam these two words nonstop in the chat. Liu Hao was irritated, but the more irritated he was, the more he didn't dare to turn his character around. The more Fang Rui yelled this, the more he felt that the danger would come from anywhere but behind him. Liu Hao carefully controlled his character to move, looking left and right. But there was no sign of Boundless Sea, only Boundless Sea's spam.

"Behind you!"

"Behind you!"

Liu Hao suddenly felt nervous.

This guy, with his nonstop spamming, was he actually going to launch a sneak attack from behind, but using reverse psychology to make him too scared to look behind him?

I'll take a look! Just one glance, fast, nothing will happen!

Liu Hao once again carefully checked in front of him and to the left and right, and then with a sudden flick of his mouse, his camera view quickly spun around, scanning the surroundings behind him. No Boundless Sea. Liu Hao let out a breath, and his view quickly returned to the original position.

Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

At this moment, Boundless Sea attacked. His position had indeed been right behind Liu Hao's character. How could such a fast glance be enough to check behind all the possible spots of cover? Fang Rui, as soon as Liu Hao finished glancing around and let himself relax, launched his charged Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

Qi energy was silent, but the charged Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow carried the character with it. The sound of the air colliding and splitting around him instantly resounded.

Liu Hao instantly smelled that something was wrong. He didn't even bothering turning around again, he just directly had his character roll and dodge. With his fluctuating mood, going from tense to relax to suddenly tense again, his controls would naturally be unsteady. Fang Rui seized this one moment. The Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow carried the qi and the character blasting forward. The rolling Spellblade, Liu Hao's character Absent Sun, was directly hit by this attack.

It was very rare to see blood from a Qi Master attack!

Bright red sprayed from Absent Sun's mouth. This was typically the sign of heavy internal injuries. The attack didn't stop there - Fang Rui continued with his familiar flurry of brutal and powerful attacks, and Absent Sun's initial 17% lead was quickly erased.

The cheers of the Happy fans reached a new high.

For the fans to put in the effort, they had to see the player's results. Only a beautiful performance could ultimately ignite the fans' support. Fang Rui slaughtered his way toward a 1v3. Liu Hao? Everyone saw how he was sent spinning in circles from Fang Rui's trash talk attack. Not openly mocking him too much was already a sign of his special relationship to this crowd.

But even if the fans were nostalgic, Fang Rui was already continuing his trash talking.

"I said so many times that I was behind you, why didn't you believe me? How many times do you want me to say it? Give me a number!" Fang Rui continued to enrich the contents of the chat channel.

Chapter 1277: The Greatest Margin in History

Fang Rui's trash talk was brazenly thrown into the public chat, but his character Boundless Sea? After completing this combo of attacks and discovering that Liu Hao had adjusted fairly quickly, he didn't continue with the opportunity and instantly tried to retreat.

"Don't run!" Liu Hao very heroically yelled this in the chat to show that he hadn't been beaten senseless by Fang Rui. As soon as his Spellblade Absent Sun stood steady on the ground, he sent out an Earthquake Sword. Unfortunately, Boundless Sea had already rolled away, hiding himself behind a giant boulder over there.

The opponent was the master of playing dirty, so of course Liu Hao didn't dare have Absent Sun directly chase him. His character moved horizontally first, pulling enough of a distance between them before charging towards that direction.

As expected, Boundless Sea was indeed gathering qi behind that boulder, but when he saw that Liu Hao was prepared, he could only helplessly give up the attack.

"So careful! Scared?" Fang Rui said in the chat.

"If you're a man then stop running!" Liu Hao shouted.

"Can't. I'm very scared of you." Fang Rui's reply seemed quite refreshing, but anyone could tell that this was a joke. Words that might otherwise be welcoming to hear sounded mocking from him. And Fang Rui's actions followed his words; as he spoke, he had Boundless Sea move away. He clearly had no intentions of fighting Liu Hao directly.

But even though he ran away, he didn't run too far away. He continued to circle around the boulder, as though prepared to go around and around with Liu Hao.

This sort of technique was a bit cheap, but coming from a dirty player, everyone thought it was very reasonable. Liu Hao was sorely tempted to use a Wave Formation to cover that whole area, but he also feared that while he was casting, Boundless Sea would suddenly jump out and ambush him. After deliberating for a while, Absent Sun came forward, but he didn't chase. He only crept a bit closer to the rock, checking his left and the right, his hand on his short sword, ready to act at a moment's notice. Liu Hao was prepared to sit here and wait for his target. Whether Fang Rui continued to circle around clockwise, or suddenly reverse and go counterclockwise, he would just wait here.

But he waited and waited, and there was no trace of Boundless Sea. Fang Rui's trash talk popped up in the match channel yet again. "Huh, what's going on, how come you're not chasing me? Didn't you tell me not to run?"

Liu Hao felt like spitting blood. This guy, did he just leave after circling around the boulder? And now, had he already circled around behind him?

Liu Hao was just about to turn around in a hurry, but in that instant, he was suddenly alert. He had been carefully watching his left and the right. He felt that in this short span of time, there was no way that Fang Rui could have controlled Boundless Sea to circle behind him without his noticing.

He almost fooled me!

Liu Hao huffed a breath. But he couldn't guess Fang Rui's plans right now. Was he trying to use his words to paralyze him, and actually taking a very long path to circle around him? Or was he still hiding behind that boulder, prepared to launch an attack on him?

Liu Hao couldn't wait around like this forever. He had Absent Sun move back away from the boulder, using the same strategy as before to pull apart the distance, and then, use this increased field of view to check behind the boulder.

He immediately saw that indeed, Boundless Sea was hiding right behind the boulder, his hands cupped before him, gathering qi again, waiting to sneak attack!

This bastard!

Liu Hao was furious. This was an exact repeat of what had just happened before! Good thing he stayed calm, otherwise who knew what could have happened.

Fang Rui? His same strategy was once again broken by the opponent. He simply tossed a "Huh, you found me again" into the chat, and then twisted and continue to circle clockwise around the boulder.

Liu Hao was about to go crazy. Who the fuck designed this map! Throwing this stupid goddamned rock right here! It gives opportunities to these kinds of guys, and the quality of matches goes way down!

Of course Liu Hao thought this way, but the live audience was swimming in a sea of amusement. Perhaps this match wasn't thrilling or intense to draw people in, but they burst into laughter watching this teasing situation.

And now, Fang Rui was doing the same thing for the third time. How would Liu Hao respond!

Absent Sun raised his short sword and began to cast. Electric Wave Formation!

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea had circled around behind the boulder, meaning that he, too, could only guess at Liu Hao's actions. Only in the final instant of a Wave Formation cast was there any sound, and this time, Liu Hao bet that the opponent wouldn't anticipate this.

His bet was correct!

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea didn't reveal himself. The accumulated electricity on Absent Sun's sword ultimately condensed into spheres on the surface of the boulder before him.

By the time the zapping sounds were audible, the electric sphere were already formed. With a flash, they were released, flowing all around. If there was a target, they would automatically lock on; if not, they would wander about freely. Liu Hao was, after all, a Spellblade who had entered the All-Stars. Even if he didn't see the target, from the flow of electricity he could draw many conclusions.

No target!

Liu Hao was shocked. This meant that Boundless Sea wasn't in range for the Wave Formation, then his position now, it must be…

Liu Hao's mind quickly outlined the range of Electric Wave Formation. His gaze settled on the scenery in front of him, and Absent Sun rushed forward.

His view widened as he pulled away, and indeed there was no sign of Boundless Sea, but there…

Behind the boulder, there was a crack just large enough to fit one person, looking like a collection of shadows. Liu Hao's pupil contracted. As an expert Spellblade, he was very clear on the quirks of all the Spellblade's skills. If there was such a crack in range of an Electric Wave Formation, there was a high chance that a character could hide there and avoid damage.

Liu Hao wasn't entirely unfamiliar with this map, but did this boulder really hide such a detail? Liu Hao wasn't sure. But now, he saw this, and immediately guessed that Boundless Sea must be right there.

Unfortunately, it was already too late.

This time, he hadn't made any preparations or calculated out any space before having Absent Sun charge forward to check behind the boulder. Seeing that crack, in the time it took for his brain to click-click-click and flash through these thoughts, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea had already attacked.

Liu Hao had guessed correctly. Boundless Sea was right there.

Landmine Quake!

Only Fang Rui's hands exposed themselves from the crack, and by the time they were exposed they'd already slapped against the ground. Qi spread along the earth, and Absent Sun had no time to dodge and was sent flying into the air. Boundless Sea no longer played dirty, shooting out like an arrow, his body like wind, carrying qi and slamming into Absent Sun's body.

Another combo of powerful attacks.

Absent Sun's health slid downwards, and the Happy fans in the crowd whooshed alive with applause.

"1v3!" they continued to scream, and Wind Howl's fans had already shut their mouths. The vice-captain in whom they'd trusted and believed didn't seem to stand much of a chance against this dirty-playing Fang Rui. This was entirely like the first and second battles, with Fang Rui firmly in control of the battle rhythm. If this continued, it wouldn't even be a question of victory, it would be… this time, by how large of a margin would Fang Rui win this 1v3?

Up until now, Boundless Sea hadn't even lost any health yet in this third battle, while Absent Sun's health had plummeted. Boundless Sea's 83% health was now in the lead. And completing a 1v3 also often involved the problem of running out of mana, but it seemed that Boundless Sea was fine on that end as well. Fang Rui's attacks were simply too efficient. When he attacked, his attacks were always effective, so his mana usage was very efficient. He had plenty of mana left to finish this battle.

But for the audience, all they cared about was victory, they couldn't care about such details right now. Those in the live crowd, those watching online, they watched as Fang Rui went back and forth with his harassment, ultimately grinding Liu Hao's Absent Sun to death. Liu Hao did display some of the skill befitting an All-Star, taking away 15% of Boundless Sea's health, a better performance than the previous two Wind Howl players, but that was all.

1v3 completed, 32% health lost. This was the final answer Fang Rui gave. The stadium hollered and cheered, not resting even as Fang Rui came down offstage and returned to his seat in Happy's player area.

1v3. Happy's Tang Rou had once wanted to do this, and failed, but now, her teammate Fang Rui accomplished it. Many of the reporters at the stadium were so excited they couldn't even sit still. They could hardly wait for the match to finish, they wanted desperately to interview right there. But of course they knew that this was impossible, so most reporters calmed down, flipping through their data and making preparations for the interviews post-match. In the midst of this, Chang Xian of Esports Home, after looking through every single 1v3 in ten years of group arena matches, he finally confirmed that Fang Rui had set a new record.

The record for the greatest margin in a 1v3 victory.

32% health lost. This result beat out the previous record set by Wang Jiexi in Season 4, 52% health lost, by a solid 20%.

It had to be emphasized was that Fang Rui was the first to appear in the group arena. With 32% health, he defeated three opponents at 100% health.

And Wang Jiexi at the time had been third in the group arena, the anchor. Even though the total reversal had been more exciting, no matter what, he was inferior both in terms of how much health he knocked away and in terms of how much he had remaining.

Fang Rui's record here was solid gold. It would be very, very difficult to surpass.

And the method he used to set this record was also worth remembering. He hadn't used an overwhelming advantage to slaughter the opponents all the way until the end. These three battles had all taken some time, they'd been played rather slowly. Fang Rui played dirty to create an abnormal efficiency. This sort of attack efficiency wasn't something that could be replicated by those hard-hitting players. When they directly collided with their opponents, there was inevitably some exchange, and the health that they ultimately sacrificed wouldn't be so low.

Playing dirty, the style that had received so many cold gazes, finally entered the history books with this record.

History's greatest margin of victory for a 1v3, was created by playing dirty!

This was Fang Rui's victory, and a victory for the dirty playstyle he'd persisted in using even after changing classes to Qi Master.

Chapter 1278: Mid-Match Break Wind Howl

A historic record! The majority of people who cared about this record were reporters. The viewers cared more about the feeling of a 10-0. Happy just needed to win the upcoming team competition.

The 1v3 chants in the group arena were replaced by 10-0s. The loyal fans who followed Wind Howl all the way to their away game were in low spirits. Liu Hao being dominated by Fang Rui wasn't a small blow to them. They had originally been hoping for Liu Hao to turn the tables with an astonishing 1v3 and show them their team's might! But they couldn't see any sort of fighting spirit in their vice-captain. Liu Hao looked completely lost facing Fang Rui's dirty tricks.

Wind Howl's fans were quiet, very quiet.

Seeing the excited cheers from Happy's fans, they felt an unpleasant taste in their mouths. This exhilaration should have belonged to them! Because Fang Rui… didn't he used to be part of Team Wind Howl? Despite having switched classes to a Qi Master, his style was still very familiar to Wind Howl's loyal fans.

This was someone who had used to bring them joy, and now?

The Wind Howl banners created by the fans always flew in the air whether it was Wind Howl's home or away game, but right now, it seemed to be thrown aside, drooping in disappointment. Wind Howl's flag bearer looked dispirited. The others weren't worried about him though, because they knew that Fang Rui had been this person's favorite player. Fang Rui had been hard for him, and now, seeing Fang Rui complete a 1v3 against Wind Howl produced a feeling he couldn't describe with words.

How would the upcoming team competition go?

Team Wind Howl's loyal fans were unexpectedly feeling doubtful towards their own team.

Their captain and core, Tang Hao. The new generation Zhao Yuzhe who they had high hopes for. Lin Feng who they wanted to inherit Doubtful Demon. The super value Liu Hao who the team had gotten at an amazing price… in the individual competition and group arena, they seemed to have been crushed by opponents on an entirely different level than them. With these people making up the team, how could they hope to beat Happy? 　

Wind Howl's teamwork wasn't anything too praiseworthy! Wind Howl's own fans knew this point better than anyone else. As for Happy? Starting from Round 9, their team had yet to lose a single round. Was Happy a team their Wind Howl could beat?

The fans were doubtful, doubtful that their team could win this match, doubtful of their team's claim to be the champions this season. Wind Howl's win record this season wasn't as stable as last season's! Didn't the team say they would form an all-new team more compatible than before after letting Fang Rui go? An all-new team? Wind Howl could see it. The team had given up on the dirty style. The dirty tricks from before had turned into a more aggressive offensive.

Perhaps this style was more like a champion's. Apart from Blue Rain's deviation from the norm, the other champion teams had all given off this sort of grand aura. Wind Howl was trying hard to construct this aura, but did it really fit them?

The former Criminal Partners had never considered themselves as the strongest duo in the Alliance, but the fans always felt steady with them there. No matter how much of a crisis the team was in, they would always be confident about their team. But now? The team's win record was worse than last season's. The team was still within the playoffs zone, but how could they not be nervous about why? The current Wind Howl made them feel like there was something missing. This sort of mystery feeling really didn't feel good!

Wind Howl's most loyal fans were pacing back and forth. Wind Howl's players were also in low spirits.　　

In the individual competition, their core player Tang Hao was crushed by Ye Xiu and then their other two players lost as well.　

In the group arena, the team sent three strong players, but their former teammate Fang Rui took all of them down with just two thirds of his health.

How humiliating. The player you let go just casually cleaned up three players you had cultivated with the utmost care. Right now, the first thoughts that came to their mind were classic idioms like "have eyes but cannot see" or "buying a wooden box and returning the pearls"...

Team Wind Howl's players felt this embarrassment the most. What should they do? Beating their opponents would obviously be the greatest retaliation. However, Wind Howl's players had been beaten one after the other. It seemed like they couldn't break free from their losses. Only the remaining second-string players on the side busily circling around and around.

"What's going on? Have you guys gone stupid from losing?" Finally, someone spoke up.

Ruan Yongbin.

Wind Howl's Cleric.　　

Healers were never replaced in any team, so their status in the team was always relatively high. In addition to healers being rarely transferred, healers almost always held seniority.

Ruan Yongbin had been a part of Team Wind Howl for nearly six years. He had joined the team alongside Fang Rui. When Fang Rui left, Ruan Yongbin became Team Wind Howl's most senior member. He was the type of player who obeyed orders and didn't like to talk too much. However, seeing how the team's morale had been shaken and how the main players all looked like they had been swatted down like flies, he couldn't resist it anymore and finally spoke out.

Healers were only needed in the team competition, so the outcome of the individual rounds never impacted them as much as the others. They could always maintain a rational mind and watch from afar the morale of their teammates rise up and down in the individual rounds. As a result, for the most important team competition, a level-headed healer could always act as a stabilizing force for the team.

But unfortunately, Ruan Yongbin spoke too rarely in Wind Howl. He didn't fully utilize the special existence brought by his class's speciality. Everyone looked at him when he suddenly spoke out. Their eyes were completely filled with confusion. They didn't look like they had been enlightened in any way.

"The team competition hasn't been fought yet! Half the points are waiting to be taken by us. We can do this!" Ruan Yongbin tried his best to say words that he wasn't use to. Anyone could say this though. The logic was obvious. What was needed was a wake up call to break apart the doubt formed in the players during the individual rounds. However, Ruan Yongbin's wake up call didn't have enough power behind it. He was talking, and everyone was looking at him, but… morale? Their morale hadn't been ignited. Only Liu Hao clapped his hands and squeezed out a smile: "Yongbin, you're right! The match isn't over yet. We still have five points to take. Why does everyone look like we've already lost?"

Liu Hao was the vice-captain. His popularity among the fans this season wasn't bad. His relations with other people in the team weren't bad either. His words were clearly more effective than Ruan Yongbin's. Ruan Yongbin let out a sigh of relief and looked at Liu Hao with gratitude. He was glad that their vice-captain could maintain a level-head and look at the match with reason.　　

Liu Hao had a smile filled with reason on the surface, but inside, he was feeling extremely annoyed. After walking off stage, he saw the expressions of his teammates and the silence from Wind Howl's loyal fans and knew his performance had disgusted quite a few people. However, Liu Hao's strength was his practically cruel ability to fake it. He could cover his true feelings well and then push the most suitable attitude for the situation onto the surface.　

As a result, he had been depressed and silent along with the other players. But when Ruan Yongbin spoke out while the others didn't respond, he could force himself and wake himself up. He acted like a vice-captain and started encouraging the others following Ruan Yongbin's example.

"Look, our fans, our fans who traveled so far to support us are feeling bitter and in low spirits! How could we disappoint them? Everyone, hurry up and get your spirits up. Let's get our Wind Howl's banner flying into the air again! We lost quite a few points, but it's just five points. Next, if we win just this upcoming team competition, we can win five points. Then, the score will be 5 to 5. Is that a loss? No! If the away team wins five points, shouldn't that be considered a win? Right now, we still have a chance to win!" Liu Hao put up his thumbs and emphasize that they just needed to win this team competition.

"What bullshit!" Wind Howl's captain, Tang Hao, suddenly interrupted Liu Hao very rudely.　　

"Let alone five points, if we can win even one more point, we can't give it up!" Tang Hao grit his teeth.

"Captain Tang is right, we can't back down even if it was just one point," Liu Hao didn't appear to be unhappy with Tang Hao interrupting him. Instead, he immediately agreed with Tang Hao. Tang Hao had raised the team's morale to the peak.

"Let's go beat them!" Tang Hao shouted, "Don't tell me you're willing to let a certain someone slap our faces!"

It was obvious who he was pointing to. Taking a former hero of Wind Howl and pinning him as the enemy was a bit ugly. When an old veteran of the team like Ruan Yongbin heard these words, his expression turned unnatural. Ling Jingyan and Fang Rui had left the team peacefully, but how could those inside the team not understand? This had nothing to do with what was right or wrong. It was the choice for the team to grow. For this choice, the team should feel sympathy for those that had been given up. Team Wind Howl shouldn't have these negative feelings towards them.

Fang Rui had won the group arena and had embarrassed Wind Howl, but this was competition. There was only victory. Nothing else mattered. It wasn't like they could hope that Fang Rui would throw the match for them.

Tang Hao unadorned despise made Ruan Yongbin feel quite unhappy. But what about the other players? Zhao Yuzhe? Lin Feng? They had just been humiliated by Fang Rui. Tang Hao's out-of-line attitude had ignited their fighting spirits.

Chapter 1279: Cowards

"Win!" With Tang Hao's final shout, although the mentality of Wind Howl's players weren't yet in unison, their low morale had reignited to a certain extent.

"It seems to be quite lively over there at Wind Howl." At Happy's side, the players were finishing up their strategy prep for the team competition. Chen Guo liked to listen on the side, but every time she listened, she would feel dizzy and her attention would run astray. Trying to follow their discussion on strategy was hard. The poor Chen Guo could only look around and noticed Wind Howl suddenly fire up, yelling and shouting fervently.

Everyone in Happy had noticed the shouts from over there too, and when they looked at them, they just happened to meet gazes with Wind Howl. Compared to Happy's relaxed and casual glance, Wind Howl seemed to be focused on a certain individual.

"Hm, it looks like our last minute changes were very necessary," Ye Xiu said.

The others looked towards Fang Rui. Happy's changes in the team competition were on Fang Rui. Today, he was the main character.

"No problem." Fang Rui gave two thumbs up to everyone.

"Then… let's get ready!" Ye Xiu nodded his head and said.

After the break was over, the referee called for them, and the players participating in the team competition started walking towards the stage.

Team Happy: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, and their sixth player, Steamed Bun.　

Team Wind Howl: Tang Hao, Liu Hao, Zhao Yuzhe, Lin Feng, Ruan Yonbgin, and their sixth player, Guo Yang.　　

Team Wind Howl's roster had undergone a transformation within these past two years. Just looking at the current line up, apart from Ruan Yongbin, no one else in the team had played on the team for three years yet. From this perspective, Zhao Yuzhe was actually the most experienced among them. Tang Hao and Guo Yang had only been a part of the team for two years. Liu Hao and Lin Feng had joined the team last summer. After this season, they would complete their first full year with the team.

An entirely new player roster meant a change in Wind Howl's original tactical style, which included their class composition. Both Brawler and Thief were still important, but their stable Knight position gradually fell to a secondary position this season. Liu Hao's Spellblade entered the team. Guo Yang's Qi Master joined the team last season and his position hadn't been too stable until this season, where he finally became a part of the main roster. Guo Yang rejecting Ye Xiu's invite to join Happy didn't seem to be a bad choice. He had at least established a firm position for himself in Team Wind Howl.

Of the total twelve players between the two teams, three of the classes were repeats.

The Brawlers, Tang Hao and Steamed Bun. The Qi Masters, Fang Rui and Guo Yang. The Clerics, An Wenyi and Ruan Yongbin.

But because Steamed Bun and Guo Yang were the sixth players, the starting lineup only had Clerics as repeats. As a healer class, two Clerics weren't anything rare.

The two teams walked onto the stage and greeted one another. The Wind Howl players, who lost in the individual rounds, clearly wanted revenge. The smell of gunpowder was heavy. The referee watched the two team's players closely. After confirming that neither side said anything out of bounds or made any violent physical contact, he gestured for the players to go to their player booths. The team competition was about to start.

Wind Howl's loyal fans had lost all hope, but after noticing how their team had suddenly spirited up, their energy returned too. Wind Howl's banner began flying around in the Xiaoshan Stadium again. The needs of the fans were quite simple. They didn't need to see any crazy results. Just their attitude alone was enough to make them feel like their support wasn't wasted.

After the countdown, the two teams loaded into the map, and the team competition began.　

The map was the Peili Town Market.

Peili Town was a small town in the Glory continent. And this marketplace had been taken straight out of this small town as a map. In reality, around ninety percent of the Glory PvP maps were taken from places on the Glory continent. The map's design already existed, so when taking the map, only its usage needed to be evaluated.

The Peili Town Market was considered a city map. Streets, different height buildings, and indoor and outdoor playable areas were common in these maps. The Peili Town Market had relatively fewer outdoor areas. Just the market plaza took up nearly half the map. This plaza wasn't just an empty field, and the market naturally had all sorts of booths and goods scattered around. The durability of these goods were rather low though, so the entire market could be seen as destructible.

The starting five characters of the two teams spawned at opposing corners.

Happy - Unspecialized Lord Grim, Launcher Dancing Rain, Qi Master Boundless Sea, Ghostblade One Inch Ash, Cleric Little Cold Hands.

Wind Howl - Brawler Demon Subduer, Spellblade Absent Sun, Elementalist Beautiful Light, Thief Doubtful Demon, and Cleric Soul Healer.

As soon as the match began, Wind Howl displayed their reinstated spirits. The entire team went into formation and ran straight for the center of the map.

The Wind Howl fans nowadays were no stranger to this scene, but in the past, when the Criminal Partners were there, Wind Howl rarely chose such a direct opening. However, the current Wind Howl would almost always rush at their opponents to crush them no matter who their opponents were.

In truth, the fans had also liked this sort of bearing in the beginning. Who didn't like to see their team destroy the opponents? In the first five rounds this season, Wind Howl had crushed everything in their path, dominating their opponents each round. However, their opponents these five rounds were Conquering Cloud, Radiant, Lightly, Bright Green, and Miracle... not a single one of them were strong teams. Wind Howl's beautiful opening was somewhat stifled by their schedule.

In Round 6, Wind Howl faced Samsara. Their momentum suddenly hit an iron wall.

Then, in Round 7, they were decimated in the team competition by Tyranny.

Round 8, wrecked by Blue Rain in the team competition.

Round 9, wiped out by 301 in the team competition.

Round 10, Wind Howl faced Seaside and swallowed them up.

Of these ten rounds, Wind Howl immediately became the bad name among strong teams. They won against weak teams, but as soon as they met against anyone strong, they crumbled...

Luckily, in Round 11 and Round 12, Wind Howl beat Misty Rain and Void, proving themselves. But in Round 13, Hundred Blossoms washed them. In Round 14, Thunderclap stomped on them again. Round 15, they suffered an embarrassing defeat to Royal Style. Round 16 and Round 17, they matched against Heavenly Swords and Parade, and Wind Howl once again stood back up.

Wind Howl was among the top eight because they were clearly superior to the weaker teams, not losing points they shouldn't be losing. However, as soon as they faced anyone even a tiny bit strong, their team instantly collapsed. Were they a strong team? Right now, this title had been knocked off of Wind Howl. Players were calling them cowards, their knees turning soft as soon as they encountered a strong team.

This round, they had run into a strong opponent after bullying two weak teams. It was time to prove that they weren't cowards. But right now, the team had been swept clean in the individual rounds. If they lost the team competition, they would have zero points. It wasn't possible to go any lower than that.

Even so, Team Wind Howl displayed their usual tyrannical and dominating bearing. The five characters formed a standard offensive formation and headed straight for the center, the Peili Town Market Plaza.

With the plaza taking up half of the map, all sorts of booths and goods were scattered and smashed apart. Even the player cameras became messy.

Zhao Yuzhe received an order and immediately had his Beautiful Light jump towards a pile of bags to the side. With a few hops, he reached the top, and before he could look down carefully, gunshots rang.

The gunshots were loud and clear. Wind Howl instantly figured out the general location of the gunfire and immediately pushed towards that direction, including Beautiful Light, who had jumped onto the pile of bags to lure in the attacks.

Zhao Yuzhe's offensive prowess was exceptional. As soon as the gunshots rang, he quickly adjusted his character's line of sight and instantly Teleported in that direction. He escaped and pushed forward. The one being attacked instead became the attacker.

"How fierce!" At this moment, the dirty master Fang Rui's trash talk popped up mysteriously in the chat.

Wind Howl's offensive had considered the surroundings too. Seeing the sudden trash talk, the five characters split the work and surveyed the surroundings to ascertain Fang Rui's position.　　

However, he wasn't there… there was only one person in their sights, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim.　　

An ambush!

In this situation, anyone would have thought that. Lord Grim was just bait. Happy's other characters were probably lying in wait in this complicated terrain. 　

However, Wind Howl didn't retreat. Continue forward!

To be able to set up such an ambush this quickly meant they didn't bring their healer.

It was a very logical deduction. Wind Howl had rushed here very fast, but if Happy could set up an ambush before they arrived, it could only mean that Happy had let go of the healer, who would slow down the team.

An ambush without a healer? What's there to be scared of!

Wind Howl's captain Tang Hao thought like this, so their momentum didn't falter. Liu Hao had his misgivings though. He had wanted them to slow down a bit and be more cautious, but seeing Tang Hao's firmness, he didn't much more of it and followed along with his captain's pace. But at this moment, a spinning blaze of fire fell towards the center of Wind Howl's formation.

Heat-Seeking Missile!

"Dodge!" Liu Hao typed a warning instinctively. His Absent Sun scrambled for his life towards outside of this Heat-Seeking Missile's range. Tang Hao's Demon Subduer raised his arms and threw a Brick, which looked weak, in comparison to the missile. However, a Brick was still much bigger than a bullet, so it was much easier to hit a target with it. And as it turned out, the Heat-Seeking Missile was smacked aside by the Brick.

None of the other Wind Howl players had moved. Only Liu Hao's Absent Sun had sped out of there. Seeing the danger averted, his face turned burning hot, though he didn't forget to call out in the public chat: "Our captain is mighty."

"If you've got the time to spout useless words, why don't you use it on moving your character instead?" The praise that he had typed into the public chat was only met with Ye Xiu's disdain.

Chapter 1280: Not Focused Enough

Liu Hao's eyes twitched a few times, and even a few old fans of Team Excellent Era felt some deja vu at that moment.

Ye Xiu, Liu Hao, this pair of old teammates had already become enemies, but their back-and-forth in the public chatl was reminiscent of their time back in Excellent Era.

Liu Hao would never forget the icy contempt that Ye Xiu showed towards his well-meaning compliment.

To Liu Hao, calling out a beautiful play by a teammate was a way of boosting the morale of the team, but Ye Xiu maintained that his praise was too excessive.

Praise was also a form of encouragement, who would feel that such things were excessive? On top of that, it wasn't as if he didn't have any situational awareness. He'd never left an opening because of it, so wasn't it fine?

But even if this was the case, Ye Xiu still maintained that he wasn't focused enough.

Yes, not focused enough, this was the flaw that Ye Xiu always pointed out when it came to Liu Hao. From the time he became a player in Team Excellent Era, to the time when he became vice-captain of Excellent Era.

"If you've got the time to spout useless words, why don't you use it on moving your character instead"

When he saw this line, Liu Hao was infuriated. He hadn't delayed his inputs at all due to these few words that he'd typed, what did Ye Xiu expect from him?

Liu Hao exploded with fury, and Absent Sun pounced towards Lord Grim more violently than anyone else. He was originally someone who could control his emotions well, but deep in every person's heart, they had certain inviolable taboos. These words that Ye Xiu said had effectively stabbed at a scar that had lasted many years. In the past, he could only brood about it silently, but now, he could finally use his actions on the battlefield to speak for himself. He wanted to tell Ye Xiu: controlling or not controlling your character for a moment isn't anything important!

Earthquake Sword!

Absent Sun swept out with his sword, directly destroying a merchant's stall in front of him. Upon clearing this path for himself, Absent Sun trampled on the wreckage and charged forwards.

Demon Subduer and Doubtful Demon, the two strongest characters in Wind Howl, followed behind Absent Sun and advanced through the trail of wreckage.

Once upon a time, they had been called the Criminal Partners, but now, this name was on the verge of becoming history. In the Alliance's voting for Best Partner, these two characters that had fought side-by-side for so many years weren't even grouped together. Being partners wasn't something that could be achieved simply by being in the same team, if not, the Best Partner selection would be selecting an entire team of five people at once.

Partnership wasn't something that the Alliance had ever clearly defined, but going by the results of previous years, these "partners" were usually the pair of core players in a team who had the most rapport, and their teamwork had to be extremely outstanding.

In today's Wind Howl, Demon Subduer was a core character, just as before, and he was just as outstanding as before, but Doubtful Demon's place in the team had gotten weaker and weaker. Brawler and Thief, this pair was no longer the centerpiece to Wind Howl's playstyle. Nowadays, who stood beside Demon Subduer as his greatest helper?

Fire Wave Formation!

Absent Sun slashed out again, directly cutting a path through the obstacles in his way. After sending out consecutive skills, Absent Sun's movements slowed down. Demon Subduer overtook him from the side, stepped in the middle of the flames of Fire Wave Formation and charged forward.

An extremely beautiful covering play.

Anyone would admit as much.

The timing of Fire Wave Formation and the charge of Demon Subduer was coordinated beautifully, and the enveloping blaze gave Demon Subduer a temporary layer of protection. At this time, anyone who wanted to attack him from close range would first have to suffer the damage of Fire Wave Formation.

But if it was from a long range…...

Boom boom boom!

Three shots sounded out, and Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain once again joined the fray.

When the Heat-Seeking Missile had been sent out earlier, everyone in Wind Howl had more or less figured out her position. She was very far away, and as such, was unsuitable as a breakthrough point, so everyone continued to focus on Lord Grim. As for Su Mucheng's continued harassment from afar, Wind Howl could be said to have foreseen it. When the cannon shots rang out, Zhao Yuzhe's Beautiful Light had already pointed with his staff, instantly creating an Ice Wall at the side of the Fire Wave Formation.

The brilliant combination of fire and ice gave Demon Subduer complete protection from all sides. The Anti-Tank Missiles that Dancing Rain fired over were a low-level skill, without enough power to shatter the Ice Wall, and if Su Mucheng were to use another skill, Demon Subduer's charge would have been completed.

Following the flames of Fire Wave Formation, Demon Subduer had rushed close to Lord Grim, and reached the effective range for a Brawler's control skills.

Sand Toss!

Demon Subduer flicked his wrist and threw the skill out.

Lord Grim simply opened his umbrella to block the attack.

Screensaver!

When Lord Grim opened the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, everyone immediately thought of this point. The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's Shield Form was so large it was borderline criminal, to the point where it could not only hide attacks, but could even hide another player who could attack from the side.

Tang Hao had obviously seen that there was no one at Lord Grim's side at the time, but he still didn't dare to attack head-on. Instead, he moved horizontally and adjusted his angle of attack, leaving the head-on assault to Liu Hao.

Liu Hao quickly grasped his intent, and Absent Sun walked forwards a few steps before attacking. As he directly faced Lord Grim's open umbrella, he sent out an Ice Wave Formation without any hesitation. He was able to maintain a more mid-ranged distance when fighting, so he didn't have to worry as much about what kind of tricks Ye Xiu was hiding behind that umbrella.

At this time, Lin Feng's Doubtful Demon had already activated Stealth, creeping behind enemy lines. Even though he was a Battle Thief, he wouldn't completely abandon the sneaky skills of a Thief.

What about Zhao Yuzhe? At this time, he had spotted a cargo crate and was controlling Beautiful light to jump on top of it. When looking down from an elevation, he would have a wider field of view and a larger area which he could attack.

When he'd jumped halfway and his field of view had expanded a little, he spotted a Ghostblade behind a pile of cargo sacks, the Taichi in his hands already charged with a Phantom Ghost's power.

"Careful, there's a Phantom Demon!" Zhao Yuzhe shouted as Beautiful Light casted a Piercing Lightning towards him.

But at this time, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had already completed the cast for his ghost boundary and an Ice Boundary instantly formed, protecting Lord Grim. Of the three characters from Wind Howl that had charged up, two were already inside the Ice Boundary.

Tang Hao's reactions were swift, directly using a Powerful Knee Strike to leap out of the Ice Boundary. On the other hand, Lin Feng was humiliated; after leaving Stealth, Doubtful Demon's movements were slowed, and he was unable to escape the sudden Ice Boundary in time, immediately being frozen into a large ice block.

One Inch Ash had successfully casted his Ice Boundary, but he couldn't avoid Beautiful Light's Piercing Lightning in time.

Piercing Lightning hit, and as it did damage, it also informed everyone in Wind Howl of the Phantom Demon's whereabouts. Just as Zhao Yuzhe was preparing to attack once again, there was already cannon fire incoming. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain had gotten control over a high vantage point and started to interrupt his attacks.

In the team competition, the players would all suppress each other and interrupt attacks, so there was rarely a situation in which a player could capitalize on one successful attack and complete a combo, unlike in the individual competitions.

Beautiful Light's attack was interrupted, but Tang Hao's Demon Subduer had already started rushing over to the spot where One Inch Ash was concealing himself, while Liu Hao's Absent Sun continued his assault on Lord Grim.

In terms of their positioning, Absent Sun was actually closer to One Inch Ash than Demon Subduer was. But at that time, Lord Grim was under the protection of the Ice Boundary. While the Brawler did have ways to attack at a medium range, if he was unable to attack at close range, the control that he could exert was insufficient. It was incomparable to the Spellblade, which was specialized in mid-range fighting, and so Tang Hao abandoned the closer target to seek the one that was farther away, attacking One Inch Ash while leaving Lord Grim to Liu Hao.

Doubtful Demon was frozen by the Ice Boundary, Demon Subduer had gone to attack the hiding One Inch Ash, Beautiful Light had been suppressed by Dancing Rain's firepower…... As he looked at Lord Grim, not far away from him, Liu Hao suddenly had a bad premonition. He could smell the prelude to a violent storm!

The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella... dipped down very slightly.

Was it about to come!

Liu Hao opened his eyes wide. For now, disregarding what attack Lord Grim was going to use, he sent out a Wave Formation, but immediately afterwards, an arrow of blood spurted out from Absent Sun's neck. Absent Sun was then lifted from the ground and thrown into the Ice Boundary.

Fling was a grab skill, and there was no way to prevent the character from being thrown. Absent Sun was thrown into the Ice Boundary and his speed immediately dropped. As he raised his camera upwards, he saw Lord Grim, who had appeared behind him.

Shadow Clone Technique?

Liu Hao had already realized it at this point, but if it was Shadow Clone Technique, it required hand seals to be cast. Lord Grim was holding the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella in front of him the whole time, how did he manage to form the hand seals?

Liu Hao only held his suspicions for a moment, before immediately thinking of the time when the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella dipped down very slightly.

That motion wasn't the hand seals. Instead, Lord Grim had momentarily let go of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, finishing the hand seals in the blink of an eye before grabbing the umbrella again...

To be able to instantly think of this after the situation had occurred, Liu Hao could be considered to be very skilled. Ye Xiu also immediately praised Liu Hao, "Your ability to read the match is extremely outstanding, but you're always unable to put one hundred percent of your attention into the match. There are far too many other things you're concerned about..."

It was these cliché line again!

Liu Hao was infuriated, but his character was in danger and he really had no ability to type something out to fight Ye Xiu verbally. The Spellblade clearly had a stronger Spirit stat than the Thief, so his Absent Sun had only been slowed upon entering the Ice Boundary and not frozen solid unlike Doubtful Demon. He had to think of a plan to quickly escape the boundary, but with Lord Grim eyeing him so closely, would he have the opportunity to do so?

At the end of the day, Lord Grim suddenly turned his head.

Liu Hao froze.

Crap!

He suddenly realized, Cleric, their Cleric! After the sudden attack earlier, they had been ambushed by Happy in the east. The west was completely barren and had eluded all of their attention. Cleric, they had completely forgotten to protect their own Cleric.

But... where was he?

Liu Hao froze again. Ruan Yongbin's Soul Healer should not have been far behind them, but how come they couldn't even see a shadow of his figure now?

Had he hidden somewhere? That guy was really dirty!

Liu Hao thought about it, this Wind Howl, they truly deserved to be called a dirty team, this attitude had affected everyone on the team, aside from their new players. Ruan Yongbin, he might only be a Cleric, but he still had a dirty playstyle. The only thing was, the master of dirty play who had influenced everyone in Wind Howl was now on Happy! Where was Fang Rui? Where was Boundless Sea?

Liu Hao suddenly realized, aside from trash talking once at the start, this guy had never appeared at all.

"!!!"

Just as he thought that, in Wind Howl's team chat, a cry for help from their Cleric suddenly appeared…...

Chapter 1281: Lost Direction

Liu Hao was skilled at reading the situation. He was the first to sense something abnormal: their Cleric, who had hidden himself, and that trash talker Fang Rui, who was nowhere to be seen.

A second later, a string of exclamation marks flashed into Team Wind Howl's chat.

"!!!!!"

The exclamation marks came from Soul Healer; this was Wind Howl's agreed upon rescue signal.

Wind Howl saw it and turned around, but no one was able to find Soul Healer's whereabouts.

Dirty!

Zhao Yuzhe immediately thought of this word. He hated this word. Even when the team had featured dirtiness as their style, he had never tried to understand it. He only felt thankful that Wind Howl ended up changing styles, discarding the word dirty. However, it hadn't been eliminated thoroughly enough. There were still hints of this word in their team.

For example, Ruan Yongbin had his character hide like a dirty thief. Zhao Yuzhe wanted to help him, but he couldn't find him...

Annoying annoying annoying!

Zhao Yuzhe was irritated at Ruan Yongbin's dirtiness. Their captain Tang Hao, Liu Hao, and Lin Feng weren't able to immediately locate Soul Healer either. Reading an agreed upon rescue signal was easy, but no one had any synergy with Ruan Yongbin's dirty style. They symbolized the new Wind Howl, while Ruan Yongbin was a Cleric player, left over from the old Wind Howl. Nearly all the other old players had been replaced, but who would have thought that the healer, a character with a different role than others, was unexpectedly going off beat from the rest of the team because of the old style. And Happy's Fang Rui had persisted with this old style, so he was able to accurately locate Ruan Yongbin's hiding spot.

Ruan Yongbin had been caught by Fang Rui, so he had sent a rescue signal. However, none of his teammates were able to find him. It looked like a hilariously stupid situation, but it let everyone realize just what kind of team the current Wind Howl was.　　

Outstanding players? Powerful characters?

Wind Howl possessed these, but whenever they encountered anyone strong, they just couldn't win. Why?　　

Now, everyone understood.

Team Wind Howl was still experiencing the hardships of going through a transformation. However, Wind Howl's deep-rooted style wasn't so easy to get rid of. Just letting go of the master of playing dirty, Fang Rui, and changing their Doubtful Demon to a battle Thief weren't enough to complete this transformation.

Wind Howl wanted to give up on their roots. For a team, this was no different than demolishing an old building and constructing a new one. Last season, their determination hadn't been too clear. With Fang Rui at the head, the team had someone who played dirty as a part of their main roster, who was displaying the soul of the old team. With the support of the others in the team, Wind Howl had looked quite strong last season.

Then, Wind Howl's new core became Tang Hao. He didn't realize the strength of Fang Rui's supportive play. In contrast, he and Zhao Yuzhe detested this playstyle. He couldn't see the soul of the team and only emphasized his own strength. He wanted his own strength to be magnified a step further, and this dirty style wasn't the support he liked. He was the captain. He was the core. The team revolved around him, and he didn't like this dirty style support. As a result, even the master of playing dirty, Fang Rui, lost his spot on the team.

Fang Rui left, and Team Wind Howl added in a whole bunch of new players. These new players, who revolved around Tang Hao, weren't dirty at all. The rest, who were good at playing around a dirty style as a foundation, had been pushed to the second-string. What waited for them was either to leave like Fang Rui did, or to change their styles to the new one.

Letting go of playing dirty didn't necessarily spell their downfall. Many outstanding powerhouses in the Alliance didn't rely on playing dirty to win. But the problem was that once Wind Howl chose to abandon the style they had been familiar with, did their new playstyle have a clear direction?

An aggressive style centered around Tang Hao?

This seemed to be their plan, but how should they bring this plan into reality? How should the players work together? What responsibilities should each character have? When fighting, how should they coordinate their attacks?

Thinking back to Wind Howl's matches this season, everyone discovered that while Team Wind Howl had gotten rid of the old style, their new style had yet to be realized either. A new and mature tactical system hadn't been formed.

Facing weak teams, they could overwhelm their opponents through superior individual skill. However, when facing strong teams, without a clear tactical system, there were holes everywhere. Wind Howl's individual round results were quite good because their players and characters were strong. However, their team competition record was a disaster, all because their style hadn't fully matured yet.

They couldn't find Soul Healer?

Maybe they could blame it on not eliminating the dirty style thoroughly enough. However, it also showcased the mess Team Wind Howl was in. Champions? Right now, no one dared to bring this word up along with Wind Howl. Becoming the champions wasn't as simple as having individually strong characters and players.

Wind Howl was like a fly without a head. They couldn't find Soul Healer's position, but they could still ask in the chat. Ruan Yongbin saw the question and replied back with his coordinates. Rescue had finally arrived. However, Happy had taken advantage of Wind Howl's confusion to attack wildly, smacking Wind Howl into a sorry state. Wind Howl had no idea what they should be doing.

Although, when Zhao Yuzhe, Lin Feng, and Liu Hao, the three who had been 1v3ed by Fang Rui in the group arena, saw Fang Rui's Boundless Sea, their target was very clear. But how dirty was Fang Rui? How could he give them a chance to surround him? Seeing that he was outnumbered, he didn't even try to be brave and scurried off into the marketplace to play cat and mouse with the three.

Fang Rui now had the attention of three of them, how was that okay? Liu Hao quickly noticed the imbalance. However, Zhao Yuzhe was still chasing after him. Liu Hao gave him a reminder and all he received was a "I can handle him alone".

Liu Hao didn't agree with this reply, but he didn't immediately point it out, because he knew Zhao Yuzhe's personality. Saying "just you alone isn't enough" would certainly infuriate him. It would definitely have the opposite effect.

Liu Hao chose to stay silent. He and Lin Feng would provide support in other parts of the battle. Shortly afterwards, Zhao Yuzhe was ambushed by Fang Rui. Happy had even coordinated with Fang Rui and shifted targets. As a result, Zhao Yuzhe was now the one typing "!!!!" The entire team hurried over to rescue him. Liu Hao had predicted this outcome though, so he came to the rescue promptly.

"Good!" Zhao Yuzhe felt very thankful for Liu Hao's prompt rescue. Everyone had also seen Liu Hao save the situation at a key moment.

But...

"It looks like you were ready for it!" Ye Xiu rushed over from the side. Lord Grim used several movement skills in a row to instantly move to Liu Hao's Absent Sun. Such a fast response, such… Ye Xiu had been ready too.

Dancing Rain's artillery barrage, One Inch Ash's ghost boundaries, and even Happy's healer Little Cold Hands appeared in Liu Hao's sight. In an instant, an offensive formation had formed. Their target: Absent Sun.

It was a trap!

Liu Hao didn't hesitate and immediately typed "!!!" He didn't think he could break through the premeditated formation set up by Happy so easily. However, even if his teammates rescued him, what then? Wind Howl had to many openings. Happy just needed to pick one and attack their openings again and again, while Wind Howl ran around rescuing one after the other. Apart from the opening, Wind Howl had never showed the initiative once. 　　

"Fight!!!" Captain Tang Hao shouted. However, was Wind Howl's problem an issue that could be resolved through morale? Their individual players were good, but they weren't overwhelmingly strong to the point where they could just crush everything in their path through superior individual skill alone. What they lacked was teamwork.

Liu Hao's Absent Sun was the first to fall. To the viewers out there though, even in this losing situation, Liu Hao's performance had no lack of highlights. He had saved Wind Howl several times during crucial moments.

"If you could completely focus on the match, how would things have turned out?" But when he fell, Ye Xiu once again lectured him on that annoying old subject.

How am I supposed to focus more? Why are you so annoying, always blabbering? Do you really think that with your trash talk, people will think that I didn't perform well? Hilarious. Even though Wind Howl's going to lose, who could pick out anything wrong with my performance?

With one player dead, Wind Howl went into an even more passive state. From start to end, they had never taken the initiative even once. Wind Howl's loyal fans had seen their players march onto the stage in high spirits, but their opponents instantly tore them apart as if they were paper tigers.

If Wind Howl had lost an intense back and forth, even though the fans would still feel sad, they wouldn't feel downhearted. But Wind Howl seemed to have gone into the match full of confidence, yet they had never gained the upper hand from start to finish. The fans weren't able to find even a shred of hope.

The Wind Howl banner once again drooped down. That loyal fan responsible for the banner was reminiscing about the Team Wind Howl with the Criminal Partners. Even though that team hadn't placed as high on the rankings as the current Wind Howl, they had never made the fans lose all hope.

Matches needed to be won, but winning wasn't everything in a competition.

Team Wind Howl failed to win a single point nor did they perform well. All they seemed to have was high morale, but when they came onto the stage, they were like balloons and instantly burst apart.

How could this sort of team give us any sort of hope? Wind Howl's fans were suddenly at a loss. A team that currently qualified for the playoffs was unexpectedly making many people feel lost.

Chapter 1282: After Round 18

Wind Howl lost.

A thorough, bitter loss.

Even though their team competitions had always had the style of bullying the weak and fearing the strong, their individual round performances had always been quite good. They'd won two points against Samsara, four points against Tyranny, and three points against Blue Rain. Aside from Samsara, in which they'd been slightly weaker, against Tyranny and Blue Rain, Wind Howl had won the majority of the individual round points.

But when it came to the team competition? A team that lacked strategic focus was that much more vulnerable in front of powerful enemies. In the team competition, it was clear that passion and spirit weren't enough to win. And this time, Wind Howl hadn't even managed to win a victory in the individual rounds, either.

0-10. Wind Howl lost cleanly and completely. Amidst the jeers and laughter of the stadium filled with Happy fans, the six players from Wind Howl who'd played in the team competition were drooping like that team flag in the midst of their fans, never to fly again.

This was the first time this season Wind Howl had lost so badly. In fact, it had been several years since they'd earned zero points in a match. How long would it be before Wind Howl was never again swept like this? Wind Howl's members were stunned! In terms of length of time they'd been in the team, each player's was shorter than the next. Had they paid attention to Wind Howl's past before? They were the ones who hated and abandoned Wind Howl's long-standing dirty playstyle, and it seemed that they had never bothered to note this team's past and tradition.

Accepting the cheers of the crowd, Happy's players left the stage. 10-0, another 10-0, and the fact that they'd won this over a strong team like Wind Howl only made this achievement even more joyful. Their performance from start to finish had been exceptional. Ye Xiu came up and wiped out Tang Hao, Fang Rui scored a record-setting 1v3, and then they'd easily defeated their opponents in the team competition. Just as Wind Howl's diehard fans were beginning to doubt their team, Happy's fans were only swelling with belief toward their team.

In the post-match press conference, even Liu Hao didn't have the heart to try and please the media. Amidst all the doubts, Wind Howl gave a few words of official, meaningless talk, and then forcefully ended their press conference. Then, Happy's players came up, and Fang Rui was immediately the subject of attention. A record-setting 1v3 against his old mother team, wasn't this a thrilling topic? As soon as the group arena had finished, the reporters had frantically prepared all sorts of questions, and now they tossed them about heroically. During this press conference, Happy's other members were basically invisible.

Round 18 finished. Happy's victory over Wind Howl was the big highlight. This time Samsara, Happy's direct competitors in terms of 10-0 scores, lost to Happy. In their home game against Thunderclap, Samsara lost an individual round, and ultimately won the match 9-1. This match that had been chosen for the television broadcast finally allowed the broadcasters to feel no regrets about their choice. This was truly an extremely exciting match, especially the team competition at the end.

There was a great disparity in both players and characters. One reporter added up the value of the players and characters in each team's roster for comparison, and the power indicated by those numbers only made this match feel even more like they were trying to use an egg to crack a rock. But ultimately, the two teams had fought in the team competition for 33 minutes, which was extremely rare to see in a match against the powerful team that was Samsara. It could be seen that they'd faced many hit and runs.

Relying on their seemingly much-cheaper roster, Thunderclap played a careful and calculating death battle against Thunderclap.

Samsara's ultimate victory had been extremely difficult, and some people had even thought during the match that it was a good thing this was Samsara's home game. If it had been Thunderclap's, then Samsara's golden win streak might have finally been broken. After that, the strategy that Samsara had used to obtain victory was exactly the same strategy that Happy had used to defeat Thunderclap in Round 16.

In the end, Samsara's Sun Xiang had forcefully broken his way through countless obstacles, performing exceptionally well to drag down Xiao Shiqin. Even though his One Autumn Leaf didn't have the same crazy attack rhythm as the unspecialized Lord Grim, the offensive power of the other members of Samsara was generally a step higher than that of Happy. Ultimately, Samsara had relied on this one opportunity to shatter Thunderclap's strategic plans.

This was raw power destroying refinement, and many people felt that it was a shame that Thunderclap lost. And after this destruction, the question of whether or not to open voice channels was once again brought up. Thunderclap, who had once taken advantage of the rule but then suffered twice, finally stood firmly with Blue Rain as a victim of the rule.

And this time, the opponents of the ban on voice comms made their point unusually clearly: the rules were killing the development of Glory.

After seeing that strategy had been completely destroyed by power, one could imagine, in the future why would anyone bother to study these sort of refined strategies? Because even if they developed them, they would be of no use. After several teams in a row successfully used these methods in battle, then the shotcallers of the more strategy-oriented teams would face all sorts of suppression, the goal simply being to prevent them from having the time to type words.

This is a slaughter of Glory strategy. If this continues, then all we will see in future battles are crude, brute-force competitions of raw handspeed. And Glory was more than just that!

The opponents of this rule let their voices resound, and all sides began paying more attention to this than before.

At first, Thunderclap had profited from this rule, but the two subsequent times, they had suffered from it. And they were also without a doubt a team that performed tactics to the peak level. Even before this season, Thunderclap was always this kind of team, but during that time they hadn't had this kind of unbelievable performance. But after Xiao Shiqin went and played around in the Challenger League, it was like the team had become gold-plated.

Even though they'd been defeated by Happy in Round 16, that hadn't seemed to waver their belief at all. Facing Samsara, this unbelievably powerful opponent, Xiao Shiqin once again prepared carefully. He continued to believe that their Team Thunderclap had the ability to defeat any opponent.

This determination moved many people, and Xiao Shiqin's popularity this season exploded. Even with a collection of nameless, ordinary players who were nothing compared to a powerhouse team, they'd still managed to obtain such shining results. This had never before happened in the history of the Alliance. Happy, the self-proclaimed grassroots team, in reality had three All-Star level players, two All-Star characters, and an evildoer unspecialized that no one in the Alliance could grow accustomed to. It'd been a long while since anyone thought of Happy as a grassroots team.

Even though Thunderclap still lost to Samsara, this loss carried a lot of weight. The debate over allowing voice comms grew more and more heated. Some people even demanded that they not wait until next season to change the rules - for something like this, if they could change it, they should change as soon as possible.

Of course, the Alliance couldn't just say they'd change and change it. After the first time this had come up, they'd been studying this problem nonstop. With a new wave of pressure from public opinion, they focused harder on this issue. And after the end of Round 18, the rankings saw new changes. Samsara's strong lead didn't change, but after Happy swept Wind Howl, their ranking rose again. They were now in fifth place, with the same number of points as Tyranny. This round, Tyranny had played a home game, but lost 2-8 to Hundred Blossoms. Because of Zhang Jiale, these two teams had a rather strong conflict. Hundred Blossoms' away game victory this round caused the diehard team-following fans to become carried away in their elation. But the blood of Tyranny fans ran hot, and brawls broke out in Tyranny's stadium. Even though they'd been provoked by the excessive behavior of the Hundred Blossoms fans, it was the host side that generally had to take responsibility for these sort of entanglements.

Fortunately, no injuries had resulted, and the Alliance only gave Tyranny a serious warning. Tyranny suffered, and because of their failure this round, they'd slid down to fourth place, with 127 points like Happy.

Blue Rain and Tiny Herb had each taken down their opponents, and were currently in second and third place.

On Blue Rain's side, they'd faced quite a bit of disruption earlier after losing points to weaker teams. But judging from their recent performance, that had just been a temporary downturn. After adjusting, their scores instantly improved, and in just a few moves they had charged back to second place on the rankings.. Tiny Herb continued their beautiful win streak in the group arena. In this round, they only lost one individual round to Misty Rain, and won by a large margin of 9-1.

Misty Rain's situation was becoming more and more alarming. With 87 points, they were already 21 points away from the playoff zone, and right behind them, Miracle was quickly catching up to them with 83 points. And this new team, Miracle, was only improving with every battle. If Misty Rain was said to still have hope at making the playoffs, then Miracle, only 4 points behind them, also seemed to have this chance.

This had a great deal to do with the change in attitude of the three former Excellent Era players.

These three were originally very depressed about their fall, and they all hoped that they'd quickly find a new home. They all fought quite hard, but how much of it was for their team, that was unknown. But because of their hard work, Miracle actually managed to earn quite good results. Praise came in from all sides, causing them to become overjoyed.

They had come from a powerhouse, and there, they had only ever been side characters. Whenever the team had results, it was very rarely because of them. But now, in this Team Miracle, the three had gradually gained a true sense of owning this home. This team's scores were earned through their hard work; the heartfelt cheers of the fans were meant for them. This sort of fortune steadily let them feel satisfied, and they steadily set down the arrogance bred from their time in a powerhouse. In the private messages between the three of them, they began to recognize that being in Miracle was really quite good.

The three of them began to fight not only for themselves, but for the team. And so the new team's scores became more and more stable. Now, the season was half over, and they were actually in twelfth place.

If Happy weren't here stealing all the spotlight, then Team Miracle really would've lived up to their name, becoming the most miraculous new team in Glory history.

But even in this current situation, Miracle would no longer be overlooked by everyone.

After eighteen rounds, the media reported on the state of the Alliance after this round and the circulating topics. But just two days after the end of this round, a piece of particularly attention-grabbing news appeared in the headlines of all the major media.

Team Wind Howl, with an asking price of 15 million, was seeking to purchase Team Tyranny's Zhang Xinjie.

Chapter 1283: Golden Body Broken

15 million!

Putting aside the target player for now, just this amount was enough to set off stormy waves. The news revealed was very clear that this price didn't include the character, only the player. Without a doubt, if this transfer was successfully completed, the value of professional Glory players would reach a new high.

It was worth noting that the current record for the most expensive player transfer was already set by Team Wind Howl. In the summer window between Seasons 8 and 9, Tang Hao transferred to Wind Howl, and that price of 10 million was currently the highest.

The winter transfer window was generally only for small adjustments and supplements, or if a team needed to fill a hole because of illness or other such special reasons. When Excellent Era obtained Sun Xiang in Season 8, that was a rarely-seen core player transfer. But that, too, was only because Ye Xiu had retired mid-season and Excellent Era was forced to fill the gap.

And now, Wind Howl directly pulled out a record-breaking transfer offer for Tyranny's Zhang Xinjie. It was clear that they had completely recognized the problems with the team and were eager to solve it.

Was Zhang Xinjie the magic treasure that would solve all of Wind Howl's problems?

When everyone thought about it, they realized that Wind Howl had made a fairly correct decision in choosing a player. After giving up on the dirty playstyle, Wind Howl was unable to establish a new tactical system. Bringing in a Master Tactician would undoubtedly help in this area. Wind Howl hoped to establish a new playstyle that involved strong offense, and since Zhang Xinjie came from Tyranny, he would entirely be able to adapt to such a style.

But in the end, relying on acquiring a new team member to solve a problem was a solution for when there was no other way. Choosing Zhang Xinjie seemed to be a correct choice, but the important point was that you couldn't just buy any transfer you wanted, especially if you were targeting the core player of the other team.

So Wind Howl didn't even bother probing carefully, they directly gave this record-breaking price of 15 million. Evidently they didn't have any win-win trade to offer, so they could only use money to open the way, and hope that they could strike a price that Tyranny had no way of rejecting.

Everyone's eyes were focused. All sorts of media came to investigate, and quickly confirmed that this news was true. Team Wind Howl indeed directly proposed an official transfer request to Team Tyranny.

But… Without even waiting to discuss any specifics, Tyranny had already given a lightning-fast answer, announcing their reply directly through the media: declined.

There'd been no official discussion, just a simple refusal. Tyranny's fans hadn't even had the time to become worried before the official response of the club was there to reassure them.

Tyranny's attitude seemed very resolute, but those who were familiar with transfer operations knew clearly that attitude sometimes was only a bargaining chip for the price. Tyranny's attitude showed that they wouldn't be moved by the price of 15 million, then, what about more?

Those looking forward to watch the excitement weren't disappointed. Less than an hour after Tyranny refused Wind Howl's price, Wind Howl followed up.

20 million!

Double the record set by Tang Hao for a solo player transfer. Everyone recognized once and for all Wind Howl's current insanity. This old team had never given people the impression of being a bold, rich, and ostentatious team. Yet as it turned out, they might be quiet when not moving, but when they moved, it was with the sound of thunder.

A team begging for a big-name player, this was entertaining for any team's fans to watch. Wind Howl's fans were still depressed over being swept by Happy, but they grew excited by Wind Howl's continuously bold strokes. Added to the fact that Zhang Xinjie was a good choice, this caused the Wind Howl fans to suddenly grow lively. Even as they waited in anticipation, they took the initiative to use their fan passion to send praises and welcomes to Zhang Xinjie. Everyone knew that in this transfer, the player's own opinion would have a great influence, especially for a big-name player like Zhang Xinjie.

In the end, this time Tyranny hadn't even made an official reply when Zhang Xinjie already made his own announcement, expressing that he had absolutely no intention of leaving Team Tyranny.

The passion of the Wind Howl fans had only just been ignited when it was immediately extinguished by this bucket of cold water. Completely thrown off, they could only blankly wait for their own team's next step.

Wind Howl's two public price offers had already made them the talk of the town, but of course in reality, a transfer was never worked out without a direct conversation between the two sides. Wind Howl was in private contact as well. 20 million wasn't their upper limit, this was just broadcast to increase the morale of the team and boost the hopes of the fans.

But afterward, in the private negotiations, Wind Howl again kicked a steel wall. Neither Tyranny as a team nor Zhang Xinjie as an individual showed any sign of wavering. In private, Wind Howl had already raised the price to 25 million and promised even better accommodations for Zhang Xinjie.

Refusal.

They continued to receive nothing but refusal, that sort of immovable refusal with no room for negotiation.

Wind Howl was helpless. Even as the outside world still anticipated Wind Howl to give an even higher price, in private, Wind Howl had hit the wall until their heads were bleeding. Their invitation toward Zhang Xinjie had instantly become a farce of loud thunder with only a drizzle of rain. When Round 19 began, two small teams had already completed two transfers that didn't draw any attention at all, but Wind Howl? After those two days of noise, there was no more movement.

The acquisition of Zhang Xinjie was unsuccessful, but they had made too much noise with this. The fans' hopes had all been lifted, but in the end it didn't work out. It had to be said that Wind Howl had been too confident with this. They'd had excessive belief in the power of money to open the road. It seemed that they hadn't even considered that in response to these prices and conditions, Tyranny and Zhang Xinjie would still say no to them.

Wind Howl now needed a backup plan to appease the fans whose hopes had been lifted. But just looking at healers, who in the current professional scene could compare to Zhang Xinjie? Besides, Wind Howl had hoped to solve the team's problems from the basis. Just swapping out a healer player would be to no avail. Wind Howl understood clearly that their current problem wasn't that their healer Ruan Yongbin maintained the dirty playstyle. The key point was that, after giving up on the dirty playstyle, the team had been unable to find a mature strategy to use in their matches.

Wind Howl, unable to obtain Zhang Xinjie, seemed like a fly without a head. And in the upcoming Round 19 of the league matches, Wind Howl faced another strong team, Tiny Herb.

Tiny Herb had strong performances in the group arena all season, but their team competitions had caused some worry. After this match, however, everyone saw clearly that even if Tiny Herb's team performance wasn't the best, it was still more than enough to take care of Wind Howl. At least they weren't as fragmented as Wind Howl, who relied entirely on each individual players' instinct and judgment to fight matches.

9-1. Tiny Herb played their away game at Wind Howl and ultimately achieved a large victory. Even though Wind Howl had scooped up one more point than they had last round, this one point was far from enough to make anyone happy.

In the same round, Tyranny, who'd received Wind Howl's request for Zhang Xinjie, displayed their resolve, winning their away game at Void with a score of 8-2.

But in Round 19, the result that was most unexpected was that Samsara's golden win streak was broken.

The team that had completed this snipe was Hundred Blossoms. In their home game, they won 7-3 against Samsara, previously undefeated in the team competition.

Samsara's performance in this team competition was indeed not good that match. After the match, analysts pointed out that their long and slow match against Thunderclap last round had crushed Samsara's rhythm thus far, and in this match, they still hadn't been able to adjust their rhythm back to normal.

But no matter the reason, victory belonged to Hundred Blossoms. After 19 rounds, every team had faced each other exactly once, and only Hundred Blossoms had managed to defeat Samsara. This was something that the Hundred Blossoms fans could feel proud of. In all these years, this team had received much more mockery than praise, and they really didn't have many honors that they could claim as theirs and theirs alone.

Samsara's golden body was broken, and this of course became headline news. But Happy was now no longer a little invisible team that would easily be overlooked and forgotten. In this round, Happy had also met their first loss since Round 9, which also earned quite a bit of attention.

This round, Happy had played their away game at 301, ultimately losing 4-6. After winning 4 points in the individual battles, Happy's supporters were sure that this would be yet another big victory and were lamenting the fact that this wouldn't be another 10-0. But in the team competition, Happy actually lost.

Ever since Round 9, not only had Happy won every match, their winning scores had never dipped below 9-1. This was a point-scoring rhythm even more fearsome than Samsara's. If the Pro League was only from Rounds 9 to 18, then the championship would already belong to Happy.

It was true that Happy hadn't met any of the top powerhouses in their crazy win streak, but teams like Misty Rain, Void, Thunderclap, Wind Howl weren't opponents that could be casually defeated. The ferocious thing was that when Happy faced these four strong opponents, their scores had actually been even higher. Among these four matches, they'd earned three 10-0's.

Happy's results these ten rounds had been even more insane than Samsara's, and everyone recognized Happy's strength. But no one really treated them as some invincible fleet.

Because Happy always had a weak point, their healer. From the very beginning, people had realized that his skill wasn't enough. This wasn't any secret, this was something that even the newspapers reported.

The various teams would of course target such an obvious weakness. But they soon realized that Happy's protection of their healer was so extreme, it could be called frenzied.

Against Hundred Blossoms, against Misty Rain, then against Void… It was very apparent in these matches.

And then Thunderclap had made clear strategic plans to target this weakness, but in the end, because Xiao Shiqin was forced into a position where he couldn't give commands, his strategy was broken. If he'd been able to give voice commands, then in this battle, perhaps Happy would lose because of their Cleric's inability to keep up with the rhythm.

Happy's weakness was extremely apparent, but so many teams were unable to grasp it. And then in Round 19, against Team 301 Degrees, Happy's weak point was broken.

It was broken through brute force.

301's captain, the number one Assassin in Glory, Yang Cong used Life-Risking Strike to directly self-destruct and steal away An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands.

Chapter 1284: The Overlooked Sacrifice

Yang Cong was named the number one Assassin in the Alliance, but his Assassin style wasn't particularly liked. For Assassins, most people liked the thrill of a one-hit kill from Life-Risking Strike. But Yang Cong almost never used this skill, to the point that people wondered if his Scene Killer hadn't even added points to this skill and only used it to bluff.

But in the most recent All-Star Competition, Yang Cong's Scene Killer revealed the fangs of an instant-kill, defeating his opponent in just one strike. Even though that was just a show, Yang Cong at least let everyone know, he knew how to use Life-Risking Strike, the most thrilling of all the Assassin's skills.

The All-Star Weekend ended, and all the players returned to their normal competition conditions. But in the match against Happy, Yang Cong once again revealed his sharp fangs, and Life-Risking Strike stole away An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands.

This move was incredibly unexpected, and losing the healer in the team competition was deadly. Lord Grim's little healing skills could occasionally save a situation at critical points, but relying on him to support a 5v5 team battle was impossible.

Happy could only launch a full, rapid offensive, hoping that they could use this to obtain an advantage of numbers. However, 301 was clearly prepared for this situation. As soon as Yang Cong's attack succeeded, they immediately lowered the tempo of the battle and began a slow battle of attrition. Neither arrogant nor rash, they tightly protected their own healer, and ultimately they swallowed Happy like this.

The battle of attrition wore on for almost 20 minutes, but nearly all of the light of this match came from that Life-Risking Strike of Yang Cong's Scene Killer. This was a brilliance possessed only by Assassins.

During the post-match press conference, Yang Cong of course was surrounded by the reporters. Everyone was extremely curious, after seven years of persistence, why did he suddenly change his playstyle in this match? Was it because he found inspiration from that performance at All-Stars?

"Perhaps!" Facing the questions of the reporters, Yang Cong smiled. "You know, it's not that I don't know how to use Life-Risking Strike, it's that I'm unable to use it!"

"What does that mean?" The reporters didn't understand.

"Because I'm 301's captain," Yang Cong responded simply.

The reporters suddenly understood. The captain was a team's soul, its banner. At any time, the captain had the responsibility of leading the entire team. They might use words to encourage the team members, they might use actions to carry everyone along, but no matter how they led, the captain, first and foremost, had to be present.

And Life-Risking Strike? This was a lose-lose playstyle. After using Life-Risking Strike, the Assassin would only be left with a sliver of health. There wasn't a single team who would miss a target like that. And Yang Cong was 301's captain. He needed to strive to remain on the field. He couldn't just simply kill one target and then come offstage.

Life-Risking Strike. It wasn't that he didn't know how to use it, but that he was unable to use it.

Because he was the captain. On his shoulders, he carried more duties and obligations than others did. He could not be an independently-acting Assassin, because he represented not just himself, but the entirety of a team.

Once they understood this, the reporters suddenly realized something that everyone had overlooked all this time.

From Season 4, everyone praised how Wang Jiexi, for the sake of Tiny Herb, quietly adjusted his playstyle, gradually putting away his more elegant, more attention-grabbing, more popular Magician playstyle. But there was another player who joined in the same season as Wang Jiexi, another All-Star level player, another team captain. From the very beginning, he had also quietly sacrificed some things, for the sake of his responsibilities.

Life-Risking Strike was the most brilliant skill of an Assassin.

Perhaps compared to Wang Jiexi, Yang Cong hadn't done as much. But both players had the same determination of sacrificing themselves for the sake of their teams. For this sentiment, it shouldn't matter exactly how much was sacrificed.

After realizing this point, all of the reporters present felt extremely moved. But even as they were moved, they were still curious.

"Then why did you suddenly use Life-Risking Strike in this battle?" a reporter asked.

"I was probably inspired after All-Stars! After the All-Star Competition, I realized that nowadays, methods like this are probably the best way I can contribute to the team. It's about time that I leave some responsibilities for other people to carry," Yang Cong smiled.

The reporters were once again stunned.

This… was someone already preparing to give way and retire!

Players from Season 3 were indeed at the twilight of their careers; very few were still active in the circle. But how many were like Yang Cong, already deciding to step down before he'd even begun to reveal significant signs of decline?

The All-Star Competition... what did it allow him to see?

Did being at the bottom among All-Stars allow him to see the exit toward which he was walking? Or did the younger players allow him to see a future that was worth looking forward to?

None of the reporters continued to press for details. They knew that even if this was Yang Cong was doing this voluntarily, even if he could still smile gently as he faced everyone, his heart would certainly have feelings of sadness. The helplessness brought by the flow of time was cruel. Who was insensitive enough to dig into this scar for details?

Yang Cong's statement already revealed many things.

Team 301 Degrees was about to change their tactical core. Yang Cong's Assassin stepped aside for this, and he could use a freer method to battle. Perhaps starting from this round, Scene Killer's one-hit kill fangs would set off a new scene in the Alliance?

No one would overlook the fact that this was the number one Assassin in the Alliance! Nearing the end of his professional career, he voluntarily gave up his position as the core player, and from this he would step onto the road of a true Assassin.

Then, after Yang Cong stepped down, who would be 301's new core?

The reporters were just as curious about this question, but 301 didn't give an answer during this press conference. Looking at 301's current players, there was Li Yihui who'd transferred from Tiny Herb. Even though he'd dropped out of All-Stars after leaving Tiny Herb, he was still a very strong player. There was also the Blade Master player Gao Jie, whose ability had been steadily increasing the past few years. These two players both had the possibility of becoming 301's new core.

But two days later, the Monday of the new week, in the register of people signing with the Alliance, some people discovered that 301 just signed a new contract. Not a transfer, but an independent registration.

Bai Shu, a name that no one knew, silently entered Team 301 Degrees. And from the public data released by the Alliance, everyone could see that this person named Bai Shu was using the character that former 301 player Xu Bin had left behind after transferring away, the Knight Tide.

Who was Bai Shu?

Countless people were desperate to know this answer, but the Alliance was currently on a weeklong break. This year's Spring Festival had arrived relatively early. January 22 was already Lunar New Year's Eve, only two days away. All of the teams were already on break. Only the Alliance was still reporting as usual on the newest transfers and replacements as they happened during this transfer window. The players of the various teams had all long gone home to celebrate the new year.

Happy also became a lot quieter. Even Wei Chen and Fang Rui, these dirty and shameless guys, very seriously and obediently reported home for the Spring Festival. In an instant, only three people were left in Happy's training room.

"It's just the three of us again!" Chen Guo said, looking at Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. She didn't feel lonely because there were so few of them. Two people still with her, this was more excitement than she'd ever had since her father passed away.

"Yup, us again," Ye Xiu said.

"Is your brother coming this year?" Chen Guo asked.

"Probably not!" Ye Xiu said.

"You're not planning on going back home?" asked Chen Guo.

"We'll see, we'll see." To this question, Ye Xiu's typical calm, free, and easy attitude wavered a bit, a rare sight to see.

"Then, let's get ready for the Spring Festival!" Chen Guo didn't ask any further.

"Are we going shopping again?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Scared?" The two women smirked at him.

"Even my legs are shaking," Ye Xiu smiled bitterly.

"Then, thanks for your hard work." The two of them showed no intention of letting him off easy.

Just as the three of them prepared to depart, Ye Xiu saw that the door to the R&D area was unlatched, and there seemed to be sounds coming out.

Ye Xiu shot a puzzled glance at Su Mucheng and Chen Guo, and the two immediately noticed this as well. The three of them went forward, Ye Xiu gently pushed open the door, and they saw Guan Rongfei sitting at the computer, completely engrossed in operating something, his mouth moving nonstop as though muttering something to himself.

"What's going on?" Chen Guo barged in, waving her hand in front of Guan Rongfei's face. "Isn't your train at 9? What time is it now?"

Guan Rongfei finally looked away in disgust after Chen Guo blocked his line of sight. After hearing Chen Guo's shout, he casually checked the time. "It's 9:40? Oh, I missed it."

"What are you doing?" Chen Guo shouted. If someone who didn't know what was going on saw this, it would have been really difficult to tell who was the one who had missed the train.

"Working on equipment." Guan Rongfei's response was incredibly simple, so simple that Chen Guo had no response. She of course figured that Guan Rongfei was suddenly investigating some clue, and then became so focused that he forgot about everything else. But her head really hurt over how this guy was always forgetting himself like this, so much that aside from his work, everything else was ignored.

"You're not going home?" Chen Guo asked.

"Don't rush." Guan Rongfei raised his finger and waved it.

Chen Guo suddenly thought that this guy must have reached some critical point, so she didn't dare to say any more and just waited to the side.

After that, Guan Rongfei continued to lose himself in his work, seemingly forgetting everyone standing around him.

"So what exactly are you working on?" Ye Xiu walked up to him.

"Look, this…" As soon as Ye Xiu came up, Gaun Rongfei immediately grew animated, beginning to chatter away at Ye Xiu.

"Huh, is that so. Let me see." As Ye Xiu spoke, he turned on another computer.

Chen Guo's jaw dropped. What happened to their Spring Festival celebration?

Chapter 1285: Strengthening the Cleric

In the end, Chen Guo couldn't harden her heart to drag these two away from the computer. As for preparing for the Spring Festival, she and Su Mucheng quietly went to take care of it by themselves.

By the time the two women finished and returned to the Internet cafe, when they came upstairs and looked, the two in the R&D room were in the exact same positions as earlier. Such focus meant that Chen Guo couldn't bring herself to interrupt them. After exchanging a glance with Su Mucheng, they quietly retreated.

There was plenty of space in the strategic planning room, so all of the New Year's goods they bought were piled up there. Chen Guo sat on the couch, looking at the points leaderboard on the wall of the strategy room. In her heart, there was a taste she couldn't describe.

The season was officially halfway over, and Happy was currently ranked fifth with 131 points, a full 30 points buffer between them and the edge of the playoff zone. Such an outstanding score had already caused tremors within the circle, and of course Chen Guo rejoiced at these scores. But nowadays, she was no longer that fan who only saw the beauty and elegance of the players' performances onstage. As the phrase went, one minute onstage was the result of ten years of work offstage. Chen Guo, with her new identity, now saw all of the hard work and hardship these players had put in offstage.

Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, Fang Rui, An Wenyi, all of the players, as well as Guan Rongfei in R&D, and Wu Chen in Happy's guild, everyone was working furiously, working so hard that Chen Guo never felt that she was able to relax. They'd made it to the Spring Festival, and she wanted to give everyone a short rest, but Ye Xiu and Guan Rongfei ended up unconsciously squatting in Glory yet again.

For the first time, Chen Guo felt that the championship wasn't just beautiful and glorious, it was cruel. Those that obtained it, those that didn't, both had to sacrifice so, so much.

If they obtained it, at least their efforts were rewarded.

But if they couldn't?

After enduring these kinds of hardships, even though she hadn't even suffered these setbacks yet, Chen Guo already felt that she could feel the pain of those who were unable to win the championship.

She couldn't help but think of Zhang Jiale, the most famous "championship loser" in Glory, having the championship slip through his fingers four times. Yet he still didn't give up. The passion of a person like him was probably just like that of Ye Xiu and Guan Rongfei!

"They're all crazy," Chen Guo muttered.

When Su Mucheng heard this, she laughed and sat down beside her. "Isn't there that saying, only the crazy survive."

"But… What if you go crazy, and you still can't survive?" Chen Guo asked.

Su Mucheng was startled, and her gaze also landed upon that leaderboard.

True… This was competition. If they treated "surviving" as "winning the championship," then it was simply fact that many people, no matter how crazy they became, couldn't become champions.

"Then probably… they can only live with their regrets!" Su Mucheng said. She didn't say anything like "as long as you tried there'd be no regrets." For those who had been pro players, she believed that playing without regrets was possible, but the disappointment of being unable to win the championship certainly wouldn't be erased by such policy of "no regrets." Ultimately, perhaps these regrets were what accumulated in the heart the most.

"Then what about you?" Chen Guo suddenly asked.

"Me?" Su Mucheng was again startled. She became a pro in Season 4, and starting from then, Excellent Era had never won a championship again. Ye Xiu had won three championships, but so far, Su Mucheng was also a player who didn't have the championship keyboard and mouse.

"Would you feel a lot of regret?" Chen Guo asked.

"Probably… as well…" Su Mucheng's answer was hesitant. She was still unsure about this question. She would feel regretful, she was sure of that. But she wasn't sure, would her regret be for herself, or for Ye Xiu? In the end, she still wasn't so dedicated to and crazy for Glory. It seemed that she had practiced just so that she could keep up with Ye Xiu's footsteps. Chen Guo, who was now fairly close with her, could observe this point, and so she asked this question.

"If… If your brother were still here, what do you think you would be doing now?" Tentatively, Chen Guo asked another question.

"If he were still here… I would probably stand at the side and bring them tea and water? And…" Su Mucheng laughed as she continued, "I would also play some Glory, so that the feeling of being together would be a bit stronger!"

"Yeah… Together." Chen Guo nodded, and didn't ask any further. The two women sat together on the sofa, lost in their own thoughts, until a voice suddenly shouted from over there, "Done! Just like that!"

.

The two looked at each other, stood up together, and quickly made their way to the R&D room. When they pushed open the door, they saw that Guan Rongfei, who normally spent all his time staring intently at the computer screen illuminating his face, had actually revealed an extraordinarily happy grin.

"What's done?" the two women immediately asked.

"This set of equipment is complete!" Guan Rongfei said.

"What equipment?" The two women peered over to see. They'd originally thought that Guan Rongfei had spent all this effort working on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella as usual, but from these words, it didn't seem like that was the case. The umbrella wouldn't be described with the word "set"!

"Just a set of Cleric equipment, that's all," Ye Xiu said from the side.

"'That's all???" When Guan Rongfei cared about something, he would display that he did indeed have an extraordinary IQ. He sharply picked up on Ye Xiu's wording.

"High intelligence, high crit, that's not too new, is it?" Ye Xiu said.

"It's the Cleric equipment set with the highest intelligence and highest crit in the entirety of Glory!" Guan Rongfei emphasized.

Ye Xiu shrugged and didn't say anything else, as though he didn't have the energy to argue.

"Highest intelligence? Highest crit?" Chen Guo repeated.

"Yes!" Guan Rongfei nodded emphatically. "Added to Little Cold Hands' skill tree, he'll definitely become the Cleric player with the strongest healing ability in all of Glory. Where's Little Hands? Let him come try it out." Guan Rongfei looked around, searching for him.

"He went home for the Spring Festival," Chen Guo said.

"What about his account?" Guan Rongfei asked.

"I'll get it!" Chen Guo immediately turned around and flew toward the training room to get the account card. Strictly speaking, the account cards were all property of the team, and so the players couldn't casually carry them everywhere. Although Chen Guo wouldn't make a fuss about such a detail, with An Wenyi's personality, he would always stick to the rules, and he'd handed over Little Cold Hands' account card without hesitation to Chen Guo before leaving.

The account card was quickly retrieved, and they swiftly logged onto the game. After trading with the account that Guan Rongfei had been using for research, a full set of Silver equipment was transferred to Little Cold Hands' body, and Chen Guo was dumbstruck.

Head, shoulders, upper body, waist, lower body, shoes, six pieces of clothing.

Cape, necklace, left hand ring, right hand ring, badge, pendant, six accessories.

Plus the common weapon for a Cleric, the cross.

13 pieces of equipment, all Silver.

Now that they were in the tenth season, more and more characters had full sets of Silver Equipment. There wasn't a speck of Orange to be found on the core players of the various major teams. But Chen Guo never thought that their Happy would also get a fully Silver-equipped character so quickly, let alone that the first character to get all Silver equipment would actually be Little Cold Hands.

"This… is now the strongest Cleric?" As Chen Guo controlled Little Cold Hands, her hands were shaking a bit.

"Strongest? That depends on how you define it. From healing amount, this is the strongest," Guan Rongfei said.

"I understand," Chen Guo nodded. Even though she wasn't a pro player, she understood things like which stats were more important for a Cleric.

Intelligence, this was the number one thing a Cleric had to strive for. How high the intelligence was determined how strong or weak the Cleric's healing ability was.

And then, the more Vitality and health, the more ability they had to survive. Every class cared about the Vitality stat, and the survival of the Cleric determined the survival of the team, so some Clerics felt that Vitality was even more important than intelligence.

Aside from that, cast speed was also an extremely important stat for a Cleric. The faster the casts, the more heals could be made, it was another way of increasing how much the Cleric could heal, and on the battlefield, it decreased the chance of interruption from the opponent.

Crits, something that had a certain probability of occurring. Critical attacks increased damage. Healing criticals increased the healing amount.

These were all stats used to strengthen the healing ability of a Cleric. And when trying to strengthen the survivability of a Cleric, all sorts of defenses and resistances were also regarded as very important.

With all sorts of stats, it was very difficult to rank them. Generally, it depended on the characteristics of the individual player, so that these Cleric stats were allocated to form the most comfortable and effective partnership with the player. This was key in choosing equipment, and was also the value of Silver equipment: only self-made equipment could achieve the ideal stat distribution.

And this set for Little Cold Hands, the stats were rather aggressive. Intelligence and crit were strengthened without restraint, while aside from that, stats like cast speed which couldn't be overlooked by any Cleric suffered a cold shoulder. On the defensive side, this equipment had high resistance to ice and dark, but they were strengthened at the cost of fire and light defense.

"This… suits An Wenyi?" Chen Guo was now a more worldly person, and she didn't have any doubts looking at the stats of this set of equipment. She trusted that Ye Xiu and Guan Rongfei wouldn't give her something to laugh at.

"Yes," Ye Xiu nodded. "An Wenyi is weaker in terms of technique and reaction, so having to constantly cast heals to support the whole team makes things too difficult. Might as well give him this set, with a slower rhythm, but a strong explosive power."

"Ice and dark resistance, to decrease the risk of him being controlled." Chen Guo knew that the attacks with controlling and restricting effects were largely ice and dark element.

"Right," Ye Xiu nodded.

"So our weaknesses are taken care of just like that?" Chen Guo asked happily.

"The equipment is only a supplement. Even with all this, his reactions are still somewhat slow, he still needs to improve!" said Ye Xiu.

"Then what should he do?" Chen Guo asked.

"It's up to him," Ye Xiu said.

At the same time, in the Glory world, in the Heavenly Domain, in front of a Level 60 100-person dungeon, Lost Fleet.

"What? Solo healer? Bro, don't kid me, okay? This is the entrance to the 100-player dungeon. The 5-player dungeon is over there," said a surprised Knight player, to this Cleric who was wearing decent equipment.

"It's just a Level 60 one," said this decently-equipped Cleric. "Solo healer is enough. With more damage, it'll go a little faster."

Chapter 1286: The Scoundrel Healer

Level 60 100-person dungeon, solo healer.

The one who proposed this ludicrous idea at the entrance of the dungeon was Happy's healer, An Wenyi. One could only imagine the extreme chaos that such a situation would force upon the healer, but An Wenyi wanted to use exactly this type of environment to improve his own reactions.

The only problem was that this idea was quite ridiculous. In Glory, there had never before been the idea of solo healer for a 100-person dungeon, even if everyone was at Level 75 now, and this was only a Level 60 dungeon. There was a level advantage, but that didn't mean that players could easily crush a 100-person dungeon. If that were the case, healers wouldn't even be needed.

An Wenyi found a wild raid group. With his current identity as one of Happy's pro players, he could directly go to Happy's guild dungeon groups to practice, but those groups would definitely coordinate with him and care for him unconsciously. The teamwork of a stable team would lower the pressure on the healer. What An Wenyi needed was the most chaotic and insanity-inducing environment possible, and a wild dungeoning group formed right outside the entrance of the dungeon fit his needs exactly.

"Solo healer…" Even though this Knight was forming a wild raid group, he had a few companions. He didn't speak for a while, probably to discuss this issue with them.

An Wenyi quietly waited to the side. If this team rejected him, he could only search for other groups. Today was only Monday, the dungeons had just refreshed for the week, so large crowds of people gathered to dungeon. Only a minority of these players had set groups. Most players just casually threw together a team and dungeoned where they could. In such a setting, it shouldn't be too hard for An Wenyi to fulfill his desire of solo healing. After all, like any online game, in activities like dungeoning, healers were always a scarce resource. And of the 24 glory classes, healers made up only 8% of the player base, but for a 100-person dungeon, more than 8% of the spots typically needed to be healers, which only worsened the scarcity.

The group deliberated for a while. Finally, they probably looked at the people they'd already gathered and the applicants to the team. There were piles and piles of the various classes, but the number of Clerics and Paladins was so low it was pathetic. Whenever any were discovered, if you were too slow by a heartbeat, they would have already joined another group.

"How about… we give it a shot?" The players were tempted, and An Wenyi's Cleric was pulled into their group.

An Wenyi let out a long breath.

Level 60 100-person dungeon, solo healer. He'd never done it before, but he wasn't going in without any preparation. Why would he choose this dungeon to do this sort of thing? This decision had been made through calculations. The person who gave him this answer was Luo Ji, that person who could write countless Idiot's Guides just from watching dungeoning videos. He'd been a great help to An Wenyi for his. After calculating the damage in the Level 60 100-person dungeons and the healing power of the Cleric character An Wenyi would use, as well as all of the various situations that were likely to occur in these dungeons, he concluded that it was theoretically possible for a solo healer to sustain a raid group for a Level 60 100-person dungeon.

The raid group was quickly assembled. After they stopped considering healers, adding people was an extremely fast thing. But very quickly, players in the group also realized the fact that, in the entire group there was only one healer.

"Solo healer?" After one person asked and received an answer, everyone was in an uproar.

"Is he a dumbass? Does he even know how to play?" Immediately, many players immediately quit the raid group.

"For a Level 60 dungeon, solo healer is enough, max efficiency!" The team leader used An Wenyi's earlier words. But still, many players who thought this was impossible left. Of those that were left, some were shocked and some were curious, and then new players were added, some discovered the solo healer and quit in a rage, more were added, repeat the struggle, until finally, a muddled raid group was pulled together.

Solo healer!

Everyone was searching for that one healer in their group, wanting to see what kind of character it was.

At this time, An Wenyi couldn't help but feel a little nervous, too. He didn't come here wanting to screw everyone over. Solo healer… he had to pull it off.

"Enter!" the team leader ordered. The team entered the dungeon, and An Wenyi's crazy training began…

Wiped out.

Ultimately, the 100-person raid group fell to the very first boss of Lost Fleet.

"What solo healer you fucker!!!" At least 50% of the entire group immediately started berating him mercilessly.

They were Level 75, challenging a Level 60 dungeon. Even if it was a wild group as long as they were supported by a normal proportion of healers, they should at least make it past the first boss without wiping out.

The self-proclaimed solo healer was thrown into a mess right after meeting the first wave of monsters, and at that time the leader was already feeling a shadow over his heart. Wild dungeoning groups were chaotic, mismatched in both awareness and cooperation, and they needed healers to frequently stabilize the situation.

And so they progressed, chickens flying and dogs jumping, and whether in the chat or in voice, the most frequent content was cries for healing: heal heal heal heal heal.

People were dying nonstop, ending their dungeon adventure, and by the time they reached the first boss, over 30 people had already died. The remaining 60 or so ultimately fell to this boss.

...

As soon as the wounded leader was sent out of the dungeon, he immediately tried to find and harass An Wenyi. That guy, he came here purely just to screw people over, right? Had the leader accidentally made an enemy of someone, who came to take revenge with an alt account? The team leader stewed in anger, but he didn't think that anyone had such a large grudge against him that they would go to all this effort to destroy a wild team that he'd casually pulled together. But when he took a circle all around the entrance of the dungeon, there was already no trace of that Cleric.

"Fuck, don't let me see you again!" the leader spat bitterly.

"It really is very difficult…" An Wenyi, who had already quickly escaped from the Lost Fleet dungeon, summarized this failure of a dungeon adventure. He'd been prepared for the chaos of a wild group, but the reality had still been far worse than his expectations.

But even though it'd turned out like this, An Wenyi had no thought of giving up. If he'd been able to do this right from the start, then would he even need this training in the first place? He'd already made all the preparations, including a drawer of Level 75 Cleric accounts.

An Wenyi did have a lot of experience in-game. He knew that this kind of scoundrel Cleric repeatedly doing this scoundrel thing would very quickly show up in the global channel, and so he'd already prepared to switch to alts.

However… always searching for a solo healer team, this action also seemed too conspicuous. Even switching accounts wouldn't be enough to hide it! An Wenyi was very thorough when considering problems, and he'd thought of this from the start, and so the new Cleric account he switched to was on the fourth server.

The ordinary servers had the same content as the Heavenly Domain, and their 100-person dungeons weren't lacking at all. An Wenyi had prepared these Cleric accounts specially for the ordinary servers, and so he began to wander all about the various servers as a solo healer, becoming a natural disaster for dungeon groups left and right.

Yes, natural disaster…

At the very start, the only thing that could be used to describe An Wenyi was "natural disaster."

One after another, wild dungeon groups were wiped out because of him, and group after group of players wasted their dungeon runs. An Wenyi was apologetic in his heart, but he twisted his head and, calm and determined, continued to be a natural disaster.

Did his skill show any increase?

Just looking at the progress in the dungeons, there was no significant change. Every run had different situations, and An Wenyi's performance had its ups and downs. Clearly, he didn't have the ability to stabilize and control these situations. But with An Wenyi's logical mindset, he hadn't anticipated any miraculous rhythm of instantly becoming God-like, so step by step he continued to use the drawer of accounts and wander around.

The new week gave him many opportunities to join dungeon groups. But the the Spring Festival quickly arrived, the time of the year with the lowest number of people online in Glory. Even though that was the case, Glory would still put out an in-game event during this time with many prizes for the players.

During an in-game event, the number of people actively dungeoning would decrease greatly. But this year's Spring Festival event also happened to be a huge group event. Even though it wasn't a dungeon, it was a dungeon-like environment for training, and so An Wenyi continued to train. After being a natural disaster for the dungeon groups, he became a natural disaster for the event groups.

About halfway through the Spring Festival, this legend of a natural disaster began to circulate in-game. Numerous players were complaining about meeting this scoundrel Cleric, and quickly even a discussion thread popped up, with the subject "Those Clerics Who Screwed You Over In Those Years." And so one after another, players showed up and told their stories, and gradually people began to realize, these experiences, how come they all sounded so similar? And afterward, the players who had been screwed over by the same Cleric character excitedly gathered together on this common ground.

"It's An Wenyi."

After Chen Guo told about this everyone about this exciting thing going on in-game recently, Ye Xiu found the thread in question. After flipping through a few of the descriptions written by the victims, he made this declaration.

"Ah?" Chen Guo was stunned.

"He's using this kind of method to crudely train his reactions," Ye Xiu said.

"This… does it work?" Chen Guo was doubtful.

"With such persistence, there'll always be some improvement," Ye Xiu said.

"But with him causing such a ruckus, he probably won't be able to persist much longer, will he?" Chen Guo scrolled through that thread, and toward the end people were already beginning to analyze this scoundrel Cleric. Even though they hadn't figured out any clues for now, it was clear that with the recent booming popularity of this thread, even ordinary players who liked to surf the discussion boards might see it, and once they saw it, they would be vigilant against any Clerics proclaiming they could be a solo healer.

"Haha, I'm sure he'll think of a way," Ye Xiu said.

An Wenyi indeed thought of a way. After being repeatedly refused as a solo healer, he began not to worry about maintaining that setup, and instead simply tried to find groups where the pressure on the healers was relatively high. In reality, after so much professional training, An Wenyi's current skill was higher than any ordinary player. He couldn't make the solo healer 100-person dungeon reality because of his own weaknesses, but for situations where there was a lack of healers and thus more pressure, he could handle them easily.

But healing step by step as usual, that wasn't the intense training that An Wenyi was looking for. And so in these kinds of groups, he took on all responsibilities, ignoring the divisions of the team. He treated the situation as though he were a solo healer, and furiously tried to maintain the health of the entire team.

Because there were still other healers supporting, it didn't fall into chaos. In fact, An Wenyi's extremely high-level wide-range observational ability became evident as he saved the situation all around. And so An Wenyi took the chance to make a request: "With me here, we don't need this many Clerics. Add some more DPS so we can go faster and kick out some healers for the next dungeon."

Chapter 1287: A Cheap Idea

The winter break for the Spring Festival passed by quickly. Guan Rongfei, who had missed his train due to being too absorbed in his research, decided to just forgo going home altogether, spending the Lunar New Year with Chen Guo, Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. It was because of his presence that Chen Guo didn't manage to experience much of a celebratory air during their Lunar New Year's Eve feast.

Guan Rongfei focused on devouring his meal when he wasn't speaking, and when he spoke, he never deviated from business. Don't look at how Happy now had a full set of Silver Cleric equipment; their overall Silver equipment development was rather lacking. This topic was definitely a heavy one, especially when Guan Rongfei ran right back to his lab and retrieved a stack of documents to show Ye Xiu the materials they were in dire lack of. The entire atmosphere of their dinner simply sank.

With what Ye Xiu had accumulated through his efforts this past year and a half, plus Guan Rongfei's wealth of experience, Happy had already been able to take many shortcuts in developing Silver equipment. Apart from the upgrade of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, the development of their other equipment had cost them extremely few materials. Otherwise, it would've been impossible for them to develop so much Silver equipment with their foundations - or lack thereof - as a new team.

However, after this half a season, their stocks had been depleted. They were good with low level materials since Wu Chen, now in charge of the Guild Department, had brought them to a standing a club guild should have. Throughout the servers as well as the Heavenly Domain, they were continuously accumulating materials. Their profits from dungeons were very stable.

However, the rare materials only a wild boss could provide, faced with a battle of guilds, wasn't so easy to gain. Wu Chen clearly didn't have Ye Xiu's ability to submerge everything into chaos and benefit from it. Plus, with Happy's current standing, it wasn't the same as back then when Ye Xiu could charge into the fray on his own and create an uproar. Balance was something Happy had to research and attain.

What Happy had as an advantage was the passion in their guild.

As a new team with a new fanbase, they had achieved some outstanding results and the passion for helping their guild and playing a part in their team's improvement swelled amongst their fans. Their efforts and dedication allowed Happy to maintain their competitiveness.

However, the rare materials from wild bosses were, at their core, very different from what could be obtained through dungeoning. There were only so many each week, you'd have to see if you could manage to win them first, and even if you did win them, would those materials be what you needed? With that, Happy was at a disadvantage.

Happy was, after all, a new team. Their need for these materials was far greater than that of the other teams.

Seeing the materials on the list Guan Rongfei handed over, Ye Xiu knew that it would be impossible to suit everyone up like they had Little Cold Hands. Next, they had to have a plan, and decide which character to focus on first.

　

Among these, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was a huge burden. Its materials were very demanding in the first place, then, as a project in development, it incurred huge material costs. After looking over the materials Guan Rongfei had used on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella's development, Ye Xiu's heartbeat had quickened. If it weren't for the necessity of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, how many pieces of Silver equipment could they have created from these materials?

"The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella…" Ye Xiu was a little hesitant. Since Guan Rongfei wanted to boost the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella directly to Level 80, there were many added variables to the research of this weapon. More variables meant a higher expense, and more importantly, this expense would continue.

"Should we give up on it for now…" Ye Xiu couldn't help but wonder, but… giving up now would mean wasting everything they had already poured into this. The research they had done on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had gotten to a point where it was difficult to stop. Even so, they couldn't just charge recklessly like this. When push came to shove, they'd have to make small scale sacrifices!

Ye Xiu took a deep breath, trying to force himself to calm down and consider this rationally. On the other hand, Guan Rongfei didn't consider so much. Seeing Ye Xiu looking over the materials required for the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, he instead became rather exultant. "It's almost done. Right now, we just need one more part. Once we confirm this one material, I'm pretty sure we'll be good."

"Can this part be modified on its own?" Ye Xiu's heart thumped again. Whether the part could be modified in isolation or not made a huge difference. If it couldn't, then this situation would be rather terrible. As a piece of equipment, if a single part had anything wrong with it, the equipment would fail; they might lose all the materials put into the equipment's conception and have to start anew. If they could modify and test it in isolation, then just redoing the part would cost far less materials.

"It can't…" Guan Rongfei gave him a most disappointing answer.

Ye Xiu sighed heavily. The next step of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was made entirely out of Level 75 rare materials. The consequences of these materials going to waste was something happy couldn't afford. If these materials were used on other equipment, then it could greatly improve Happy's overall strength. Seeing the materials required for other pieces of equipment, Ye Xiu made a decision. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella would have to be set aside for the moment!

Yet, he hadn't even made his decision known when Guan Rongfei continued, "We can only modify it locally, at a cost of about three rare materials."

"..." The solemn decision Ye Xiu had made immediately dispersed. Though the expense of three Level 75 rare materials was rather painful, it was far more acceptable than all the materials the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella would be using!

"Good luck!" He quickly swept away the heavy heart of having to abandon the progress of his weapon and changed to encouragement.

　

"When the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella is finished, should we push all the other equipment to Level 80?" Guan Rongfei said in a smug tone. His passion seemed to have extended from researching the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella to whether it was possible to upgrade the rest of their equipment to Level 80 under the current level limit.

"That's… a little too taxing on our materials. no?" Ye Xiu said.

"I'll do my best to get out a list," Guan Rongfei replied.

"Don't rush it," Ye Xiu hurriedly reminded him. "Let's go step by step according to the plan we had decided on!"

"But how cool would that be. All Level 80 equipment!" Chen Guo suddenly called out.

　

"Calm down!" Ye Xiu yelled. He hadn't expected this at all. Didn't they know what Level 80 meant? Didn't they know that Happy couldn't afford to undertake such a wide scale high level project like this? It was too irrational to push Guan Rongfei's passion in that direction at a time like this. Ye Xiu noticed Chen Guo's wine cup; was the boss drunk?

　

"The base stats of a piece of level 70 Silver equipment is equal to Level 75 Orange equipment. That means Level 75 Silver equipment is Level 80 Orange equipment. Conversely, doesn't that mean that Level 80 Orange equipment is equal to Level 75 Silver equipment? If we can find a way to improve our Level 75 Orange equipment and upgrade them to Level 80, then wouldn't they be like Level 75 Silver equipment? Though they won't be Level 80 Silver equipment, but being able to completely arm ourselves with Level 75 Silver equipment, that'll still make us very powerful at this stage!" Chen Guo exclaimed.

The room immediately quieted down. Ye Xiu glanced at Guan Rongfei and Guan Rongfei glanced at Ye Xiu. The two were already in deep contemplation. As for Su Mucheng, she was staring at Chen Guo in surprise. Though equipment editing wasn't her forte, she knew far more than Chen Guo would just through sheer exposure, and she definitely had a clearer understanding of the value of Chen Guo's sudden idea.

"Although this idea is a little cheap, but from a cost-efficiency perspective, this is a good idea," Guan Rongfei decided.

"Cheap!" Chen Guo's focus was always on the negative adjectives.

　

"Isn't that the basis of your idea? Using cheap equipment and resources to imitate more high-end equipment?" Ye Xiu retorted.

"How come it sounds so… bad coming from your mouth?" Chen Guo couldn't find any sort of rebuttal and simply sulked.

"Can Orange equipment be modified directly under the equipment editor....? This is something that's currently being researched, but I doubt anyone has figured it out completely. What the equipment editor can do is take equipment apart into parts, but there are too many unknowns regarding the variables and formulae that decide how the combined product of these parts is created. We aren't even all that clear on what materials make up some of the parts of dismantled Orange equipment. Currently, only the game developers can increase the stats and level of Orange equipment in their updates," Guan Rongfei mused.

"Orange equipment is just an example she brought up. In reality, we don't need to use the Orange equipment produced by the system, but create the Orange equipment from scratch using the equipment editor," Ye Xiu suggested.

"Using the equipment editor to create Orange equipment…" Guan Rongfei furrowed his brows.

"Then upgrade them to Level 80," Ye Xiu continued his train of thought.

"This idea is like, in a test, everyone is working hard to get that 100 percent. We can easily get a 90 percent, then do a bonus question that no one else knows of, thus boosting our score to 100, too," Su Mucheng drew an analogy.

"Of course, in the long term, getting 110 percent or a solid 100 percent would be best. However, in the short term, this is the quickest, most effective way to increase our strength," Ye Xiu concluded.

"Let's try it!" Guan Rongfei finally nodded. Ye Xiu was delighted because he knew that this guy didn't care much about things like team results or cost-efficiency or saving up. What really incited his passion and interest was the process of developing equipment itself. Thus, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was a very interesting project, as was creating Level 80 equipment. Crafting the highest intelligence and critical Cleric equipment was alright, too. Working on something you were interested in, passionate about would make you more dedicated and efficient; you'd do better. Currently, making Orange equipment instead of Silver equipment with the equipment editor was an entirely new idea that seemed to have motivated Guan Rongfei.

Of course, anything that came out of the equipment editor would have silver names, and was "Silver equipment" from this perspective.

　

However, if you didn't try to reach the high stat possibilities that Silver equipment would give you, but something only on the level of orange equipment, then the standards for materials would definitely be lowered. The only awkward thing was that they couldn't aim for the best for their Silver equipment, but had to make it a level below on purpose, that… was something Guan Rongfei really didn't have any leads in.

The chopsticks in his hands suspended in the air above the dishes, the gears in Guan Rongfei's head were already beginning to turn.

Chapter 1288: Big Surprise

The Spring Festival passed in the blink of an eye, and the various players made their way back to their teams. Unlike other people who could slowly readjust to their work after a long break, pro players needed to quickly adjust their condition back to normal. Round 20 of the League matches was right in front of them.

On the sixth day of the Spring Festival, January 28, Happy's players were already beginning to return to the team. When An Wenyi returned, he obtained the account card that had received a complete makeover.

He was Happy's weak point, the target of many opponents' strategies, and Happy had made many plans and arrangements revolving around him. His existence seemed like such a burden, and the outside world's cries for Happy to find a qualified healer player had never broken. An Wenyi knew all of this better than anyone. For a new player, the pressure on him was extremely high. But An Wenyi persisted. He knew that his own abilities were limited, and he knew that Ye Xiu had dug him out of the game not for any talent he had but out of helpless desperation. An Wenyi at least had some special trait and stood out just a tiny bit among the ordinary crowd.

There was still a lot he needed to work on. An Wenyi knew this clearly, and so he was always working hard. He hoped that he could gain something. During the entire winter season, in fact, he'd held worry in his heart. Before, Happy had chosen him because they had no other choice. But now, with Happy's current results, they could definitely attract a better healer. An Wenyi was truly quite scared that he would be replaced just like that. Especially because he was such a logical person, he felt that Happy's doing so would indeed solve the problem once and for all.

Every day after the winter transfer window opened, he carried this worry. But it seemed that Happy didn't have any intention of making any moves during this transfer window, which reassured him a little. And then during the Spring Festival, and he went home to celebrate the holiday. Even then, An Wenyi didn't dare slack off, and he continued his harsh training.

But on the last night he was at home, he still had a nightmare. Chen Guo came to find him, telling him that a new Cleric player arrived to the team, and An Wenyi was now left to fend for himself. She only told him now because she wanted to let him enjoy the holiday first…

An Wenyi was frightened awake in a cold sweat. A method like "let you enjoy the holiday first," which took into account the human feelings involved, was definitely something that fit Chen Guo's style. After that dream, he had no way of falling back asleep.

The next day, he returned to the team. Carrying the mood that the nightmare had brought him, he returned to Happy, he returned to the training room, and Chen Guo pushed the account card for Little Cold Hands back into his hands.

In that moment, An Wenyi's heart finally relaxed. There were only a few days left in the transfer window. It looked like the team really didn't plan to find anyone to replace him.

And then, as he inserted the card and logged onto his character, An Wenyi found that in the room, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Chen Guo were all looking at him strangely, as though waiting for something.

An Wenyi suddenly had another bad feeling. But he never could have predicted that, when he logged onto the account and checked the character's status and equipment as usual, he was suddenly blinded by an eyeful of silver words.

Silver equipment?

One piece, another piece, in total thirteen pieces. A full set of Silver equipment.

An Wenyi was stunned.

"How about it, still recognizable?" Chen Guo came up to him with a smile.

"This… this is…" The cool and logical An Wenyi was stammering.

"High intelligence, high crit, it should fit you very well. Become the fiercest Cleric in Glory!" Ye Xiu said.

"This is really… too great…" An Wenyi's mood was complicated, but he wasn't someone who could open his mouth and burst forth with eloquent poetry. In the end when he opened his mouth, he only gave this simple sentence of praise.

He worried that the team would give up on him. But in the end, the team hadn't given up. They'd actually created a whole new set of Silver equipment for him, a complete set, the first complete set of Silver equipment in Happy. For him. Someone who was nothing more than Happy's weak point, Happy's vulnerability, the one in Happy who was most viewed as dragging everyone down.

An Wenyi logically thought that he would be replaced, but he was met with the team's "illogical" response. He hated the illogical, but at this moment, he had no idea what he could say aside from "really great."

"Keep working hard!" Chen Guo said.

"Yes!" An Wenyi nodded his head firmly. Not only did the team have patience toward him, they had belief in him. And he could only repay them with his determination and loyalty.

"But don't take this equipment to join dungeon teams in game. If you lost it, that'd be bad," Chen Guo added, laughing.

"Ah… you know…" There was an added weight to Chen Guo's reminder, so An Wenyi immediately realized what Chen Guo was actually saying.

"Not bad," Chen Guo praised him.

An Wenyi sweatdropped. His diligent and harsh training had caused so many complaints and made countless victims. In order to improve, An Wenyi could only toughen his skin and continue because he truly couldn't think of any more effective method. In a dungeon he had to observe the whole situation and choose the skill and grasp the timing and make judgments and position and so on and so forth. Compared to pure reaction training, An Wenyi felt that this method would allow him to reap greater benefits.

Because An Wenyi had been training nonstop ever since he'd joined Happy, but to be honest, after a year and a half, the improvement in his reaction times were complete unsatisfactory. It looked like he was naturally limited in this area, and so from early on he'd searched for breakthroughs in other areas. And this sort of grinding training seemed to him an explosive way to improve himself.

"Alright, since you just got back, take a rest for now. When everyone gets here we'll start practicing again," Ye Xiu said to An Wenyi.

"I'm not tired, I'll take another look. An Wenyi was fiddling with Little Cold Hands, a Little Cold Hands clad in all-Silver equipment.

Ye Xiu smiled and didn't stop him.

With this, Happy had given An Wenyi a huge Lunar New Year's gift. But they hadn't expected that someone had also brought back a huge Lunar New Year's gift for Happy.

Wu Chen, after returning, didn't immediately return to the guild department. With a smile, he logged onto his own account in the training room and then displayed the guild's inventory for everyone to see.

"Surprised?" Before, it was Ye Xiu and the others waiting to enjoy An Wenyi's expression. And this time, it was Wu Chen's turn to wait and enjoy their expressions.

"This is…" Chen Guo was dumbstruck. She'd created this team, but her in-game life still continued, and she had an approximate understanding of how many materials the guild had. But she didn't have the habit of checking too often because she felt that that would be hovering over the guild work, and she didn't want to do that. So Chen Guo, as the boss, actually paid less attention to the guild storage than she had as an ordinary guild member. She didn't remember when was the last time she'd checked on Happy's stores. But no matter what, these pages upon pages of filled boxes was almost ridiculous, especially the numerous rare materials included within.

"From the event?" In the end, Ye Xiu reacted first. Although there weren't many rare materials, there was no way they'd come from wild bosses. Only so many wild bosses could spawn in one week's time. These could only have come from the Lunar New Year event.

"Yup! Unexpected, right? Everyone is very enthusiastic, you know!" Wu Chen said.

"Everyone?" Chen Guo was confused.

"The fans of Team Happy!" Wu Chen said proudly. As the guild leader, Wu Chen could be considered the member of Happy who had the most interactions with ordinary gamers and fans. He watched as Happy's fan base grew bigger and bigger, and he had the greatest impression of the fans' enthusiasm. Although a club guild could gather a large number of fan players, these players ultimately came to play the game, not to do any work for the team. So, the club could only directly control a portion of full-time or half-time players. And for these, the club needed to pay them for the benefits. They weren't reliant on fans' love and support.

But Happy wasn't quite the same right now. A new team with outstanding results. The fans that they'd gathered were still fresh in their excited support! They gave their time and effort simply out of love without keeping track of the cost. And this time during the Lunar New Year event, players in Guild Happy voluntarily organized groups to build the bricks and tiles that the team needed, and they received a roaring answer. Later, many players who hadn't joined Guild Happy but were still fans of Team Happy all came to participate. They earned materials and sent them to Guild Happy without hesitation.

Because of this massive, widespread, passionate support, Guild Happy's storage grew full to bursting in just a few short days.

"This is really… too great…" Chen Guo also entered the state An Wenyi had experienced earlier, the "didn't know how else to express praise."

"It's not just Heavenly Domain, either. The stores in all the normal servers also earned a lot from this event," Wu Chen said.

"Then… we really need to thank everyone!" Chen Guo was deeply moved, immediately going to Happy's official Weibo account to post a thank-you message.

Very soon, numerous people flocked to comment and reblog. The team had received their support, which made the fans very happy. The screen displayed nonstop everyone's shouts of well-wishes and encouragements, so many that there was no way for Chen Guo to reply to them all.

Happy now had its own official website as well. Chen Guo immediately went over there, prepared to write a more official and formal thank-you message, but after clutching her head for a while, she felt that there was no way she could express her current emotions in writing. She sat there in a daze.

"This is really too powerful. You organized this?" Ye Xiu asked Wu Chen.

"I can only say that everyone's emotions accumulated into this. Plus, everyone can see Happy's condition right now, and that we need this kind of support," Wu Chen said, smiling.

"This is really a great surprise," Ye Xiu said, voice filled with emotion.

"It's just that the rare materials are a bit lacking. The game system is still selfish!" Wu Chen sighed.

"Even ordinary materials are good," Ye Xiu smiled. Now that they were prepared to make Orange equipment in the equipment editor, the number of rare materials they needed would greatly decrease. They'd only just discussed this plan at the Lunar New Year dinner, and now the guild brought them this huge explosion. Happy's fortune in the new year was really incomparably strong!

Chapter 1289: Second Half of the Season

Little Cold Hands' complete set of Silver equipment, a new equipment creation methodology, the fans' boom in material donations during the Spring Festival, these non-stop, pleasant surprises took a while for Team Happy to digest. However, they couldn't bask in celebrations for too long, since Round 20 was in two days.

This was Happy's home game, so the team did not need to travel arduously. However, it could be said that their opponents this round were the strongest within the entire Alliance.

Team Samsara stood before Team Happy again after half a season's worth of matches.

Nineteen rounds ago in Round 1, the reigning champions showed their dominance to the team fresh out of the Challenger League. After 19 rounds though, most were seeing Happy in a completely different light. No one still considered Happy to be a grassroots team; this was a team that was shoulder to shoulder with Blue Rain, Tiny Herb and Tyranny, with 130 points each. Also, Team Samsara was no longer undefeated. In Round 19 which happened the previous round, they lost to Team Hundred Blossoms. In the Pro League, there was no such thing as "impossible".

In their previous encounter, Happy lost to Samsara 0 to 10. It could be considered a complete and utter defeat. This time, the media was sure to label this a grudge match, and fans of Happy were hoping for Happy to take revenge.

Although everyone was paying attention to this match, all the reporters of the big media companies were still focused on the transfer market. The end of the winter transfer window was in less than three days, and every team had only made minor adjustments so far. Were none of the teams going to make any big changes this winter? That was improbable!

Wind Howl and Misty Rain had proven themselves unsuccessful for the first half of the season. Even the fans' support might waver if they didn't make any significant changes in the winter, especially for Team Wind Howl, who were very vocal when they tried to acquire Zhang Xinjie from Tyranny? Why did they fall silent after the offer of 20 million?

The media waited for a big move from these teams in vain. Instead, they received word that Team 301 expressed interest in Royal Style's Tian Sen and his Exorcist Peaceful Hermit. Apparently they had already made an offer to Royal Style.

301 was currently in 10th with 98 points. Royal Style's performance was abysmal, ranked 13th with only 82 points, even losing to the new Miracle.

Royal Style's points were dismal, and the transfer market's atmosphere this season was also dismal. Furthermore, the long term sponsor of Peaceful Hermit was losing patience with Royal Style. There was already leaked information that they would not be working with Royal Style after the end of this season.

Royal Style was a powerhouse past its prime. In Season 1, they had battled Excellent Era for the title of champions. Their decline was hard for many to witness. Royal Style would be the most suitable representative of a "has-been" in the Alliance if it wasn't for the freakishly quick decline of Excellent Era.

In this sad state, even a forever-sidelined team like 301 wanted a slice of their pie. And this slice was the former top God character, Peaceful Hermit.

Team 301 has fully revealed their ambitions. After their long term captain Yang Cong stepped down from the team's core position, they actually took the stance that they would like to shake things up.

Royal Style's performance had declined year by year. Their financial situation was no better, being limited by their core player Tian Sen. The timing of 301's move was picking at Royal Style's achilles heel.

What would happen if Tian Sen and Peaceful Hermiet really transferred to 301?

There were already people who couldn't resist fantasizing about this. This purchase would definitely end up in 301's core lineup. Along with their captain Yang Cong, who had stepped aside but could still throw down with the best of them, and the new recruit, the mysterious Bai Shu. The reporters always thought that Bai Shu was no ordinary player. However after much investigation, they could only prove that he was not a member of 301's training camp. Although at the age of 22 wouldn't he be way too much of a late bloomer if he really was from the training camp? If he wasn't from the training camp or another team, where did 301 pluck him from? He was also directly given control of 301's existing Knight character. With no previous characters to explore, the reporters were out of options and could only wait for 301 to reveal some information on their own terms. However, 301 had put that idea to the side for now and instead made plans to acquire Royal Style's Tian Sen and Peaceful Hermit...

The biggest commotion in the winter transfer window actually came from Team 301, who only had a small role in the playoffs for many years. This was very surprising for everyone.

Regrettably, this show didn't get another act. Tian Sen personally expressed his intention to stay at Royal Style no matter what.

"Peaceful Hermit belongs with Royal Style. His inheritance will never be severed while he's in my hands!" This is the resounding statement that Tian Sen made through the media, thus ending any plans 301 had for a purchase. There would never be a shortage of idealistic individuals within the Alliance. All players shared the desire to be champions, but all players also had their own goals, their own ideals that they would never abandon. Tian Sen refused to abandon his team for his own advancement,and further expressed that he was willing to take a salary cut to reduce the financial burden on his team.

Tian Sen's actions was praised by many. A pro player did not only shine on the battlefield. In this moment, Tian Sen's personal character far outshined the God-level character that he controlled in the game.

Such a rare opportunity for a big transfer ended just like that. The media did not get what they were waiting for, so they could only dutifully report the regular situations and predictions for the second half of the season. Round 20 was finally set to begin.

The arrival of the reigning champions once again allowed the focal point of the alliance to be brought to Xiaoshan Stadium. On match day, countless Glory fans roamed around helplessly, hoping against hope that they would encounter someone who wanted to return their ticket to the match.

At around six o'clock, Team Samsara's bus pulled into Xiaoshan Stadium. The players entered the stadium while flanked by the on-site security, through packs of fans and media personnel. There was no shortage of attention for the reigning champions.

And what about the players of Team Happy? At around half past six, they left from the back door of Happy Internet Cafe and crossed the road. There was even someone eating a piece of fruit. They arrived in the most lowkey fashion.

The two teams entered their own prep rooms respectively. They performed some final touches, such as collecting their thoughts, revising their battle plan, and making any last-minute adjustments before the match.

After this at around 7:40, the two teams entered the stage. There was no need for a fancy opening for such an anticipated match. The viewers' enthusiasm would be sparked as soon as the players entered via their entrances. Team Samsara displayed the terror of being the reigning champions. Their fans fully filled the area of the stands specifically for the away team supporters. They immediately created a deafening commotion, loudly yelling out their team and their players' names. Samsara's banner fluttered in midair in Xiaoshan Stadium. In the first half of the season, this banner was only placed below their opponent's once, and that was to Team Hundred Blossoms in Blossoms Stadium. This time, the banner waved rather menacingly, as Samsara was facing Happy, who they had swept previously in a 10-0. After an ordinary opening of introducing the players, handshakes and greetings, each team made their way towards their player stands and waited for the match to begin.

In the broadcast, the casters Pan Lin and Li Yibo had already turned the show into you guess, you guess, no, you.

"Will Team Happy once again send out Ye Xiu first in the individual competition? We know that from the nineteen rounds that have been played so far, Ye Xiu's win streak in the individual competition is eighteen rounds; it's off by one because he didn't play in the individual competition in the first round match against Samsara. Well, how would Happy go about this match against Samsara? Coach Li, if Ye Xiu doesn't appear in the individual competition this match, will his win streak count as broken?" Pan Lin asked.

"From the way the Alliance calculates their statistics, this would count as breaking his win streak. A win streak constitutes continuous victories. If you stopped playing for one match then that breaks the continuity. If you then resumed and won, we could only call it a perfect win rate, and not a win streak," Li Yibo explained.

"Well Coach Li, do you think Ye Xiu will have a perfect win rate or maintain his win streak?" Pan Lin asked.

"I reckon Ye Xiu will not shy away. His win streak is like the insurance for Team Happy's morale. He would dampen it if he chose not to play," Li Yibo said.

"Then what about Samsara's side? Will they send out Zhou Zekai or Sun Xiang to attempt to end Ye Xiu's win streak?" Pan Lin started his guessing game once again.

"This will probably depend what the Samsara players themselves want. Er… it doesn't seem likely for Zhou Zekai to try. As for Sun Xiang, I think it's possible that he might even put himself forward," Li Yibo did not dare to be too concrete with his words.

"Haha, then let's wait and see!" The two commentators finally concluded their guessing game.

"Okay, the match is about to begin," Pan Lin saw that the referee has approached the players' stands of each team so they could send out their players.

"Let's see who Team Happy sends out!" Pan Lin called out, while the cameras quickly panned to Happy's player seats.

"Ye Xiu. It's Ye Xiu!!" Pan Lin shouted loudly.

At Happy's bench, Ye Xiu stood up, waved at the clamoring fans to acknowledge them, and walked towards the competition booths.

"What about Samsara!" Pan Lin continued shouting. The camera shots cut about wildly.

On Samsara's side, the first player for the individual competition also stood up.

It's… Jiang Botao…" Pan Lin said, after glancing at Li Yibo. This time, Happy didn't slap their faces; rather, it was Samsara. Albeit, it was more of a gentle pat across the cheek. Zhou Zekai? Sun Xiang? Neither appeared. Samsara has sent out their vice captain, the Spellblade player Jiang Botao.

"It looks like Samsara didn't want to allow Ye Xiu's win streak to disrupt their rhythm too much. Jiang Botao has been sent out in the first round of the individual competition quite frequently in the past. It looks like Samsara didn't put much thought into what we were discussing earlier. Let's see how Jiang Botao plans to play," Li Yibo skimmed over the arrangement.

Chapter 1290: Who counters who?

The match quickly began. The map that Ye Xiu chose with the home team advantage was once again a simple and straightforward one. The strategy that he chose was to fight head on. This was quite surprising as an old general's strongest weapon was experience. Choosing a map that contained a lot of complexities would be advantageous for him. But not Ye Xiu. Armed with the unspecialized, he would always pick a map that allowed him to play aggressively. And up until now, no one had been able to stand up to his aggression.

In this match against Happy, Samsara had not chosen to specifically counter this arrangement. As Li Yibo said, sending out Jiang Botao first was a very ordinary, comfortable arrangement for Samsara.

When the characters loaded and saw the simple map, there was nothing else to do but to charge forward!

"Senior, you can't keep winning! You have to leave us juniors something to aim to surpass!" Jiang Botao started chatting with Ye Xiu over the public chat. The Alliance had stressed that use of the voice chat was being discussed, but they had yet to reach a decision. For now, everything remained unchanged. This rule was not actually that important for the Alliance in terms of gameplay. Why did the Alliance ban voice chat in the beginning? It was for easier broadcasting. The players could not talk and had to use text to chat, making it easier for the viewers to see their communications and strategies. There was no other intention besides this. If the players used voice chat, then the broadcasters wouldn't have it as easy. Further, if they split the voice chat into a public one and two more, one for each team, then how do they decide which voice chat to tune in at any given time? Opening voice chat would allow the players to communicate fully, but the viewer's experience would not be the same as before, where they could catch every small detail in the communications.

The current scene was a great example. Everyone loved seeing the banter between players. If it were voice chat and the broadcaster had to switch the sound around, a lot would be missed.

In the end, the Alliance was currently still in discussions with the broadcasters with no outcome yet. For now, everyone was still using text to communicate in this match.

"Well of course!" on this side, Ye Xiu actually went and agreed with Jiang Botao. Everyone was surprised, but a second message followed quickly: "That's why I didn't play in Round 1! No matter how well I do, my win streak can only reach 37. See, I left you a whole round's worth to surpass!"

"Just play…" Jiang Botao wasn't really trash talking. He liked to chat a little with others. But now, he really couldn't keep chatting after what Ye Xiu said.

"Why don't you give Senior a hand? Perhaps just type GG?" Ye Xiu pressed on.

"Senior, please stop joking around," Jiang Botao said.

"It's not like it makes a difference in the outcome!" Ye Xiu continued.

"Regardless, I should at least give it a shot!" Jiang Botao wasn't affected by Ye Xiu's taunting. He still chatted as if this was a regular conversation.

The two characters met after these few words. Ye Xiu did not control Lord Grim use his long-ranged attacks hurriedly. He allowed the characters to continue to get closer. Just as he was about to step into the enemy Spellblade's attack range, Lord Grim suddenly accelerated!

Movement skill!

This had already become a signature move of the unspecialized Lord Grim. It seemed that Ye Xiu didn't plan to play cat and mouse with his opponent at a mid- to long-range; rather, he planned to get up close to deal with his opponent. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had always played like this. He had never kited his opponent, not even when equipped with plenty of mid- to long-range methods of attack, or against an opponent who could only attack at close range. He always fought aggressively for the initiative and used any means possible to seize it.

A Shining Cut flashed out, and Lord Grim raced forward several units in an instant. Jiang Botao already saw through Ye Xiu's intentions, and Empty Waves retreated back. He leapt backwards while the Silver shortsword Divine Chain glinted. An Earthquake Sword rolled forth!

Jiang Botao, the vice captain of Samsara, had gained increasing popularity by the year as Samsara won back to back championships. But his technical skill and style did not really have any uniqueness to it like many other players did. His play was very ordinary, neither unexpected nor low-key. Games would finish seemingly very naturally.

In other words, Jiang Botao's matches didn't have waves of highs and lows where large portions of health were traded. The damage would accumulate steadily, and he would eventually win by slowly accumulating small advantages. It didn't matter whether those who lost to him were ahead or behind during the match, they would always come out of it feeling like they lost by "that much". However, regardless of how little "that much" was, a loss was still a loss in the end.

At first, people were of the opinion that Jiang Botao had frighteningly accurate calculations. However, they gradually realised this was not the case. It was more accurate to say that he did not let a single detail slip.

Jiang Botao was that type of meticulous player, whether it was in the individual or team competitions. He would consider and deal with any possibility that would arise in battle. Because of this, it was very hard for anyone to score a high combo against him. Jiang Botao was seemingly a counter to Ye Xiu in this regard: Ye Xiu's unspecialized focused on an unbroken combo in a one on one.

Lord Grim charged forth aggressively before his eyes, but Jiang Botao was well prepared. Empty Waves had already leapt back and used an Earthquake Sword as Lord Grim activated his movement skills.

In this moment, it looked as if Lord Grim's Shining Cut wasn't closing the distance, but rather pushing him to headbutt the Earthquake Sword. No time to dodge? Most ordinary players would feel this way; however, for a pro player, there was room to dodge even though the two skills were fairly fast.

Left?

Or right?

Jiang Botao was fixated on Lord Grim's every move. Empty Waves took up another stance after his jump backwards, ready to send out another Wave Sword as soon as Lord Grim dodged.

Turns out, it was neither left nor right. Lord Grim still charged forth, but his shoulders forcefully lurched forward.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Ye Xiu chose not to dodge. Rather, he forcefully had Lord Grim activate this Striker skill. An increased defence would lessen the damage taken. For a skill like Earthquake Sword that swept away the target, however, the most troublesome thing about Reinforced Iron Bones was the Super Armor status that it grants.

Even so, Reinforced Iron Bones couldn't stop Empty Waves from sending out more attacks. However, this unexpected move from Ye Xiu still ended up making Jiang Botao hesitate for an instant. Jiang Botao was still paying all his attention to the left and right sides of his attack.

As the Silver weapon Divine Chain was raised for another attack, Lord Grim's hands already sent an object flying.

Puff!

It was only a soft sound, but thick, purple smoke quickly spread and engulfed the area. Lord Grim slipped out of Jiang Botao's field of view in a blink.

Ninja Tool: Smoke Bomb!

Jiang Botao froze.

Under the cover of the thick smoke, he had no idea about Lord Grim's position.

The thick smoke continued to spread. Were there any flow currents that seemed irregular?

Jiang Botao observed closely. If a character moved within the smoke, it would definitely disrupt its natural spread. Traces of movement could be spotted like this.

But, there weren't any!

No movement?

Impossible! Under this cover, why would Ye Xiu not attack? Then there was only one possibility!

Jiang Botao 's right hand swiped the mouse and his left hand flew across the keyboard. Empty Waves turned, stepped back and Divine Chain slashed outwards. Wave Wheel Slasher!

Lord Grim would suddenly appear behind him with a Shadow Clone Technique.

That was Jiang Botao's prediction.

Thus, Wave Wheel Slasher was unleashed, with intention to immobilize the opponent with sword waves. The purple smoke swirled and a part of it dissipated, but it didn't find a target. Lord Grim was nowhere to be seen.

Jiang Botao knew at this moment: This is bad…

A spurt of blood flew out from Empty Waves' neck. Lord Grim did indeed appear next to him and mercilessly delivered a Cut-Throat.

Did he use Shadow Clone Technique or some other movement skill? That was no longer important. Jiang Botao only knew that Ye Xiu used a timing difference perfectly. He completely predicted Jiang Botao's reaction.

Following the Cut-Throat, the short blade in Lord Grim's hand flicked again. The Assassin knock-up skill, Leaping Blade, sent Empty Waves into their air.

Falling Light Blade!

However, Empty Waves barely left the ground when he used this Swordsman low-level skill, and suddenly plummeted.

But…

Gore Cross!

Two perpendicular lines of blood appeared on Empty Waves' back. He avoided being sent into the air, but Lord Grim continued his attack and didn't dodge. This skill was chained so quickly that Empty Waves wouldn't have had a chance to completely get airborne. Jiang Botao's quick reaction seemed like it was playing right into Ye Xiu's hands.

The combo began.

"Guess what combo I can reach?" Ye Xiu actually took the time to throw out a message. Obviously, this was targeted towards the fact that Jiang Botao was rarely on the receiving end of a high combo.

"I don't think it will be that high," and Jiang Botao actually replied. Under these circumstances, he was still in the mood to chat.

"Yeah, seems like the combo was just a dream," when Ye Xiu sent this message, the combo reset to zero.

However, this did not mean Jiang Botao had a chance to escape. Ye Xiu's unspecialized Lord Grim only aimed for the combo effect, and not the combo statistic.

Fake Combo! His attacks continued to chain beautifully one after another.

"It really is difficult to deal with!" Jiang Botao sighed.

"A little too many details right?" Ye Xiu replied.

"Yeah… way too many." Jiang Botao had a headache.

Jiang Botao could counter Ye Xiu to an extent? It looked like this was the wrong call. In reality, Ye Xiu's unspecialized countered Jiang Botao. There were too many skills, too many ways to chain skills, and overall too many variations. If Jiang Botao really wanted consider every detail, his rhythm beginning from his thought process would be slow by a beat. Jiang Botao's brain had no way fully keep up with the amount of details for this opponent.

Jiang Botao fell.

Even though there were many struggles in the process, it didn't affect the final result.

"Next time, send someone else up," Ye Xiu smiled. He acknowledged the amount of trouble Jiang Botao had while facing him.

"Is there still a next time?" Jiang Botao was confused. The two teams have already met twice this season. The individual competition was done for them, so when would next time be?

"Oh, if you guys don't make the playoffs, then I guess there's no next time," Ye Xiu said.

This bold presumption of Samsara not making the playoffs again left everyone speechless.

Chapter 1291: Firing Line

Thus, Jiang Botao lost the first individual match.

19!

It seemed like Happy's fans had already prepared for this. After Ye Xiu won, the stadium was immediately filled with innumerable flashing signs.

Another match was added to this record and even Team Samsara weren't able to stop Ye Xiu's consecutive victories.

"10-0!!!" Someone very daringly yelled. Last time Happy had been crushed by Samsara ten to zero, but this time? At the very least, Samsara wouldn't have a chance like that anymore, but the possibility of Happy winning ten to zero was still there.

"That'll be rather difficult, won't it?" Commentator Pan Lin wondered aloud with a smile.

"Haha…" Li Yibo chuckled but didn't dare agree. In the individual match that had just end, he hadn't commentated much. He had been a little scared. As the match started, he had wanted to note that Jiang Botao's playstyle was somewhat of a counter to Ye Xiu's playstyle, but due to how small the map was, the two sides soon met and engaged, not giving him much of a chance.

At first he had thought it was a shame, but now, he was glad that he hadn't managed to get that chance.

The results of the match gave a very clear message. Jiang Botao's meticulous style had fallen apart in trying to keep up with Ye Xiu's unspecialized barrage.

He had almost gotten his face slapped… When he realized this, Li Yibo had subconsciously stroked his own face. It was a good thing he hadn't spoken up; after this realization, he immediately commented on how Ye Xiu's style countered Jiang Botao's.

Li Yibo, having managed to get to safety, finally got the chance to accurately display his ability as a commentator, and during Happy's match too. Even Pan Lin was impressed, but Li Yibo was cheering for his good fortune.

It seemed like reserving judgement had its benefits.

Li Yibo had finally grown some wisdom. In the past, he loved to rush to express his opinion first, then prove it through the match, thus showing off his analytical wisdom. However, he had recently found that more and more often, his analytical wisdom would head in the complete opposite direction. In the future, he'd have to be more patient, Li Yibo concluded from these experiences.

The second individual match soon began.

On Happy's side, Su Mucheng rose to the challenge while Samsara sent out Wu Qi. He was the Assassin player of the team and a member of their main roster during the two consecutive championships. But after Sun Xiang transferred in, he mostly appeared as the sixth player.

Launcher against Assassin, one with a very far range, one with a very close range. Both sides played cautiously. Su Mucheng kept a close eye on the distance between them, while Wu Qi didn't dare approach without an opportune moment.

"What a troublesome Assassin. Team Samsara surely has raised many very talented members! After Yang Cong, I'd say that he'd be a good choice for the Alliance's Number One Assassin." At the player stands, Ye Xiu commented on Wu Qi as he watched the match.

"True. He's patient and merciless. He's mastered all the characteristics an Assassin should have." Wei Chen nodded in agreement.

"Could it be that… Team Samsara will soon have a five All-Star line up?" Chen Guo wondered aloud at the side.

Ye Xiu and Wei Chen glanced at each other, their gazes considering.

"We'll have to see how popular their team is. If even after the votes are split up between the five players, all five are sent into the All-Stars, then that'd be terrifying," Fang Rui commented. He had analysed the situation objectively. All-Star voting was all up to the fans, so many of the votes were given blindly. Those fans loyal to their team would unhesitantly give the players their vote even if said players had yet to reach that level.

　

If all five of Samsara's got into the All-Stars, all supported by their fans, then that could only mean that their fanbase was large enough completely crush the fanbases of other teams. Otherwise, they'd have to gain the votes of unaffiliated fans. For Wu Qi, this was something he truly had no advantage in, a player who was so close to entering the All-Stars getting delegated to sixth player in the team competition due to Samsara's extremely grand line-up. And, with Samsara's strength, the sixth player had very little room to perform. Without a chance to display their talents, how would they gain popularity? What Ye Xiu was commenting on was, in the end, only strength. If you wanted to talk about popularity, there were too many subjective variables.

　

"Who knows? Maybe by the end of this season he'll be making a fuss about leaving Samsara!" Fang Rui laid this misfortune upon Samsara, head resting on his hands.

However, his logic wasn't faulty. If the other had the ability but no chance to show it, who knows what thoughts would spawn? More importantly, WU Qi had already won two championships as a member of Samsara's main roster. He might have higher pursuits now, such as a place in the team competition line up...

　

As Happy discussed Wu Qi's future with interest offstage, the two onstage were still testing the waters. The two were using movement and position to circle each other, trying to find an opening. Though Su Mucheng could maintain an offense with her range advantage, Wu Qi didn't give her much of a chance to launch an effective one.

As time ticked by, the match seemed like a game of tag. Su Mucheng kept chasing after Wu Qi, throwing all sorts of bombs at him.

"That's a little hasty," Wei Chen suddenly commented. His tone was concerned, clearly talking about Su Mucheng.

"Her attack efficiency is really low. If this continues, she'll have problems with her mana," Fang Rui also spoke up.

"Her opponent is baiting her into it," Ye Xiu noted.

It was the three of them who typically had more to say on matches. The rookies would sit around them and listen to learn something from it.

"Purposefully circling the boundaries of the map, baiting Su Mucheng into attacking, he's trying to deplete Dancing Rain's mana and wait for a chance to strike back." Since there were rookies listening in, Ye Xiu would often explain in more detail to help them understand.

"What if she just stops attacking altogether?" Luo Ji asked.

"She has to retract her offense carefully, pace it well. Her opponent planned this and isn't just attacking her mana, but her skill cooldowns too. If you abruptly stop an offensive and your skill tree isn't complete, then you'll usually leave many openings which the opponent can grasp. Thus, Su Mucheng generally paces her attacks well to suppress her opponents, but now she's losing her pace a little. If this continues, her Firing Line might expose an opening."

Firing Lines were a term unique to Launchers. A Launcher's offensive relied on depth and layering. The further away a target was, the lower the accuracy of attacks; the closer they were, the riskier it would be for the Launcher. Every Launcher had a Firing Line of optimal distance unique to them which depended on their skill level and playstyle, as well as their mastery of different skills. This was the distance at which a Launcher could maintain the strongest offensive, termed the Firing Line. If you wanted to break through a Launcher's offensive suppression, then breaking past their Firing Line was crucial. To do this, one had to understand how each Launcher maintained and operated their Firing Line - which skills they preferred to use, how they arranged these skills, what methods and pacing they were used to - and think of a way to break through.

This was relatively basic theoretical knowledge in Glory, and after playing Glory for so long, there was no need for Ye Xiu to explain these basic ideas to Happy's rookies anymore. He just had to make sure they understood that what Wu Qi was currently doing was aimed at throwing Su Mucheng's Firing Line into chaos. To do this, he had displayed admirable patience, forcing Su Mucheng to mess up the rhythm she had been maintaining so well.

Boom boom boom!

　

Onstage, Dancing Rain sent another round of cannonfire. Her attacks were converging more and more. Under this dense firepower, Wu Qi didn't seem to be holding up very well. However, he didn't let his Assassin character Cruel Silence hide completely, continuing to expose himself to Dancing Rain's line of sight, baiting the other into attack.

Boom boom boom!

The attacks continued without pause, but offstage, the frowns of Wei Chen, Fang Rui and the others continued to get deeper.

"This isn't good!" Fang Rui exclaimed.

　

Just as he said this, Wu Qi's Cruel Silence, who had been jumping around and dodging for so long, suddenly grew bold and shot forwards like an arrow.

　　

"See! There was an opening, he's gotten past the Firing Line!" Fang Rui exclaimed. In the past, they had been opponents and now they were teammates, so he understood Su Mucheng's Firing Line rather well. After considering things from Wu Qi's perspective, he could even figure out approximately what the other planned to do next.

Of course, Wu Qi's thoughts wouldn't mirror Fang Rui's exactly, but they had caught more or less the same opening. Su Mucheng's Firing Line was getting rather patchy. She had been unable to execute her original fearsome offense to perfection due to the lack of a few certain skills.

I can get past!

In that moment, that was Wu Qi's only thought. Cruel Silence, went full speed, not wanting to waste a single moment of this opportunity, and charged towards Dancing Rain in an attempt to break through her Firing Line in one go.

"Haha…" Just as everyone in Happy was on the edge of their seats in worry for Su Mucheng, Ye Xiu chuckled.

"What are you laughing at?" Chen Guo asked.

"A cunning rabbit has three burrows*, have you ever heard of that?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Of course, what about it?" Chen Guo couldn't understand.

"Who said that you could only have one Firing Line?" Ye Xiu chuckled.

Never mind those old and young pro players, even Chen Guo immediately understood with that.

Onstage, the cannonfire didn't stop. Su Mucheng naturally wouldn't stay there like a sitting duck and let her opponent close in. She had Dancing Rain continue to hinder her opponent's momentum. However, Wu Qi had already judged Su Mucheng's Firing Line to be messed up and incapable of blocking his momentum.

He got through!

Just as Cruel Silence took another step forwards, Wu Qi let out a breath of relief. He had already broken through Su Mucheng's Firing Line, so the firepower at the following distances would only get weaker. In addition, the other might make mistakes in her panic as he closed in.

It was all coming to an end!

As Wu Qi thought this, boom boom boom, with three bangs, three Anti-Tank Missiles came soaring over.

It was just a low level skill so Wu Qi didn't think much of it, easily having Cruel Silence pass through the missiles.

Continue forward!

This was the only thought on his mind.

But...

What was happening? The firepower didn't seem to be weakening?

Wu Qi, darting in and out of cannonfire, realized that his charge was very unsuccessful and didn't achieve the results he had hoped for at all. He couldn't help but turn his head and look back. There wasn't anything wrong, Su Mucheng's Firing Line should've been left in the dust behind him! Yet this offensive...

Chapter 1292: Composed Samsara

"Not just one Firing Line…"

Spectators often had a clearer view of the overall situation, and Samsara's players had realized the crux of the problem at this point, too. Wu Qi hadn't managed to break through, but instead had fallen into an attack arrangement that Su Mucheng had set up for him.

But… Su Mucheng wasn't a new player! The Golden Generation, joining the alliance in Season 4, had become well-know very early on and gained fame rapidly, meaning that they had long since been researched by the other teams. The Firing Line wasn't something new. From the very beginning, finding the Firing Line was the heart of researching a Launcher. Su Mucheng's Firing Line was no secret, hadn't been for a long time, and wouldn't have remained one for long anyways.

Because this was a competition, everyone would give it their all on the field, and the Firing Line was each Launcher's DPS limit. In competitions, players often felt that their best wasn't enough, so who would hold anything back? Unless, of course, you were bullying someone with skill far inferior to yours, then you wouldn't need to give it your all. Even so, there wouldn't be a disparity of skill so big between anyone who had the ability to get into the Alliance, at least to the extent that one could bully the other.

Samsara's members exchanged looks. Happy wasn't an opponent they would underestimate, and Su Mucheng wasn't an easy opponent to fight. Even if they had crushed Happy 10 to 0 in the previous match, this round they would only be more prepared. However, they really hadn't thought that Su Mucheng had more than one Firing Line. She hadn't even hinted at such a talent in the previous matches.

"She's gotten better," Zhou Zekai suddenly said.

The others frowned, continuing to watch the match. Under Dancing Rain's cannonfire, Wu Qi's Cruel Silence didn't have any success closing in. Dancing Rain casually pulled away further as she blasted him. The distance between them slowly grew until...

"The Firing Line!" Jiang Botao called out. This distance was where the Firing Line they were familiar with was at. Cruel Silence had been suppressed by the attacks, Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain slowly pull away, and just like that, Cruel Silence, who had already broken through Su Mucheng's first Firing Line, was pushed back into it again.

Cannonfire poured down like a storm and this offensive was clearly a step above the previous one. This was Su Mucheng's true Firing Line, the one Wu Qi had originally broken through. Yet, he hadn't imagined that there would be another Firing Line hidden behind this one which disrupted his charge and sent him back.

That unknown Firing Line had already caused Wu Qi huge problems in his advance, and the current one he was caught in was what everyone knew to be Su Mucheng's true, strongest Firing Line.

Under the blasts, Cruel Silence's health dropped at an alarming rate. What experienced player wouldn't know what would happen when you were in a Launcher's Firing Line? Launchers wouldn't stand there like an idiot and just DPS but adjust themselves according to the opponent's response to ensure their target remained in their Firing Line. It was easy to get into a Firing Line, but much harder to get out of one.

Samsara's players all turned to look at Sun Xiang simultaneously. He had been teammates with her for half a year, after all.

　　

"Did you know she had this level of skill?" Lu Boyuan nudged Sun Xiang, asking.

　

Sun Xiang shook his head, face filled with confusion. In reality, when he had arrived in Excellent Era, the Spear and Cannon Duo that had been established in Season 2 met an untimely death. Though One Autumn Leaf and Dancing Rain had both still been in the team, they had lost the sense of partnership they had in the past. Sun Xiang was rather depressed at this, but Su Mucheng's professionalism was flawless; they just didn't have that sort of chemistry. Partnerships did somewhat depend on fate. It wasn't uncommon for forced partnerships to end in an absolute mess in the Alliance.

However, even as teammates, Sun Xiang really didn't know that Su Mucheng had all these tricks with her Firing Line.

"With her skill, I think she can probably maintain her Firing Line at a wider range. What do you think, Little Zhou?" Jiang Botao said.

"Yeah," Zhou Zekai nodded.

"However, she purposefully controlled her skill use, focusing on the range of her Firing Line. But because it was so focused, she could combine and use the skills that were freed up interchangingly to split off a second Firing Line…" Jiang Botao analyzed.

The Samsara players around them all nodded. They weren't like Happy, full of rookies. Samsara's line-up was the most stable in years. This group of players had grown together, gained experience together. They understood and complemented one another very well. Communication was simple and convenient for them. Samsara's two consecutive championships was a result of these players growing to their peak. Luck would always play a factor in who became the champions, but this luck could only be grasped if you had enough power.

　

Now, this championship team managed to analyze Su Mucheng's current playstyle completely with just a few sentences.

"How cunning," Jiang Botao continued to comment.

"Yeah… If needed, I believe she could increase the range of her Firing Line, instead of splitting it into two like this," Lu Boyuan agreed.

"However, she didn't do that. She held back, making her choices seem more varied. She's managed to maintain great control over this," Jiang Botao sighed.

　

"It's not looking good for Wu Qi!" Blade Master player Du Ming exclaimed.

Everyone fell silent. It was a shame that the person they had admiring was their opponent. If their opponent performed well, then it meant trouble for them. However, the confidence of a championship team wasn't anything to scoff at. Faced with an impending loss, their mood seemed very calm, not at all panicking because of two consecutive losses.

In the end, it was Su Mucheng who claimed victory. The cheering in Xiao Shan Stadium drew on for a good while.

　

This was Samsara, after all! That immensely powerful Samsara, and yet, Team Happy was currently leading 2 to 0!

Wu Qi returned to the player bench. He was naturally in a rather bad mood due to his loss.

"That really was too sly of her!" Accepting the towel his teammates handed over, Wu Qi wiped his hands before throwing the towel onto his seat dispiritedly. It was clear that, in the end, he had figured out what was going on with Su Mucheng's Launcher.

"We'll watch out next time," his teammates consoled him.

"Watch this, I'll avenge you!" Lu Boyuan said.

"It's not a group arena, avenge my ass." Wu Qi glared.

"You can avenge yourself later in the team competition," Jiang Botao told him.

"Am I in the starting line-up for the team competition?" Wu Qi's eyes shone.

　

"Ahem!" Jiang Botao cleared his throat. "Next time, next time."

Wu Qi returned to his dispirited state. In reality, they had already gone over the line-up before in the prep room prior to the match. It was exceedingly rare for a team to wait until the match itself to announce their line-up to the players. Wu Qi already knew that he would still be the sixth player for the team competition. He was just expressing his desire to be a part of the starting line-up. Seeing his state, his other team members started laughing. Getting into the team competition starting line-up for Samsara was very difficult nowadays. However, Samsara was a team with a truly impressive atmosphere, able to discuss this rather sensitive topic freely.

　

"Well, I'm off," Lu Boyuan said to his teammates before he headed off. On Happy's side, their third player was also a Fighter class player, Steamed Bun.

"Aiya, it's this guy. If I lose, you can't blame me, okay? That guy's hella weird!" Seeing Happy's next player, Lu Boyuan hurriedly turned back to speak with his teammates.

"If you lose, you can hand your place in the starting line-up to me!" Du Ming hollered.

"Hand it to me!"

"Me me me!"

All the players on rotation joined in. Lu Boyuan smiled, already walking towards the stage.

"As expected of a championship team…" Happy's members were also paying attention to the situation with Samsara.

　

After two consecutive losses in the individual round, the team wasn't at all panicked. This team didn't have any very experienced veterans, but they were all very composed players. This might be the result of the confidence gained in these two years as two-time consecutive champions. Even opening with two losses wouldn't impact their confidence. The psychological advantage that taking a lead had was completely lost when faced with Samsara. On the contrary, their confidence, their composure, their leisurely attitude would unstabilize their opponents.

However… considering that Happy's third player was Steamed Bun, there was no such setting that would make him feel unnerved. Chest puffed out and head held high, Steamed Bun got onto the stage with several long strides. He gained quite a lot of cheers.

Compared to the rest of the Alliance, Team Happy's line-up was one of the least stable. Steamed Bun didn't have all that many opportunities to perform but he was quite popular amongst the Happy supporters since he could always bring surprises to the match. A match with Steamed Bun was never boring.

"Samsara's third player is Lu Boyuan. This player is a model competitive player. He has great mental fortitude and his forte is performing at his peak under pressure, turning the tables on his opponent. After falling behind by two points, he's the third to come up, but this is exactly the type of situation which he performs well in!" Pan Lin commentated on the two players in the live television broadcast.

"As for Happy, they've sent out Bao Rongxing. Eh, this player… He's a very… well, no matter where he is, he's a player who has a very inconsistent performance. Do you agree, advisor Li?" Pan Lin asked.

　

"Ahem!" Li Yibo coughed.

　

"Ahem ahem!" Li Yibo coughed more.

"Bao Rongxing is the one player that can bring the most unexpected of situations to a match," Li Yibo concluded. A player that was so unpredictable really wasn't one he dared to predict anything about.

"Alright, now the match will start," Pan Lin announced.

　

On the field, the characters were loaded into the maps. For Happy, Brawler Steamed Bun Invasion; for Samsara, Glory's current Number One Grappler, Chaotic Cloudy Mountains.

"Alright, let the match start! Both characters are running directly for the center," Pan Lin called out.

"Lu Boyuan struck first! Don't Grapplers usually wait for the opponent to make a move and then counter, Advisor Li?" Pan Lin asked.

"Yes, because grabs are the highest priority skills in Glory, so Grapplers have the ability to break through an opponent's offense. Using grabs during an opponent's offense is usually harder for the opponent to deal with," Li Yibo said.

"But Lu Boyuan is really taking the initiative here!"

"Samsara has, after all, lost two matches in succession. They need to be fierce in order to raise their morale!" Li Yibo explained.

Just as he finished speaking, Lu Boyuan sent a message. "I'm not gonna give you a chance to mess things up, man!"

"Advisor Li?" Pan Lin turned his head towards Li Yibo.

Li Yibo had a bitter expression. What was up with people today; how come even Team Samsara decided to start slapping the faces of commentators?

Chapter 1293: Being Too Skilled Can Become An Opening Too

"Too messy!" Steamed Bun sent a head-shaking sighing emoji like a teacher lecturing a student. Then, Steamed Bun Invasion faced Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's attack directly.

Circle Sweep Kick!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountains leaped into the air and looked as if he were trying to step on Steamed Bun Invasion. However, everyone knew that Grapplers had all sorts of grab skills. Getting kicked wasn't the scary part. It was the sweep following the kick that was terrifying. The sweep had grab priority, and it knocked the target to the ground.　

Steamed Bun looked like he knew about the threat of this skill. He didn't use a skill to fight force with force. Instead, he rushed forward aggressively and then dodged to the side.

Lu Boyuan was watching Steamed Bun Invasion's movements closely. If Steamed Bun didn't move too far away, he would still be able to hook onto the target if he adjusted his Circle Sweep Kick. But when Steamed Bun Invasion dodged, he strode three steps. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's legs weren't that long. His attack was dodged cleanly. But Lu Boyuan still had his Chaotic Cloudy Mountain finish the sweep in the air. Even though it didn't hit a target, it stopped his character's aerial momentum.

Whoosh!

Steamed Bun Invasion threw a Brick. His prediction was off, and the Brick whistled by Chaotic Cloud Mountain.　　

"Oh! You've got some skill!" Steamed Bun Invasion praised his opponent. At this moment, Steamed Bun Invasion slid forward, wanting to attack with a Tiger Flips the Mountain when Chaotic Cloudy Mountain fell.

Lu Boyuan saw everything clearly and didn't say a word. Just when his character was about to touch the ground and the instant Steamed Bun Invasion's arm smashed towards him, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain suddenly raised his two legs, twisting onto Steamed Bun Invasion's shoulders.　

Aerial Twist!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain twisted in the air, and his two legs, wrapped around Steamed Bun Invasion's shoulder, threw him onto the ground.

Lu Boyuan used this grab skill for a dismantle effect. Being able to stop Tiger Flips the Mountains using such precise manipulation of a skill required incredible perception.

Samsara's fans fired up. Even though it was just a skill hitting, it was a brilliant play.

The attacks weren't over yet though.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had wrapped around Steamed Bun Invasion's shoulders and flipped him towards the ground, but the throw wasn't aimed directly downwards. Midway, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain loosened his legs and landed on the ground first. He then stepped forward and reached out with his hands, catching the tumbling Steamed Bun Invasion.

Overhead Toss!

Anothing skill was released. Steamed Bun Invasion was grabbed by Chaotic Cloudy Mountain and thrown towards the ground. A huge rumble exploded. Just the sound alone told how heavy this throw was. It still wasn't over yet though.

Ground Toss!

While one arm threw Steamed Bun Invasion onto the ground, the other hand stretched forward and grabbed him again, not leaving Steamed Bun Invasion any time to roll away. His arm hoisted him up and threw him back into the air.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain jumped up high. This time, he used both hands to grab Steamed Bun Invasion and then: Slam Dunk!

With matchless strength, Steamed Bun Invasion was thrown fiercely towards the ground This high-level skill's power was no small matter. Steamed Bun Invasion smashed into the ground, forming a crater. From the way his body was bent, it looked like his back had snapped.

With just this brief combo, Steamed Bun Invasion had lost a fifth of his health. It hadn't even been ten seconds since the two characters had met. Luo Boyuan's efficiency made everyone gasp in awe. The Samsara fans were already going crazy. Happy's fans couldn't help but start to sweat for Steamed Bun.

Lu Boyuan didn't get distracted by the previous combo. After Slam Dunk, he immediately pounced on Steamed Bun Invasion.

Brick!

Steamed Bun Invasion leaped out from that crater, while also throwing a Brick. His attack had been quite sudden. However, after a season of competitive play, Steamed Bun's crazed love for Brick, which was often used as soon as it went off cooldown whether or not it made any sense, had become a signature move for him. How could pro players not catch onto this and fall for it again and again?

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain sidestepped it, dodging the Brick, and continued to press closer.

Sand Toss, Poison Needle, Molotov Cocktail.　

Steamed Bun looked like he was panicked and was throwing whatever he could at his opponent. How could such a brainless offensive stump Lu Boyuan? Chaotic Cloudy Mountain continued to press closer and closer.　　

Brick!

Another Brick!　　

After a few more skills, the Brick came off cooldown again and Steamed Bun Invasion immediately used it without any hesitation.　

Lu Boyuan didn't know whether to laugh or cry. Had this guy been thrown silly? What the heck was this?　　

"Has Bao Rongxing lost it?" On the broadcast, Pan Lin was dumbfounded. There didn't seem to be any hints of thought behind Steamed Bun's moves. He just looked to be throwing things randomly. He looked completely powerless. An extra being helpless against the hero was common in movies, but this was the Pro Alliance. It was said that there were no weak players in the pro circle, but this ridiculous performance seemed to show otherwise!

Li Boyi also thought the same, but he resisted opening his mouth. This Bao Rongxing always pulled out the biggest surprises. Casually declaring a verdict wouldn't be good. It would be better to keep watching. Maybe he was currently trying something crazy. What if it takes effect immediately afterwards?

Li Yibo thought in this way. Lu Boyuan didn't dare be careless either. They had studied Steamed Bun's matches in particular, but apart from his love for Bricks, he didn't seem to follow any other rules. There wasn't much that could be done for pre-planning against this sort of opponent. He just had to perform well when the time came. Focus! Focus was important because Steamed Bun could suddenly pull out a trick from nowhere. Sometimes Steamed Bun's plays would be brilliant, other times his plays would be stupid. If he didn't focus, maybe the stupid play might work out. Quite a few players had fallen against this rookie. And after they lost, they would complain to the reporters incessantly and looked as if they could go on for three days and three nights.

Lu Boyuan didn't want to capsize like them, so even if Steamed Bun looked like he was lost, he didn't let down his guard. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain once again pressed towards Steamed Bun Invasion. Lu Boyuan didn't force his way through. He used a low-level Fling as a probe for the start of his next round of attacks.

Lu Boyuan stared closely at Steamed Bun Invasion's movements. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's two hands reached out, but then he saw Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly crouch down. His right knee lifted up, while his left foot pushed off the ground.

Powerful Knee Strike!

This skill name flashed through Lu Boyuan's mind. Which attack was faster, Fling or Powerful Knee Strike? The answer was clear in an instant.

Powerful Knee Strike would arrive first, but Fling could be saved through some adjustments. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain crouched down, while his two hands reached upwards. He was planning to Fling his opponent once the Powerful Knee Strike passed. Lu Boyuan once again displayed his precise judgement, but this time, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain did all this for nothing. The Powerful Kee Strike he had been anticipating didn't appear.

All of the viewers saw what had happened.　　

Steamed Bun Invasion had lifted his right knee and his left foot pushed against the ground, but he didn't soar through the air. This attack wasn't a Powerful Knee Strike. It was just a normal one. But the problem was that for a normal knee strike, this distance was too long; it didn't even reach Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. It was a complete miss.

Steamed Bun Invasion raised his knee, minding his own business, and didn't hit the target. However, not hitting the target seemed to have the same effect. When Steamed Bun Invasion was two steps away, Chaotic Cloudy appeared to have been hit by the knee strike. His body crumbled and bent, his two arms went up into the air as if he were surrendering.

Everyone was dumbfounded at this strange scene.　　

When Lu Boyuan saw that he had predicted wrong, he knew that the situation wasn't good. But when he tried to adjust Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's position, crack!

The crisp clear sound of bones shattering could be heard by everyone. After Steamed Bun Invasion feinted a knee strike, he suddenly used a real Powerful Knee Strike. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was still crouched down. Right when he was about to retreat, this Powerful Knee Strike hit Chaotic Cloudy Mountain square in the chest.

Everyone's hearts turned cold at the sound of this crackling. It was as if they could feel the pain from this attack themselves. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain fell backwards, and Lu Boyuan immediately Quick Recovered. Steamed Bun Invasion's Powerful Knee Strike had been extremely fast though. He landed on the ground and followed with a Tyrannical Chain Punch, beating on the fallen Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

Lu Boyuan was depressed!

Focus, focus! He had been so focused, yet he had still fallen for a trick. That hadn't been a Powerful Knee Strike previously, but a regular knee strike. Using a regular knee strike made absolutely no sense. It wouldn't be able to hit anything. It wouldn't be able to block anything. If Chaotic Cloudy Mountain hadn't dodged it and continued forward, Steamed Bun would be in the grasp of his hands. But the problem was that not a single brain cell of his thought that this would be a regular knee strike. Had he baited himself?　

Lu Boyuan couldn't help but think about what had happened previously as Steamed Bun Invasion pummeled him. If that had been a trap, then Steamed Bun was truly bold. It was because he was skilled enough that he could react in that instant. If it hadn't been him, if it had been a random player from the game, Lu Boyuan was certain that Steamed Bun Invasion would instead be the one pressed to the ground.

An opening had appeared because he had been too skilled?

Luo Boyuan couldn't accept it.

Tyrannical Chain Punch ended, and Steamed Bun Invasion leaped back. Lu Boyuan recovered and had Chaotic Cloudy Mountain get up. As soon as looked up, he saw Steamed Bun Invasion's knee rise up again.

Powerful Knee Strike!

Lu Boyuan was just about to have Chaotic Cloudy Mountain dodge to the side, but then he saw that Steamed Bun Invasion didn't fly forward. It was another empty knee strike. Lu Boyuan only then remembered, Powerful Knee Strike had just been used. That wasn't a low-level skill. It couldn't be off cooldown yet.

"You're crazy!!" Lu Boyuan lost his cool. Using a normal knee strike at that distance? Apart from crazy, there was no other explanation. Just when he blurted this out, Steamed Bun Invasion raised his arms and threw a Brick.

"A Brick again? Is that all you know?" Lu Boyuan shouted as Chaotic Cloudy Mountain dodged. He wasn't the type of person who liked to talk a lot during a match, but facing this opponent, Lu Boyuan felt like if he didn't vent, he would choke to death.

Chapter 1294: Thought Process Off Target

The audience members looked at one another.

As Lu Boyuan had thought, it was precisely because he was too skilled that he was hit by the Powerful Knee Strike. If it were a normal player, then they would've already used a Fling to throw Steamed Bun Invasion to the ground.

　

The viewers definitely comprised of normal players, so they didn't understand why Chaotic Cloudy Mountains had ducked down low before straightening up with his arms in air like he was surrendering. As Lu Boyuan cursed, wondering what the hell Steamed Bun was trying to do, the viewers, who had no idea what was actually going on, were trying to figure out what the hell Lu Boyuan was trying to do.

Right now, Lu Boyuan, someone who usually didn't speak much during matches, was yelling in the channel. Words like "are you fucking crazy" and the such could probably count as personal attacks, if pressed.

Lu Boyuan had completely lost it!

It wasn't just the audience who thought so; even the live commentator Pan Lin was commenting on this. Lu Boyuan's current state was just too far from his usual self.

"Calm down!" No one would've expected that, onstage, Lu Boyuan's opponent Steamed Bun would send a message admonishing him.

"Panicking like that isn't proper." Another followed. Where had Steamed Bun learned all this from?

"Fuck!" Lu Boyuan exclaimed. Why the hell was this guy suddenly scolding him?! They were opponents, okay? What the hell does my panic have anything to do with you?! And plus, I'm not panicking!

As Steamed Bun scolded the other, his actions didn't stop. With his Brick a miss, he did a Sand Toss.

Lu Boyuan wasn't in the calmest of states right now, but he wasn't panicking either. Chaotic Cloudy Mountains dodged perfectly. After Sand Toss, Steamed Bun Invasion continued to close, but Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountain wasn't a ranged class, so there was nothing he wanted more than for his opponent to be close. As Steamed Bun Invasion closed in, he naturally wouldn't retreat and just observed the other's motions. Lu Boyuan decided to forgo taking the initiative and returned to the usual style of Grapplers, waiting for his opponent to make the first move and countering. He'd see what tricks this guy had up his sleeves.

Thus, Steamed Bun Invasion arrived in front of Chaotic Cloudy Mountains as the latter slowed down his pace on purpose.

Brick!

Lu Boyuan was close to tears.

Was this really the legendary use-immediately-after-cooldown style?

To be honest, if you really wanted to calculate this kind of pacing, it would be very troublesome. Although Brick wasn't a low-level skill, it wasn't very high either. It was a skill Brawlers learned very soon after advancing classes and had a short cooldown. Considering the frequency at which Steamed Bun used the skill, calculating the cooldown of this skill would be very distracting.

This was probably the real motive behind his frequent usage...

A skill like Brick didn't deal much damage, but because of its crowd control, you had to be wary of it. Steamed Bun, using this skill so frequently and making it so that his opponent's had to stay on guard against it was very distracting for his opponents. In addition, this guy often used his skills in a chaotic mess, suddenly throwing in some troublesome skill; it really was quite hard to guard against!

Lu Boyuan felt like he had discovered something; he felt like he was close to figuring out his opponent's thought process.

However, this seemly random and completely mindless use of Brick Throw wouldn't just distract the opponent, it would also disrupt your own rhythm! After all, skill usage needed to be paced. Sometimes a different skill would evidently work better in this scenario, but Steamed Bun just always chose Brick. Wasn't that a little wasteful?

Lu Boyuan, who had thought he was beginning to understand, realized that his logic didn't work out after considering it a little more.

Lu Boyuan's thoughts, very unfortunately, went down an erroneous path. He had started trying to figure out Steamed Bun's thought process and rationalizing the other's actions from a theoretical perspective. And this was something that even Ye Xiu, who had far more experience and time with Steamed Bun, had failed to accomplished in two years.

As for why Steamed Bun liked Bricks, that was something Ye Xiu could explain to Lu Boyuan. It was because Bricks were easy to come by and unsuspecting. After you used them, you could just toss them aside to get rid of the weapon.

Trying to use Glory theories to figure out this problem would only get further and further away from the truth of the matter. Lu Boyuan was thinking himself into a mess. It was true that counterattacking was a Grappler's primary style. However, this style required you to have a precise understanding of your opponent's style, a decisive judgement, quick eyes, and steady hands.

Yet right now, the one Lu Boyuan was trying to figure out was Steamed Bun. Steamed Bun, the mystery that even Ye Xiu had failed to figure out after two years.

　

And so he lost.

He lost without knowing how he lost in a complete mess. It was only when Chaotic Cloudy Mountains fell that Lu Boyuan woke up from his stupor of trying to figure out Steamed Bun.

　

He lost just like that?

　

Lu Boyuan was shocked. He had been under this strange impression that there was plenty of time, and he had plenty of health. Trying to figure out Steamed Bun was like losing yourself in an abyss.

After leaving the booth, Lu Boyuan was still scratching his head. As he walked back to the bench, he kept looking up at the playback on the big screen. It wasn't until he was back at the bench that he smacked himself on the forehead, "Fuck, I'm so dumb!"

When he had gone up there, it was with the decision to take the initiative more and not give this weird player any chances to play tricks. Why did he end up trying to figure out his opponent as he fought?

"My willpower wasn't strong enough!" Lu Boyuan bemoaned.

"I don't know why, but there was a moment where I thought to myself, I can't play like this, I have to figure him out," Lu Boyuan explained.

　

"And somehow as you were trying to figure him out, you lost, right?" Wu Qi said.

"Yeah," Lu Boyuan nodded.

"It's 3 to 0 now, hey!" Jiang Botao reminded everyone. Right now they really were falling behind. Happy's fans were screaming and cheering, yelling thunderously about a flawless victory. As for Samsara's accompanying fanclub, they were much more subdued. They had actually lost every round in the individual competition. That really was a hit to their morale.

"Hey, did you guys actually fight seriously?" Du Ming asked the three individual competition players.

The three looked at one another.

"It's competition, there'll always be losses every now and then," Cleric player Fang Minghua comforted everyone.

"We'll take back two points in the group arena!" Sun Xiang stood. He was the first player for the group arena.

"Good luck!" His teammates encouraged.

"One versus three!" Someone said.

"No, don't, I wanna go up. I want to fight that sister in Happy," Du Ming hurriedly disagreed.

"You want to take revenge?" Everyone mocked him. They all naturally remembered how Du Ming had fought Tang Rou at the All-Stars Weekend. Back then, Tang Rou hadn't even been a pro player, just a noob, but her ferocious and relentless attitude left a deep impression. It was also then that Du Ming had lost face, getting humiliated by Tang Rou before being annihilated by Ye Xiu. He had been depressed for quite some time after that.

"I remember Ye Xiu also fought you back then, how come you don't go looking for him for revenge?" A teammate immediately asked.

"What revenge? I just want to spar," Du Ming said.

"Is it because she's pretty?" Wu Qi grinned, an arm around his shoulders, "I mean, she really is quite pretty."

"Fuck off," Du Ming pushed him away.

After falling behind 0 to 3, the atmosphere around Samsara was still as natural as ever. No one jumped up yelling something like "we have to win the next round" or anything. However, none of them lacked this determination.

In the live broadcast, Pan Lin was analyzing the line-ups the two teams might possibly have set, while Li Yibo felt like he was just waking from a dream. He was shocked to realize that he hadn't made a single comment throughout the past three matches. Pan Lin had thrown the discussion to him a couple of times but he had gotten by with just a few noncommittal noises. He had been ever so careful like that and ended up not giving any analysis whatsoever.

He had to make his presence more evident! Li Yibo, suddenly awake from his stupor, listened to Pan Lin's analysis, and hurriedly found a place to interrupt.

"Yes!" Li Yibo continued Pan Lin's train of thought. "Samsara's group arena line up has been constant with Sun Xiang first and Zhou Zekai as the last line of defense, with a few players on rotation in the middle. As for Happy, starting with Fang Rui and ending with Tang Rou is also a relatively consistent line up. From the line ups, Samsara seems to have a slight advantage. And the advantages in the group arena stack. I'm wondering if Happy will make adjustments to counter Samsara's line-up. In Happy's line-up…"

"Happy's player is coming onstage!" That was when Pan Lin suddenly announced.!

"Ah, yes, it's… Fang Rui…" Li Yibo felt rather helpless when he said the name. He had only just wondered aloud if Happy would make any adjustments or not, and then Happy had decided to use their usual line-up. Li Yibo felt depressed! He didn't dare finish his thought on Happy. He had been prepared to talk about this possibility and then emphasize the possibility of Happy's line-up remaining unchanged. But he hadn't even gotten halfway there when Happy's player entered the field! There was a small break between the individual competition and the group arena, could you not be so eager to fight? Do you all have something against me? Li Yibo was going to cry.

"Yes, Happy's Fang Rui seems to have decided to get into the player booth early. Let's see, as for Samsara, oh, Samsara's player has decided to get onto the field, too. It's Sun Xiang; seems like neither team has any intention of deviating from their usual arrangements," Pan Lin noted.

"Er, in this match, from the individual competition to the group arena now, it seems like neither team has decided to make any special arrangements to counter the other. They're treating the match as a normal match and haven't made special preparations in accordance to their opponent's identity," Li Yibo could only say.

"But Samsara is already behind by three points. They won't have a good time in the following games. Will they really be beaten ten to zero, like the audience is cheering for? Then Happy really would've taken their revenge," Pan Lin wondered. If this was like before, the idea of Happy winning a flawless victory against Samsara would probably make most people laugh their heads off, but now even the live broadcast was discussing this possibility in a serious fashion. The rise of Happy's position and power in people's minds was truly something terrifying to behold.

"We'll have to see how Samsara performs." Li Yibo didn't think Happy could do it. However, he didn't dare make any predictions. This was Happy, and even when he was being extremely cautious, they still managed to slap him in the face. It was better if he didn't make too many predictions like that!

"Both players have entered their booths, but it seems that the referee is going to wait for the break to finish. Coach Li, could you give us your view on this match between Fang Rui and Sun Xiang?" Pan Lin asked.

My view your ass! I don't want to do these pre-match predictions! Li Yibo cursed internally.

Chapter 1295: The Patient Sun Xiang

Despite being pushed beyond his ability, Li Yibo still had to say a few words. He didn't dare ascertain which side had the advantage though, so he just introduced the traits of each player. Meanwhile, Pan Lin was feeling down. He could do an introduction. The purpose of the guest commentator was to provide a deeper level of analysis! He could understand where Li Yibo was coming from though, so he didn't pursue it. The two chatted for the break period, and then the group arena officially began.

Happy - Fang Rui, Boundless Sea.

Samsara - Sun Xiang, One Autumn Leaf.

As for the map, since Fang Rui played dirty, he naturally wouldn't be like Ye Xiu and pick a wide open field. This particular group arena map had numerous holes and ditches. As soon as Boundless Sea loaded into the map, he immediately hid in one of the holes and vanished. This trench-filled map had many intersecting ditches. Players who wanted to move stealthily would have an easier time.

Boundless Sea leaped down into a trench and skillfully maneuvered around without needing to look up to figure out his position. Shortly afterwards, Boundless Sea made it to the center of the map and then headed towards a narrow ditch on the side. He quietly peeked his head above the ground but was blocked by a stone tablet. He carefully exposed half of his head and then looked outwards.

Fang Rui's familiarity with this map didn't need to be said, but unfortunately, Boundless Sea couldn't find anything in his field of view. To his surprise, One Autumn Leaf was not at the center of the map.

Fang Rui was astonished and checked who his opponent was again subconsciously. Correct, it was One Autumn Leaf, and the player was Sun Xiang, not Ye Xiu who had been as dirty as him in the past.

Sun Xiang… he didn't charge to the center of the stage? Sun Xiang also moved strategically?

This was truly outside of Fang Rui's expectations. From his understanding, like Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe, Sun Xiang looked down on this sort of playing. These new generation players preferred to happily battle it out at the center.

Sun Xiang maintained this same style this season with Samsara, but he suddenly switched it up this match. Was this because his opponent was the dirty Fang Rui?

Making changes because of the opponent. No one had thought Sun Xiang had it in him, but it was happening right in front of their eyes.

Fang Rui scratched his head. He suddenly realized that he had no idea what to do next.

What would a strategically moving Sun Xiang do? He couldn't understand at all because that punk had never played that way before!

Fang Rui didn't whether to be happy or sad that his opponent was giving him special treatment.

His current ambush position should still be good. Fang Rui carefully sized up his surroundings. If he were facing a different opponent, he could try to predict what his opponent would do next through the terrain, but against Sun Xiang… how could he make a prediction for someone who he had originally thought didn't know a thing about moving strategically? 　

Was he patiently waiting, or was he putting himself forward as bait?

Fang Rui pondered. In the meantime, he started trash talking Sun Xiang.

"Hey, where are you? You've been ruined by Samsara. You were never like this before!" Fang Rui acted like he was friends with Sun Xiang. In reality, the two had never interacted with each other before.

The chat was silent. Sun Xiang didn't respond.

"It's a match after all. Play how you like to play. Don't concern yourself over who your opponent is! Maybe my dirtiness is giving you a lot of pressure, but using a style you're not familiar with might not get the results you're expecting!" Fang Rui didn't mind the opponent not replying back as he continued to chatter.

As he talked, his Boundless Sea wasn't just standing there quietly. He was moving cautiously through the trenches, investigating the area around him.

Where was One Autumn Leaf?

The viewers obviously knew the answer. Sun Xiang's opening move had caught everyone off guard. He had done the same as Fang Rui. One Autumn Leaf had also moved stealthily through the trenches.

"Sun Xiang's choices today are quite surprising!" Pan Lin had been talking about it earlier.

"Yes, this isn't his usual style," said Li Yibo.　　

"It looks like he has some misgivings over Fang Rui's dirtiness," Pan Lin said.

"Yes… Fang Rui's Qi Master is similar to Ye Xiu's unspecialized in some sense. The opponent isn't familiar with this new playstyle or class. Most of his experience with Qi Masters isn't useful because Fang Rui's playstyle is entirely different from other people's," Li Yibo said.

"But do you think Sun Xiang might be overcompensating by changing his own playstyle?" Pan Lin said.

"Ah… this… let's take a look at their performances first. I believe Sun Xiang should have come prepared. Fang Rui is most likely surprised by Sun Xiang's actions." Li Yibo didn't provide a detailed analysis, instead giving a simple prediction.

Sure enough, Fang Rui was surprised by Sun Xiang's actions. Seeing the constant stream of trash talk, Li Yibo felt incredibly happy. He had made a correct prediction, even if it wasn't anything admirable.

"Sun Xiang is really keeping his composure today!" Pan Lin said.

From their omniscient view, they could clearly see that Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf had reached the center of the map too. However, he wasn't as active as Fang Rui. He picked a spot and then quietly stood there.

"Sun Xiang, this player…" Li Yibo wanted to say something, but he stopped himself. He was like a player who had been beaten again and again. His confidence had been slapped into nothingness.

"It's a very short section of the trench. The turns on both ends are within reach of a Battle Mage." Pan Lin introduced the features of this position.

"Yes…" Li Yibo was itching to say something! But the other voice in him was telling him to calm down.

Sun Xiang was waiting patiently, while Fang Rui searched for his opponent. Boundless Sea maneuvered through the trenches, while occasionally peeking his head up to check his surroundings above the ground. The trash talk in the public chat hadn't stopped yet, but none of his messages received a response.

Finally, Boundless Sea approached One Autumn Leaf's hiding spot. Boundless Sea was practically crawling as he moved silently. Not a single sound could be heard. Everyone's heart leapt to their throats. As soon as he turned and showed his head, One Autumn Leaf's Evil Annihilation would immediately pierce him.

But when he was two steps away, Boundless Sea's movements suddenly stopped. He leaned close to the side of the ditch as if trying to hear something.

The only thing separating the two characters was a corner. If you drew a straight line between them, it would only measure ¾ of a unit. Neither side moved. Neither side uttered a peep. Only Fang Rui's chattering could be seen in the public chat.

Fang Rui wasn't really talking anymore. After saying a few key points at the start, he didn't have anything else to say. He had even started resorting to something as unrefined as copying and pasting his own words. The two stopped at this bend.

Nervous and anxious.

The crowd didn't know whether the two players had noticed each other. The tension made it hard for them to breathe.

The first to move was Fang Rui. He carefully peeked his head up just the tiniest bit. After looking around above the ground, Boundless Sea retreated a bit. His two hands swiped against each other and a Qi Blade formed an arc, flying around the corner. He listened carefully to any noise.

He heard it… and saw it.

The instant the Qi Blade turned the corner, One Autumn Leaf stepped into view. Sun Xiang had been waiting patiently until now. His opponent was finally this close to him. He didn't hesitate or make any feints. His One Autumn Leaf rushed out. In the end, he chose a direct confrontation.

More importantly, because of the terrain, Fang Rui's only choice was a direct confrontation as well. With the distance between them and Sun Xiang's swift and decisive response, Fang Rui didn't have any time to make any dirty escapes. To his left and right were walls, while One Autumn Leaf's spear was in front.

Li Yibo felt very regretful.

Seeing Sun Xiang's position, he had guessed Sun Xiang's plan: wait until the opponent found him. This position was extremely good. Because of the outside surroundings, Fang Rui wouldn't dare easily leap out. Inside the trench, if Fang Rui was close enough, he could force a direct fight and not give Fang Rui any chance to escape.

However, with his dimming confidence, he was too afraid to say his guess. And now, it looked like Sun Xiang was doing exactly what he had thought. After determining that Boundless Sea was right next to him, he immediately began doing what he had always been good at.

The trenches used for stealth had become Fang Rui's cage. The dirty style wasn't just in tactics but in techniques too. But no matter what, all of them required a certain amount of space to maneuver around. However, with the left and right blocked by walls and a One Autumn Leaf attacking fiercely from the front, he wasn't given any chance to jump out. His only choice was to retreat backwards. Right now, the master of playing dirty was helpless. Even the cleverest housewife cannot cook without rice.

Sun Xiang had been waiting for this very moment.

Afterwards was his usual strong offense. However, his prior patience had helped him win this situation. Sun Xiang's offense seemed even more effective and made the opponent look even more helpless.

Sun Xiang's advantage wasn't just in technique, it was more tactical. The timing and terrain all stood on his side. His performance only looked more steady.

Boundless Sea eventually fell. No one had expected that Fang Rui's dirty style wouldn't be able to be displayed in a map suited for it. Fang Rui had been suppressed as soon as he ran into his opponent. Unable to display his dirty tactics or his techniques, he was killed in the trenches.

Yes, up until death, Fang Rui hadn't been able to get Boundless Sea out of the trenches. 　

In the group arena, Sun Xiang won the first round with a 72% health lead.

Chapter 1296: Mo Fan vs Sun Xiang

Finishing with 72% health left could be considered a massive advantage in the group arena.

Because this sort of advantage could stack in the group arena, the group arena was very different from individual matches, though it might seem that they were both 1v1s. In the individual competition, all you needed to do was beat your opponent first, but in the group arena, you had to consider how to use the least amount of HP possible to defeat your opponent.

Efficiency. The group arena valued the efficiency of your attacks far more. In the round that had just ended, Sun Xiang had doubtlessly managed to exhibit that excellently. Using positioning and patience, he had greatly diminished the space his opponent had to perform, winning very efficiently.

A player who usually depended on hand speed, mechanics and technique to win his opponents had suddenly decided to switch tactics and lure and trap his opponent, even managing to trick the Master of Dirty Play, Fang Rui.

"This is a very atypical victory for Sun Xiang!" Li Yibo was now confidently expressing his own opinion on the previous match. Before, when he was given the chance to make an accurate prediction, he was too careful and missed it. Li Yibo, frustrated, was frantically trying to make up for it by showing off how much he knew about Glory. For a moment, not even commentator Pan Lin had the chance to cut in and say anything. It was just good that there was a time limit to switch between players for the group arena. After Happy's Fang Rui returned to the bench, Happy's second player quickly headed off.

"How come this guy brought his brain with him today?" Fang Rui complained, returning to the bench. "This guy" naturally referred to Sun Xiang. It was clear that in his eyes, Sun Xiang was the kind of player who didn't use his brains to fight.

"You were rather impatient, too!" Ye Xiu replied.

　

"Yeah!" Fang Rui lamented. "I should've just stayed there and continued to stall, and see who snapped first!"

Ye Xiu didn't know if he should laugh or cry. "There's no way you didn't know about that ambush point. You should've been more careful."

"Didn't I say that I didn't know he brought his brain today?" Fang Rui retorted.

"..."

"Ok, I admit, I underestimated him," Fang Rui sighed.

"Sun Xiang's choice of action was truly rather unexpected." Ye Xiu gazed at the stage. Sun Xiang, once the overconfident captain of Excellent Era who thought himself more than good enough to replace Ye Xiu, had truly matured after being relegated and then defeated in the Challenger League.

Crafting such a plan, especially in the group arena, meant that he was starting to understand his position more, as well as what he should do on the field. He was no longer fighting for himself, but the entire team.

"Mo Fan… might not be able to do well against him either…" Fang Rui said, watching Happy's second player, Mo Fan, as he entered the booth.

"That'll depend on how he plays. The current Mo Fan isn't the Mo Fan of the past with his monotonous style anymore," Ye Xiu said.

After half a year of actual battle experience, everyone had grown. Mo Fan wasn't that same scrap-picker who would always lie in wait to ambush. He learned to judge the situation, and to use a wider variety of styles and techniques. Still, he had managed to preserve the habits and virtues he had gained from scrap-picking in-game. He had patience, he was careful, good at finding and grasping opportunities. These were the characteristics that suited a Class like Ninja, which focused on moving undetected.

Originally, Deception was a widely known and hated character in the online game. Before, many guilds had noticed him and his talents. However, his loner personality caused him to ignore the olive branches being extended his way from all over. It wasn't until he was pulled into the pro circle by Ye Xiu that his potential was realized, proving that the guilds hadn't misjudged him. It's just that Ye Xiu managed to brute force this talent, who no one else had been able to recruit, into his camp.

After Mo Fan went up, the second round soon began. In the beginning, Mo Fan didn't dart into the shadows and move carefully like usual, but instead had Deception run towards the center at full speed.

"Happy's Mo Fan is also one who's good at hiding and ambushing, but it seems like he's not planning on doing that this time!" Pan Lin noted, seeing Deceptions movements.

"In reality, with so many gullies in this map, one can use them at any time so long as they aim well. In the last match, Fang Rui's playstyle was a little too dirty to work," Li Yibo commented. History was always on the side of the victors, so the losing Fang Rui immediately turned into a bad example.

"This time, it seems that Sun Xiang doesn't plan on using the same method as the last round," Pan Lin brought up. Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf had also quickly ran for the center after the match began, returning to his usual style.

"An ambush like that wouldn't work a second time," Li Yibo said.

"So this time he had One Autumn Leaf charge directly. This is the Sun Xiang we're all more familiar with. It seems like this match will be a direct clash between the two. Okay, their characters have now entered each other's field of vision. What will they do next? Huh?" Pan Lin was just getting rather excited over all this when Deception, who had been charging forward head on, suddenly rolled to the side and jumped into a gully after appearing in One AUtumn Leaf's field of vision.

"Uh, it seems like Happy's Mo Fan still intends to use the terrain to cover his movements. However, he's already been seen, so Sun Xiang can probably make a relatively accurate judgement of his position, no? Huh?" Just as Pan Lin was saying this, Mo fan's Deception then jumped out of the gully after moving around for a while.

"What is he doing? Advisor Li?" Pan Lin couldn't understand and immediately went to ask Li Yibo.

"He's probably trying to confuse the other using his pace!" Li Yibo answered rather weakly. He really wanted to append a "this is my personal opinion and might not be right" to the end of his words.

"Sun Xiang doesn't seen very affected. One Autumn Leaf is continuing forwards," Pan Lin exclaimed.

Shuriken!

In the end, the one to strike first was still Decepton, who had a few mid-ranged skills.

　

Clang!

One Autumn Leaf didn't slow down, flicking his spear up and knocking the shuriken away in midair. Just from a technical perspective, Sun Xiang performed flawlessly.

The shuriken didn't do anything to his opponent. Deception flicked his hands again. Fwoosh, fwoosh, fwoosh, fwoosh, four shurikens flew out in rapid succession. This time, it was the improved version of Shuriken: Storm Shuriken.

　

The shurikens sliced through the air, all four of them approaching rapidly. This time, Sun Xiang could no longer block them all with pure mechanics alone.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

In the end, One Autumn Leaf forwent blocking and directly used a Dragon Breaks the Ranks to charge forward, ignoring the damage from the shurikens.

Under the effects of Dragon Breaks the Ranks, all Storm Shuriken did was deal damage. It didn't hinder One Autumn Leaf's advance at all. One Autumn Leaf arrived in front of Deception in the blink of an eye.

Poof!

The struck Deception exploded into smoke and his real body appeared behind One Autumn Leaf. Despite facing Dragon Breaks the Ranks at such a close range, he could still dodge so precisely. Mo Fan's mechanics were impressive.

Ninja Arts: Bird Fall!

　　

Deception, who had appeared in midair with a Shadow Clone Technique, immediately stepped down with both feet at One Autumn's Leaf's shoulders. Sun Xiang reacted extremely fast though. With the momentum of Dragon Breaks the Ranks still in effect, One Autumn Leaf had already jumped up and turned, throwing himself back with his own momentum. His spear Evil Annihilation struck with deadly precision.

Sky Strike!

The lowest level skill used at the best timing. Deception's Bird Fall couldn't hit One Autumn Leaf's shoulders anymore. In midair, Mo Fan adjusted himself swiftly, and Deception's Bird Fall ended up stepping right on the tip of One Autumn Leaf's Evil Annihilation.

Such precise mechanics! It was truly awe inspiring. The venue immediately exploded into applause.

Ninja Arts: Bird Fall might be a level 45 skill, but it didn't have very high priority. Meanwhile, Sky Strike might be the lowest level skill, but its knockup priority was very high.

Bird Fall couldn't stop Sky Strike's upwards momentum, and Deception was still thrown into the air. It was just that since he had used skill to step on the spear, he didn't take any damage. He was thrown into the air, but he didn't tumble out of control like he would have, if he had been hit directly by Sky Strike.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

Deception might not have been thrown too badly into the air, but Sun Xiang tried to rip that composure away. One Autumn Leaf's Evil Annihilation retracted and then struck lightning fast, a Level 60 skill thrown out, in pursuit of the airborne Deception.

Poof!

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart hit, but after a bang, the airborne Deception was replaced with a straw dummy with a poof of smoke.

Ninja Arts: Hundred Streams!

Deception, having already landed, rapidly formed seals and his ninjato swung. Streams of water lunged towards One Autumn Leaf.

　

Sun Xiang had not noticed the sneak attack from behind, but since Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart had hit a straw dummy, he knew that an attack was imminent. He didn't even bother turning to look, having One Autumn Leaf dodge to one side immediately. As he dodged, he turned his camera to see the Hundred Streams flowing across the ground. If he had been just a little late in reacting, he would be inside a water prison right now.

"Mo Fan is competing with Sun Xiang in mechanics!" Pan Lin yelled in shock. As a newbie, this sort of courage was truly quite shocking. What was even more shocking was that after these exchanges, neither side had gotten the upperhand. It seemed like they were at a draw.

"His reactions are very fast, his mechanics precise!" Li Yibo noted. He was, obviously, commenting on Mo Fan. As for Sun Xiang, there was no need to use these general praises to comment on his performance anymore.

But after these evenly matched exchanges, Deception rolled to the side and jumped into a ditch. He had turned and hid after seeing that his attacks weren't working.

Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf rushed over, Evil Annihilation held in front of him and ready to strike.

However, Deception had disappeared. A short, small ditch just like the place Sun Xiang had hid last time. It had turns left and right. Where did Deception go?

Sun Xiang was trying to make a decision when, under One Autumn Leaf's feet, the ground suddenly loosened.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Chapter 1297: Mo Fan’s Characteristics

Deception hadn't left! After entering the gully, he had hid there and used an Underground Tunneling Technique.

Sun Xiang's view was focused on the two turns at the ends of the gully. He had been trying to figure out which way to go and hadn't thought to think of what was under his feet. By the time Deception's movements were large and close enough to be sensed, it was too late to react.

The ninjato struck One Autumn Leaf under his chin harshly, throwing him into the air. Mo Fan, Deception, was the first to land a hit!

　　

Annihilate, Flame Cut, Neck Bind Technique, Ninja Arts: Flickering Charge.

Four skills landed on One Autumn Leaf in flawless succession. Even if it was Sun Xiang, he was helpless against it.

"Beautiful!" Fang Rui yelled from Happy's player bench.

Talented at timing, Mo Fan had a very solid grasp of landing combos. However, even if the system judged it as a combo, that didn't mean it was unbreakable. From a certain perspective, false combos were the real unbreakable combo. However, a consistent use of this sort of comboing, a characteristic of Ye Xiu's unspecialized, was extremely hard to master without experience. In this area, Mo Fan's talent wasn't outstanding.

However, for a system-determined combo, especially a combo of five or fewer skills, Mo Fan had such outstanding mastery that even Ye Xiu looked on with awe. This came from the habits he had developed in game. When scrap-picking, you weren't meant to entangle with targets, so he would always find a good opportunity to unleash a barrage of attacks, take what he needed and leave in the shortest time possible. This barrage had a max of five skills. More, and Mo Fan would judge it as an inappropriate time to strike.

After all this time, Mo Fan had developed a habit of using this monotonous battle style. His habits meant that anything coming after his barrage was lacking in comparison. After joining Happy and undergoing professional training, he was finally beginning to change. At first, Ye Xiu had hoped he would be able to completely change this style of fighting in short bursts, but he soon began to realize that this habit of Mo Fan's wasn't just a thing of mechanics, but also of his spirit.

Focus.

Mo Fan's focus would also fluctuate with this rhythm. When he unleashed his barrage, his focus would peak. His mechanics would be precise, efficient, comparable to a God. However, after this short burst, he experienced a clear slip. His mechanics after that would be nothing comparable to how well he had performed in that period.

　

This instantly condensed overpowered focus was the reason why Mo Fan could fight on par with a God for short bursts. This was almost like a skill of his that had a cooldown.

After realizing this, Ye Xiu also realized that this would probably become a characteristic of Mo Fan's style. His eventual style would probably also develop from this.

Thus, Ye Xiu stopped expecting Mo Fan to eventually get rid of his habit and instead helped him develop his talents, teaching him how to combine his skills to make sure he could endure throughout the battle.

In the past, Mo fan would run after getting what he wanted. After his barrage, he usually wouldn't have to fight any longer, and thus naturally didn't have to consider what skills to use after that. He would throw out whatever was convenient during his barrage. However, you couldn't fight that way in an actual match. The battle was far from over after a single barrage! It was unacceptable if he was sent into a panic at what to do after, or using two skills and being unable to follow up.

　

Mo Fan had completed this transformation. When his barrage wasn't indiscrimmitory, his battle ability was vastly increased. Now, on the field, his focused barrage could match Sun Xiang strike for strike.

　　

However, it wasn't unexpected to Ye Xiu that he still turned and ran after a few exchanges. At this point, his focus would scatter, and he definitely wasn't a match for Sun Xiang then.

However, not even Ye Xiu expected it when, after retreating for only a brief moment, Mo Fan came back with another barrage.

Underground Tunneling Technique, Annihilation, Flame Cut, Neck Bind, Ninjutsu: Flickering Charge.

Under the limit of Mo Fan's overpowered focus, not even Sun Xiang could match this combo of five skills.

But… wasn't a little too close together with the previous barrage?

In reality, Ye Xiu wasn't sure how many times Mo Fan could gear himself up into that focused state. He also didn't know how long it would take to enter that state after a previous barrage. Ye Xiu could only tell, by experience, that this sort of peak performance in short bursts was a sign that he was stretching his limits. That was why his focus would scatter after each barrage: it was a sign of mental strain. However, this time, Mo Fan had consecutively unleashed two barrages. How much strain was he putting on himself, doing this?

"This kid is really pushing himself!" Team Happy's members naturally all understood Mo Fan's characteristics. Seeing how he had unleashed a second barrage so soon, Wei Chen called out in surprise.

　　

"How long can he last if he fights like this?" Qiao Yifan wondered aloud.

Everyone fell silent. Mo Fan was still quite a loner. His style had matured, but no one knew how he would use it and where his limits where.

　

His combo successful, Mo Fan once again had Deception hide.

"Huh? How come he doesn't continue his offensive?" Pan Lin couldn't really understand. Though his combo had ended there, it was perfectly feasible to strike fast and unleash a new barrage of attacks after this combo.

"He probably doesn't think he has a solid enough grasp of this opportunity…" Li Yibo theorized.

"Mo Fan very rarely performs long combos! With his mechanics, I think he can definitely do better. I think he's a little too cautious," Pan Lin commented.

"Heh, this is probably because of his background!" Li Yibo said.

"You mean, as a scrap-picker?" Pan Lin asked.

　

"Yes, the most important thing for scrap-pickers is to secure their own safety! If they can't even keep themselves safe, then how would they scrap-pick? Though, of course, Mo Fan is a pro player now, but he's been active in-game for a long time. Caution and care is probably a habit he's built up over all that time," Li Yibo replied.

These words made sense and Mo Fan did have this sort of habit from long-term scrap-picking but these two clearly hadn't noticed what was really going on with Mo Fan. You could say, that apart from his teammates in Team Happy, no one knew that Mo Fan's style came with a cooldown. After all, Mo Fan didn't regularly appear in matches and hadn't played many compared to the rest of Happy.

But in this match, against a strong opponent like Sun Xiang, Mo Fan's potential seemed to have been forced to appear in its entirety. The match had barely started and he had already unleashed two barrages of attacks, successfully depriving One Autumn Leaf of a good chunk of his health. This was something no one expected. From everyone else's view, after Sun Xiang had managed to get rid of Fang Rui so efficiently, wouldn't a rookie be easy to deal with?

Since Sun Xiang had finished his first opponent with a 72% health advantage, the Happy fans didn't dare to yell ten to zero anymore. Instead, the Samsara fans had gotten hyped, yelling one versus three and whatnot. One versus three was also something that held a rather terrible story for Happy. Samsara's fans yelling this was killing two birds with one stone: mockery amongst encouragement.

However after Mo Fan had managed to draw first blood like this, Samsara's fans shut up. They began to discuss how could this rookie be so strong?

　

Everyone was struck dumb by Mo Fan's barrage and even Sun Xiang didn't dare underestimate his opponent. It was rare that someone would be able to match him in technique and mechanics like that. Thus, Sun Xiang, looking for a trace of Deception, was more cautious. He had to look down every now and then, as if Deception might just pop out of the ground.

No!

Deception had disappeared completely this time. Sun Xiang couldn't find him no matter how he looked and was feeling a little helpless. He knew that this player had a terrifying amount of patience. This was a… a player who had waited so patiently that the referee had given him a red card. This was something only he could boast in the history of Glory.

Thinking of the red card last time, Sun Xiang decided to just stop moving. One Autumn Leaf just stood there in the open. You coming out, Deception? You want another red card?

　

However, was this Mo Fan still the Mo Fan of the past?

　

Before, Mo Fan had just stayed there, unmoving, being seen as passive and unsportsmanly. However, the current Mo Fan might not be prepared to strike just yet, but he was rather active. He kept having Deception reposition himself, trying to find a chance to attack. With One Autumn Leaf not moving, Deception immediately went behind him. It was just that after getting behind One Autumn Leaf in the gully, he felt that the distance was too far to execute a sneak attack. It was unreliable. After checking it over, Deception left again.

Boos rose from the crowd. Naturally, all from Samsara's fans. Though Happy's fans didn't like this sort of wait, they were willing to give their players some leeway.

Deception had gone in a circle and not found a good opportunity. That was when the referee struck, unexpectedly giving Sun Xiang a yellow card.

Sun Xiang stared in shock. What the hell was this?

　

In reality, Sun Xiang didn't really understand the rule regarding passivity and sportsmanship well either. He didn't need to research something like that with his style. However, in the current situation, Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf was standing there, unmoving while Mo Fan's Deception was circling around, trying to find an opening. Who was passive and who was active was clear.

Sun Xiang, who could now curb his temper and impatience, really had improved greatly. Last match, his self-control had won him a beautiful victory. This time, however, it had brought him a yellow card.

It wasn't just Sun Xiang who was shocked, Happy's members were also exchanging looks!

The yellow card was a system message and Mo Fan, naturally, could see it. If it was Fang Rui, then he'd could probably use this to spout a good load of trash talk. However, Mo fan probably spoke even less than Zhou Zekai. Trash talk was naturally a skill that wouldn't appear with him.

Sun Xiang, forced to move by the yellow card, could only have One Autumn Leaf start looking for Deception. The group arena was also a 1v1, so the map wasn't too big. One Autumn Leaf began moving along the gully, keeping a careful eye on interior and beginning to reduce Deception's room for movement. Deception also began to head towards the direction One Autumn Leaf was coming from.

Chapter 1298: Keep Calm

The two characters approached each other little by little, and the match seemed to have turned into the scene seen in the last match. Everyone's hearts jumped into their chests as they waited for that moment to arrive.

However, before any of the audience could react, the two characters suddenly accelerated.

"They've found each other!" Pan Lin yelled.

The crowd could see the overall situation better than the participants with their omniscient view. However, to gain a deeper understanding of what was occurring, they would need to rely on the player's perspectives. The broadcast and the big screen had both replayed the shot just now from the two character's perspective,

　

In that moment, a figure flashed through the views of Deception in the ditches and One Autumn Leaf next to it, and neither of them missed it. Their characters charged and clashed!

Boom!

An explosion of purple smoke.

They hadn't even engaged each other when Deception tossed a Smoke Bomb. Then, he darted out of the range of the smoke.

Did he want to run?

　

No!

Darting out, then in, Mo Fan had Deception play this sort of trick with Sun Xiang, but was this enough to shake Sun Xiang?

　

Shattering the Lands!

　

Sun Xiang responded in the most forceful way. In the purple smoke, he didn't know where Deception was so he directly used a level 75 ultimate.

Boom!

Evil Annihilation slammed into the ground and roaring magical energy buffeted the smoke, causing it to bubble like boiling water.

Deception once again ran out of the purple smoke, his figure swaying a little. Clearly, he had been hit by the shockwaves made by this skill, his health having been reduced. Sun Xiang had broken right through Mo Fan's trick in the most brutal way.

Dragon Rises from the Sea!

　

Evil Annihilation swung again and a wave of tide-like magical energy unfurled, breaking through the smoke. Through the break, Deception's figure was already exposed.

　　

Charge!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf raised his spear and charged out of the smoke, arriving in front of Deception in the blink of an eye. Sun Xiang didn't hope that this skill would hit his opponent; he was just using it as a movement skill.

Shining Cut!

Mo Fan once again overturned expectations, Deception advancing rather than retreating. With an Assassin skill Shining Cut, Deception's form flashed forwards, intending to slide right by Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Sun Xiang was shocked, hurriedly adjusting himself. Evil Annihilation swerved, but it was too late. Deception had already flashed behind him.

In that moment, the two characters seemed to have completed a Switch, and just as the passed each other by, the two rapidly cancelled their skills, stopped, and turned.

Dragon Tooth! As One Autumn Leaf turned, Evil Annihilation stabbed forward.

A hit!

But, a puff of smoke rose; it was another Shadow Clone.

Sun Xiang didn't hesitate. As One Autumn Leaf turned, he swept his spear out and executed a Tyrant's Destruction, reaching a full 270 degrees around.

However...

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Another Underground Tunneling Technique, Deception darted out of the ground and, as One Autumn Leaf epically sweeped his spear across, hit the other's jaw in an uppercut.

Ninjutsu: Cicada Shell Double Slash!

Deception's follow-up came rapidly, executed in an unbreakable combo. Sun Xiang already knew it wasn't good when he was hit by the Underground Tunneling Technique and had prepared himself. However, the follow-up was so fast, so precise; there was no opening at all.

And then...

Annihilation, Storm Shuriken, Ninjutsu: Shadow Dance!

Again, the same five skill combo under Mo Fan's absolute focus had rendered Sun Xiang helpless. However, the last skill in the combo was the ultimate skill Shadow Dance. This was a skill that could be manually controlled and the mechanics required were far more demanding than other skills. For Mo Fan, whose limit was five skills, this skill would only be used in his five skill barrage if he planned to manually control it. The focus needed for the mechanics for this skill was comparable to two, three, even four other skills.

In a pro-level confrontation, Shadow Dance had to be manually controlled.

The audience didn't know that Mo Fan had this sort of limit. They just thought it was a climax to the match, their applause thunderous.

However, Happy's players knew that this choice of acton meant that Mo Fan was challenging his limits. It wasn't just a small challenge either, but throwing himself directly in the deep end.

"That's too much of a stretch!" Wei Chen commented.

"But with this skill, he can at least retreat completely, right?" Fang Rui said.

　　

"But he… doesn't seem to have such an intention." Su Mucheng was the only one in Happy who really communicated with Mo Fan, though it was only very little.

"No, he doesn't…" Watching the match, Ye Xiu could see that after the Shadow Dance, all ten shadow clones had lunged forwards to attack, not giving himself any escape route. By this point, his focus was at its limit. Could he still control this skill to the same high level?

Bang!

With a resounding noise, a Deception shadow clone flew out of the pile of people. One Autumn Leaf, not even fully out of Falling Flower Palm's pose yet, threw his Evil Annihilation forwards with his other hand, unleashing a fearsome magical energy.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

The rapid follow-up of Rising Dragon Soars the Sky after Falling Flower Palm didn't even wait for this Deception to fly out much before catching up and clamping down, magical energy striking and devouring everything in its path. The other shadow clones were all turned to smoke one by one. Everyone knew that Sun Xiang offensive had struck the heart of Deception's Shadow Dance.

"It really was a bit of a stretch…" Ye Xiu sighed.

Mo Fan wanted to surpass his limits, but the step he had chosen to take was too big. His focus scattered, his Shadow Dance wasn't executed flawlessly, revealing an opening that Sun Xiang immediately caught and used.

The audience couldn't see the depth to this, only knowing that these two were exchanging blows, the battle was spectacular. The crowd went wild, and the commentators of the broadcast Pan Lin and Li Yibo were also going on about this unexpected performance from Mo Fan, how he was able to match Sun Xiang blow for blow.

"I hope so…" Ye Xiu was a little concerned. Mo Fan had unleashed several barrages in succession and continued to challenge his own limits. Wasn't he a little too excited? This… seemed like he was losing control.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had long ending lag, and it was hard to follow-up on this. Sun Xiang could only wait until the skill ended and have One Autumn Leaf charge over to launch a new round of attacks.

　

"Before it was Mo Fan who was on the offensive, but now it looks like it's Sun Xiang's turn. One Autumn Leaf is advancing, how will Mo Fan deal with this? Deception… Deception ran away… I…" Pan Lin swallowed a curse. This Mo Fan's style was really quite depressing! Such a spectacular exchange, wasn't it thrilling going head to head? Sun Xiang had such a spectacular response to Mo Fan's offensive, so can't you just respond in kind and think of the audience a little? When the opponent countered, you immediately ran without any hesitation. Where's your courage to face Sun Xiang head on? Where's your mechanics that can match him blow for blow?

"This… This Mo Fan is really keeping a clear head about him! He didn't let it get to his head," Li Yibo said.

"But in competition there's no need to adhere so strictly and monotonously to such an arrangement, right? Young people should be more passionate, more reckless. This kind of strict and mechanical playstyle is a little too boring," Pan Lin offered.

"Heh, what if this is interesting to him?" Li Yibo simply said in reply. In that moment, he shone with his former identity as a pro player. Only those who had stood in the same shoes had the right to say these empathetic words. Interesting? What was interesting? The red-blooded excitement of head on clashes, intense APM battles? That was just the definition to you viewers. To each pro player, their chosen playstyle was the most interesting to them. Maybe some will purposefully change their styles to appease the crowd, but this was a trend that had appeared only after Glory became commercialized. However, Li Yibo, from an older generation of players, rejected this sort of commercial air deep down. He liked to see players maintaining their unique style, even if there were some he, his knowledge rather outdated, couldn't figure out...

Li Yibo's lightly spoken words had Pan Lin rather stunned. He didn't know what to say in response. On the stage, Mo Fan's Deception managed a smooth escape, using the gullies peppered across the map to conceal himself.

　　

"He's got a pretty clear head!" Fang Rui exclaimed.

　　

"Yeah, he's nowhere near as reckless as you though!" Su Mucheng said to Ye Xiu.

"Stretching his limits and performance might be an attempt to confuse his opponent. This kid must have been secretly observing my performance and learning valuable lessons from me!" Wei Chen decided.

"Shamelessness?" Steamed Bun asked.

"Bastard, he learned that from your boss!" Wei Chen cursed.

"Of course, boss is best at everything!" Steamed Bun boasted.

"Hahahaha, I won't object to that in this case!" Wei Chen laughed out loud, satisfied with the follow up attack Steamed Bun had given Ye Xiu.

"Steamed Bun doesn't understand, don't you go feigning ignorance. You're the most shameless," Ye Xiu retorted.

"Don't be so humble. You're the best at everything!" Wei Chen emphasized the word "best".

"You…"

"Mo Fan is still in the match and you're here talking nonsense!" Chen Guo got angry and yelled at the two.

"Aiyou, boss, relax, relax," Wei Chen hurriedly assured her, "Mo Fan will be fine."

"Really?"

"So long as he can keep this pace up," Ye Xiu said, "His opponent hasn't figured him out yet. Old Wei is right. By overstretching his limits, he's misled his opponent. His opponent will be having doubts about him, giving him a good chance."

"Mo Fan…" Chen Guo didn't continue her train of thought. In reality, she had wanted to express surprise that Mo Fan could beat Sun Xiang, but then she realized that this would be a blow to the players on the team, so she held back. However, she was still shocked at Mo Fan's improvement.

Could he win? Chen Guo gazed at the stage.

Mo Fan didn't fail everyone's expectations. When Deception was at 14 percent health, One Autumn Leaf fell, and the surprise Chen Guo didn't voice was yelled out by Pan Lin.

"I never would have expected that Happy's Mo Fan could defeat Sun Xiang!" Pan Lin cried out.

Chapter 1299: Challenging His Limits

Deception only had 14% health remaining. One Autumn Leaf had started the fight with 72% health, yet those comparing the matchup on paper would still think Mo Fan would be less likely to win.

Even so, Mo Fan won, and his victory astonished many.　　

Because Sun Xiang truly was strong. He had sunken to the Challenger League for the season and ended up losing that to Happy, but the champion team Samsara still wanted him, showing a deep-rooted recognition of his skill. Two seasons of failure hadn't affected people's evaluation of him.

For such a player, despite starting the fight with only 72% health, most would favor him in a match against a rookie.　

His opponent Mo Fan was astonishingly valiant. He went equal with Su Xiang in multiple direct confrontations, which left a deep impression on the viewers.

In the end, Sun Xiang unexpectedly lost the fight.

Sun Xiang walked down slowly from the stage.

In the past, if he lost against a rookie, he would feel ashamed and fly into a rage. However, the current him didn't have an expression of anger, although he obviously wasn't happy either. He raised his head, looking at the replay on the big screens. He pondered as he watched.

"Nice job!" When he returned to Samsara's bench, his teammates welcomed him back. Losing to Mo Fan was a bit surprising, but if you looked at the outcome, Sun Xiang had nearly completed a 1v2. Mo Fan's Deception only had 14% health left. In the group arena, this sort of performance was splendid.

"That Mo Fan…" Sun Xiang felt like he should have grasped something, but he was drawing a blank right now.　　

"We can slowly figure it out when we go back and review the match!" Jiang Botao patted him. He could see that Sun Xiang seemed somewhat troubled by the match.

"Okay, it's finally my turn." Du Ming got up excitedly.

He was a player who yearned for competition. Before Sun Xiang transferred to Samsara, he had appeared on stage very often. But when Sun Xiang joined, Sun Xiang took up a spot on the main roster, and Du Ming's position instantly fell.　

Saying that he wasn't sad about it would be false, but Sun Xiang's skill was truly there. His addition improved Samsara's strength even further. Du Ming couldn't ask the team to reject an upgrade, so he could only accept it.

Du Ming had his own plans for his future, and he hoped for more opportunities on the stage. But he was still a part of Samsara, and his resolve in Samsara hadn't been shaken! Winning three championships in a row with his teammates of many years and then leaving for his own selfish fights would be the most beautiful outcome.

As a result, even though his position was on the fringe, Du Ming worked even harder.

No one in a championship team had weaklings! Du Ming had plans on leaving Samsara, but his pride and arrogance as a part of Samsara had not lessened.

"Good luck!" His teammates yelled to Du Ming.

"Relax!" Du Ming waved carefreely to his teammates behind him like a cool person.

"Fuck, he's acting like he's our team's biggest trump card," Wu Qi cursed, "Captain, I'm not the type of person to pick fights, but I wouldn't be able to bear it if I were you."

"Haha," Zhou Zekai chuckled.

Du Ming walked onto the stage, into the player booth, and his character loaded into the map.

Blade Master, Moon-Luring Frost.

Whoosh whoosh. As soon as he loaded into the map, Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost immediately drew his sword, displaying his impatience.

"COME!" He shouted in the chat.

Mo Fan obviously didn't respond and quietly ran over.　　

Du Ming didn't move strategically either. After Moon-Luring Frost slashed his sword a few times, he headed straight for the center too.

Like last round, the two characters practically saw each other at the same time.　

Into the ditches?

No, this time, neither side went into the ditches. The two characters came across each other, and then after a short pause, they started fighting.　　

Shuriken!

Mo Fan's Deception attacked first.　

This low-level flying tool posed no threat Sun Xiang, and it was no different for Du Ming.

Moon-Luring Frost raised his sword and swept it aside.

Triple Slash!

Du Ming started his offense just as fast as Sun Xiang. Sun Xiang had used Dragon Breaks the Ranks, while he used Triple Slash. His momentum might not be as powerful as Dragon Breaks the Ranks, but it was more nimble.　

His sword led the way. Du Ming observed Mo Fan's reaction cautiously. He hadn't forgotten how fast Mo Fan had countered after Sun Xiang and him brushed past each other last match. Anyone who saw that scene couldn't help but pretend they were there, and feel their bodies drip with cold sweat at that reaction speed and mechanical skill. Du Ming had done the same and felt stunned. However, he still wanted to try it and see if he could do what others couldn't.　

First slash, second slash...

The first and second slash of Triple Slash came out, and Moon-Luring Frost rapidly closed in. However, Deception didn't move. He didn't meet it directly with an Shining Cut like last time.

What is he planning? Du Ming muttered to himself. Triple Slash's third slash flew out, both an attack and a movement, towards Deception. At this moment, Du Min lowered his head. Mo Fan's usage of Underground Tunneling Technique had left a deep impression on him too. Du Ming didn't want to fall for this sort of trap.

As soon as he lowered his head, he saw a glint of cold light from in front of him.

Caltrops?

When had he thrown these?　

Du Ming was startled. He immediately had Moon-Luring Frost's third slash switched directions. Moon-Luring Frost moved horizontally and dodged these Caltrops.

How dangerous!

Du Ming yelled in his heart. Ninja Tools - Caltrops, a low-level skill. If an opponent stepped on it, it would harshly reduce the opponent's movement speed. And even though these Caltrops were thrown onto the ground, they weren't easy to see. If Du Ming hadn't looked down because he was wary of Underground Tunneling Technique, he would have certainly stepped onto the Caltrops.

"You're quite cunning!" With the change in direction from Triple Slash, he didn't step on the Caltrops. Du Ming didn't distract himself despite the close call. His next move had already begun.

Sword Draw!

Sword qi flew out. With this as a cover, Moon-Luring Frost leaped up, Falling Phoenix Slash! He directly shot down from the sky, creating an arc in the air.

Deception turned and ran.

"Hey! You bastard!" Du Ming shouted. Against Sun Xiang, that punk had rushed forward and fought a few exchanges directly, but against him, he just ran away. What was that supposed to mean? I'm scarier than Sun Xiang? Du Ming didn't think so. He couldn't understand what Mo Fan was thinking.

"Looks like Mo Fan's tired…" Happy's players saw through it.　

In the previous fight, he had played explosively multiple times and played to his limit. Those were just the two plays at the beginning too. Afterwards, in order to win against Sun Xiang, Mo Fan had fought even harder at his limits. He had beaten Sun Xiang, but those who didn't understand him wouldn't know how hard he had worked for that win. Now, against Du Ming, he didn't fight like he had with Sun Xiang. It wasn't that he didn't want to, but he couldn't. His energy didn't let him reach that crazy concentrated state.

"This punk, with that in him, we should put him in the individual competition more!" Wei Chen said.

Just when they were commenting on him, Mo Fan suddenly erupted!

Combo. Another invincible combo. Except this time, the first sneak hadn't been executed too well, and Du Ming was able to respond. However, Mo Fan didn't let up, the second, third attack… he attacked as if he were comboing and then finally on the fourth strike, he was able to break Du Ming's defenses.

Annihilation!

For the fifth strike, Deception actually used Annihilation. This low-level knock-up skill was never a finishing move for a combo. This could only mean that Mo Fan had no plans on stopping his combo.　　

"Is he crazy!" Wei Chen yelled out in amazement.

They thought Mo Fan was tired already, but he once again showed up with his three axes. On the fifth strike, which should have been the limit, he didn't stop but continued.

Flame Cut!

A blaze followed along the blade's path. Following Annihilation, this attack struck Moon-Luring Frost. The sixth strike was linked very precisely as well.

Then, Underground Tunneling Technique! Deception sprinted forward, but...　

"Too slow," Ye Xiu said.

Yes, the seventh strike was too slow. After being set ablaze by Flame Cut, Moon-Luring Frost made a move.

Falling Blossom Form!

It was faster than Deception's Underground Tunneling Technique. The swordpoint stabbed into Deception's back, and blood spurted out. Deception crashed to the ground.

The damage dealt by the Blade Master's four Level 75 skills weren't too terrifying, but the other areas were increased further.

A forced knock-down, Falling Blossom Form.

Maxed attack speed, Meteor Form.

High priority, Piercing Wind Form.

Sword qi that can pull the target, Curving Wind Form.

Falling Blossom Form just looked like a careless attack, but Deception had been knocked to the ground.

Falling Light Blade!

Moon-Luring Frost attacked again from the air towards Deception.

This combo was fast and without any openings. Deception, who had just crashed to the ground, could do nothing.

But afterwards, Deception rolled up and tried to dodge Feather Scar's control.

Lunge!

Sword light chased after Deception.

Pu! Deception poofed into smoke, turning into a strawman.

"Fuck!" Du Ming cursed angrily. Ninjas had more escape skills than other classes. What was usually a combo would be easily dispelled in front of Ninjas.

Du Ming had Moon-Luring Frost turn around in search of Deception's whereabouts.

The earth underneath him loosened.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

At the crucial moment, an opening appeared on Du Ming. Just like how Underground Tunneling Technique had struck One Autumn Leaf, it struck Moon-Luring Frost squarely. A combo once again began.

"He…" Everyone in Happy was dumbfounded.

"He's… purposely attacking his own limits…" Ye Xiu could see it. Confuse the opponent? They had overanalyzed it. Mo Fan had been challenging his own limits the entire time.

Chapter 1300: Long History

Mo Fan was testing his limits, but the reason why limits were called limits was because they couldn't be broken easily. Improving one's mechanics and awareness wasn't like farming for equipment in-game. You couldn't just get lucky and suddenly improve your strength with a piece of powerful equipment. These were things that were improved day by day, training and training, slowly accumulating real battle experience. If you wanted to break through your limits, it was the same. It wasn't as simple as one day becoming passionate about it, deciding to work hard and achieving a breakthrough.

　

Mo Fan was continuously testing his limits with disregard for everything else. He really was in a state he had never reached before in training. However, breaking through one's limits wasn't like farming equipment. It wasn't as if once you accomplished it everything was good. An abrupt breakthrough was one thing, but mastering it was another. In other words, you had to accumulate experience bit by bit.

　

Being able to defeat Sun Xiang, even if it was a One Autumn Leaf with only 72 percent of his health, was already an amazing breakthrough for Mo Fan. Against Du Ming, he wanted to continue, and was still stubbornly, even more wildly challenging his limits again and again. However, his condition had already been slipping, and though he had managed to surprise Du Ming, the other soon turned the tables. Deception's 14 percent health couldn't take much more before he eventually fell. Du Ming's victory was without suspense. Mo Fan's performance felt like it had plummeted at at the most crucial moment.

It seemed like defeating Sun Xiang had taken a lot out of him, however, he was still so fierce in this match...

Although he was just a newbie, Du Ming still felt a sense of respect rise for Mo Fan. This kind of opponent who never gave up was always worthy of respect, no matter where, no matter if they lost or won.

Leaving the stage, Mo Fan seemed rather worn out as expected. For him, it was a mental exhaustion. Constantly drawing together his focus to launch a barrage of intense attacks was like drawing himself tight like a bowstring. He had pushed himself, uncaring of the consequences.

"That was too reckless of you," Ye Xiu commented, looking at Mo Fan.

Mo Fan quietly glanced at Ye Xiu, but didn't say anything, returning to his own seat. Qiao Yifan passed a bottle of water over. Mo Fan stared for a moment in surprise before accepting it, nodding at Qiao Yifan in thanks.

What was this guy thinking? No one knew. The only one who could really communicate verbally with him was Su Mucheng. And even if it was Su Mucheng, she merely spoke more often to him, but never got a look into his thoughts.

"Talk with him more often!" Ye Xiu was helpless and could only hand things over to Su Mucheng, asking her to guide the loner.

By then, Happy's third player for the group arena had already stood.

Tang Rou, after the 1v3 incident, had been a constant as the anchor for the group arena. When she stood, the atmosphere in the venue chilled somewhat. Even now, Tang Rou's popularity was still at rock bottom. Even their home turf fans weren't very happy with her. It was clear what position she had amongst the fanbase. Plus, Happy only had her left while Samsara still had Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost with 91 percent health, and a full-health Zhou Zekai, Glory's Number One, Zhou Zekai.

There was no point in continuing.

That's what everyone thought. Even if they announced Samsara's victory now, no one would care, probably.

However, Tang Rou simply ignored all of this. She stood, accepting the encouragements and blessings from her teammates and walking towards the stage determinedly. Even if she heard the jeers from the crowd, she didn't care. In their home games, Happy's fans would give her face considering that she was a member of the team, but in an away game, Tang Rou was like a public enemy. If she could endure that, then this silence in their home game was like an applause.

This sort of atmosphere in a home game was really rather strange and oppressive. Even Samsara's players felt uncomfortable, looking around at Happy's fans. They, of course, knew why this was, it was just that they didn't think it would be so intense. Tang Rou was receiving this sort of treatment from her own team's fans, the ones who would most stand up for them. And their support of Team Happy was so passionate too. This truly was strange.

They all knew too clearly what this sort of circumstance meant for a pro player, but a young lady like Tang Rou still managed to endure.

Samsara had researched Tang Rou's matches. After the one versus three event, the biggest change to Tang Rou was becoming the last line of defense in the group arena rather than the spearhead. Apart from that, there was no change. Her fearsome performance remained the same. Her popularity might have frozen, but her strength was still improving steadily. Amongst the rookies this season, she was definitely the best when considering pure ability. If it wasn't for the fact that she had started a little old, her future would have been limitless. Then, with her flawless looks and demeanor, a lot of people felt that what had happened with her was a shame.

Slowly, there were some voices that spoke out, hoping that people could be more lenient on the rookie. However, there were always those that just wouldn't let go, especially Esports Home's Ruan Cheng as a representative, who was now a professional hater of Tang Rou's. No matter what article or commentary he was writing, he could always twist it to hate on Tang Rou a little. However, it was more Tang Rou's attitude that exacerbated it. If she could stand up and address the issue with sincerity, with the winds beginning to change and people beginning to stand up for her, then this incident might have passed by without further trouble.

　

However, she didn't. Tang Rou didn't seem to have anything to say about this. This was why many fans hated her. Everyone felt that she refused to learn from her mistakes, staying as stubborn as a mule. Then some tied this to her appearance, arguing that she was probably used to being spoiled because of her looks, so she thought she was special and could do whatever she wanted. The few who spoke for her failed to pull her out of this slump.

However, what was most depressing for the haters was that they couldn't use her performance on the field to attack her. After the one versus three incident, Happy entered a period of consecutive wins. The worst of their scores were 9 to 1, and even their loss against 301 Degrees was a 4 to 6. They had still managed to obtain the two points from the group arena. With their group arena always victorious, Tang Rou's performance as the last line of defense in the group arena was really flawless. This meant that they were trying to pick bones from eggs, discussing subjective things such as "what techniques were appropriate".

They had been left hungry for so long...

But now, against Samsara, Tang Rou was in a difficult place as the last line of defense. It was such a difficult place that these starved people thought that even if Tang Rou lost here, it wouldn't be anything they could feast on.

She was set against almost two whole opponents, with Zhou Zekai as one. Losing was all too expected.

After Tang Rou entered the booth, the atmosphere changed, buzzing chatter arising from the crowd. The crowd was chatting, discussing, gossiping, like no one cared about the following match. Since they didn't like the next player on Happy's side, they had already convinced themselves of how the following match would end.

There was no more sounds of encouragement. In fact, the number of people who were even remotely paying attention to the match had plummeted. Only Samsara's supporters were still cheering, happy that they would finally be able to take back two points in the group arena.

The match started. The applause that would usually ring out at a time like this was few and far between.

　

"Is this because of… Zhou Zekai?" Feeling this awkward atmosphere at their home game, Chen Guo was smiling in a rather strained way.

Tang Rou truly was unpopular, but when she was on the stage, she was still representing Happy. The fans might not like her, but they couldn't not hope for Happy's victory. Thus, when she went onstage to defend the arena, she would usually get some applause.

However, this time, it seemed like Happy's fans had given up on her.

Chen Guo knew that there was only one reason why this would happen. The fans believed that Happy couldn't possibly win.

Why?

　

Because Samsara had almost two full health characters left, a huge advantage.

Because one of these two was Zhou Zekai, Glory's Number One.

　

Zhou Zekai's strength went beyond just boosting the morale and confidence of his team. He hadn't even gotten onstage yet, and he could already influence the attitudes of the fans.

"They have Zhou Zekai, we can't win…"

Chen Guo now truly understood Zhou Zekai's status in the Alliance, seeing how he could create such ideas even in a home game.

　

Chen Guo was a little annoyed at these fans, but not long ago in the Spring Festival event, the passion of their fans had proved how much hope they had in Happy. Perhaps they couldn't be blamed. The only thing to be blamed was the sheer strength of Zhou Zekai's presence and… how deeply unpopular Tang Rou was. Perhaps, if it was a different member of Happy, they might've gotten some encouragement and support.

　

"Ai…" Chen Guo sighed. Tang Rou's persistence made Chen Guo feel even more helpless than Zhou Zekai's strength. That young lady really wasn't "soft" at all. Was her name given to use as mockery? Chen Guo silently thought in exasperation at that renowned father of Tang Rou's.*

　

The match begun under the attention - or lack thereof - of the audience. But the players onstage didn't know about the reactions of the crowd. Du Ming was very much looking forward to this match. As the match started, his character Moon-Luring Frost made a few more cool poses than he did last match.

　

"I never would've expected that we would meet in an official match," Du Ming sent into the chat.

　

Tang Rou replied with a smiley face.

　

"Let's give it our all!" Du Ming yelled excitedly.

"Of course," Tang Rou replied. Soft Mist charged out and Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost also charged directly. The two characters steadily entered each other's views without dodging or retreating, clashing head on.

Tang Rou was once the person who had put Du Ming in the most humiliating position.

In the audience player versus pro round of the All-Star Weekend, he had somehow lost to a challenging normal player and twice, too. For a long time, he had become a joke in their circle. But his opponent had been a normal player, while he was a pro. He couldn't go seeking revenge for something like that! Du Ming could only accept his misfortune and was depressed for a good while.

That was until the player that had defeated him seemed to have the intentions of going pro, and now, she was finally here on the same stage as Du Ming.

Revenge? Two years had past, and Du Ming really didn't have any intentions for revenge. However, he couldn't forget that incident. Thus, one day, after he realized that Tang Rou was entering the pro circle too, he began paying attention to her. The target of his attention wasn't one to keep a low profile either. Not long after entering the pro circle, she had gotten into quite the snit with the one versus three incident. She was the main character of it even.

　　

But she didn't manage the 1v3 and broke her promise, going from the protagonist to the antagonist, someone everyone hated.

Du Ming was stunned. Disregarding everything else, she was truly a girl with character, and she was also very beautiful.

His past grudge had faded and blurred, and Du Ming began to develop a liking for the young lady he had been paying attention to. Especially the one versus three incident, that had Du Ming's heart aching for her.

He really did want to go and support Tang Rou, but… just think of his position! After the one two three four All-Stars on Team Samsara, then the Assassin Wu Qi and Cleric Fang Minghua, only then you could get to him. For this sort of sensitive topic, the reporters would casually ask for Samsara's members' opinions, but it would never fall to him to answer.

Seeing Zhou Zekai hesitate for half a day before spitting out a very strange "really strong" as an answer, Du Ming kind of wanted to go up and punch in his handsome face.

Really strong my ass, what's really strong???

Du Ming had never felt so anxious about Zhou Zekai's lack of speaking ability.

Back then, Du Ming's state could be described as heart-in-throat. However, he soon realized that his worry was excessive. Though her popularity might've plummeted, Tang Rou's performance was even more stable. In the following period, Happy had performed even better than Samsara.

Du Ming's admiration for this young lady shot up another notch.

Round 20 had finally arrived and Samsara was once again faced with Happy. This time, Du Ming and Tang Rou had the chance to face each other on stage.

Du Ming was hyped, and the Samsara players on the bench were all deep in discussion too.

The attention Du Ming had directed at Tang Rou was no secret in Samsara. For example, Jiang Botao, immensely skilled at communicating and reading others, could easily see that this guy had a crush.

　

"That guy took his sword and charged. Seems to me he's in a pretty good state! Does this guy want to express his admiration for his goddess by crushing her?" Wu Qi wondered aloud, seeing Du Ming's more eager than normal performance.

　

"He's probably trying to attract her interest through showing off his own talent," Jiang Botao, as expected, was skilled at understanding others.

"How childish, like an elementary school kid!" Fang Minghua exclaimed.

"Holy crap!" Someone yelled in shock and Samsara's players all facepalmed, lowering their heads in silence for Du Ming.

Moon-Luring Frost, charging up excitedly, had been thrown to one side by a Circle Swing.

"Has he already been wiped out?" Lu Boyuan had a hand over his eyes, peeking at the situation through his fingers.

　

"No…" Zhou Zekai said.

"Ah, I was too careless!" Du Ming yelled into the chat.

　

"Jesus, this is embarrassing…" Samsara's players all decided.

　

"He won't start yelling 'I love you' or something right then and there, will he?"

"If that's the case, well, the transfer window still had two days to go, let's sell him!"

"Sell him to Happy?"

"That's probably exactly what he wants!" They laughed.

Onstage, the battle continued.

TN: *The "Rou" in Tang Rou means "soft" or "gentle", the same "soft" in Soft Mist, so, Chen Guo is talking about Tang Rou's birth name, not the name Soft Mist

Chapter 1301: Mistakes and Plays Going Beyond One’s Skill

Du Ming had been a bit too excited when he went onto the stage. The instant he went forward to make the first attack, he had still been wondering whether he should chat some more. But with Tang Rou's current skill level, how could it be so easy to deal with her? Tang Rou immediately saw a huge opening. A Circle Swing came out, and Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost kneeled.

Again!

Du Ming's mind raced like galloping grass mud horses*. He had wanted to put on an eyecatching performance, but as soon as the fight began, his show was smashed apart. He had let such a huge opening appear and be taken advantage of. How could he show any face?

Du Ming panicked and blurted out "I was careless".　　

But this was a competition! Wasn't giving this sort of explanation to the opponent even more shameful than being beaten down? Luckily, besides Samsara's players, no one else thought that. The viewers thought Du Ming was saying these words to his teammates, explaining to them the reason for his mistake.

Tang Rou saw Du Ming's shout, but why would she care? While Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost hastily got back up, Soft Mist's spear whistled towards him, once again putting Du Ming into a panic.

To put it simply, Du Ming looked excited, but his excitement wasn't excitement for the match. It was excitement for meeting Tang Rou again in a match. As a result, he wasn't actually in a competitor's mentality. His performance wasn't as stable as when he had fought against Mo Fan previously. He kneeled as soon as the fight started, and then Tang Rou's crazy offensive instantly took out 20% of his health.　

Too shameful!

Two years ago, he could have said that he had been caught off guard facing a normal player and had been too careless, but this time? If he lost again, wouldn't that indicate how incompetent he was?　

I CAN'T LOSE!!

Du Ming shouted in his heart. After Soft Mist's combo ended, he immediately launched a counterattack.　　

"Isn't Du Ming being too impatient?" Even Pan Lin instantly saw the issue. Tang Rou's combo had ended, but the situation hadn't reset back to zero. She still held the initiative. The combo had finished, but her offense hadn't ended yet. Her attacks were linked very closely together, yet Du Ming unexpectedly wanted to counterattack despite these circumstances. It just wasn't a good decision. Sure enough, Du Ming only just started his counterattack before Tang Rou's follow-up attacks smashed it apart, and another combo started.

"This Du Ming… At the All-Stars Weekend two years ago, he hadn't just lost to a normal player, but Tang Rou, who had only just started playing the game. He lost a lot of face there! It looks like he wants to redeem himself. Holding these thoughts, it's no surprise he's in a rush. I hope he can quickly calm himself down." Li Yibo was quite confident with his analysis this time because there was no other explanation he could think of. If he knew that Du Ming's train wreck of a performance stemmed from his crush on Tang Rou, his mind would also be racing like galloping grass mud horses.

Soft Mist started another combo. The damage from this combo was even higher than the last. Moon-Luring Frost lost 23% of his health. He only had 48% health remaining now, not even half. As for Tang Rou's Soft Mist? Because she had traded blows at the start, she only lost 4% of her health from this exchange, which was already lower than usual. All of this was because of Du Ming's unusually poor playing.

"Damn, this is the pace to a blowout!" Samsara's players had been joking around in the beginning, but now, their tone was more serious.

They knew about Du Ming's thoughts, so they could understand why he hadn't been able to contain his excitement at the start of the match, but he still hadn't adjusted his mindset. This wasn't right. As a pro player, personal feelings should not be affecting your playing to such an extent. If he really lost in such a manner, the team would need to give him a harsh reprimandment.　

Samsara's players stopped their banter. Their eyes were focused on the match.　

　

After two combos, his character was not even at half health, while his opponent had only lost 4%.

What am I doing?　　

Du Ming asked himself honestly.　　

I might have been waiting this match for a long time, but haven't I been too negligent? This was a competition.

When competing, I should be going in with a steady mindset. Getting too excited or getting too indifferent is no good, and Team Samsara is the best in the Alliance at this point. Despite having won two championships already, we've always kept our calm, never arrogant in victory and never hateful in defeat.

I haven't won or lost, yet I've become a complete mess just because I'm meeting a girl I like?

Yes, a complete mess!　

No one was more clear than him just how terrible he had been playing. He could lose, but not like this!

Come!

Tang Rou didn't try to understand Du Ming's mindset and started off with two combos. Her combos were smooth and successful. She obviously didn't plan on stopping here. Her third wave of attacks instantly arrived.

Triple Slash!

Du Ming's Moon-Luring Frost suddenly dashed out at an unexpected moment.　　

"Du Ming is really being too impatient!" Pan Lin shouted.

Li Yibo was just about to add to these words, but the match progressed extremely fast. Moon-Luring Frost looked like he was just about to crash into Soft Mist's attack, but instead just barely dodged it.

It had been an extremely narrow dodge.

Was it a coincidence? Or had Du Ming suddenly become precise?

Du Ming quickly told everyone the answer. The instant he brushed past the attack, the second slash came out. When he dodged the attack, his sword struck Soft Mist, and his Moon-Luring Frost moved horizontally, using the second slash to circle around Soft Mist. The third slash followed closely afterwards, and the instant it hit, Moon-Luring Frost was behind Soft Mist.

Everyone was dumbstruck, including the players on both teams. Du Ming's sudden burst had been completely outside everyone's expectations. His play had been extremely fast and precise.

Fast wasn't difficult for an overly excited Du Ming, and it was precisely because of that extraordinary speed that Samsara's players felt like he had exceeded his skill level.

But with speed, Du Ming lost precision. Because although he was excited, his mindset wasn't in the right place. His attention wasn't on the match. Without any focus, how could he be precise? As a result, Du Ming might have been fast, but he was also imprecise. It was how Soft Mist was able to instantly break through his attacks and complete two devastating combos.

However, Du Ming had finally become focused again. This Triple Slash had been beyond his skill level, and for a moment, Tang Rou wasn't able to keep up with the sudden change in pace. Two of the three slashes had struck Soft Mist, and Moon-Luring Frost had also circled behind her. Du Ming's counterattack was truly resounding this time. A flurry of sword slashes along with increased damage from back attacks splattered blood across the air. Du Ming had the nickname "Berserk Blade Master" for a reason. The word "Berserk" showed precisely what his playstyle was like. And right now, he was going wild, an extremely precise wildness. A full combo landed on Soft Mist's back.

31%.

This was the total damage dealt by Du Ming's combo. It was far higher than anything Tang Rou had done. One reason was because Du Ming's combo had been from the back. Another reason was because Soft Mist's equipment was still a little bit lacking compared to Moon-Luring Frost's.

Soft Mist's health instantly plummeted to 65%. As for Moon-Luring Frost? After completing his combo, he hadn't received any damage. All of Tang Rou's attempts at resisting had been blocked by him. Moon-Luring Frost's health was still at 48%.

65% to 48%. The gap didn't seem that large anymore.

This time, Du Ming did not show mercy to those had wronged him. He wasn't finished with just one combo and followed up with more attacks.

Berserk Blade Master.

Du Ming's style was actually very similar to Tang Rou's. He was good at fighting for the initiative, forcing fights, and violent attacks.　

However, Tang Rou wasn't caught unprepared like last time. Her spear, Dancing Fire Flowing Flames, and Du Ming's lightsaber, Lingering Ice, clashed. Just from the name, it sounded like a battle of ice and fire. The glow given by the two weapons intertwined as if trying to devour the other.

"The battle has only just begun!" This clash pulled the battle back to a point where neither side had the advantage. Du Ming had the time, so he immediately typed out a message. Apart from fighting each other in this match, he also hoped that they could have a bit of chat together.

Of course, telling the other side "this is my true power" through these words was also a bit of selfishness on his part.

"There's no saving him…" When they saw Du Ming back to his usual self, Samsara's players returned to their relaxed state. And seeing how that guy even felt the need to say a few words, they collectively put their hands to their foreheads.

"Shouldn't he win the fight before spouting nonsense?" Samsara's players started discussing amongst themselves.

"But if he wins, who will listen to his nonsense?"

"It looks like he's got the guts to chase after her to Happy's side and worm his way into a relationship."

"He sounds so pitiful. But if it's like this, can we feel relaxed putting him in the team competition?"　　

"There's nothing we can do. The lineup is already locked in."

"All five players are needed to win this match! What if his mind is too preoccupied with other things?"

"He looks fine right now!"

"He looks fine right now, but what about afterwards? He'll feel like he performed well in front of his goddess, and then he'll go crazy thinking he's in heaven, what then?"

"That really might be a problem!"

"Yes, we can't be careless. We'll have to shoulder his burden in the team competition!"

"Hey hey...." At this moment, Wu Qi interrupted their discussion, "He isn't even playing in the team competition. I'm the sixth player!"

Chapter 1302: The Belief for Victory

Du Ming had recovered his usual form. His performance was slightly better than usual, aided by the fact that he was somewhat excited today. But what about Tang Rou? She worked as hard as always. She never let her guard down, regardless of the situation or the opponent.

The publicized bet for a 1v3 had already passed, but in Tang Rou's mind, she still hadn't achieved her goal of a 1v3!

Even though she was the anchor in the group arena, and there weren't three opponents for her to beat up, Tang Rou always played with the mindset to do so.

Du Ming switched suddenly from making extraordinary blunders to making extraordinary plays. This large variation did catch Tang Rou off-guard, but her mental state wasn't affected.

Strive for victory.

Tang Rou would always have this mentality. Regardless of whether her opponent was weak or strong, regardless of whether her opponent was blundering or playing beautifully.

Du Ming used the chat, thinking that Tang Rou would now acknowledge his skill. Unfortunately for him, Tang Rou didn't consider anything along those lines.

Bring him down! That was the only thing she was thinking. If Du Ming knew that his goddess's attitude towards him was so single-minded, who knew how long he'd be depressed for.

Thankfully he didn't know, so he felt some satisfaction that his goddess could witness him playing better than his normal skill. However, when he said "The battle has only just begun!", Tang Rou definitely hadn't just begun. While Du Ming considered this a reset and an opportunity to regain the upper hand, Tang Rou maintained her rhythm and clung onto any opportunities to launch attacks.

Du Ming thought that typing some words in this situation would be no big deal. He still underestimated Tang Rou's drive for victory, and also her tunnel vision for it.

She had zero intentions of chatting with Du Ming. The words that Du Ming thought were no big deal actually caused him to momentarily lose initiative.

Tang Rou was once again given the role of the aggressor. Magic emanated from and swirled around Soft Mist, while she wildly charged towards the gates of victory.

Du Ming didn't expect to be suppressed so soon. Even though his mental state was quite steady right now and he defended well, Tang Rou's offensive also felt more concentrated than before...

This tireless attitude was really indistinguishable from that time....

Du Ming's mind started wandering again, rewinding to the Allstars Weekend from two years ago, when his team Samsara was hosting. A beautiful newbie was fortunate enough to get the chance to challenge him. Berserk Blade Master Du Ming didn't want to be cruel and pick on this pretty girl. Turns out the pretty girl was cruel and picked on him, promptly destroying him when they fought.

Du Ming had been anxious. Disregarding the rules, he quickly issued another challenge which he won. The girl then accepted and won again! Du Ming felt ashamed and restless at the time, and with no regard for anything else, kept fight fight fighting… Then he somehow summoned God Ye Xiu, who tore him a new one.

Du Ming was very bitter at the time. He was very bitter that the newbie made him lose face big time. But now… thinking back, why did he feel a sense of sweet nostalgia?

What would have happened at the time if it wasn't for the meddling Ye Xiu? What would have happened if they kept fighting? Du Ming even started fantasizing about how the story could have continued…

Boom!

Magic gathered in front of Moon-Luring Frost's chest and exploded loudly. His guard had been broken through!

Crap!

Du Ming realised that his concentration had slipped yet again. Facing this matter, it really was hard to control his own emotions! Du Ming hastily controlled Moon-Luring Frost to try to salvage the situation, but he was too late. Tang Rou would never let an opportunity slip, and Du Ming was met with an intense wave of attacks. This formed a complete offensive when combined with the previous wave of attacks. Moon-Luring Frost was thrown around by the magical explosions, and his health dropped in chunks...

"Next time, I definitely won't lose!!!" Du Ming called out.

"Still yelling… He couldn't be more embarrassing if he tried!" Samsara's players did not know whether to laugh or cry. Du Ming's performance really was unacceptable. It was fortunate that Samsara still had a big advantage. What if this was the deciding match? What if this match was the championship finals? This kind of unstable performance would render his entire team's effort for naught.

Du Ming returned from the stage. Samsara's players put away their laughing and joking faces they had during the match and switched to looking at him with austere expressions.

Du Ming lowered his head. Of course he knew where his problem laid. He did take control of the situation at some points, but somehow it slipped from his grasp in the final moments of the battle.

"I…" Du Ming wanted to give a reason for his failure, but it was embarrassing to open up about subjects such as crushes.

"You played rigidly, and your concentration was off," said Jiang Botao.

"Yeah." Du Ming nodded. He couldn't argue against that.

"Our captain is very angry. He said you didn't put enough importance on the competition; when the whole team was working hard for victory, you were too engaged with your own thoughts. If this were the championship match and we lost the points because you were distracted and we ended up losing the championship, what would you do?" Wu Qi said.

Du Ming raised his head in surprise. "The captain said that much?"

"Yeah, the captain's rage induced many words," Wu Qi said.

Du Ming rolled his eyes. Wu Qi was definitely just trolling. However, the words may have been nonsense, but idea behind it was not. What if Samsara really lost their chance at three consecutive championships because of him? When Du Ming thought about this, he suddenly felt a wave of fear. This really should not have happened… Du Ming raised his head and watched the replay from his match. 70% of his play in this match was trash.

"As someone with experience, I know this is quite difficult for you. But you need to learn to control it. No matter what happens, it should not affect your performance on stage," Samsara's Cleric player Fang Minghua said. In esports, the average age of the players was very young. There was a big pile of players who were still in their teens, and very few were married. But Samsara's Fang Minghua was one of the few who was.

"I will…" Du Ming nodded his head.

On stage, the final battle of the group arena was about to start. Samsara's captain Zhou Zekai had already entered the stage, and the countdown for the start of the battle quickly began.

"That win came pretty easily…" On Happy's side, Fang Rui expressed his opinion as his team were discussing the match that just concluded.

"Yeah. That kid from Samsara is very inconsistent," Ye Xiu said.

"Wasn't Du Ming the one who lost to little Tang twice in the All Stars Weekend two years ago? I bet he lost his calm today after seeing her! Hahaha!" Chen Guo laughed.

"Probably!" Ye Xiu nodded. Du Ming's crush was completely known to the people at Happy, whom he had never interacted with.

"This match…" Chen Guo looked at the stage and the loading bars for the two characters, and didn't know what to say.

Even though Tang Rou had just won, there was a period where Du Ming performed above expectations. After that, there was also a steady period where he defended well. Du Ming still managed to grind down some of Soft Mist's health, which now sat at exactly 50%. Now, she was to face the number one in Glory, Zhou Zekai.

"Can she win?" Chen Guo felt her heart leap. If she really won, surely Tang Rou would become a hero? Even Happy fans who didn't like her would relish in the fact that she defeated Zhou Zekai with 50% health, since this was glory that belonged to all of Team Happy. If it was like this, then everyone would slowly change their opinion of Tang Rou. It would only be a matter of time before they started liking her again.

A sense of belief brewed within Chen Guo's mind. She also felt the change of atmosphere from the viewers. Their disinterest when Tang Rou entered the stage melted away. Expending 50% health to deal with Du Ming was nowhere near enough to establish confidence in anyone, but it did give them a sliver of belief. The player currently on stage was not like the viewers. She would not lose her fighting spirit just because she had to face Zhou Zekai.

She was pushing her limits. She worked hard to bring one down, and there was no doubt in anyone's mind that she would continue to work hard; maybe she would work even harder to bring down the next one. Zhou Zekai, the number one in Glory, would make many players lose part of their will to fight before the fight even started. To them, losing against him was almost an expectation.

No one could see this attitude at all on Tang Rou. She was just a rookie. If she lost here, not even her haters would be able to make a big deal out of it. But Tang Rou herself carried the air of someone who wouldn't forgive herself for losing. Once again, she charged forward, poised for victory, with no regard for anything else.

The first to attack was Cloud Piercer.

A fight between a ranged class and a melee class would always start off advantageous for the ranged class. The dance between the two opponents consisted of the melee class attempting to close the distance and the ranged class attempting to maintain it. At the start, it might seem one sided the ranged class uses the melee class for target practice, but as soon as the melee class got close, they could potentially reverse the ranged class's advantage in one fell swoop.

Charge, charge forward! Soft Mist darted around through the hailstorm of bullets. A Sharpshooter was a subclass that has perfected the art of shooting. It didn't have the same fancy array of armaments compared to its three cousin subclasses. It only focused on guns and bullets. Its skills revolved around various methods for shooting.

Quick shots, spread shots, dual wielding, chains. The Sharpshooter had the most shooting styles and stances. The hailstorm of bullets they unleashed was a true bulletstorm. There was little smoke and explosion, just bullet after bullet whizzing past.

Can she make the charge?!

Soft Mist advanced in what was probably the strongest bulletstorm of the Alliance. Every step forward seemed that much more difficult.

Cloud Piercer's health was still full while Soft Mist's continued declining. However, she seemed like the one with an advantage right now, because the distance between the characters that determined life and death was shrinking slowly but surely. Her health was not being wasted.

Charge! Destroy him!

Gradually, this voice appeared within everyone's heads. At this moment, they forgot who the opponent was. They forgot their mindset that losing to this opponent was only normal.

"Charge!" a shout suddenly erupted in the stadium. Soft Mist finally covered the whole distance. With 17% health remaining, she managed to charge directly up to Cloud Piercer's face.

"Destroy him!" Happy's fans had long forgotten about their previous cold shoulder of Tang Rou, and hollered madly.

Although Soft Mist's remaining health was low, sometimes a melee class could decide the outcome of the battle in one direct confrontation with a ranged class. The two sides would had vastly different fighting styles and had huge differences in strength at different attacking distances.

But…

Bang bang bang bang…

Cloud Piercer continued shooting. Even though Soft Mist was next to him, he used the Sharpshooter's Taijutsu skills. Cloud Piercer began directly trading with Soft Mist.

Gun Fu…

This wasn't a skill described by the game. Rather, it was a high-end technique invented by the players themselves by mixing and matching skills. Most in the online game could only use Taijutsu. Gun Fu was a technique that only pro level players could achieve. Because of its immense difficulty, it was still difficult to gain an advantage using Gun Fu against a pure melee class. It mostly just prevented Sharpshooters from being helpless once locked in close combat, unlike other long ranged classes.

Right now, Zhou Zekai showed off his Gun Fu. Legs, knees, elbows, as well as bullets… they entered into a brawl with the spear that was in Soft Mist's hand.

It could be seen that even Zhou Zekai using Gun Fu could not suppress Tang Rou. His skill only carried him that far. Gun Fu was indeed very sophisticated, being very swift and accurate. However, it still lacked a melee class's ferocity. Its sophistication could not suppress this wave of ferocity.

He might have been able to deal significant damage, but the ability to control and limit the opponent was too weak. This was the drawback of Gun Fu.

However, the difference between the health of the two characters was far too large.

When Soft Mist got into attack range, her health was 17% compared to Cloud Piercer's 100%.

Zhou Zekai's Gun Fu was indeed more skillful; the Great Gunner Cloud Piercer's equipment was also much stronger than Soft Mist's.

Therefore, even though Zhou Zekai's Gun Fu could not suppress Tang Rou's Soft Mist, he could just rely on trading health. Everyone know that the victory this round still belonged to Zhou Zekai.

In the end, this was the reality.

After getting close, Zhou Zekai chose to fight head-on against Tang Rou with Gun Fu. Tang Rou could only reply by fighting head on. She already got that far, there was no second option.

Finally, Soft Mist fell. That tiny sliver of belief did not bear fruit.

However, that was only this one time. What about next time? What would happen next time?

Cloud Piercer still had 75% health remaining.

During the explosive melee, Soft Mist's 17% health managed to trade away 25% of Cloud Piercer's.

What if Soft Mist entered the battle with full health? Starting at 100% and paying a 33% gap-closing tax, how much damage would she able to do with the remaining 67% health?

98.5%! So close to 100%! If Soft Mist started on full health this fight, she would only be 1.5% health from victory. Maybe she really could have done it?

Of course, if it was a fair fight where both started on full health, Zhou Zekai probably wouldn't use Gun Fu to force out the ending, rather he'd seek a chance to keep the distance. Regardless, this theoretical calculation still let people see hope.

With hope, there would be belief.

For Tang Rou, there was a belief that she could defeat Zhou Zekai!

Happy lost the group arena. However, when Tang Rou left the stage, she heard applause for the first time in a long time. Applause directed towards her.

Tang Rou smiled.

She could bear the coldest reception and continue walking forward with her head held high.

However, support and encouragement would always allow one to feel happiness.

"How amazing!" Du Ming exclaimed, upon seeing the atmosphere change throughout the stadium. Then he met the eternal stares of all his teammates.

"Using Gun Fu to crush a Battle Mage, how amazing! Captain, I'm your biggest fanboy!!" Du Ming hollered at Zhou Zekai as he left the stage.

Chapter 1303: Happy’s Cleric

The group arena eventually ended in Samsara's favor. With the individual rounds resulting in a 3 to 2, a 10-0 was now entirely impossible. This meant that neither Happy nor Samsara fans had a good slogan to chant. They had always found 10-0 to be the smoothest of slogans.

Having caught up after winning the group arena, Samsara's morale had been boosted greatly. Their fans were also much more lively. As for Happy? They were a little disappointed that they hadn't managed to claim victory in the group arena, but Tang Rou's performance had far exceeded their expectations. They didn't seem to worried about losing two points, but Happy's players were feeling far more conflicted. They could feel the pressure from Samsara.

There was a rather long break between the individual rounds and the team competition. The players of the two teams were gathered in their own groups, discussing strategies for the team competition. Technically, teams were allowed to return to their prep rooms during this time, but most teams found it troublesome, so they usually wouldn't run back to their prep rooms.

"For the individual rounds, both sides have losses and wins. How this match will go is truly hard to predict. What do you think, Advisor Li?" During the break, apart from ads, the live broadcast could only have the commentators kill time.

"Indeed, it's hard to predict," Li Yibo solemnly agreed with this judgement, "On paper, Samsara's lineup is stronger, but Happy has the home advantage."

"Then what do you think will be the deciding factor?" Pan Lin asked.

Li Yibo felt pained. This was exactly the kind of precise prediction he wanted to avoid, but he knew that if he avoided all questions like this, he would be worthless as a special guest. Thus, most times, even if he was hesitant, he had to harden his heart and give them something.

　

"Hm, I think… it will depend on the healers. Happy's healer is their weakness. This isn't a secret anymore. In the past, many teams have tried to capitalize on this weakness, but the only team to have succeeded so far is 301. We can see that even though Happy's healer isn't the best, without him, Happy's team still cannot operate at its peak and they will still lose. In this round, I think Samsara's focus point will still be Happy's healer."

"Will they have their Assassin use Life-Risking Strike?" Pan Lin wondered.

　

"Possibly…" Li Yibo contemplated, "One hit KO, a powerful offensive, or like Thunderclap, using strategy to pressure them. I think all these are equally possible. It depends on Samsara's choice."

"Haha, comparatively, I'm actually more interested in how Happy is going to use their Cleric in this match against Samsara. Many of the strategies they plan around this weakness of theirs are very interesting," Pan Lin commented.

"Heh," Li Yibo chuckled, "A significant weakness in their formation, but Happy has never gone to find a way to patch it up. With their current record, they could easily find a better Cleric player during the winter transfer window. However, Happy doesn't seem to have any intentions to do so. Sometimes I feel like Happy's Cleric might seem like a flaw to us, but in Happy's designs, he's a trap, one to counter their opponent's strategies."

　

"Ah!" Pan Lin was stunned by Li Yibo's analysis, "Your view on this is truly brilliant!"

"With this weakness, Happy can more or less predict what the opponent is going to target. Then, with a cunning and experienced veteran tactician like Ye Xiu, they might've long since calculated for what strategies their opponents will use," Li Yibo said.

　

"That's brilliant! Absolutely brilliant!" Pan Lin exclaimed even as he felt a little strange at this behavior. It had been a while since this Li Yibo had made such bold predictions about another team's tactics.

"So how are they planning on dealing with Samsara this round? Like you, I too am very curious." Finishing his speech, Li Yibo gave a sigh of relief. He was rather direct. Either he didn't speak at all, or he analyzed everything comprehensively if he did. Pan Lin had already agreed with his views and began to delve deeper into discussing it.

The two killed time like it was a talk show and continued to discuss until the team competition was due to start.

Happy: Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, sixth player Tang Rou.

Samsara: Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Sun Xiang, Lu Boyuan, Fang Minghua, sixth player Wu Qi.

　

With the formations revealed, the two began their commentary on the lineups.

　

"Advisor Li, I've realized that these two teams share a point of similarity today," Pan Lin noted.

"Oh?"

"These two teams haven't made any arrangements in accordance to their opponent. They've both chosen to use their most frequent lineups in this match," Pan Lin explained.

"Indeed. The two teams are facing this match with a normal attitude. They didn't place importance on this match like the outside world did and are treating it like any of the other 37 matches," Li Yibo determined.

"Yes, but this match is still amazing nonetheless."

"The players have performed unexpectedly well, thus leading the high performance of the match," Li Yibo said.

　

After a few exchanged sentences, the players had finished their greetings and entered their booths. The team competition was ready to start. The projection started to show the characters of each team, first the away team, and then the home team. Each side had one onstage, switching positions and the screen began showing the data for each character.

When Samsara's One autumn Leaf and Happy's Dancing Rain appeared simultaneously, the atmosphere suddenly changed. Many of the Glory fans at Xiaoshan Stadium were past-Excellent Era supporters. One Autumn Leaf and Dancing Rain were two characters with six years of history together and harboring far too many of their hopes and dreams. Today, they were once again side by side, but not as Best Partners anymore, but as opponents. This feeling was heart rending for the Excellent Era fans, who had gotten so used their partnership. In that moment, the applause in the stadium was a little dry.

It was just good that the character introductions wouldn't last too long. After these two, two new characters appeared, then, eventually, it got to the healers of the two teams.

Samsara, Laughing Song; Happy, Little Cold Hands.

"Huh?" Someone immediately realized something was wrong when Little Cold Hands appeared.

　

"That's Little Cold Hands?" Someone called out in surprise. The equipment and style was completely different from the Little Cold Hands that they had seen for half a season.

The commentator Pan Lin and guest Li Yibo also noticed this situation.

　

"Little Cold Hands' equipment seems to have changed," Pan Lin noted.

Li Yibo nodded, already looking to the data displayed on the screen. The moment he saw it, he sucked in a breath.

"1810 Intelligence?" Li Yibo blinked. Yes, he wasn't hallucinating. Among Little Cold Hands' four stats, the intelligence was 1810.

"1810?" Hearing this data, Pan Lin was struck dumb. To do his job, he naturally had to have a good knowledge of Glory. He naturally wouldn't be expected or able to remember what the stats of all the pro accounts were, but some rather outstanding stats he knew like the back of his hand.

"No way! Tyranny's Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock only has 1570 Intelligence!" Pan Lin looked at Li Yibo in disbelief and hurriedly went to check Little Cold Hands' data himself. That's right, the Intelligence really was 1810.

By then, Li Yibo's attention had shifted.

"A full set of Silver equipment!" Li Yibo sucked in another breath, a pained feeling rising in his heart. Fuck, in the end he still got face slapped by Happy! He had only just said that they weren't at all focused on strengthening their Cleric, purposefully creating openings to use as bait, yet in the blink of an eye, they might've not switched players, but they had strengthened their Cleric to its limits. This intelligence was 240 points above the Alliance's Number One Cleric; wasn't that a little overdoing it?!

Li Yibo's mind drifted a little, but Pan Lin continued looking and noticed something else.

"These four stats… don't they look a little off, Advisor Li?" Pan Lin called.

Li Yibo returned to the present and hurriedly took a look.

"Er… This…" Li Yibo's foundations were very solid, so he understood, looking at Little Cold Hands' final four stats.

　　

"They're pushing intelligence to the limit, no wonder it's so high," Li Yibo commented.

"Nowadays… are there still people who would do this?" Pan Lin said, confused.

"No." Li Yibo shook his head with certainty. In order to maximize a player's combat potential, balance was necessary. It was more common to see this push for intelligence in the online game. These Clerics had immense healing ability which would reduce the difficulty of the dungeon run. However, the pro scene was pure PvP. It was good to have powerful healing, but one must consider the other abilities of the healer. The stat increases the system gave upon levelling up were the same for everyone, so no one would get more or less than anyone else. Thus, the eventual four stats of the character would be adjusted by the equipment. The stats on equipment were limited though, so you had to lose some to gain some. Intelligence was the primary focus, but that didn't mean you should sacrifice everything for it.

However, that's exactly what Little Cold Hands had done.

Then, looking closely, the crit...

"This… this is entirely a PvE Cleric!" Li Yibo couldn't help but yell.

"His ice and dark resistance is pretty high," Pan Lin said,

"High counter control, but the other spirit based stats are only so-so. They didn't seem to have pushed for them," Li Yibo noted. The Cleric class' growth was mainly in the spirit stat, then the intelligence stat.

"Intelligence, crit, they're pushing these two to the limit… In terms of purely healing power, this is probably Glory's Number One Cleric," Li Yibo decided.

"No…" Just as he had made his judgement, Li Yibo suddenly rejected it. "It's better to say, looking at just the amount healed by a single skill, this is definitely the Number One Cleric. However, his cast speed isn't outstanding, so if we consider cast time, cooldowns, etc, then it's really hard to say how his heal per second is."

"What is Happy trying to do, making a Cleric like this?" Pan Lin said in shock. By then, the two Clerics had left the stage, switched out for the sixth players of each team.

Chapter 1304: Challenger

No one was paying attention to the sixth player right now. Everyone was discussing Little Cold Hand's huge transformation.

A full set of Silver equipment. Even though they could not see the stats, to the players, the dazzling silver lettering could only be described as tyrannical. 1810 Intelligence. It was immediately obvious that this was the highest Intelligence any Cleric had in Glory. The entire Xiaoshan Stadium was buzzing with whispers.

Was Happy's weak point, their healer An Wenyi, about to make a counterattack?

The problem was that the main criticism towards An Wenyi had been his skill. Everyone felt like if Happy could find a better healer, the team would instantly improve. However, Happy did not replace their healer and instead sharply upgraded his character. This method of fixing their weak point didn't seem logical?

The crowd didn't care about all that though. As soon as they saw their own team's character suddenly burst onto the stage with flashing Silver equipment, they instantly erupted with excitement. On the broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo started to discuss this issue.

Why was Happy willing to spend so much on strengthening their healer character instead of spending the money on a better healer player?

Was there something special about An Wenyi that made Happy willing to pile so many of their resources onto him?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo looked at their information on Happy, but they just couldn't figure it out. The battle officially started, and the two characters loaded onto opposite corners of the map.

The map was Labor Mining Site, located at a mining site at the foot of a mountain. The structure of the terrain was complex, and there was no part of the map spacious enough to fit all ten players fighting at the same time. It was a map which required each team to move into a formation before advancing ahead into the terrain.

Happy moved swiftly as soon as the battle began and pressed forward, taking the middle route. Samsara pushed forward as well, but as they moved, their chat blossomed with liveliness.

"Did you guys see Happy's Cleric?" Jiang Botao and Lu Boyuan typed out simultaneously.

"I saw," Fang Minghua replied.

"What are your thoughts?" Jiang Botao asked. When discussing a healer, Fang Minghua would obviously be the one with greater authority.

"High intelligence, high crit, his heals will be stronger. Happy is making up for An Wenyi's weakness to a certain extent," Fang Minghua said. Samsara had analyzed Happy's weaknesses long ago. There was no need to re-emphasize this point.

"But aren't his stats a bit imbalanced?" Jiang Botao said.

"It's a bit on the extreme side. His cast speed is too mediocre. He'll require more protection when he's healing," Fang Minghua said.

"So you're saying that his teammates will have to take up a greater burden?" Jiang Botao pointed out the important part.

"Yes," Fang Minghua affirmed.

"It's indeed not bad a adjustment!" Jiang Botao said.

"How are we playing this?" Sun Xiang asked. The huge change that Happy had made happened to be the main focus point of their prepared plans.

"I suggest no change," Fang Minghua said.

"Mm, just treat it as a normal match and put pressure on the healer!" Jiang Botao said.

Happy's healer was their weak point, which became the focus of every team's strategy. But even without the healer being the weak point, targeting the healer was a very common strategy in the team competition. Samsara adjusted by treating this match as an ordinary one. They clearly had their misgivings towards suddenly upgrading An Wenyi's equipment.

Along with Pan Lin, Li Yibo, and many others thinking the same question, Samsara didn't think strengthening the character was a good solution.

This method may have resolved the old issue, but it brought up a new one too: the rest of the team had to share the extra burden. That meant everyone else needed to focus more of their attention towards protecting him. The hazard might have been reduced, but it had also become more spread out. What would happen if someone became distracted for a moment and failed to complete their task of protecting him?

Therefore, focus the healer!

Team Samsara's final decision for the core of their strategy had not changed. As for the specifics, those would change depending on the circumstances. They had to at least just how much the upgraded healer character impacted Happy.　　

The two teams soon came across each other. They did not immediately fight. On this complicated map, the instant the two teams found one another, the two teams scattered to quickly occupy advantageous positions.

The long-ranged classes searched for attacking spots, where they could better display their firepower. The close-ranged classes searched for routes, where they could better hide themselves while moving forward.

As the main team, Happy had a smoother time on this point. They had been prepared and practiced long beforehand. Everyone quickly found a good spot for themselves. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain climbed to a rock jutting out of the mountainside and made the first attack in the team competition.

Bang!

A Stinger arced in a curve as it flew through the air. It quickly dropped down, and with a bang, it exploded like fireworks. Countless missiles burst out.

Boom boom boom...

The stingers crashed to the ground and turned the area into a sea of fire. Sun Xiang and Lu Boyuan were depressed. These two close-ranged players had picked this ditch to close in on Happy, but as soon as the fight started, Su Mucheng sent a missile at them.

One went left, and the other went right as they scurried out of the ditch. The two could only stare at Dancing Rain, who was on top of that rock with her hair fluttering in the wind. There was nothing they could do. They didn't have the range.

Zhou Zekai looked to have moved sluggishly, but he had been waiting for Happy to fall into position to make the first move. After Dancing Rain attacked and exposed herself, Cloud Piercer, Samsara's longest-ranged character, immediately moved towards her. Only he had the range to keep Dancing Rain's support under control.

But before Cloud Piercer could move into position, a gunshot landed beside him. Zhou Zekai could tell from the sound that it wasn't from Dancing Rain. The only other person who could fire a gun was Ye Xiu's Lord Grim.

Lord Grim had climbed over a ruined wall. The distance between him and Cloud Piercer was only five steps. Lord Grim could even combo his movement skills. What was five steps to him?

Zhou Zekai also realized the crisis. Cloud Piercer hastily retreated.　　

Lord Grim used his movement skills and rapidly rushed at him.

Ye Xiu, Zhou Zekai.

The number one players of the old and new generation. A face to face confrontation had come.

Who was better? Everyone was curious about this question.

Zhou Zekai had debuted in Season 5. It was from that season onwards that Excellent Era never entered the finals again. But at that time, Ye Xiu shined as brilliant as ever. The crown of number one player in Glory belonged to him. Who would have thought that Samsara, a mid-tier team, would find this quiet person who would one day became the Great Gunner and become the number one Glory player of the new generation.

When the Zhou Zekai of that era fought against Ye Xiu, no one would have regarded it as a battle between number ones, but rather a pretty good rookie versus a God.

But soon, everyone started to realize that this Zhou Zekai wasn't as simple as "pretty good". After Samsara took in this player, their fate instantly turned around. That season, Samsara made it to the playoffs, a breakthrough for them. However, because of the quiet personality of Zhou Zekai, he didn't synergize well with the rest of the team. In the end, the team was only able to make it to playoffs but nothing more.

Samsara had a headache over this problem, but soon afterwards, they uncovered a new rookie in Season 6. At that time, Jiang Botao had been a part of Team Parade. After a careful observation, Samsara quickly confirmed that Jiang Botao was exactly what their team needed, a person to stand by Zhou Zekai. That winter season, Team Samsara impatiently purchased this rookie. After half a year of practice, Jiang Botao was able to become the link between Zhou Zekai and rest of the team just like they had wanted. And in Season 7, Jiang Botao took up the position of vice-captain. At this point, the young players of Samsara had matured. The Season 7 Samsara had finally broken past the first round of the playoffs. Zhou Zekai's popularity was incomparable that season. In comparison, Excellent Era had started to go on the decline. The title of number one started to falter. Wang Jiexi? Huang Shaotian? Zhou Zekai? These names started being mentioned. Among them, Zhou Zekai was the youngest and his performance on stage was the most dominating. Everyone thought highly of his future. The only thing he was missing was a championship victory.

Finally, in Season 8, Ye Xiu retired midway. The former number one said goodbye to the stage, and someone needed to take up his banner. That season, Zhou Zekai and Team Samsara seized the championship cup. It seemed to be a declaration that he was the successor to the title. And in Season 9, Samsara won the championships for a second time. From then on, his title as number one was unshakeable. But then, in Season 10, the former number one, Ye Xiu, returned...

Who was the real number one?

The media definitely wasn't going to miss such a fiery topic. But Ye Xiu was already at such an old age. Excellent Era had started declining years ago, and now, he was leading a grassroots team. Wouldn't debating whether Zhou Zekai and Ye Xiu was the current number one be seen as a joke?

Ten years of glory, the former number one player, had now unexpectedly become a challenger. And some even thought that he wasn't qualified.

But Ye Xiu's performance and Happy's performance showed otherwise.

Ye Xiu was undefeated in the individual competition. After Happy started coming together in Round 9, their record had crushed Samsara's ever since. Ye Xiu had earned the qualifications to take back his title as number one.

As a result, the media started working hard to utilize this as a topic. In Round 1, everyone had been questioning Ye Xiu's qualifications!

Unfortunately, neither Ye Xiu nor Zhou Zekai came across each other in the individual rounds. Finally, not long after the team competition began, the two had already started fighting.

Lord Grim rushed forward, while Cloud Piercer retreated backwards. Everyone seemed to have stopped breathing. Thenn, a formless qi suddenly struck Cloud Piercer from behind.　

FUCK!!!　

Countless curses exploded.　

We want to see a fight for number one, could a dirty bastard like you not fucking interrupt it???

Chapter 1305: A Long-Awaited Scene

Using a Qi Blade, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea interrupted the contention for number one between the two generations without any hesitation. The countless players and reporters, who were interested in it, immediately started cursing.

Qi Blade wasn't easy to notice even when facing it head on. As a sneak attack, even the number one player wasn't able to notice it. However, this was a team competition. Zhou Zekai hadn't noticed it, but others had.

The instant Jiang Botao gave the warning in the team chat, Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer dodged. One person's warning and another person's movements coordinated beautifully.

But with this opening, how could Lord Grim not seize it to close in onto Cloud Piercer? People realized that Ye Xiu and Fang Rui were also coordinating with each other, and it had probably been planned beforehand. While everyone was overjoyed at seeing a fight between Ye Xiu and Zhou Zekai, Ye Xiu and Fang Rui conspired together and formed a pincer attack on Zhou Zekai.

The contention for number one and a qualified challenger were truly exciting topics, but did the players on stage care?

Just when these two formed a pincer attack onto Cloud Piercer, Samsara's Jiang Botao hurried over. The 1v1 that everyone had been hoping for didn't happen. The two had only just seen each other before everything turned into a mess. Lord Grim was currently interrupting Jiang Botao's Empty Waves from casting a formation, while Cloud Piercer was blocking the dirty sneak attack from Fang Rui's Boundless Sea.

The fight between the two sides had started all-around, but Happy's more prepared utilization of the terrain gave them a certain advantage. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain was a troublesome existence for Samsara, and the only one who could keep her in check was Cloud Piercer, who Fang Rui and Ye Xiu had intercepted. Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash rushed over to provide support, and An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands stood beside him with his cross raised. The silver Holy Contract radiated with holy light as he chanted. This seemed to be his first time supporting his team in a direct conflict. An Wenyi was a bit excited. Could he finally participate in a team battle outright in the open? Before this, the situation always needed to be set up in a certain way before he could do anything, and Ye Xiu didn't hold back in telling him the reason.

An Wenyi was Happy's weakness. His technical skill was poor. Everyone in the Glory scene knew that. Believing in one's own lies wasn't something a logical person like An Wenyi did. Ye Xiu also trusted in his personality and didn't feel the need to keep his skill level a secret. Cleanly pointing it out would help him grow faster.

Reality was as such. An Wenyi was always clear where his shortcomings were and always consciously worked on improving them. The only thing restricting him was probably his talent. His rate of improvement seemed to be very slow, and he couldn't help but worry about his future.

However, Team Happy's actions wiped away this worry.

An Wenyi was extremely confident right now. He was certain he would definitely become qualified to be the lifeline supporting the team. He wouldn't be like before and sometimes become the bait for the team's tactics.

Cast. Small Heal.

Even though Little Cold Hand's equipment didn't stack cast speed, Small Heal was a low-level skill, so the cast time was short anyways, and it was quickly cast.

Holy light flew out and converged onto Lord Grim.

Crit!

The high crit rate didn't let him down. After a switch of equipment, the very first skill Little Cold Hands used had crit.

The holy light surrounding Lord Grim looked to be brighter than usual. His health immediately went up a notch.　　

That feels so good!

For a healer, nothing was more satisfying than watching a health bar go up. The others felt a thrill watching their attacks deal damage, but Clerics felt a thrill watching their skills heal.

The bigger the heal, the more satisfying it felt. And this was just a Small Heal, and not a huge one.

An Wenyi calmly observed the battlefield, waiting for a chance to use a high-level skill. When he had been adjusting to his new character, that sort of leap almost made his heart jump out. In real combat, in a fight, a leap in health meant a nullification of all the hard work the opponent had put in. This was the type of attack only healers could do, a spiritual blow to the opponents.

Come!

The always logical An Wenyi couldn't hold back his excitement. He had been holding it back for too long. He had been waiting for this day, this moment for too long.

Which side?

An Wenyi looked left and right, searching for an area that needed his support.

One Autumn Leaf and Chaotic Cloudy Mountains climbed out of the ditch and entered the fray. Samsara's healer Fang Minghua and his Cleric Laughing Song looked to be in a position symmetrical to Little Cold Hands. He was also in position, waiting for a side that required his assistance.　　

This was a battle between healers! How exhilarating! An Wenyi saw Laughing Song across from him. The other side seemed to have noticed him too. The hot bloodedness in his mind couldn't help but surge forth again.

There!

An Wewnyi suddenly found an opportunity. However, that side didn't require any healing. If he placed a Sacred Fire there, would he be able to restrict One Autumn Leaf's mobility?

Ah! This side too!

Or maybe I should Hypnotize Empty Waves?

Would I be noticed though? Little Cold Hands had a slow casting speed. Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer could interrupt his cast with just a single bullet.

Maybe I should cast a Sacred Fire first! An Wenyi made up his mind, but...　　

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf suddenly swept outwards with his spear. After finding an opening, he took a step and attacked Little Cold Hands with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

The distance isn't enough!

The first thing An Wenyi noticed was that Dragon Breaks the Ranks wouldn't be enough for One Autumn Leaf to fully close in onto him. But this surprise attack had still drastically increased the threat towards him.

An Wenyi didn't panic.

Sacred Fire!　

He had originally planned on using this skill to decrease One Autumn Leaf's mobility, but One Autumn Leaf broke off from the fight first. The Sacred Fire was still sent towards him nonetheless.　　

Under the light of Holy Contract, the pale flames slid out from it. One Autumn Leaf had only been five units away, so the Sacred Fire was bound to be within his path. The spell had been timed to the extreme. But the instant the pale flames leapt up and it looked as if One Autumn Leaf would step on them, One Autumn Leaf leaped into the air.

Frightening reaction speed and extraordinary technical skill were all things An Wenyi lacked, but at this moment, Sun Xiang displayed these traits beautifully. It was just an instant, but Sun Xiang was able to react in time.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks was forcefully cancelled, but because he had jumped, the momentum carried him high into the air.　　

Shattering the Lands!

One Autumn Leaf's Evil Annihilation danced in the air. Under the gloomy backdrop, the flickering black light looked even crueler.

An Wenyi was still engrossed in what had just happened. How he envied Sun Xiang's reaction speed and technique! It was only an instant later, and One Autumn Leaf was coming down with a Shattering the Lands!

An Wenyi's reaction speed had always been his weakness. The attack itself was a large AoE move. Where could he dodge to?　　

He had nowhere to dodge, and he had no attack that could stop Shattering the Lands. Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash was close to Little Cold Hands, but he had no way of helping because this attack could not be blocked!

Boom!　

Magic waves rippled and shook the earth.

Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash promptly jumped out of harm's way, but Little Cold Hands wasn't even able to take three steps before the spreading shockwave landed.

No one could block the attack, but they could always rescue him after it.

An X-1 Extruder launched from Dancing Rain's cannon towards Little Cold Hands. Anyone in its vicinity would be pulled away.

This sort of protection was only temporary. Getting the healer to safety required constant defense. Starting from Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf breaking through, Samsara held the initiative because Happy needed to maintain a certain distance from their target of protection.

Ye Xiu and Fang Rui weren't able to continue fighting on the other side. They needed to shrink their defensive zone to protect their healer.　

Random Firing!

Zhou Zekai seized this timing to fire a burst of attacks. Bullets shot out from his dual guns and under his extraordinary control, nearly every bullet threatened Lord Grim and Boundless Sea.

This wave of attacks stopped the two from retreating, using a strong offense as a defense.　

Empty Waves began casting a wave formation!　　

"Interrupt!"

Ye Xiu called out in the chat. This wave formation could not be allowed to be summoned. Lord Grim raised his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and used its shield form to block Cloud Piercer's attacks. Fang Rui's Boundless Sea went into the cover provided by the umbrella and let out an attack towards Empty Waves.

Samsara's offensive had been repeatedly thwarted by Happy's players, but finally, Lu Boyuan found an opening to act.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountains flipped his palms...

Grapplers didn't have long-ranged attacks, and there was no one near him. However, the movements he made made An Wenyi's heart leap.

This was… the Qi Master skill, Cloud Grasping Fist!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountains was a Fighter class, so a skill of the same class could be added to his weapon. And in this match, he chose Cloud Grasping Fist. In order to target Happy's weak point, had this been an arrangement they had planned from the start?

An Wenyi wanted to dodge, but he immediately discovered that Sun Xiang had his eyes completely fixed on him.

With Dancing Rain's X-1 Extruder flying over, One Autumn Leaf wasn't able to press closer for now, but if Little Cold Hands moved, he would be outside of X-1 Extruder's protection, and One Autumn Leaf would instantly start attacking.

Samsara's teamwork put him in a helpless position. An Wenyi felt despair. However, the moment Chaotic Cloudy Mountains sneak attacked with Cloud Grasping Fist, a character stood in front of him.

Phantom Demon, One Inch Ash.

Chapter 1306: What Makes Him Special

Cloud Grasping Fist didn't have mountain-splitting power. When One Inch Ash came over to block it, the qi landed upon his body and instantly pulled him toward where Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was. This skill only pulled the target toward the user, it didn't restrict the target's movements. One Inch Ash, who had purposely taken the attack to help Little Cold Hands, was of course prepared for this. As he was pulled away, he also sent an attack.

Ghost Slash!

The blade light arrived in front of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain a second before the person did. But Lu Boyuan had seen that the opponent had taken the initiative to serve as a meat shield, so an attack like this was within his expectations. He dodged to the side with precise timing, already thrusting a hand toward One Inch Ash's shoulder.

Lu Boyuan had predicted Qiao Yifan's actions, but Qiao Yifan had actually also guessed that Lu Boyuan would respond. The problem was, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's hand had arrived in the last second before Cloud Grasping Fist wore off. Cloud Grasping Fist didn't restrict the character's skills, but movement was undoubtedly locked. Even though Qiao Yifan knew that Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's attack would arrive, he simply had no way of controlling One Inch Ash to dodge. Lu Boyuan's hand flashed out with incredible precision, and his positioning was beautiful. Helpless, Qiao Yifan tried to change the direction of his Ghost Slash, but he still couldn't catch up to Chaotic Cloudy Mountain's movement.

Qiao Yifan was already out of strategies, but fortunately, this wasn't an individual battle. A Laser Rifle was accurately fired toward Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, forcibly splitting the connection he had tried to establish with One Inch Ash. Even though it failed to cause any damage, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had already recovered from the movement-restricting effects of the Cloud Grasping Fist.

Moonlight Slash, Full Moonlight Slash!

Two slashing attacks one after another instantly leapt toward Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. The slashing attacks of a Phantom Demon didn't cause much damage, but Lu Boyuan of course wouldn't just let his character be chopped up. He quickly backed up two steps, avoiding these two attacks. One Inch Ash quickly withdrew, as he had no intention of getting tangled with him here.

Even though Happy hadn't taken too much damage for now, their formation had unquestionably been thrown into chaos by Samsara's continuous disruption. Over by Little Cold Hands, Dancing Rain's X-1 Extruder had already exploded, and One Autumn Leaf was rushing forward. Dancing Rain again tried to block him, but he didn't dodge or retreat. Over there, Fang Minghua's Cleric Laughing Song was already casting, clearing covering for One Autumn Leaf as he forcibly killed off Little Cold Hands.

Happy was now completely on the defensive, all starting from when Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf had broken through with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Once upon a time, Samsara's weakness was their lack of a close-range, brute-force attacker. But after obtaining Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf, they finally had a character who could charge through, forcibly carrying the whole team into the offensive.

Samsara's weakness had been fixed with a transfer, but what about Happy's weakness? Right now, he was suffering under One Autumn Leaf's furious attacks, helplessly waiting for rescue by his teammates.

"It really is hard to understand Happy's actions." Pan Lin and Li Yibo, in the television broadcast, were discussing this topic instead of the events going on in the match.

They'd originally thought that Happy had gone to all this effort to update Little Cold Hands' equipment because An Wenyi had some special talent that would allow him to control this character very well. But just looking at this ongoing match, they couldn't tell. All they saw was, as usual, the weakness of An Wenyi's slow reactions. And this weakness was directly causing trouble for Happy in this match.

"If he had used Sacred Fire a little faster to restrict One Autumn Leaf's movement space, then One Autumn Leaf's formation-breaking charge might not have been successful."

"If his reactions were a little faster, he should have been able to dodge that Shattering the Lands. He shouldn't have been hit and then directly exposed in front of One Autumn Leaf. Now the whole team has lost the initiative."

"Team Happy's team roster here relies on the Phantom Demon's support and control to strengthen the battle ability of the whole team. So, as soon as the battle begins, they need to let the Phantom Demon successfully cast his boundaries. And the Launcher is the core of long-distance attacks. In other words, Lord Grim and Boundless Sea are the only ones directly controlling the situation from the front. This arrangement requires the team's Cleric to give a certain amount of support. An Wenyi has failed to do this, and so Happy was quickly scattered by Samsara…"

The two continued to discuss and analyze the problems. And An Wenyi was the core of this heap of problems. The simple conclusion drawn was that if Happy changed their Cleric player, even if it couldn't be said how the battle would ultimately play out, at least Happy wouldn't be so quickly broken by Samsara in a battle where they had the map advantage.

Yes, broken.

By this time, Happy had already been broken for good.

The Ghost Boundaries hadn't been set. The healer had been stolen away and was being beaten up. Only under Dancing Rain's desperate supporting were Lord Grim and Boundless Sea able to struggle out of their situation and turn around to try and save the healer. But Samsara instantly turned fire, with Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf throwing away Little Cold Hands and attacking Lord Grim and Boundless Sea. Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer took over for him, continuing to rain damage upon Little Cold Hands.

Inside-Out Tactics.

One of the basic strategies in Glory. Close- and long-range attackers exchange positions, continuously outputting damage.

And now, Inside-Out Tactics were being used by Sun Xiang and Zhou Zekai, these two pinnacle attackers in the Alliance, with One Autumn Leaf and Cloud Piercer, these two pinnacle characters. One could only imagine how powerful it was. Because of the restriction caused by the inside-out exchange of these two players, Happy had no way of interrupting their offensive. Over the course of this season, Samsara had used this method to swiftly wipe out who knew how many crucial characters on the opponent side. Even if it didn't succeeded, this method greatly restrained the opponents, preventing their strategies from effectively playing out.

The situation Happy faced now was even more disastrous. Their healer was directly kicked out of the match by the opponent.

Happy lost, but no one expected that they could lose so quickly.

11 minutes and 58 seconds, that was how much time this team competition ultimately took. This was only a little over two-fifths of the average team competition duration of 25:47. Anyone could tell that this was a match where the healer was immediately killed off.

Samsara's fans were jumping and laughing. Who cared if they lost the individual rounds? The ultimate victory still belonged to them. Happy's fans, meanwhile, were quiet. When they'd seen Tang Rou's performance in the group arena, when they'd seen Little Cold Hands flashing new Silver equipment, they had held high hopes for this team competition. They truly felt that their team was about to defeat the champion team Samsara. But in the end, the team competition was such a swift and brutal defeat.

An Wenyi disappointed everyone. Although he had always been called Happy's weak point, thanks to the team's intentional protection with their strategies, he had never affected Happy's victory. But this time, it was exactly as Pan Lin and Li Yibo had analyzed. An Wenyi's weak point left a gaping vulnerability in the match, and it was this vulnerability that led to Happy's rapid loss to Samsara.

"Just switch the Cleric player!" The supporters in the stadium, the supporters in front of the television, even Pan Lin and Li Yibo in the live broadcast were giving this suggestion to Happy.

"Increasing the character's strength won't help! The character is dead, the player is alive! You have to start from the player!" At the end of this match broadcast, this was Li Yibo's exclamation.

In the post-match press conference, this issue became the focus. And An Wenyi, at the center of this whirlpool, hadn't been sent out by the team for this press conference. He sat in the prep room, silently staring at the television as Ye Xiu was swarmed by the media, the reporters firing question after question about An Wenyi.

An Wenyi took off his glasses and buried his face in his hands.

He'd really screwed up this time, he knew. The team had built this Cleric character just for him, a character specially catering to his playstyle, but his performance was still like this. It looked like he really wasn't suited to be a pro player. Everything he'd hoped for, dreamed of, they were no more than soap bubbles bursting in the air, right? Maybe this was the final chance the team would give him, and now they were probably going to find a new player. The transfer window still hadn't closed…

"Do you think An Wenyi is even at the professional level?" An Wenyi had taken off his glasses, but he couldn't stop the sound from reaching his ears, and he heard from the television a reporter asking such a direct question. Unlike many commentaries where they tried to tactfully express that An Wenyi's skill wasn't good enough, this reporter bluntly questioned whether he had a chance as a pro player…

An Wenyi wasn't the only one left in the prep room during the press conference. After hearing this brutally direct question, Qiao Yifan reflexively began searching for the remote to turn off the television. But then, they heard Ye Xiu's clear and certain answer:

"Of course. Without a doubt."

Qiao Yifan froze, and then slowly, the hand holding the remote slowly fell back to his side. He looked at An Wenyi, and saw that his teammate had lifted his head, a shocked expression on his face. But soon, he put his glasses back on and stared attentively at the television.

"Then how do you explain his performance today? There were several moments that I don't think were because of accidental mistakes or such reasons. They happened because he's not good enough, right?" a reporter asked.

"No." Ye Xiu shook his head with a smile. "That was because he's only had this new character for two days. He needs to adjust to the character, and at the same time, he needs to adjust to a few responsibilities that he hasn't taken on before."

"Responsibilities that he hasn't taken on before? What is that referring to?"

"Just like in today's battle, a Cleric standing directly at the front of the battlefield," Ye Xiu said.

"But he didn't do very well."

"This was his first time, and this was against Team Samsara. How well would you hope he'd do?" Ye Xiu asked.

"That is to say, Happy won't look for a new Cleric player, and will continue to believe in him?"

"Absolutely," Ye Xiu said.

"What's so special about him, that Happy has such faith in him?"

"Special? He is a member of Team Happy. That's what's special about him," Ye Xiu said.

A member of Team Happy…

An Wenyi stared blankly at the screen. When he once again doubted himself, when he once again lost confidence in the future, Ye Xiu appeared in front of everyone and clearly emphasized his identity.

He was a member of Team Happy.

Was all of the faith just from that? An Wenyi was extremely moved. But clearly, the reporters weren't touched by such an answer. To them, this was too idealistic, this was belief for the sake of belief.

"If An Wenyi repeats his performance today, will you still say that statement?" one reporter asked.

"I think that he won't give me that difficulty," Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1307: The Buddhist Monk from a Foreign Land

Ye Xiu's declaration at the press conference didn't dispel many people's doubts. Stubbornly insisting on using someone, who was universally regarded as having subpar skill, received all sorts of criticism. The forums, in particular, had lots of nonsense like An Wenyi was Chen Guo's sugar daddy, and he could not be kicked because of the boss's authority. Numerous people actually accepted this conjecture, quite a few were even Happy's fans.

Fortunately, the reporters weren't so unreasonable and only criticized Happy's obstinacy.

"Happy's future this season is looking quite good, but perhaps it will end because of their stubbornness!"

A few media stations reported in this way because the transfer window had closed after this round and Happy truly had no intentions of recruiting a better healer. An Wenyi was the only person they could rely on now. Healers were different from other classes. There were usually no substitutes for them. Cries of mourning could be heard all around Happy. Even many of Happy's supporters complained about their team's stubbornness. Rumors without boundary started to spread further and further.

The only voice that could thoroughly dispel these doubts was a strong performance, but...

"Don't be anxious. This isn't something that can be resolved in a match or two." Early in the morning, Ye Xiu got up and found An Wenyi practicing since who knew when.

"The entire team needs time to get used to this new way of playing. It wasn't just you that made mistakes against Samsara. The team didn't protect you well enough either," Ye Xiu said.

"You're not consoling me, are you?" An Wenyi asked.　　

"I always say it how it is," Ye Xiu said.

"I believe you," An Wenyi nodded his head. Ye Xiu was truthful to the extent that he could infuriate others.

"Continue to work on your reaction speed. It'll always be helpful. And then practice and play together with the team to work on our synergy," Ye Xiu said.

"Maybe we can go back to how we played in the past…" An Wenyi said these words, thinking with the team in mind. He was a bit scared of holding back the team from winning just so that he could become a qualified Cleric.

"That style of play isn't sustainable. Even that slow Li Yibo is starting to smell out the traps inside. Do you believe that the likes of Yu Wenzhou, Zhang Xinjie, Wang Jiexi wouldn't be able to? We need to think about the long term. Starting from now on, we need to think about playoffs," Ye Xiu said.

"Playoffs?"

"I don't think we'll decline so far as to fall out of top eight," Ye Xiu said.　

After Round 20, the fluctuations on the rankings were miniscule. Only four teams had changes. 　　

Royal Style beat Radiant 7-3, and Miracle lost to Tyranny 1-9. As a result, two of these teams switched places on the rankings. At the moment, Royal Style was in 12th, while Miracle was in 13th.

Apart from that, there was Team 301 and Team Void. These two teams confronted each other directly. In the end, Team 301 won 9-1 versus Team Void. And in this match, the player Bai Shu, who Team 301 had dug out from who knows where during the transfer window, triggered quite a discussion.

The unknown newcomer displayed extremely high technical skill, and what was even more astonishing was that he seemed to have plenty of competitive experience.

A nobody having exceptional technique could perhaps be explained by bitter closed door training, but rich competitive experience wasn't something that could be obtained in seclusion. The Glory online game couldn't bring about this sort of high-level experience either.

Where did this Bai Shu come from?

Finally, Team 301 gave the answer to this mystery by revealing his identity. This guy was also a pro player, but he wasn't a domestic player. He was a Chinese pro player from England's Glory Super League.

This was… foreign help?

The pro circle was astonished. It obviously wasn't only China that had a Glory competitive scene. Glory was a popular global game, and many countries had formed their own leagues. It was just that up until now, each country had their own competitive formats. The scene was still young too, so there hadn't been any across-border interactions yet. At most, it would just be a few videos of other pro matches appearing on the Internet. The international scene had unfamiliar players, equipment descriptions that they couldn't understand, and it didn't offer anything that they couldn't see in their own country, so it naturally didn't have much of an impact.

But this time, Team 301 officially broke the communication barrier and recruited a pro player from outside of the country.

Bai Shu quickly received numerous interview invites from several media outlets. In the end, the one who came out on top was Esports Home, the country's highest authority in esports.

Bai Shu's unknown history was finally revealed through the interview. There was nothing crazy about him. He had been a student studying abroad and liked to play Glory during his free time. He was quite talented, so his skill level quickly improved. After making a name for himself in the Glory community, he attracted the attention of pro teams and was recruited. He already had nearly four years of competitive experience. Team 301 expanded their search for talents to outside of the country and brought Bai Shu back to China.

The Glory news reporters weren't as clueless towards the international scene like many normal players. England's Glory Super League had the highest level of competition in the European region, and Bai Shu had been a core member of one of the top teams there. His skill wouldn't lose to top player in China. From the results of the Round 20 match, many people believed that Bai Shu was at an All-Star level.　

These were just words, though. He needed to prove it with action.

How bad was Happy's An Wenyi? How good was 301's Bai Shu? For a moment, these two topics became the most popular topics in the Glory competitive scene, and a match that would put them to the test had finally arrived.

Round 21. Happy had an away game against Hundred Blossoms, while 301 had a home game against Tyranny. This time, there wasn't too much debate from the broadcast for which match to show. Team 301 versus Team Tyranny was picked. Everyone was very curious about this international player.

Bai Shu's performance didn't disappoint. In their match against Tyranny, Team 301 won 8-2. Bai Shu's performance in the team competition was even more praiseworthy. In this match, Team 301's captain Yang Cong once again used Life-Risking Strike to OHKO the opposing side's healer. Tyranny's healer was on a completely different level than Happy's An Wenyi though.

An Wenyi was considered the Alliance's worst healer, while Zhang Xinjie was considered Glory's best healer. Zhang Xinjie had the experienced generals Han Wenqing, Zhang Jiale, and Lin Jingyan surrounding him, yet under Bai Shu's brilliant cover, Yang Cong was able to land a fatal blow.

The monk from the foreign lands had quite the skill! On the other hand, the domestic healer looked quite shameful. Happy ended up losing to Hundred Blossoms 4-6.

In the individual competition, Ye Xiu once again stood undefeated. Happy also won the group arena. However, in the team competition, their healer once again failed them, which led to their defeat.

The dissatisfaction of the fans rose even higher. But apart from complaining about it, there was nothing else they could do. The transfer window had passed, so no matter how terrible An Wenyi may be, Happy could only keep using him, unless they decided not to use a healer in the team.

The gloomy Happy fans didn't lack passion, giving all sorts of advice to Happy, but no matter how it was spun, it always came back to asking Happy to switch healers. Enlightened by Team 301, their search started expanding outside of the Alliance. An unknown but enthusiastic fan had gathered numerous matches showcasing healers from the international scene and then sent all of them to Happy's public mailbox for Happy to survey.

Chen Guo was helpless. She could only give another official team announcement expressing the team's faith in An Wenyi. She also hoped the fans could understand and be patient for a better future.

When the announcement came out, it persuaded a few, but there would always be stubborn fans. Happy's statement once again gave rise to all sorts of rumors. Possibilities such as An Wenyi being the boss's sugar daddy was no longer enough to satisfy them.

Including Happy's loss to Team 301 in Round 19, this was their third consecutive loss. However, just like last time, the rankings barely changed at all. No one really cared whether Conquering Clouds and Radiant, the 17th and 18th place teams, moved up or down. The other change was Void, who lost to Thunderclap 3-7, being overtaken by Misty Rain, who won 7-3 against Royal Style. However, these two teams were 20 points away from the playoffs zone. Apart from them, Team 301 was closing in onto the playoffs zone. After beating Happy in Round 19, Bai Shu joined their team. Ever since that round, Happy had lost three in a row, while 301 had won three in a row. The distance between 301 and the eighth place Wind Howl had shrunk to 13 points.

Team 301 looked to be making a strong comeback in the second half of the season. Their captain Yang Cong stepping back and their new player becoming a part of the main roster had changed Team 301's tactical style. Yang Cong seemed addicted to Life-Risking Strike at the moment. Team 301 might just make it their main playstyle. As for Bai Shu, everyone was still very curious about how much more potential he had left to show.

As for Happy's current predicament, besides their loyal fans, no one else truly worried for them. On the other hand, people like Ruan Cheng had found a gold mine. Their disgust towards Tang Rou had spread to the entirety of Team Happy. They couldn't find anything to criticize Tang Rou for at the moment, so they just brought her team into the mess.

In the new issue of the Esports Time, Ruan Cheng attacked Happy ferociously. However, his timing was poor. In Round 22, Happy would be facing Radiant. For the current Happy, a small mishap like this wasn't enough to a team like Radiant to upset them. After three consecutive losses, Happy made a resounding comeback with a 10-0, a loud slap in the face to people like Ruan Cheng.

Ruan Cheng wanted to cry but no tears came out. What could he do? Esports Time was released biweekly, so they couldn't publish immediate reports. When his article came out, Round 22 had ended. Ruan Cheng's criticism towards Happy received all sorts of condemnation from the community due to Happy's 10-0 victory.

Are you blind?

Countless Happy fans cursed angrily at Esports Time, at Ruan Cheng.

Chapter 1308: Tyranny’s Home Stadium

After Round 22, there were only only small changes on the points ranking. Clearly, after half a season of accumulation, the various teams all had a solid point foundation, and it would be very difficult for the points of one round to cause any big shifts on the rankings.

In the three rounds after the new year, the most-eye catching team was undoubtedly 301..

None of 301's opponents these three rounds - Void, Tyranny, and Hundred Blossoms - were weak. But 301 had still managed to win beautifully with a 9-1 and two 8-2 victories. Bai Shu didn't disappoint all those curious about him and had a strong performance in all three matches. 301's Captain Yang Cong had already completed his style change in these few rounds. He was no longer that directly-attacking warrior Assassin. Cold, ruthless, deadly, this was the impression that today's number one Assassin in the Alliance gave everyone, and he did a better job than many other Assassins who had always used this style. This sort of clean and neat style change led people to feel that this was a player who had always been somewhat underestimated.

Even though 301 hadn't risen on the leaderboard after these consecutive victories against strong opponents, they were steadily closing the gap between themselves and the top 8. After this round, their opponent Hundred Blossoms had fallen to eighth place with 131 points, only eight points ahead of 301.

The other team that was worth paying attention to was Team Wind Howl. Wind Howl, named the soft-footed shrimp*, had really been beaten bloody by the strong teams during the first half of the season. 10-0'd by Happy, 9-1'd by Tiny Herb, that was the tragic ending they faced in the last two rounds of the first half. During the winter transfer window, they'd tried to invite Tyranny's Zhang Xinjie with much fanfare, but ultimately they'd failed to make the deal, and they'd left behind a strong impression that they desperately needed to adjust the team. If they wanted to make any acquisition after that, all of the teams were lions with jaws gaping wide. Any player could have an asking price over ten million for them.

Wind Howl was quite desperate, but they weren't going to be taken for a ride like this! Zhang Xinjie was a player that could truly take care of all their problems, a God, a popular player, they were willing to pay a sky-high price. But now any random player cost over ten million, this was simply robbing a burning house. To Wind Howl, these players were just spare tires. There was no way they'd make such a large investment.

They were unwilling to be cheated, but they also couldn't discuss any suitable transfers. In the end, the transfer window closed without Wind Howl being able to complete any discussions. They could only pretend they had everything together, sending out an announcement expressing the team's belief in the current roster, belief that their current strength was enough to win everything, and so on.

Quite a few people who liked drama all anticipated seeing Wind Howl's continued fall! But at this moment, the match schedule helped out Wind Howl. In the opening of the second half of the season, none of Wind Howl's opponents were strong teams. Conquering Clouds, Radiant, Lightly, in front of teams like this, the soft-footed shrimp could still bare its fangs and wave its claws, eating them one by one. After Hundred Blossoms lost to 301, Wind Howl reached seventh place.

And coming up next? In Round 23, Wind Howl's opponent was Bright Green, a team that with Seaside was already locked in the relegation zone. It looked like Wind Howl, for now, wouldn't be falling.

Those paying attention to Wind Howl were only interested in seeing results. The fans who truly enjoyed watching high skill and technique displayed during a match had quite a few high-level confrontations they could choose in Round 23.

Tyranny vs Happy, Blue Rain vs Samsara, and 301, who had found its momentum in the second half of the season, would be playing their away game against the team whose team competition style had completely changed this season, Thunderclap.

After deliberating, the television broadcast team finally decided to give up on the match between the number two Blue Rain and the number one Samsara, simply because the difference between Samsara and Blue Rain was a whole 22 points. Even if Blue Rain earned a ferocious 10-0 victory over Samsara, they still had no way of shaking Samsara's huge lead. After thinking of this kind of result, this match felt a lot less interesting.

On the other hand, Tyranny and Happy were currently tied at 148 points, and their relative ranking was determined by the outcome of the previous match they'd played against each other. This time, whoever won would reach fourth place on the rankings.

The higher the rank at the season's end, the more prize money and dividends the team could earn. It also had a bit of an effect on the playoffs. In the playoffs system that had come into effect last season, the right of playing the home match in the third tie-breaking match between two teams was given to the team who had the higher ranking in the regular season. Even though this home match didn't include the right to choose the maps, the boost in morale from the home fans was useful.

For the broadcast of Round 23, they ultimately chose to show Happy's away game against Tyranny.

February 21.

City Q.

After the All-Star Weekend, Team Happy once again arrived at this city.

Tyranny's home stadium had actually sent a large bulk of security officers to welcome Team Happy. After half a season, Chen Guo had never seen such a welcome before!

"Is this necessary?" Chen Guo said.

"This is an official match, and the arriving person is Ye Xiu," the captain of the officers said in a very serious tone. But as he spoke, a coldness also seemed to flash in his eyes as he coolly glanced at Ye Xiu. His right hand seemed to subconscious drift toward the baton hanging at his hip.

"The hatred is that bad?" Even though Chen Guo was an Excellent Era fan in the past, she had never followed the team to Tyranny's home stadium, and didn't know the atmosphere here. As soon as she asked this question, she suddenly heard a loud shout from somewhere: "Ye Xiu, 1v1 me!"

And then a water bottle flew toward them, its cap very rudely opened, spilling water all over them.

"7 o'clock, 7 o'clock!!" This security officer's directions were like the directions given in a Glory match. Immediately, people charged toward the 7 o'clock direction, seizing the target. As for what happened afterward, Happy's members didn't know. The target was tightly surrounded by security and swiftly escorted inside the stadium, all the way into the prep room.

"How scary!" Chen Guo exclaimed with lingering fear. "What if that hadn't been water? What if it was acid or something?" Chen Guo examined where she'd been soaked by the water.

Ye Xiu was dumbfounded. "Isn't that a bit too cruel? How bad is this hatred?"

Right after he said that, there came a knock on the door of the prep room. It was a very precise and rhythmic knocking, quite eerie.

"Who is it!" Chen Guo was instantly on full alert.

"Zhang Xinjie," answered the person outside the door.

"Uh…" Chen Guo hadn't expected that it was actually a God and quickly opened the door.

"I heard that you all arrived, so I came to greet you." Zhang Xinjie greeted everyone in the room, and Chen Guo quickly let him in.

"Who's first from Tyranny in the individual round?" Ye Xiu asked.

This was a question that would very easily chill the atmosphere. But Zhang Xinjie still responded, "You'll see when the battle starts."

"Are you going in the group arena?" Ye Xiu asked another question.

"No…" Zhang Xinjie said.

"Do you know how to have a conversation?" Chen Guo finally couldn't restrain herself any longer.

"What is there to talk about?" Ye Xiu retorted.

Chen Guo was just about to answer, but Zhang Xinjie actually agreed with Ye Xiu's view. "Yes, I just came to greet you all. Play well, everyone. I'll take my leave now." After speaking, he just left.

"What?" Chen Guo was so confused. "There's nothing going on, he really came over purely to greet us? Was he trying to strengthen his sense of existence or something?"

"Then I'll go strengthen mine too!" Ye Xiu stood up.

"Do you need me to go too, Boss?" Steamed Bun jumped up.

"Up to you!" Ye Xiu didn't care either way.

"Let's go." Steamed Bun followed him.

"Me too, me too!" Fang Rui also joined the excitement.

"Boring." Wei Chen expressed his disdain toward these guys. The others were all more rule-following, and naturally didn't go along with this fun.

The three left the room. The prep rooms of two teams were generally either directly opposite or next door to each other, so it wasn't long before Chen Guo heard the hallway sounding with Ye Xiu's voice. "Open up, I'm here!"

With that tone, it sounded like this was his own home, and he couldn't be any more familiar.

The door to Tyranny's prep room opened. Without invitation, Ye Xiu just walked right in, followed by two others.

"The host team's prep room is always nicer!" Ye Xiu exclaimed. "What's the temperature here? Ours is a little cold." After saying this, he saw the control for the air conditioning on the wall and very skillfully controlled it a bit.

"Why are you here?" Standing to the side, Han Wenqing asked.

"Reciprocating the greeting!" Ye Xiu said.

"Old Lin." Fang Rui also greeted his old partner Lin Jingyan.

"The number one Brawler Lin Jingyan!" Steamed Bun shouted.

Lin Jingyan was instantly very happy. It'd been a long time since anyone had given him that title. This inexplicable guy from Happy was very good at chatting, it seemed!

"Happy's idiots are already here!" At this time, the door to the prep room was pushed open again, and a person charged in.

"Talking about people behind their back, where's your professionalism?" Ye Xiu turned around. The person who had just entered was Zhang Jiale.

"Oh, you're here." Zhang Jiale acted like he had nothing to do with it.

"You were the one who threw that water bottle just now, weren't you!" Ye Xiu said.

"What water bottle?" Zhang Jiale was confused.

"Don't pretend. I saw that throw style, it was completely like a grenade you'd throw," Ye Xiu said.

"What's all this nonsense?" Zhang Jiale said.

"I'll teach you a lesson during the match." As Ye Xiu spoke, he headed outside.

"Teach you a lesson!" As Steamed Bun left the room, he also gave Zhang Jiale an aggressive and intimidating shout.

"Those guys in Happy… they're really confusing!" Zhang Jiale watched as these two people left.

"Did you really throw that water bottle?" Even Tyranny's own members were asking him. Evidently, even though this thing had only happened just earlier, the news had already spread to Tyranny's players.

"I'm not that childish!" Zhang Jiale said. "But was it only water? How come they didn't put in a drink or paint or something? Let those guys from Happy go onstage all bright and colorful, hahaha."

"How bad is this hatred!" someone exclaimed.

"Gah!" Zhang Jiale jumped. "There's another one!"

"There was always another one…" Lin Jingyan was speechless. Fang Rui had come over to chat with him, so when Zhang Jiale had come in, he'd only seen Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun, and didn't notice that Happy still had another member waiting in ambush.

"If you come to Happy again, there might be drinks or paint or something waiting for you!" Fang Rui said to Zhang Jiale.

"How bad is this hatred!" Zhang Jiale said.

"Who said it wasn't?" Fang Rui laughed. "See you!" He said his goodbyes toward everyone and then left.

"Damn. Next time we go, we really have to be careful. Happy's dirty and shameless, they'd definitely do something like that," Zhang Jiale said, after Fang Rui left.

"Why's it so cold in here?" After saying this, Zhang Jiale felt the temperature in the room, and then saw the air conditioning control on the wall.

"18 degrees? Are you guys crazy!" Zhang Jiale shouted.

"It was probably Ye Xiu…" Everyone remembered how Ye Xiu had been fiddling with the control earlier.

"Just like I said! Those guys can do anything!" Zhang Jiale said.

T/N: 18 degrees Celsius, about 64 degrees Fahrenheit

*Soft-footed shrimp = coward/weakling

Chapter 1309: Who’s Under Pressure

In Round 23 of the regular season, where Team Happy faced Team Tyranny in their away game, the players from both teams had already started entering the stadium with holographic projections showing off each character's flair.

"Ye Xiu, your record ends here!!"

The moment Ye Xiu stepped foot into the stadium, the crowd started issuing battlecries. This was evidently something premeditated.

"Haha, what a nostalgic feeling!" Everyone else was shocked, but Ye Xiu simply laughed it off. Come to think of it, he hadn't encountered this kind of treatment for a long time. His reception at the All-Star Weekend was similar, but ultimately uncomparable to during Tyranny's actual home game. The All-Star Weekend was a grand occasion for all of Glory, and having it hosted in Tyranny's home stadium would only result in slightly more Tyranny fans. There would still be many other fans from other teams, or even neutral fans of Glory, so Ye Xiu's reception wouldn't be as grand as this one, where seemingly everyone in the stadium was targeting him.

While walking towards the player seats, Ye Xiu respectfully listened to the various jeers that the crowd were freely coming up with and shook his head, "It's been a few years already, how come these fellows from Tyranny can't come up with any fresh ideas?"

After Team Happy, Team Tyranny's players entered the stadium, which was naturally a completely different scene to behold. Team Tyranny's fans had an unstoppable passion, whether it was against their enemies or for their team.

The players from both teams met each other, and as everyone crossed the stage and shook hands, the crowd once again hollered, "Ye Xiu, your record ends here!" Ye Xiu, who was shaking hands with Zhang Jiale, laughed and said, "Listening to the hopes of the fans, your first player must be under a lot of pressure?"

Since the competition was about to begin, divulging who would be playing first was no big deal. The gazes of all the players from Team Tyranny fell onto Lin Jingyan.

"Oh, it's Old Lin, hehe," Ye Xiu said.

"..." Lin Jingyan was depressed. The reactions of the fans in the crowd were something that the players couldn't predict. Ye Xiu wasn't wrong, with such expectations from the fans, the pressure on him was considerably weighty. If he wanted to win against Ye Xiu, it really wouldn't be an easy feat!

"It's been hard on you, I'll just take this point first," Ye Xiu took the opportunity to say this as he was shaking Lin Jingyan's hand.

"You're too arrogant," Lin Jingyan said.

"Work hard!" Ye Xiu patted him, continuing to be as arrogant as ever.

"Old Lin, you can't lose!" Zhang Jiale got fired up.

Lin Jingyan innocently looked at him, "Why don't you go?"

"I already went the last time! Now it's your turn!" Zhang Jiale said without any hesitation.

"Naturally, I'll do my best," Lin Jingyan said. Since he had already been selected as the first player, there was no need to hide his true feelings. Ye Xiu was truly a troublesome opponent. His response seemed to lack passion and fervor, but the stability he had from his many years of experience was something that up-and-coming new players couldn't compare to.

In no time at all, the competition officially began and the players from both teams entered the field. Team Happy's first player was, as expected, Ye Xiu, and Team Tyranny's was Lin Jingyan. The crowd took it upon themselves to start the jeering again, but Ye Xiu had already been tempered by years of experience and was unfazed by it. On the contrary, it was Lin Jingyan who was under a great amount of pressure. To be honest, this was a scene that Ye Xiu had seen countless times, but Lin Jingyan had never experienced it himself. When he'd arrived at Team Tyranny, Ye Xiu had already changed to the unspecialized, and the first time they'd met, it had been at Happy's home stadium where the atmosphere was naturally very different. It was only now that they were playing at Tyranny's home stadium that Lin Jingyan began to understand exactly what kind of attitude Tyranny fans had towards Ye Xiu.

"How bad is this hatred?" This was a question that Lin Jingyan really wanted to ask.

Go onstage, log-in to the character, enter the map. The players already couldn't hear the the shouts from the crowd. Still, the fans of Tyranny continued to use all their effort to verbally assault Ye Xiu.

"Stop making so much noise." All of a sudden, Ye Xiu's message appeared in the public channel.

"It'll be over in a flash." Ye Xiu used these words to send his message to the crowd.

Could everyone possibly stop making noise after that? The noise from the crowd momentarily grew even louder, to the point where Lin Jingyan could faintly hear their cries from inside the player booth.

"This is unscientific!" Lin Jingyan was astounded. He'd spent so many years as a professional player, and except from at the very beginning, when the facilities were basic and crude, it was his first time being able to hear the crowd after entering the booth. How many decibels was the noise outside? Wasn't this Ye Xiu too good at adding fuel to the fire?

"Old Lin, hurry up and accept your death!" Ye Xiu began to provoke him in the public channel again.

Lin Jingyan ignored him. This kind of trash talk could no longer affect him. He wasn't some new generation player or a rising talent. At the time when Ye Xiu was unparalleled, he was already part of the Alliance. He had a better understanding of Ye Xiu's strength than other people. After all these years, they had encountered each other more than just a few times. Lin Jingyan didn't want to tally their battle record though because he knew that it would just make him unhappy.

He wasn't arrogant or overbearing; he had been called a God for many years, but he was never one of those at the peak. Neither rising nor falling, it made people feel as if he was a little muddleheaded. He had thought that his professional career would come to an end like this, slowly heading to its boring end, but then he was released from his team.

After accepting Team Tyranny's invitation, three players at the twilight of their professional careers had gathered in the most hot-blooded of all the Alliance's teams. Champions?

Lin Jingyan didn't think he would be in over his head so quickly, unexpectedly wanting to aim for this height again. In this team, with these players next to him, his once-dwindling passion was suddenly re-ignited.

They had fought vigorously for an entire season, but tragically fell short at the last step. Countless people felt great pity for them, and at that moment, Lin Jingyan had thoughts of retiring. But at his side was a player even older than him, who, right after losing the championship, had straightened his back at the press conference and said, "We'll be back next year."

Han Wenqing was even older than him, but he still hadn't given up!

Zhang Jiale had placed second four times, but he still hadn't given up!

And then there was that Ye Xiu, who had dug out an entire team from an Internet cafe before stubbornly triumphing over Excellent Era and imposingly slaughtering his way back into the Alliance.

All of them hadn't given up, how could he be the first to give up?

Lin Jingyan stayed on, holding on to the dream of becoming a champion and starting his efforts anew.

Dark Thunder walked out of the respawn point, strategically moving towards the middle of the map. Lin Jingyan didn't want to fight Ye Xiu head-on. It had already been more than half a season, but the unspecialized Lord Grim wasn't something that could be adapted to in half a season. This was simply because they didn't have the necessary conditions to practice for him. Aside from the actual competition, they could only rely on their theorycrafting, but without putting it into practice, their grasp over the unspecialized was still unsatisfactory.

So Lin Jingyan decided to use tactics, taking a roundabout route to advance. After walking halfway, he saw another message from Ye Xiu in the public channel, "Old Lin, could you hurry up, I've been waiting for half a day."

Lin Jingyan ignored him, continuing to move at his own pace. If talking more could help you win, Huang Shaotian would already have won six championship titles.

After going in a roundabout fashion for a while more, Lin Jingyan finally saw Lord Grim, who had been waiting for him in the center of the map. The guy was just standing there, gripping his umbrella in a self-satisfied way! Why didn't it seem like he was here to compete! For a moment, the old general, Lin Jingyan, had gotten infuriated. It had passed in a moment, but he still had to control himself from getting irritated.

After fighting against each other for so many years, could he still be unaware? Ye Xiu's arrogant self-confidence was something he did for show, if one were to think he was actually arrogant and fight him under these false impressions, they would truly have been duped. This guy was truly dirty! Lin Jingyan couldn't help but think of the blood and tears that he had shed in the past, before frantically dispelling these thoughts from his mind.

How could he think of such things now, it was too hurtful to his morale!

Lin Jingyan directed Dark Thunder to hide at one corner, carefully watching Lord Grim's actions. Upon closer observation, the guy looked like he was taking a stroll in a self-satisfied manner, but he was actually moving towards a few places where one could sneak attack from, blocking them completely without leaving any openings.

"Old Lin, you've arrived, right? How long have you been squatting for? You'll eat a yellow card, you know!" Ye Xiu started talking again.

"I've arrived, I'm observing you now!" Lin Jingyan replied.

"Really? Do you need me to make a few relaxed-looking poses for you?" Ye Xiu replied.

"Sure, you can start posing," Lin Jingyan said.

"Alright!" Ye Xiu replied, and Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella quickly transformed into its gun form.

Gatling Gun!

Lord Grim's body turned, sending the bullets flying out in a horizontal arc and causing the surrounding dirt to fly into the air. Unexpectedly, he completed a full 360 degree turn, and a bullet exploded just to Dark Thunder's side. Lin Jingyan's judgement in having his character stay completely still was truly incredible.

"How was it?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Nice gunplay," Lin Jingyan replied.

"Let me show you another trick," Ye Xiu said.

"Oh?"

Poof!

A cloud of purple smoke up as Lord Grim threw out a smoke bomb, concealing his entire body before disappearing without a trace.

"This isn't nice to look at," Lin Jingyan said, but he was already frantically adjusting his camera angle, afraid that Ye Xiu would use the smokescreen to have Lord Grim quietly creep over.

But according to reason, he shouldn't have been exposed yet, right?

Lin Jingyan had some hesitation in his heart, and in that moment, his judgements weren't as resolute as before.

This guy, what was he planning on doing?

Lin Jingyan didn't see Lord Grim quietly creeping over, and he didn't want to act blindly and expose Dark Thunder's location, so he continued to endure, waiting for the purple smoke to disperse.

"Look at this trick now." Suddenly, Ye Xiu sent another message into the public chat. At the same time, in the midst of the purple smoke, a blinding white light suddenly flashed.

"Fuck!" Lin Jingyan swore, but his screen was already filled with white.

Flash Bullet, a Spitfire skill. But by now, everyone knew that Lord Grim's perverse Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could add a different skill to each of its forms, and this time, Ye Xiu had evidently added Flash Bullet to the gun form of his weapon. Borrowing the smoke screen of the Ninja skill, Smoke Bomb, he had waited until the smoke had gradually thinned out before throwing a Flash Bullet. The light pierced through the smoke, finally dazzling Lin Jingyan.

"I can't move! He still doesn't know where I am, I'm not that easy to find," Lin Jingyan thought.

"Haha, you don't dare to move now, right? Why don't you guess whether or not I can find you?" At that moment, Ye Xiu sent another message in the public chat. After being dazzled by Flash Bullet, he couldn't see anything, but he could still talk without any impediments.

Chapter 1310: Backfire

Lin Jingyan wanted to cry.

This is exactly why they hadn't figured out Lord Grim's unspecialized class after half a season. Apart from possessing all the low level skills from all 24 classes, he could also equip different skills to his weapon. That meant that Lord Grim had the chance of knowing any skill that wasn't a classing or awakening skill, so long as Happy had enough skill scrolls.

Under such circumstances, how many different combos could Lord Grim execute? That wasn't something a human mind could calculate. Especially since they didn't know what skills would be set into the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, how would they know what to look out for?

Looking at his whited out screen, Lin Jingyan didn't know if he should act or if he should wait it out. In the end, he made a decision: he'd endure it!

　

Skills added to a weapon would be at most rank 1. The effects of Lord Grim's Flash Bullet wouldn't last long, and Lin Jingyan refused to believe that this guy could figure out his whereabouts in such a short time.

That's what Lin Jingyan thought, thus, Cold Thunder stayed there, unmoving and calm.

　

The audience, as well as Tyranny's players, were just about close to crying.

Lord Grim was already standing in front of Cold Thunder. If he moved the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella forward just by a bit, he would hit the other's forehead.

Old Lin, you've been tricked!

The spectators with their omniscient view actually all knew that Ye Xiu had probably caught sight of Dark Thunder when Lin Jingyan had first creeped into the center of the map.

The TV broadcast chose a shot of Lord Grim's view. There was a split-second where a figure flashed by in the corner of the screen.

Yes, just a shadow, just a split second. Pan Lin and Li Yibo had even had a very long and enthusiastic discussion as to if Ye Xiu had seen it or not. Back then, no one could be certain if Ye Xiu noticed or not and how far he could go in determining Dark Thunder's position from that.

It wasn't until a Flash Bullet blinded Dark Thunder and Lord Grim's form appeared from the dispersed purple smoke, accurately darting towards Lin Jingyan that everyone was certain that Ye Xiu had noticed that split-second incident and accurately determined Dark Thunder's position.

Then, Gatling Gun swept forth, Smoke Bomb, he really put on quite the act. It wasn't until the Flash Bullet was used that Ye Xiu managed to close in without Lin Jingyan's notice.

　

Victory had already been decided...

Lin Jingyan's sight came back while he was being attacked, and then received a head-on beat down from Lord Grim. There had yet to be anyone who could counter Ye Xiu's unspecialized blitz. Lin Jingyan tried and tried and tried, but still lost in the end.

The first individual competition ended and Ye Xiu left the stage with a victory to thunderous cursing. Things like how fake, how deceitful, how treacherous, what a showoff!

No matter what, that's how it was like for Ye Xiu at Tyranny. If he lost, there would be endless mockery, and if he won, it wasn't much better. No matter how he won, the Tyranny fans would still find it dirty, unhonorable, low end.

　

The passionate, open Tyranny fans would all become mean and petty when Ye Xiu was concerned, nit picking at everything and not seeing anything good in him.

　

However, Ye Xiu was completely unmoved, calmly returning to his seat.

"Tyranny's home game atmosphere doesn't seem to be affecting Ye Xiu at all!" Commentator Pan Lin exclaimed.

　

Li Yibo, sitting to the side, gave a strained smile. He was from Tyranny and though it had been a long time, he had personally seen this scene before, shaking his head and saying, "It's not affecting Ye Xiu, but instead it's affecting Lin Jingyan's performance. The atmosphere Tyranny's fans created has backfired."

"Ah?" Pan Lin was stunned.

"This atmosphere is something Lin Jingyan has yet to experience, having been on the team for half a year. When the match started, everyone was yelling about ending Ye Xiu's consecutive wins. It's easy to yell, but what about for Lin Jingyan, who is actually going up against Ye Xiu? In the end, this is only giving him more pressure," Li Yibo explained.

"Oh… so that was why he had accidentally revealed his shadow while moving to the center of the map, giving his position away to Ye Xiu," Pan Lin said.

"Yeah…" Li Yibo sighed again.

Pan Lin didn't continue the conversation. This saying wasn't illogical, but how could you be certain that Lin Jingyan's mistake was because of this pressure? Pan Lin felt a little incredulous, so he couldn't really bring himself to agree so fervently. By then, the second players on each team were heading towards the stage..

Happy, Mo Fan, Deception.

Tyranny, Song Qiying, Sunset River.

"Hey, the second round is a clash between two newcomers," Pan Lin exclaimed.

"Indeed!" Li Yibo confirmed, looking interested. There were quite a few talented rookies this season. Tyranny's Song Qiying was definitely one of them. As for Happy, they had a particularly large number of rookies. Tang Rou, Bao Rongxing, and this Mo Fan, then there was their Cleric An Wenyi. However, if you wanted to say whether or not they were talented, that was a bit of a problem over here.

　

People originally had high expectations for Tang Rou, but then there were some conflicts with her character and her popularity plummeted. Though this had some effect, Tang Rou's performance in the field continued to be outstanding. The Alliance was very conflicted. The selection for the Best Rookie award wasn't like the All-Stars voting; popularity wasn't considered. From pure performance, Tang Rou was the most outstanding rookie this season.

In addition, her position in the team was something no other rookie could hope for. She was the last line of defense for the arena, and no other rookie was taking such an important position in their team. She also performed extremely well in her position, scoring consecutive victories. Her performance in the team competition was rather amazing as well. In typical circumstances, Tang Rou would be a steady first in bot popularity and skill. Even if her popularity was low, Tang Rou's performance would be enough to convince people.

But the problem was that Tang Rou's popularity wasn't just a little low, it was practically in the negatives. Award Tang Rou with Best Rookie under these circumstances? The Alliance really felt that they didn't have enough support to do that. They had never experienced such a situation. They were burning brain cells trying to figure out what to do. They just hoped that an even more outstanding rookie would appear.

But, there were none.

In this era, even if rookies had talent, they needed their teams to give them a chance to shine. Many mature teams had talented rookies, but they weren't as reliable as veterans due to their lack of experience. Each team had their own way of cultivating young talents. Some did throw their rookies into the thick of things directly, like Lu Hanwen who became a core member of the team at 14 and successfully took the title of Best Rookie. On one hand, he truly had talent, and on the other hand, he had enough chances to show his talent. Diamonds will shine, but this will wasn't the same for everyone.

This season's Tang Rou was like last season's Lu Hanwen; she had plenty of chances to shine, and she made good use of them, become a unique talent amongst the rookies.

The Alliance hoped for some new rookies. They didn't have to be better than Tang Rou, just being on par with her was good enough, and it would solve all their problems. Now there was still half a season. After the first half of the season, would there be any teams that felt their rookies were settling in well and could take on more responsibilities.

Li Yibo knew of the Alliance's attitude, so when he saw a match between rookies, his interest was peaked. Would there be any rookies that'd make a good final run and get to Tang Rou's level?

"Heh, this pair of rookies is pretty interesting!" Li Yibo opened up a discussion with this topic. "This Mo Fan used to be a notorious scrap-picker in game before getting pulled into the team by Ye Xiu and attending the Challenger's League with Happy. He's a rare self-taught talent these days. As for Tyranny's Song Qiying, he's a talented product of Tyranny's training camp. He grew under professional training, coming from a very orthodox background. What's interesting is that this Striker player did not inherit the style of Tyranny's Han Wenqing, but instead, from what we've observed, took after the Tyranny vice-captain Zhang Xinjie. His style is very meticulous."

"That's true indeed. This match will truly be interesting!" Pan Lin commented.

"Let's see which rookie will perform better!" Li Yibo exclaimed.

The silent Mo Fan and serious-as-Zhang Xinjie Song Qiying were both the kind of player that didn't make conversation. After the match started, there were no communications in the chat. The two met and opened combat directly.

A wild, self-taught style and a meticulous, academic style clashed. In this battle, Song Qiying attempted to break through Mo Fan's barrage in a frontal confrontation. However, Mo Fan's peak performance was enough to suppress Sun Xiang. Song Qiying was really struggling to deal with it. Every time he felt that an opening was imminent, Mo Fan would always swiftly pull a full retreat.

Song Qiying really didn't like this sort of pace. This was way too abrupt; who even fought like this?

However, this was the exact kind of opponent he had trouble dealing with, and fell to a disadvantage in the match.

　

"What do you think?" At Tyranny's bench, Han Wenqing posed this question to the others as they watched the match.

"It seems like that Mo Fan can only use five to six skills at a time well. He'll always break off his offense after these few skills and won't follow up with a new offensive afterwards, but instead clearly slows his pace down. It really does look like Cooldown Play," Zhang Xinjie analyzed.

　

"However, his execution of those few skills of his is truly very high," Zhang Jiale commented.

"Compared to before, he's improved immensely and his style has become more varied. However, he really has yet to solve the problem of continuity in his offense," Lin Jingyan added.

"If he can really solve that problem, then he'll become even more scary!" Zhang Jiale exclaimed.

　

"Yes," Lin Jingyan agreed.

　

"However, the current skill combos seem very complete and mature already. They don't hold much to continuity," Zhang Xinjie brought the topic down for deeper analysis.

"Could it be that he plans on persisting in his use of this style?" Zhang Jiale wondered aloud.

"He can clearly do better, so why doesn't he try?" Lin Jingyan voiced his confusion.

"What if he can't try?" Han Wenqing suddenly cut in.

Chapter 1311: Improvement

"If he can't try?"

Han Wenqing's words stunned everyone.

"Then… he can only endure and perfect this style," Zhang Xinjie completed Han Wenqing's analysis.

Thus, everyone fell silent. As for why he can't try, that was a problem gossips would definitely be interested in. However, as Happy's opponent, it wasn't necessarily important. They only valued the consequence: what kind of player would Mo Fan grow into?

"When we go back, we should take another look at this player's battles!" Zhang Xinjie decided.

As for the match, it was Mo Fan who claimed the final victory. Just as the match finished, Song Qiying charged out of the booth and rapidly approached Happy's player booth.

"Is this little guy so persistent post-match? That's even worse than Zhang Xinjie!" Fang Rui commented.

　

"You think Mo Fan will pay him any attention?" Wei Chen asked.

"Uh… that'll depend on if Mo Fan can understand his intentions or not. If he does, then I don't think he'll refuse?" Fang Rui guessed.

Just as he said this, Mo Fan also came out from the Happy player booth. He didn't even look at the other side, walking directly towards the steps that led off the stage.

"Hey!" Seeing this, Song Qiying called out, breaking into a run and eventually catching up with Mo Fan.

Mo Fan looked at him strangely, confused.

Song Qiying didn't have the sturdiest of constitutions. After sprinting for a few steps, he was left panting for breath.

　　

"I… How can you play like that?" Song Qiying said.

　

Mo Fan frowned, clearly not understanding what Song Qiying was trying to express. Thus, he ignored the other and turned to leave.

　

Song Qiying didn't block his way, panting as he hurried over to Mo Fan's side. "What on earth was that tempo of yours? Why don't you continue with your offensive? With your skill level, isn't that better?" Song Qiying said.

　　

This time, Mo fan understood him. He didn't stop walking, turning his head to look at Song Qiying, saying, "I can't.'

"Why can't you?" Song Qiying persisted.

Why couldn't he?

This question had Mo Fan deep in contemplation, but he wasn't able to formulate a response to that. In the end, he gave Song Qiying an infuriating answer: "Because I can't."

"What do you mean, because you can't? Hey hey, everything has to happen for a reason, no? Is it because you have to use such a tempo? What is forcing you to maintain it?" Song Qiying continued to pursue the question.

Mo Fan's frown deepened, but he didn't know how to answer. He wanted to get rid of this annoying person as soon as possible, and his footsteps subconsciously quickened.

"How come you're not speaking anymore? Oh, is it a team secret? Uh, we're opponents, so I really shouldn't ask so much, but I think there's a lot of improvements and adjustments that are worth making to your style!" Song Qiying exclaimed.

By then, they had arrived at Happy's player bench. Mo Fan quickly walked to his own seat. Song Qiying had followed him here, but, helpless, he knew that he couldn't go and sit at Happy's bench. Plus, his last words had been heard by everyone in Happy, all of them looking back at him with no idea what to do. They had been joking that Song Qiying was chasing after Mo Fan for the chance to touch his hand, that he was even more strict and formal than Zhang Xinjie! They hadn't expected that he had been clinging to Mo Fan, trying to talk about something like this.

"Kid," Ye Xiu spoke up, "You're right in saying that his style needs improvement. However, you're the same, hm? You have much to improve, too."

　

"I'll do my best, but he…" Song Qiying didn't seem like he was willing to give up.

"He'll also do his best. I look forward to your next match against one another," Ye Xiu smiled.

　

"Thank you, senior, for your guidance." Then, Song Qiying actually bowed to Ye Xiu.

"Ah, there's no need for that…" Ye Xiu hurriedly went to stop him, but there was no way he would make it on time. The entire venue exploded at once, whistling, jeering.

"Look… That's why I didn't want you to do that!" Ye Xiu said helplessly. No matter what reason Song Qiying had for bowing to Ye Xiu, the Tyranny fans would immediately be pissed off!

"It was deserved." Song Qiying refused to be swayed. The reactions of the audience didn't make him regret his actions at all. Once he had said that, he returned to Tyranny's player bench. It was, instead, the veterans of Tyranny who were nervous.

"What happened? What did Ye Xiu say to you?" Zhang Xinjie asked.

"Don't take anything that guy says to heart; it's all trash talk, got it?" Zhang Jiale said in absolute seriousness.

"He only said that I had much to improve on," Song Qiying explained.

"Huh? How come it sounds so… nice?" Zhang Jiale was confused and glanced over at Happy. He saw Ye Xiu looking over, too, and smile, waving, when he saw Zhang Jiale look around.

Zhang Jiale decisively turned his head away, face dark as he said, "Try to not interact with him, alright? Look at how sly and evil his smile is."

Song Qiying looked back, puzzled. How come he couldn't see anything that resembled slyness or evil?

"Alright, go and rest. Don't worry too much about the result of the loss, " Zhang Xinjie said to Song Qiying.

Song Qiying nodded, returning to his seat, yet his mind was still on the loss just now. How come he absolutely had to use such a tempo? That was the question that had caught his curiosity.

By then, the third player on both sides had gone up already. For Happy, it was as always, Su Mucheng and her Dancing Rain, while Tyranny sent Zhang Jiale and his Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

"It's time for us to get a point!" The two Gunners attacked as Zhang Jiale made his proclamation. In the end, Zhang Jiale achieved his goal of gaining a point, defeating Su Mucheng and gaining a point in the individual competition for Tyranny.

Afterwards, Happy sent out Fang Rui, Steamed Bun and Tang Rou for the group arena. As for Tyranny, it was Qin Muyun, Bai Yanfei and Han Wenqing. The two sides exchanged blows, fighting all the way until the fifth round where Tyranny, eventually, claimed victory.

"The instability of this Bao Rongxing is truly quite the headache! When he's in his element, he can accomplish miracles, but when he's not, it's like he's sleepwalking." The determinant of the group arena was clear as day: Steamed Bun. His performance wasn't so good this time, and he was defeated easily by Bai Yanfei. Tang Rou was unable to turn the tides against one and some players and Tyranny gained another two points.

The one on one portion of the match came to a close, and Tyranny was, for now, in the lead 3 to 2. The team competition was decide today's victor.

"You can take careful note of Zhang Xinjie's playstyle in the team competition. If I recall correctly, he's your idol, right?" Ye Xiu told An Wenyi while they prepared for the next match.

This young person, standing in the line of fire, was still holding Happy's health up match by match. In the previous round, Happy had beaten their opponents 10 to 0, but the team competition had been focused on a vicious, relentless offensive. As a healer, he was more on the defensive end, so An Wenyi had limited space to perform last round. But now, the time for battle had come once more. Tyranny… An Wenyi was once a fan of this team. But after joining Happy, he had slowly begun to see Happy as home, while his feeling for Tyranny cooled. In the first half of the season, when they fought Tyranny, An Wenyi had felt a little weird, but this time he was very calm.

Zhang Xinjie? An Wenyi glanced over at Tyranny's player bench. Zhang Xinjie sat there, posture straight, as he rested his mind with closed eyes.

"I've seen plenty of his matches," An Wenyi replied. There was no way he wouldn't have thought of looking to a God for ways to improve. An Wenyi was well acquainted with watching Zhang Xinjie's matches to learn from him.

"Watching recordings and learning through actual battle are very different. Remember to pay attention!" Ye Xiu said.

"I will." An Wenyi would've loved nothing more than to become the ultimate healer overnight, and he wouldn't miss any chance to improve. Being able to personally experience the skill of the number one Cleric Zhang Xinjie was a rare chance, something that only happened twice per season.

Soon enough, it was time to start the match.

For Happy, it was Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan and An Wenyi with Tang Rou as the sixth player, the same line up they had used against Samsara.

As for Tyranny, it was Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, Bai Yanfei, Qin Muyun and Zhang Xinjie, with Song Qiying as the sixth player.

"Tyranny is still persisting in their rotation. Zhang Jiale only participated in the individual match and isn't in the team competition lineup," Pan Lin noted after seeing Tyranny's lineup. In this season for Tyranny, even Han Wenqing was no longer a set feature of the core team. The three veterans, he, Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale, hadn't appeared in the team competition together for a long time.

　

Other teams rotated in order to counter their opponent. However, Tyranny's rotation seemed to just be for rotation itself. They had persisted like this for half a season. At first, their performance was subpar, and people had been uncertain about them. However, their performance slowly stabilized, and the doubtful voices petered out. Even so, Tyranny's performance this season was nothing compared to last season. As for this rotation, it was less like strategy and more like reducing strain on their older players so that they could keep up. After realizing this, all that was left were sighs and mourning.

　

The team competition ended in Tyranny's victory.

Though Zhang Jiale hadn't been fielded, their team was experienced and cunning enough. The flaws of Happy's An Wenyi were magnified whenever they met a strong team, especially since they were against Tyranny and their number one Cleric. In the data for the two Cleric's performances, An Wenyi had lost humiliatingly.

"Ay…" An Wenyi sighed. He was rather numb to defeat now, and going against Zhang Xinjie directly this match, the other's performance had An Wenyi's self-doubt multiplying.

When the two teams shook hands post-match, An Wenyi's head was bowed low. Now, every defeat of Happy's had his hand in it. He was probably that "useless teammate"* in the eyes of his opponents. He didn't want to face that sort of judgement.

"You have a very good grasp of timing." It wasn't until he heard someone say this to him when they shook hands that he lifted his head.

"I finally understand why Happy insists on keeping you," Zhang Xinjie, the number one Cleric that he had idolized for so long, was saying to him in person.

Chapter 1312: Another Target to Research

An Wenyi was stunned. Just as he wanted to reply, Zhang Xinjie was already leaving to shake hands with the next member of Happy.

It sounded like a casually spoken formality, but if it came from Zhang Xinjie, then it wasn't just a courtesy. This strict Tyranny vice captain would only say something like this if there was enough proof to back it up.

Happy hadn't been stingy in the support and trust they gave him. An Wenyi was incredibly moved by this and had worked hard to repay them. However, there was always that voice of doubt. That voice of doubt grew louder and louder with each defeat.

He was too rational, to the point where the care his team showed him couldn't penetrate the darkness in his heart.

However, Zhang Xinjie, the player he idolized, one known for his meticulousness, had said the words he had most needed to hear at a time he needed them most.

The darkness in his heart cleared as easily as that. This was, perhaps, so-called serendipity.

He could do it! Because if even Zhang Xinjie thought so, then there was no way it could be otherwise!

　

An Wenyi's mind was filled with these voices. He raised his head, facing each member of Tyranny with a smile, shaking their hands.

　

Happy had been defeated by Tyranny 2 to 8. This live broadcasted match didn't have many spectacular scenes to savor. The broadcasters regretted their decisions because the other Blue Rain versus Samsara match was unusually fierce, eventually ending in Blue Rain's victory of 7 to 3. After Samsara had lost to Hundred Blossoms, they had another loss added to their score. Additionally, the lead they had on the second ranked team had been reduced to under twenty points. Samsara's image of invincibility had finally loosened after their second loss.

　

However, though this match was spectacular, the most unexpected match was the Thunderclap's home game against 301 Degrees. The score ended in 1 to 9, Thunderclap being crushed. More importantly, their team, one that rivaled Samsara in strength, had been defeated once again.

The reason?

Yang Cong of 301 Degrees had used Life-Risking Strike again to take out Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher.

From Happy to Tyranny and now Thunderclap, this was the third time Yang Cong had struck with Life-Risking Strike, taking out a vital member of the opposing team and giving his team the victory.

Yang Cong, who originally didn't play such a style, had used it so crazily after switching styles. In five rounds, he had used Life-Risking Strike three times, and even more terrifyingly, he had succeeded all three times. This use rate and success rate was suffocatingly impressive.

Something else that should be taken note of was that apart from Round 19, where the assassination of Little Cold Hands had been all up to Yang Cong, in Round 20 against Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock and this round against Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher, Bai Shu had been critical in both situations.

　

What style did this guy have, and how was he so good at cooperating with 301 Degrees' players? No one in the Alliance had the answer, and each team had all looked towards England's Super League for reconnaissance on Bai Shu's ability. Everyone had sensed that 301 Degrees was on the rise. Don't just look at how they were only ninth on the current rankings, but 301 Degrees had recently all been pitted against strong teams, yet were still rising through the ranks. On the other hand, teams like Wind Howl were against mid-lower tier teams, and only then did they seem unstoppable. If they were to meet a strong team and fall, then they might be tossed out of the top eight with a pursuer like 301 Degrees behind them.

　

301 Degrees...

Suddenly, they had become an unknown enemy. All the teams were researching them, including Happy. However, at Happy's current strength, it was difficult to obtain information from England's Super League. There was pitifully little videos they could find from searching the web. In the end, after looking all over, using VPN and cracking their devices, they had finally managed to connect to a video hosting service over in England and found info on the team Bai Shu was once a part of: the England Super League team, Sprout.

　　

Then, watching this team's videos, they were rather shocked.

In that team, Bai Shu used a Knight called Bough. Apart from this Knight, there were two Assassins in this team. In the team competition, these two Assassins appeared together, and not in rotation. However, these team competitions were different from the Glory Pro Alliance. In the England Super League, team competitions were a 6v6.

The style Sprout employed was the one 301 Degrees was currently using: Assassin's Life-Risking Strike. Bai Shu's Bough had an important role in this team, covering for the two Assassins and ensuring that their Life-Risking Strike would hit. After watching the battle recordings, it was clear that Bai Shu wasn't only an expert at covering and supporting, but also doing all sorts of CC on the target when the Assassins were preparing to use Life-Risking Strike. In addition, he'd even help deal the finishing blow to a weakened opponent when the Life-Risking Strike wasn't enough.

His awareness, methods, habits, none of it was something that could be summarized easily and quickly. They had to spend a lot of time to research. The big teams all felt depressed! Wasn't there enough to research from scratch this season?

Ye Xiu's unspecialized Lord Grim, Fang Rui's dirty Qi Master, and now 301 Degrees was joining in, too, bringing in an expert that no one understood.

There was nothing that could be done. No matter how troublesome, they still had to do it. However, Team Happy's luck could be considered the best. The next time they'd meet 301 Degrees would be Round 38, the last match of the season. They had plenty of time to research Bai Shu and 301 Degrees, after Bai Shu's recruitment and Yang Cong's switch in playstyle.

　

For Happy, what was more of a headache, was the problem of their healer. After losing to Tyranny in the twenty-third round, the hate against An Wenyi continued. Even Chang Xian, who always supported Happy, was expressing concern.

　

"He has talent. We believe in him." These words were no longer enough. The people needed to see proof in their performance.

In Round 24, Happy's away game was against Team Parade.

With Happy's current performance, no one thought that a lower ranked team like Parade would be enough to test An Wenyi's skills. It'll probably be just like when they beat Radiant 10 to 0, covering their healer's weakness with powerful offensive.

But in this team competition, Happy was met with trouble.

"Did you think you could crush us like you did with Radiant? Don't be so arrogant!" Parade's captain, Grappler player Wu Shuai yelled imposingly into the chat.

Around eight minutes after the battle started, Team Parade's formation was still very whole, but Team Happy's One Inch Ash had already been wiped out. Happy was currently at a one player disadvantage and Parade was launching a fierce offense, trying to defeat another of Happy's members before their sixth player arrived.

　

It was all that guy's fault!

The match wasn't being live broadcasted on TV, so the fans were mostly watching on TV. Previously, in the 1v1s, Happy had lost a point in the individual matches, taking a lead of 4 to 1. However, from the start of the team competition, they hadn't been able to grasp the initiative. Parade was very accurately aiming for Happy's weakness: Little Cold Hands.

Strategy, class, map choice, all of it was precisely planned. In the end, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had fallen to Parade, desperately trying to cover for Little Cold Hands. When they saw this scene, Happy's supporters felt a ball of rage burn in their hearts.

If it wasn't for him, the team wouldn't have had to retreat and fall to a disadvantage.

If it wasn't for him, Qiao Yifan would've been better able to set up his Ghost Boundaries!

If it wasn't for him, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash wouldn't have lost so much health.

It was him, it was all him!

　

"Even I can do better than him!!" Many fans slammed their keyboard in rage. And now, after killing One Inch Ash, Parade was targeting Fang Rui's Boundless Sea.

"Fuck! They might as well not have a Cleric!" In the online stream, the comment section was filled with such jeers.

This was something none of Happy's members could see. All they knew was that the situation wasn't looking good for them at all. They also knew that if they lost this round, the last barrier protecting An Wenyi from criticism would fall. Though the team could have faith in him as usual, what about himself? After defeat after defeat, each a blow to his self confidence. If this time, they lost to Parade because of his mistakes, then it would probably be a critical strike. Could he still hold on after something like that?

"Hey, great healer An! We're attacking your Boundless Sea, you know? Can you still manage to keep him alive?" The captain of Team Parade continued to trash talk in the chat, unafraid of revealing their intentions. They had planned it this way anyways.

　

"Don't panic, it's not as bad as he says," Ye Xiu sent into the team chat.

"Understood." Surprisingly, he gained such a reply.

Ye Xiu was stunned.

This was a simple reply, but if An Wenyi could still type, then that means he hadn't panicked at all. He had kept his calm, observing the battlefield and waiting for the time when he would be needed. Meanwhile, he could easy find time to respond to Ye Xiu when he wasn't needed.

"Very good!" Ye Xiu, based on this conjecture, had given a response to An Wenyi's reply.

　

The audience all thought that it was An Wenyi who had dragged the entire team down. However, in Ye Xiu's eyes, An Wenyi hadn't made any serious mistakes this match. The one who had performed poorly was Qiao Yifan. He was too nervous, too set on covering Little Cold Hands that he had worked himself into a mess, desynchronizing with the pacing of the team.

"Is there any need to heal Boundless Sea?" Ye Xiu mocked back in the public chat as he charged forward.

Chapter 1313: Just in Time

"He's coming!" Wu Shuai yelled into the Parade chat. Their focused offense on Boundless Sea was just because they wanted to lure Lord Grim over.

Wiping out Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash? This result wasn't something that satisfied them. Though they acted confident, in reality, Happy - even lacking one player - still threatened them greatly. However, if they could send Lord Grim out of the running, then their victory would be certain.

　

Their encirclement of Boundless Sea was to lure Ye Xiu over into trying to save him: their true target was Lord Grim.

"Prepare!" Wu Shuai ordered. Parade's team members clearly weren't properly trying to beat Boundless Sea, all waiting for a chance to lunge in the other direction!

"There's a plot!" This naturally wouldn't escape the Master of Dirty Play, Fang Rui, and he quickly sent a warning in the Happy chat.

　

"Worry not!" Ye Xiu replied as Lord Grim continued his advance.

"Switch!" Wu Shuai ordered, and Team Parade surrounded their target.

In an instant, it wasn't Boundless Sea in the encirclement, but Lord Grim.

　

"Scared yet?" Fang Rui hollered in the chat. This time, it fell to him to save Lord Grim. However, Team Parade hadn't truly formed an encirclement around him, but they did around Lord Grim, and it seemed much stronger.

Would they be alright?

Fang Rui wondered in his heart, observing Team Parade's formation and trying to find a chance to team-up with and break Ye Xiu out. That was when, with a boom, someone was sent flying out of Parade's sturdy encirclement with a Falling Flower Palm from Lord Grim, and the latter broke out easily.

"Haha, a paper mache encirclement?" Fang Rui would never miss out on a chance to mock his opponents.

"What happened?" Wu Shuai yelled angrily into the team chat. He naturally wouldn't send this into the public chat and draw jeers from his opponents.

"How come my skills are on cooldown!?" the one sent flying by Lord Grim yelped.

　

"No, not cooldown, they've been sealed! Sacred Fire? When?" that person added.

　

Sacred Fire?

The people watching the live stream all froze. When was Sacred Fire used?

The Parade members on the battlefield had already turned their gazes to Little Cold Hands. Their teammate naturally wouldn't lie to them. Did Little Cold Hands strike just now?

　

No one knew...

In that moment, they had completely ignored Little Cold hands, as if the Cleric were nothing but air.

"It was probably Lord Grim!" Someone suddenly called out.

　

"You're right!" The entire team suddenly seemed to realize something. Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could have all sorts of skills set into its different forms. He must have set a Sacred Fire into the weapon's Priest class form. That guy was a sly bastard like that, always switching the skills he had on his weapon so that he could mess with everyone.

"Good job!" Ye Xiu sent that praise into the team chat, because this Sacred Fire really did come from Little Cold Hands. It was just that he had timed the activation so well that just as Ye Xiu struck out, when his opponent was about to defend, a Sacred Fire began to burn under Ye Xiu's surprised gaze, sealing that member of Parade's skills. The skill he was about to use to block Lord Grim never came, allowing him to break through with a simple Falling Flower Palm.

"Again!" Team Parade, believing that they had already found the crux of the problem, turned and pursued Lord Grim.

　

Sky-Piercing Strike!

　

However, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea had already arrived to help, pushing his palms out and shooting forth a blast of qi. Parade's membered rushed to dodge it, their formation completely destroyed by now. Then, a missile descended, mushroom cloud rising. The Parade characters in each area getting blasted off their feet. Their offensive had been shattered.

With their offensive gone, Happy was free to launch their own. They might be one head short for now, but they wouldn't let this opportunity pass them by.

Shining Cut, Slide Kick, Knee Strike!

Lord Grim activated three skills in rapid succession, arriving in front of a character in the blink of an eye and sending them flying.

　

Pulse Break: Break Strength! Break Intelligence!

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea shot by, jabbing the character twice. The target's stats immediately plummeted. At the same time, a ring of light descended and Little Cold Hands' Holy Commandment blanketed them just in time.

　

With all these damage increasing statuses, if they didn't attack now, then when should they?

Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, and Su Mucheng all used their own methods to deal as much damage as they could to this poor character. Their target had no way to stop their remaining health from decreasing, and it dropped like a rock.

Having been knocked completely out of it, the members of Parade hurriedly adjusted themselves to counterattack and save their teammate. However, the three members of Happy didn't seem to be able to take their eyes off their target, ignoring all the attacks that came their way and continuing their crazed barrage of attacks.

Were they planning on wiping him out first?

They would choose to do that with a numbers disadvantage? That was a huge challenge for their own healer! However, wasn't Happy's healer the worst in the Alliance? Could he really hold this situation steady?

　　

Parade had planned on simply ignoring An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands, but with the current situation, they couldn't just let the guy heal as much as he wanted - even if his healing was crap!

　

"Interrupt!" Wu Shuai yelled.

"Interrupt what?" The team members were confused.

　

"Their healer!" Wu Shuai was vexed. They needed him to explain such a simple arrangement?

"Where… is the healer?" The members of Parade continued to voice their confusion.

　

"Huh?" Wu Shuai turned his view in a full circle, but he really couldn't find Little Cold Hands.

"Where'd he hide?" Just now, everyone had been so focused on dodging the blasts. Plus, they hadn't thought much of Little Cold Hands either, to the extent that no one had noticed where the guy had hid.

"Fuck!" Wu Shuai yelled in rage. If he sent someone to search, then that would just be wasting time. It would be better if they didn't bother for now.

"Save him first!" Wu Shuai ordered. They continued to launch their attacks at the three attackers, but those three really were stubborn, persisting with their offense.

Their attacks struck that poor character while Team Parade's attacks struck them.

"Focus on Lord Grim!" Wu Shuai hollered. If they successfully made such a trade, then it was really worth it! Don't run, please don't run!

Lord Grim really didn't run. He simply made sure that Parade's attacks wouldn't disrupt his own. Damage? He just took it. Parade instantly became more enthusiastic. They had finally taken out a significant chunk of Lord Grim's health, when a light suddenly washed over him and erupted, turning all of their screen white.

This was a Great Heal, a Great Heal that crit. Instantly, Lord Grim's health skyrocketed. Though it didn't completely negate all of Parade's efforts, what it healed made Parade feel powerless.

"Where's that damn Cleric!?" Wu Shuai roared. Their underestimation of Little Cold Hands was destroying them.

"Did no one notice? Open your eyes wider!" Wu Shuai demanded.

Thus, when Little Cold Hands' heal came over once more, someone finally noticed where the holy light of the cross was coming from.

"Nine o'clock!" The member of Parade that had found Little Cold Hands yelled.

　

"Go and grab him!" Wu Shuai said, finally sending someone to deal with Little Cold Hands.

Seeing that he had been exposed, An Wenyi had Little Cold Hands run without hesitation.

However, the current garb that Little Cold Hands had on wasn't the movement speed equipment he had during the Challengers League. After focusing all his stats on healing, Little Cold Hands' movement speed began to display the weakness that was typical to healers. Run, where could he run to?

　

An Wenyi had barely ran anywhere, when he heard the sound of approaching footsteps. His pursuer was using skills to catch up to him, and it didn't take long before the other had caught up.

"I've caught him!" The Parade member excitedly reported. Yet that was when Little Cold Hands suddenly came to a halt and turned around, as if having given up.

What the hell was this? The Parade member felt a moment of suspicion rise in his heart when, boom! His character was sent flying.

　

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Happy's sixth player, Soft Mist, had arrived.

"Just in time." An Wenyi even had the time to type!

"Nice train driving," Tang Rou complimented back. A train was a gaming term that referred to luring a large group of mobs into a specified position for attack. The more precise the positioning, the better the train.

"Let's go!!" Tang Rou, having finally arrived at the scene of battle, was in high spirits. She ignored the person she had knocked flying and charged towards the battlefield over yonder.

　

Shattering the Lands!

Soft Mist announced her arrival with a high-level skill, jumping high into the air. Her spear Dancing Fire Flowing Flame making a red trail through the air as it fell with its wielder, a blazing Soft Mist.

Boom!

　

Shattering the Lands, shaking the very foundations of the earth, Soft Mist's appearance was too sudden, her attacks swiftly finding a new target. She knocked someone into the air and then, in the blink of an eye, had landed with a Shattering the Lands over here. Parade's members fumbled to respond, dodging out of sync. This strike had once again destroyed their formation.

　

"Wipe out this one first!" Ye Xiu called out. Tang Rou didn't bother with a typed response, using her actions to show that she understood. Dancing Fire Flowing Flame swinging at its target's weak points.

"Interrupt the healer!" Ye Xiu gave another order. Currently, they had completely taken the upper hand. If they didn't wipe this guy out of the game, then they'd have wasted this chance.

Then, Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng repeatedly switched targets in synchronization, using ranged attacks to interrupt the healer's support. Tang Rou and Fang Rui focused completely on DPS and An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands had run over too, regrouping with the others.

　

Finally… their target fell, and Happy dismantled Parade's lead.

"The healer!" Ye Xiu made a swift decision. Currently, it was Happy that had the advantage in numbers on the field.

The entire team lunged for their opponent's healer at once.

Wipe him out!

　

Happy's members surrounded Parade's healer, tossing attacks over in rapid succession. At the same time, they paid careful attention to Team Parade's attempts at support. Parade struck left and right but couldn't rescue their healer. With the healer under siege, they couldn't recover health, and the characters that came to try and provide support took heavy damage.

　　

At first, everyone thought that Happy was trying to wipe out the other's healer, but looking closer, they realized that they had actually kidnapped their healer and were slowly chipping away at the health of the rest of their members.

"Attack their healer!" Realizing that they couldn't continue like this, Wu Shuai hurriedly gave new orders. Parade's members immediately charged at Little Cold Hands.

"Heh, didn't you say our healer was useless? Is this trade worth it?" Ye Xiu mocked.

Chapter 1314: Team MVP

Ye Xiu's mockery caused Parade's Captain Wu Shuai feel his heart skip a beat.

This exchange really was imbalanced. Happy's healer was such trash! But aside from this, what else could they do right now?

You couldn't afford to hesitate in a match! Wu Shuai was very decisive when he needed to be, so even though his heart jolted, he didn't waver. He continued to lead his team members to charge towards Little Cold Hands.

An Wenyi didn't waste any time. As soon as he saw people rushing toward him, he cast a Great Cure on his own Little Cold Hands, pulling his health very high. Then, Parade began their attack. But when Wu Shuai looked over at Happy's progress on the other side, he wanted to cry.

This wasn't a problem of whether this trade was balanced! This trade might not even be completed in the first place! Happy was progressing much faster in killing off their target.

"Bring him away!" Wu Shuai hurried to direct. As they attacked, they tried to pull Little Cold Hands away, to buy themselves more time to kill him off.

"Not fast enough." An Wenyi, the one who couldn't control a situation even when putting his all into a battle, actually found the time to type words right now, even when he was being surrounded and attacked from all sides.

Indeed… they weren't fast enough.

Wu Shuai didn't lack judgment, he just wanted to put his all into striving for this goal. But when An Wenyi said this, he understood that Happy had calculated everything. Anything that he did was futile.

It ends here.

Wu Shuai understood very clearly that this match was going to be decided right here.

Wu Shuai sighed and watched as their team's healer finally fell. And Little Cold Hands? Even after being surrounded, the character still had a third of her health left!

What if we copied them?

Wu Shuai suddenly had another thought, to try and learn from the way Happy had surrounded Parade's healer. But before he could give any orders, a Satellite Beam was already falling from the sky, a spinning pillar of light that expanded. Parade's members instinctively began to dodge, and their encirclement was broken just like that.

There was no way. They had no healer anymore.

Wu Shuai discovered what the difference was between their current situation and that of Happy earlier. At that time, Happy had their healer helping out, while Parade's healer had been cut off in the encirclement. That was why they could play to wear them out. But now, even if they locked Little Cold Hands in an encirclement, they didn't have a healer to support them anymore, and stubbornly trying to maintain this encirclement would only use up even more of their health.

There was really no way.

Wu Shuai once again felt that they were at the end, and this time he finally didn't experience any new breakthroughs. By the time Parade's sixth player arrived, they were at a disadvantage in terms of numbers, and they still didn't have a healer. They couldn't turn the situation around. Wu Shuai actually began to feel a sense of longing for that Little Cold Hands, the one deemed by the entirety of Glory to be worst pro Cleric.

Right now, even if they only had a Cleric like that, would they lose? Absolutely not!

They were unwilling, but they could only fall. In the end, Parade couldn't defeat Happy in the team competition and lost in a bitter 1-9.

In the post-match press conference, the reporters asked Wu Shuai for his feelings about this match. He said the standard polite words, but as he talked and talked, he gradually began to think seriously.

Where was the match point of this team battle?

The beginning had gone so smoothly, they'd easily killed off one of the opponents. With that kind of lead, how come they fell over like a toppled mountain by the end?

Wu Shuai pulled himself back to the match, in that moment when they had killed off Happy's Phantom Demon One Inch Ash, pretended to surround Boundless Sea, lured in Lord Grim, surrounded him. But then Lord Grim, with a thrust of his palm, casually escaped from the encirclement that they had prepared so carefully. And the reason was that the character supposed to intercept him was unexpectedly hit by a Heavenly Fire and became unable to use any skills.

It had happened so quickly during the match, there wasn't any time to analyze it. Parade just thought that it was a skill that Lord Grim had put on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, but was that really the case?

Wu Shuai recalled that moment in detail. Lord Grim was surrounded, and then he immediately tried to rush outwards. Sacred Fire was a skill that required reciting lines. Where did he have the time to stop and cast?

It was Little Cold Hands.

It was An Wenyi.

Yes, that was correct, that was exactly how it happened…

And then Happy counterattacked, scattering their formation, and the match situation was instantly flipped around.

The match point was when Lord Grim instantly broke through their encirclement. And that had been the result of that Cleric, who'd been looked down upon by them - no, looked down upon by the entire Glory circle! If it weren't for his move then, no matter how high Ye Xiu's skill was, he couldn't have immediately pushed open a road with one palm. Parade's brothers weren't noobs, after all!

That guy was really lucky.

When Wu Shuai thought this problem through, this was his final conclusion. Ultimately, he still didn't believe that An Wenyi had such ability. He still felt that that player was just a blind cat that'd run into a dead mouse. But since he'd already thought to this point, he couldn't help but think more about Little Cold Hands' performance this match. And after doing so, he discovered that that player had appeared again and again at the crucial points of the match.

We… lost to that Cleric?

"Impossible!" Wu Shuai suddenly said aloud.

"What's impossible? What did you say was impossible just now?" The reporters had been listening to another player from Parade answer a question, but when they suddenly heard this word from Wu Shuai's mouth, they immediately turned their attention toward him.

"Happy's Cleric isn't so simple," Wu Shuai said.

"Hehehe," the reporters all snickered. What was he saying? He couldn't beat Happy, so he didn't even agree what Happy's weak point was anymore? How petty! With your strength, it was no big surprise that you weren't able to beat Happy, do you really need to make excuses like this?

Wu Shuai's words didn't incite any excitement from the reporters. They continued their interviews, until Parade's conference was over and Happy's began. And then, the first sentence they heard from Ye Xiu's lips was praise for An Wenyi.

"Today's victory was all thanks to An Wenyi's outstanding performance."

An Wenyi?

Outstanding performance?

Putting these two phrases together, how come it felt so conflicting? Could they really be written together? The reporters felt a bit dizzy.

"What? Did no one notice?" Ye Xiu asked, extremely surprised, as he watched all the reporters exchange glances. He added, "Did you watch the match?"

"Of course," the reporters all answered.

"Did the stats for this match come out yet?" Ye Xiu suddenly asked the Alliance worker at the side.

"They're out," that person answered.

"Who was the team competition MVP?" Ye Xiu asked.

"An Wenyi." The Alliance employee gave the answer from the stats.

"Huh?" The gathered reporters were shocked.

Ye Xiu grinned. "I'm glad that the Alliance was watching the match seriously."

The reporters were greatly embarrassed. An Wenyi was the MVP of this match? The reporters forgot the interview and all began discussing with each other, but everyone only had a fuzzy impression of An Wenyi's performance in the match. Before they watched the match, they were already in a certain mindset. Matches should be enjoyed, but they didn't have that mindset toward An Wenyi, so much so that even though they were Glory specialists, they hadn't even realized the MVP of this team competition.

Without being able to figure out the why, this press conference couldn't continue. The reporters could only bring out a few scripted questions, like asking An Wenyi about his view of his performance today.

"I did the right things at the right times," An Wenyi said.

"Oh? Could you give us some detail?" the reporters asked.

"You… you should just rewatch the match!" An Wenyi was a bit speechless. They wanted him to use words to describe his performance? It wasn't that he was disdainful, he was… rather embarrassed, because those were all his highlights. He couldn't just open his mouth and say "at that most critical moment, good thing I used my Sacred Fire" or whatnot. He was An Wenyi, not Wei Chen.

The press conference ended inconclusively like this. By the end, the reporters still had questions in their hearts. They didn't understand how An Wenyi became the hero of this match. After the conference finished, they all immediately revisited the match, and now that they were in the mindset of looking for highlights, these specialists quickly realized what they had missed during this match. This was too unprofessional.

"An Wenyi found his footing?" the reporters wondered.

An Wenyi, whom the entire Glory circle viewed as dragging down his team, suddenly became the team MVP. Wasn't this change just too dramatic?

The reporters of the various media were all already imagining the articles to write about An Wenyi. The match between Happy and Parade originally wasn't anything interesting to report on. But now that An Wenyi had become the MVP of this match, this topic was really quite incredible.

As for those looking for thrilling headlines in this round, Samsara's home game against Tiny Herb and Tyranny's home game against Blue Rain were both top-level confrontations.

In the end, both matches ended with the home team's victory, both 7-3. Tiny Herb's win streak in the group arena was finally broken in this round. Of all the consecutive win records in this season, only Ye Xiu's individual win streak had yet to be sniped.

In this round, Wind Howl, who'd been swaggering with their recent win streak against weak teams, finally ate a loss. And this time, their opponent absolutely couldn't be called a strong team.

Miracle!

One of the new teams this season played their home game against Wind Howl and ultimately defeated them 7-3. In the confrontation between previous Excellent Era players, it was actually the seemingly lower, lagging members of Miracle that obtained victory.

Wind Howl was the team that defeated many weak teams to appear strong. But after this loss, their standing on the rankings immediately changed. Right now, they were seventh place with 148 points, followed by Hundred Blossoms only one point behind them. After that, ninth place was the recently-strong 301. After defeating Royal Style 8-2 in their home game this round, there were now only 7 points between them and the playoff zone.

But this time, 301 didn't use the fierce Life-Risking Strike again.

Chapter 1315: Terror and Despair

Team Wind Howl, after failing to complete a transfer during the winter transfer window that would solve their problems, entered the second half of the season.

Even though they had sustained repeated losses against strong teams in the first half of the season, Wind Howl was still firmly strong against the mid and low-tier teams. This allowed people to maintain a thread of faith in them.

But now, Team Miracle.

Even if this team did better than expected, that only meant that they had a certain amount of strength. With a score of 102 points halfway through the season in 12th place, they couldn't really be called strong. This was the typical score of a mid-tier team.

But now, Wind Howl had lost to this mid-tier team.

This was tantamount to tearing away their last piece of clothing. Could Wind Howl get results? That question mark was becoming bigger and bigger. In the post-match press conference, Wind Howl's Captain Tang Hao was furious, severely reprimanding his team for not working hard enough.

But could Wind Howl's problems really be solved just with hard work?

Things weren't that simple! Hard work couldn't solve everything in Glory. Aside from hard work, you have to have the correct method, and today's Wind Howl lacked not hard work, nor the determination to pursue victory, but rather the method for obtaining victory, especially in the team competition.

Originally, Wind Howl's key to victory was their dirty playing. Now, they had thrown away this key, but they hadn't found a new key that could continue to open locks. All the locksmiths were struggling away, but no matter how they tried, they just couldn't unlock that door to victory.

"Come on, work hard, get your spirits up, we can't lose!" These sort of morale-boosting sentiments couldn't solve the problem at the core.

What should Wind Howl do?

In this week's edition of the Esports Weekly, Wind Howl actually became the subject of the headline. After everyone finished discussing how weak An Wenyi was and how strong Bai Shu was, Wind Howl's strength as a team became the new topic everyone cared about.

Wind Howl themselves were suffering nonstop the protests of their fans. Wind Howl urgently needed a match where they could prove their strength. And so, their chance arrived in Round 25, with their home game against Samsara.

Was it a bit too extreme… aiming for them as a proof of strength?

Wind Howl's players felt the urge to eat their account cards.

"This is our best chance." Their captain Tang Hao, however, appeared fearless before them.

"What could prove our strength better than defeating Samsara?" said Tang Hao.

"Get your spirits up everyone, use this battle to show everyone who we Wind Howl really are." In the prep room before the match, Tang Hao mobilized his teammates.

But Wind Howl's players were truly somewhat numb to these sort of words by now.

Onstage, individual competition, three battles, loss loss loss.

The stadium resounded with boos. This was only the individual competition, and they were already getting wrecked?

Tang Hao's face turned livid. But what else could he do? He didn't know anymore…

Soon enough, the group arena ended. Now, not only were there boos, members of the crowd were already leaving the stadium early. They didn't even want to watch the important team competition anymore, and used their early departure as their strongest form of protest against the team.

After the individual competition was over, Wind Howl was 0-5.

Following that match with Happy, would they be swept 0-10 again this match? That time, at least, was Happy's home game. But this time, they were being swept by the away team. It was truly a slap to the face.

After the team competition, the cheers and shouts for Samsara were already louder than those for Wind Howl. What made Wind Howl lose even more face was that some of the cheers for Samsara were actually from Wind Howl's fangroup. What kind of disappointment and anger was this? The team competition finally began…

Meanwhile, on another battlefield…

"Again…" The audience members were dumbfounded as they watched Radiant's healer, 2 minutes and 34 seconds in the team round, slain by one knife of 301's Assassin Scene Killer.

Life-Risking Strike!

Even more fearsome was that this time, Scene Killer didn't die right after using Life-Risking Strike. He was actually protected by Bai Shu's Knight Tide. After that, 301's healer, the Paladin 007 piled on a series of healing skills, instantly pulling Scene Killer's health back…

An Assassin that had successfully used Life-Risking Strike to kill the target, actually didn't die?

Everyone was stunned. This was absolutely the first time this had ever happened in Glory history.

This Team 301 Degrees, to what extent would they perfect this assassination style?

Radiant's strength couldn't match 301's. After losing their healer, the rest of the team fell like a mountain toppled over, and the match was quickly decided. 301 earned a large victory this round, full points with a 10-0.

Shortly after, the match between Wind Howl and Samsara was also decided. Samsara lived up to expectations and defeated Wind Howl, sweeping them in a 10-0.

301 and Wind Howl had only had a difference of 8 points between them, and with this, they instantly swapped positions on the leaderboard. Would Wind Howl be able to remain in the top 8? That would be determined by the final result of another team's match.

Hundred Blossoms faced Lightly this round.

This confrontation caused Wind Howl to fall into despair.

In the end, Hundred Blossoms defeated Lightly 8-2, rising to seventh place. 301 rose one place to eighth, finally entering the playoff zone. All of this had arrived terrifyingly quickly. At the halfway mark of the season, Round 19, 301 still only had 98 points, but after six rounds, they had already risen to 150 points. 52 points in six rounds, that was an average of 8.7 points per match, far surpassing the number one team Samsara's match average of 8.3 points.

In Round 19, 301 defeated Happy in the team round because Yang Cong used Life-Risking Strike to take out Happy's Little Cold Hands. But they had really gotten strong starting from Round 20. The arrival of the player Bai Shu truly gave 301 something that that Alliance had never seen before, a strategic playstyle revolving around the Assassin's Life-Risking Strike. Bai Shu had integrated into the team very quickly, making it obvious that he was a player with an extremely high Glory IQ. And the new system that he brought hadn't even reached its full potential yet. 301 was still testing things out, still getting used to everything. But even so, they had already earned a terrifying point-scoring rate. Once this strategy was perfected, what kind of fearsome and deadly power would it have?

Now, people were realizing that Bai Shu's arrival didn't just bring an unknown expert, but an unknown strategy, ultimately raising an unknown team.

"What a headache!" everyone complained. But at this moment, some people didn't even have the time to complain about this.

"What a headache, how long are we planning to play for?" Ye Xiu said.

"You guys already lost long ago, if not for your disgustingly dirty hide-and-seek this match would already be over! Is there a point is there a point? Just come out and 1v1 me! A good and honest match to decide victory, do you dare, huh, do you dare?" Huang Shaotian raged.

Just as all the various matches were ending, Blue Rain's home game against Happy had already lasted over forty minutes. Right now, Blue Rain had lost one player, and the five others were all on the field. Happy, meanwhile, only had two players left. But even in this situation, Happy's two players still didn't GG, nor did they come out to end this faster. They were actually very patiently dealing with Blue Rain.

"What bastards!" Seeing this scene, a number of elite guild members felt their hearts sour.

Once upon a time, in the Heavenly Domain, they sent out large armies, only for them to be cruelly teased by these two guys! Seeing how even Blue Rain was now dragged around by them for so long, everyone suddenly felt a bit gratified.

Lord Grim, Deception.

These were the two players still alive from Happy. Without a doubt, Happy didn't have any chance of victory against Blue Rain, who still had an intact roster. But these two people still refused to give up, ducking and hiding all over, dragging out what should have been a 31-minute match over the current 42-minute mark.

"Before the last moment, the match isn't considered over," Ye Xiu lectured Huang Shaotian very seriously. "1v1? Is that a battle method that belongs in the team competition?"

"You... What kind of method is your hide-and-seek then?" Huang Shaotian used a powerful self-control to turn his swearing into ellipses.

"This is training, do you understand? The playoffs give points by number of players remaining. We Happy are already adjusting to the rhythm of the playoffs. Are you convinced now?"

"Convinced you...." The powerful self-control was once again exercised. "You two, you're still trying to earn some player points?"

"Not necessarily! If you're skilled, then come and 1v2 us!" Ye Xiu called.

"Alright! I'll fight you two by myself!" Huang Shaotian said.

"Everyone else, back off by a hundred body-lengths," said Ye Xiu.

"They've backed off, backed off."

"That fast?" Ye Xiu was doubtful.

"Backing off right now."

"Alright, let me take a look."

Blue Rain's players were instantly on full alert. Between the five of them, they had a 360-degree view of their surroundings. Even the slightest silhouette wouldn't escape their notice.

"You didn't back off! Liars!" Ye Xiu said angrily.

"You didn't even look! You're the liar!" Huang Shaotian was also furious. They hadn't seen anyone poking their head up to look. This guy wasn't even over here.

"I guessed!" Ye Xiu said.

"You sneak!" Huang Shaotian shouted.

"Stop wasting time, come find us already, this match is already so long, aren't you all annoyed?" Ye Xiu called.

Everyone felt tears streaming down their faces. You're the ones at fault here!

"Not too far off. They should be in this area." In Blue Rain's team chat, Yu Wenzhou had already made this judgment.

"Split up. Shaotian and I will take the channel on the left. Song Xiao, you and Zheng Xuan take the right, around that large boulder." Yu Wenzhou continued to lay out plans.

"Huh? What about me?" The Paladin player Xu Jingxi was confused. His name hadn't been listed in the split.

"Mm, left and right are both ambushes. You just walk directly forward, serve as the bait," said Yu Wenzhou.

"Too cruel…" Xu Jingxi felt like crying.

Chapter 1316: Pointless Move

A hide-and-seek match that had lasted for over ten minutes now. If this were Happy's home game, Happy's fans might still find this interesting. But this was Blue Rain's home game. Seeing these two people with no chance of reversal but still shamelessly dragging this on, they'd started booing early on.

But just then, when Ye Xiu expressed that this was training for the playoffs, the boos were actually interrupted for a second. In that instant, everyone actually agreed with this sentiment, but soon enough, as Huang Shaotian sent a series of messages, everyone woke up. This was just a fabricated excuse, right? The boos suddenly grew even louder.

Then why did they still want to drag this out?

To be honest, not even Happy's players were sure. Even if it was for a reason like accumulating match experience, this right now was nowhere near the rhythm of an ordinary match. What kind of experience could they get?

Only Ye Xiu knew the real reason.

If it were just himself, he probably would have directly said "GG" by now. But he still had Mo Fan beside him. With only two people left, Ye Xiu was already prepared to give up, but Mo Fan's Deception still went on the rhythm of escape.

"This guy…" Ye Xiu was surprised, but he quickly followed.

Mo Fan had played a number of professional matches now. He should understand the situation they were currently facing, he should be able to judge that they didn't have much of a chance with a 2v5. But he didn't give up, he only temporarily avoided facing the opponent head-on, as though waiting for an opportunity to counterattack. Ye Xiu couldn't bring himself to quell his enthusiasm, and could only follow along, running and hiding for over ten whole minutes.

In over ten minutes, the two just ran away. They hadn't found the chance to take out a single target. But Mo Fan was very patient and very persistent. Ye Xiu, too, was never someone who gave up easily. He wasn't as bullheaded as Mo Fan, but since he was being stubborn with this guy right now, he might as well play to his fullest, and put effort into his running around.

Until now.

"This is probably it." After studying his surroundings, Ye Xiu said this to Mo Fan in the chat.

Mo Fan's Deception also looked around and didn't object. He was an expert at running away. Although they faced fewer pursuers now than they would in the crowded in-game world, the pressure here was much higher. Professionals were no trivial matter, after all. Fortunately, Mo Fan had improved greatly, otherwise he certainly wouldn't have been able to evade the enemy team's pursuit for these ten minutes.

Right now, they had finally reached a situation where there was no more path to take.

There was no road of retreat, they could only go forward. Now, if they wanted to run, they could only forcibly break through the encirclement. Ye Xiu carefully studied the surroundings, but he saw Deception's hand moved, lifting the ninjato in front of him. Following Deception's gaze, he also saw Blue Rain's Paladin, Soul Speaker, slowly wandering toward them.

Deception was just about to jump forward, but a string of words from Ye Xiu jumped out in the chat. "It's bait."

Mo Fan paused, and then responded with his own string of words. "Then what do we do?"

"Just wait, ignore them," Ye Xiu answered.

And so Soul Speaker walked closer and closer, until he didn't dare walk any closer, but he still saw no sign of the two targets. Xu Jingxi couldn't do anything, and could only ask in the team chat.

After a while, a message from Yu Wenzhou appeared in the match chat. "This is meaningless! We've already stepped on the stairs for you, just come down already!"

"So that's what this is about! I was just wondering why you were looking down on us so much," Ye Xiu answered.

"Right, then just come out!" Yu Wenzhou said.

"Can't. If I fell for such a crude trick, how embarrassing would that be?" said Ye Xiu.

"Then what do you want to do?" Yu Wenzhou asked.

"I can already tell the positions where you guys are lying in wait, I'll try forcibly breaking through from here," Ye Xiu said.

"Left or right?" Yu Wenzhou asked.

"Either."

As soon as this message appeared in the chat, Lord Grim's silhouette immediately appeared in Swoksaar's field of view.

"Oh hey, what a coincidence," Ye Xiu greeted in the chat.

"Perfect timing!" Huang Shaotian shouted, and Troubling Rain immediately swung his sword to meet him.

"Now you're the one in charge of the chat?" Ye Xiu laughed. Lord Grim rushed forward without any sign of weakness.

The two characters were fighting in earnest. Huang Shaotian wasn't an opponent that Ye Xiu could get rid of so quickly. Yu Wenzhou had already controlled Swoksaar to support him, and the rest of Blue Rain had already run up to surround him.

Yu Wenzhou immediately realized something was wrong.

"Where's Deception?" He stopped his controls and shouted in the chat.

A silhouette charged forward!

Blue Rain's arrangement had originally locked down this area, but because of how Lord Grim had suddenly jumped forward with a powerful attack, he'd drawn everyone's attention and Blue Rain had suddenly left openings. Mo Fan was extremely precise at choosing positions, and Deception rushed toward these openings. Before Blue Rain's players could react, Deception had already escaped from the area they controlled.

"Let's see where you can run!" Huang Shaotian shouted as Troubling Rain slashed ferociously.

"Who said I wanted to run?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"Then this is?" Yu Wenzhou didn't understand.

"Decoy! Threaten the east and strike to the west!" Ye Xiu said.

"What's the point in his running away?" Yu Wenzhou asked.

"Run for another ten minutes?" Ye Xiu offered.

"…" Blue Rain was truly, completely speechless. This is an official match! Are you guys seriously just playing hide-and-seek here?

"Go die!" Troubling Rain's attacks became even more frantic. Zheng Xuan and Song Xiao's characters had also arrived, beginning to surround and attack Lord Grim, while Swoksaar restarted his curse casting. Lord Grim's health plummeted.

But at this moment, behind Swoksaar, a silhouette appeared. Deception had circled around and suddenly came into sight over here, and the Shurikens in his hand flew outward toward Swoksaar. Yu Wenzhou heard the warning from his teammates and quickly dodged. But after Deception used the Shurikens, he instantly arrived before him, jumped up, and slashed downward toward Swoksaar.

Ding!

The sound of metal colliding with metal resounded. Troubling Rain used a Triple Slash, instantly flashing in front of Swoksaar and blocking this attack from Deception. The next two slashes smoothly continued to push Deception back.

But because Troubling Rain had come over here, the encirclement around Lord Grim suddenly had an opening. With a toss of a grenade, and a Shining Cut, Lord Grim split through to arrive in front of Swoksaar, but the attack failed to land - he twisted into a Charge and once again crashed toward Troubling Rain.

Huang Shaotian knew that if he were passed through again, this guy would definitely escape.

Formless Phantom Blade!

Huang Shaotian directly used an ultimate attack. In front of Troubling Rain, the swordlight formed a net, flying toward Lord Grim.

But in the chat, a message from his teammate suddenly popped out. "Behind you!"

Behind Troubling Rain was Deception, who had just been forced away by his Triple Slash.

He returned so quickly?

Huang Shaotian was shocked. This was to say, he hadn't actually driven this guy back earlier, this guy had voluntarily chosen to back off. Only then could he so calmly execute this sudden swing around.

Body Bind Technique!

Mo Fan's sudden explosion of hand speed and control was incredibly powerful. Huang Shaotian truly hadn't expected that he would return so quickly, and any warning from his teammates was too late. No matter how powerful Formless Phantom Blade was from the front, the back was filled with openings. Deception stuck right to him and directly interrupted his powerful attack. However, he didn't use his skill until the end, he actually once again took the initiative to retreat.

But Huang Shaotian didn't feel fortunate at all. Deception had retreated, but Lord Grim's Charge had now arrived right before him.

Boom!

Troubling Rain was blown to the side. Deception had already thrown out a Smoke Bomb, filling the area with purple fog. Lord Grim continued to move and instantly vanished within. The skill that Yu Wenzhou had prepared could now only rely on luck as he threw it in there, and nothing came of it in the end. By the time Blue Rain passed through the purple fog, those two from Happy had already run far off.

"Is there a point to this, is there??" His slashes couldn't reach them anymore, so Huang Shaotian could only vent his anger through the chat.

"Haha, I think it's pretty interesting!" Ye Xiu answered.

"Referee, a guy like this should be directly disqualified!" Huang Shaotian complained to the judge. But this was an official League match, not the All-Stars. Even though the current situation was infuriating, they hadn't broken any rules, and the judge couldn't directly decide the outcome. He could only ignore Huang Shaotian. Blue Rain's five players were truly depressed as they had no other choice but to regroup and continue the chase.

After another ten minutes of struggle, Blue Rain caught up to Lord Grim and Deception, resulting in another intense battle. This time, Blue Rain finally didn't miss their opportunity, and killed the two off very ferociously. In the short amount of time between the end of the match and all the players logging off, Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan actually flogged the deceased corpses of Lord Grim and Deception.

This was an extreme way of humiliating the opponent and incredibly rude. It would be no surprise for such behavior to incite a war of words. But at this time, seeing the extremely agitated actions of these two Blue Rain players, all of the audience members felt a pleasure welling up within them.

These two guys had unnecessarily dragged on this battle for a full 23 minutes.

If you drag this on and actually accomplish something, then fine. But these two didn't manage to do anything, they were just running and hiding, all the way until they had nowhere else to run or hide. Was this purely just to sicken everyone?

But in the post-match press conference, Ye Xiu didn't see it like this at all.

"A pointless move? Of course not. We were searching for an opportunity the entire time! But Blue Rain simply did too well today. Overall, very strong. We couldn't find our chance, and regretfully lost the match in the end. Alas!" Ye Xiu lamented.

The reporters were in a daze. Motherfucker, what's there to regret about losing a 2v5? How come from your tone it sounded like you were doing a 2v5 and then messed up, allowing the five to defeat you?

"Next time, we'll continue to work hard!" After the gloom, Ye Xiu eagerly expressed his stance.

Still work hard?!

He's just saying that, he's not serious, is he?

The reporters, who were ready to flip a table after those 23 minutes of useless struggle, felt like collapsing.

Chapter 1317: Concentrated Hot Topics

Even though Blue Rain won this match 8-2, their spirits were low because of those last 23 minutes.

But Yu Wenzhou, who could normally analyze any problem, was completely perplexed this time. He truly could not see the reason why Ye Xiu and Mo Fan had dragged on the battle for those 23 minutes. Were they really looking for an opportunity to defeat the five of them? Yu Wenzhou didn't think Ye Xiu was that naive. Were they really just trying to screw with everyone on purpose? Yu Wenzhou didn't think Ye Xiu was that childish.

Then what was the reason?

In fact, Yu Wenzhou had thought about this the entire time after the battle ended, and when the players shook hands at the end, he actually asked Ye Xiu. But Ye Xiu had merely given him an inscrutable smile.

Now, when the reporters asked him about his opinion on those extra 23 minutes, Yu Wenzhou was very honest as he shook his head. "I was thinking about this the whole time, but I could not think of what their goal was in doing this."

"What kind of goal could there be? He was just doing this to screw with us!" Huang Shaotian said immediately.

Yu Wenzhou smiled wryly and shook his head, expressing his disagreement with that sentiment.

"You can't always think of him as so high and profound," said Huang Shaotian.

"But at the very least, there has to be logic," said Yu Wenzhou.

"Screwing with people, isn't that a very logical thing for him?" Huang Shaotian said.

"Normally, perhaps. But not during a match," said Yu Wenzhou.

These two Gods of Blue Rain just directly discussed in front of the reporters, but in the end they still didn't reach a conclusion. Those 23 infuriating minutes had become an unsolvable riddle.

What kind of secret was hidden within?

Some of the less serious media just reported like this, garnering a sizable reaction in the circle and provoking all sorts of incredible theories.

Countless people were stuck on these 23 minutes. But Happy itself wasn't too concerned about it at all. The 23 minutes came and went, and Ye Xiu hadn't said anything about this to Mo Fan. He'd just been helping Mo Fan, with his personality, do what he wanted to.

But Ye Xiu very much appreciated how, after he'd created a diversion to help Mo Fan escape the encirclement, that kid had doubled back to try and help out Ye Xiu. In reality, Ye Xiu hadn't planned for that to happen; he'd been prepared to sacrifice himself and then let Mo Fan to continue to hide for as long as he was able. But Mo Fan had actually returned after escaping to save Ye Xiu. It looked like this guy finally knew what it meant to be teammates. And in that moment, when he'd been helping Ye Xiu break free, the two of them had coordinated quite well.

Watching each of Happy's rookies grow and develop put Ye Xiu in a very good mood. But Happy's scores weren't nearly as crazy as they'd been during that one period. From their loss in Round 19 to 301, to their loss to Blue Rain today, in those seven rounds, Happy had lost five matches.

Right now, Happy was in sixth place. In terms of placement, that only seemed slightly worse than the fifth place they'd been able to maintain earlier. But back in Round 18, Happy had been earning points even faster than Samsara, whereas now, Samsara's lead was unchanged and the only two teams in the second tier, above 180 points, were Blue Rain and Tiny Herb. After that, Tyranny, Thunderclap, and Happy were in the 160-point tier, and Hundred Blossoms and 301 were in the 150-point tier, which wasn't far off at all from the 160-point tier.

The situation of the top 8 instantly became more complex. 301 was shooting up after the winter transfers, increasing the competition. For now, Wind Howl had become the sacrifice for 301 and were kicked out of the top 8.

Still, the differences weren't too large right now, and Wind Howl certainly wasn't done for. Although their current situation was so bad that their home fans were cheering for the away team, they still maintained the strength of their individual members. Even if they still couldn't find a suitable system for the team competition, as long as they played the individual battles well and earned points from the weaker teams, Wind Howl still had a chance at top 8.

After them, Void couldn't be ignored either. Misty Rain, still struggling to solve their strategic problems, seemed to be a bit weaker. And then Royal Style, Miracle, and such teams were now a solid 40-50 points behind. They didn't have much of a chance at the top 8. As for the teams that were to be relegated, Bright Green and Seaside, their chances of survival had basically dwindled away.

The situation with the top 8 was still the event to watch. Who would rise to here? Who would fall from here? This was the topic most nerve-wracking and thrilling about the regular season.

In the blink of an eye, Round 26 began. The teams near the eighth-place cutoff all became important subjects for the media to report on.

Among them, Wind Howl, who'd just been thrown out of the top 8 after Round 25, desperately needed to return to their place. For a team that'd claimed that their goal was to obtain the championship, it'd just be too embarrassing if they couldn't even make it to the playoffs. But Wind Howl's luck with their match schedule was reaching an end. After easily abusing a series of weak teams, it was finally time for them to face their demonic match schedule.

Round 26, away game against Tyranny.

Round 27, home game against Blue Rain.

Round 28, home game against 301.

Two powerhouses and a competitor for the top 8. Those who didn't have much faith left in Wind Howl were already predicting what place they'd fall to after these three rounds. Even Wind Howl themselves expressed their nervousness during team meetings. But to the outside world, they still had to maintain appearances, repeatedly expressing how their condition was improving.

And so, they faced Team Tyranny. As the two teams shook hands before the match began, Lin Jingyan stared at this unfamiliar Wind Howl and felt overcome with emotion.

When he'd left, he had already been past his prime. His condition had slipped, and he no longer had the ability to serve as the core of a team. This could be considered a normal replacement of the old with the new. But after this, Wind Howl also let go of Fang Rui and a whole host of old "officials," instead digging up new face after new face from outside.

Lin Jingyan was now already completely unfamiliar with this Wind Howl. Unfamiliar with the players, unfamiliar with their playstyles, and unfamiliar with the atmosphere this team now expressed.

Lin Jingyan didn't know what he should be feeling.

In terms of results, it was true that Wind Howl last season had done far better than it had while he'd been on the team. This season, even though they'd fallen to ninth, that was about the same score they'd had while Lin Jingyan was still there. Their team had always hovered around eighth.

From this it could be seen that these new Wind Howl players were quite strong. They'd done what the old Wind Howl had never managed to do, but the outside world viewed them as being in poor condition. Reading between the lines, this showed just how high everyone's expectations toward Wind Howl were.

Playoffs? No. The people in Wind Howl now were all hoping to charge for the championship victory. And this was a height to which Lin Jingyan had never managed to lead Wind Howl. From this point, he wasn't as strong as this new generation of Wind Howl players.

It looked like Lin Jingyan was in no position to criticize this Wind Howl. But he was somewhat saddened by this new Wind Howl.

Elite player after elite player had gathered in this team, but in the end, they had molded together into an unremarkable whole. Even now, they didn't have a mature strategic system.

"What in the world are you guys doing?"

As he shook hands with these current Wind Howl players, Lin Jingyan truly wished he could ask them all this question.

He was now gone from Wind Howl. But after so many years with them, how could his feelings disappear so quickly?

Seeing Wind Howl's fans leave the stadium early, cheering for the opposite team, Lin Jingyan could imagine just how disappointed they were. He was someone who understood these fans the best.

When he turned around and looked, in the seats reserved for the guest team fans, the audience members were sitting all scattered about. Was Wind Howl's fan group dispersing because of their disappointment?

But Wind Howl's flag was still flying as high as ever.

It was Old Lu.

Lin Jingyan saw the fan who was raising that flag high up. It was a fan who had followed Wind Howl for a whole nine years - he'd been with this team longer than any of the players currently in Wind Howl. Accurately speaking, he'd been with them even longer than Lin Jingyan had. After all, Lin Jingyan had said farewell to Wind Howl after Season 8, leaving his experience with the team capped at seven years.

He had left.

But Old Lu was still here, lifting Wind Howl's flag just like before, occasionally giving it a strong wave.

Lin Jingyan waved his hand at him, and Old Lu nodded toward him.

They'd known each other for nine years now, growing alongside Wind Howl as this team was established.

Did Old Lu still remember what the old Wind Howl was like? Lin Jingyan couldn't help but wonder.

Very soon, the first individual competition was beginning, and Lin Jingyan stood from his seat. For this match, he was the first to go on in the individual match.

The applause from the crowd now was from Tyranny's fans, but Lin Jingyan couldn't help but look toward the away team's audience section. Old Lu wasn't waving the flag right now. It looked like he was saying something to the seemingly bleak Wind Howl fans beside him.

Lin Jingyan didn't worry about it any more; this wasn't something that he should worry about. He walked steadily toward the stage, at the same time glancing at the electronic display to see who his opponent would be.

Tang Hao?

When the name was displayed, Lin Jingyan hesitated for just the barest moment.

He turned his head to look toward Wind Howl's player area, and indeed, it was Tang Hao coming onstage.

Wind Howl wasn't letting their powerful general anchor the group arena? They were sending him to the individual round?

What were they trying to do? Get a head start? The team's spirits were low, so they wanted to get everyone energized with a strong opening?

Even as Lin Jingyan made guesses, his footsteps were steady as he stepped onto the stage.

Ever since that time he'd been defeated by Tang Hao at the All-Star Weekend, Lin Jingyan had never met Tang Hao in an individual battle. Now, his skill level was likely even worse than it'd been at that All-Stars.

But…

"Would he be any more difficult to fight than Lord Grim?" Lin Jingyan said to himself.

Chapter 1318: Only Victory

As soon as he was onstage, Lin Jingyan set aside all his feelings toward Wind Howl. Right now, he was a member of Team Tyranny. No matter who his opponent was, victory was his number one priority.

He entered the match. His character loaded in and moved forward toward the center of the map. But when the Brawler Demon Subduer appeared in his field of view, Lin Jingyan couldn't help but feel a sharp pang of sadness.

Sometimes, he envied Zhang Jiale.

He had transferred to Tyranny, but at least he hadn't separated from his character.

The character belonged to the team. Lin Jingyan understood this, of course. But after seven years of partnership, he felt that he and Demon Subduer were one. The Brawler character that Tyranny had made for him, Dark Thunder, wasn't bad at all, no worse than Demon Subduer. In fact, in order to fit his style, this Dark Thunder might be more similar to the old Demon Subduer than Demon Subduer itself currently was.

But still, it wasn't the same…

It wasn't just the name. All of the feelings that had accumulated after so many years of partnership with his character, they couldn't just be transferred to a new character so easily, even if the stats were almost the same. This was perhaps something that rookies could never understand - probably they would all happily change to a stronger and more suitable character if given the chance.

In the end, this day had finally arrived.

Lin Jingyan sighed to hismelf. Ever since leaving Wind Howl, he had always wondered what it had be like if he had to face Demon Subduer one day. But before, he had only ever met his old character in the team competition, where the situation was so chaotic that the feeling wasn't particularly sharp. But now, the individual round, it was as though he and Demon Subduer were the last ones on Earth, and Lin Jingyan's feelings were tumultuous.

Demon Subduer was circling around his spawn point. It seemed that Tang Hao had guessed that Lin Jingyan would choose to move strategically, and so he was currently studying his surroundings very carefully.

Lin Jingyan watched him, and, slowly and carefully, he controlled his Dark Thunder to follow Demon Subduer's turning, finely adjusting his position.

Right there!

With Lin Jingyan's thought, Dark Thunder swept his hand and threw a Paralysis Needle.

What a simple ambush, everyone thought.

But it hit!

Even though a Paralysis Needle was silent, Tang Hao had been turning Demon Subduer's field of view the whole time. How could a top God like him make the naive mistake of leaving a blind spot?

But he hadn't discovered this Paralysis Needle, and this simple ambush actually succeeded in hitting Demon Subduer's body.

Dark Thunder jumped out from his hiding spot.

This was a map with very good weather. The sunlight shone in mottled patterns on the ground, and as Dark Thunder rushed toward Demon Subduer, the chaotic shadows swayed.

Demon Subduer couldn't move after being hit by the Paralysis Needle, and Dark Thunder tossed a handful of sand right onto his face.

After Paralysis, Blind…

Consecutive status effects. No matter how skilled Tang Hao was, in a situation like this, he couldn't withstand the attacks of an old and experienced expert like Lin Jingyan.

Lin Jingyan had calculated the duration of Blind very precisely. Right when it was about to wear off, a Brick hit Demon Subduer's head from behind.

After Blind, Dizzy.

And so a new offensive began. When he fought until he had no way of continuing, Lin Jingyan wasn't greedy. He knocked Demon Subduer over and then quickly hid himself again.

Tang Hao almost felt like he was going crazy. This series of attacks had really come out of nowhere. How had that Paralysis Needle managed to hit him? With that barrage, he had lost a fourth of his health, while his head was still filled with fog.

Poor Tang Hao lacked the multi-angle view or the replay ability of the broadcasters.

At first, the audience had also been confused as to how Tang Hao hadn't seen the needle, but Tang Hao's point of view was replayed several times, and people realized that in that moment, there truly had been no Paralysis Needle in his view.

Where had the Paralysis Needle gone?

After analysis from all different angles, the crowd finally realized what was strange.

It was the light!

It was the shadow!

It was Lin Jingyan's choice of position. When he had controlled Dark Thunder to throw the needle, it had passed through an area where the light and shadows interlaced. And so, in that instant, the needle truly seemed to vanish.

This was something that could be done in Glory?

The crowd was dumbfounded.

Using descriptors like extensive and profound to describe an online game was somewhat excessive. Even the creators of this game couldn't have thought of so many details. It was this group of pro players, those standing at the top of Glory, who were constantly digging up the subtle quirks of this game, and then finding uses for them in a match that could shock even the game's creators.

Did Tang Hao know about this sort of thing?

Seeing how off-balance Demon Subduer seemed as he flipped up from the ground, everyone felt a bit sympathetic for him. To be beaten down like this in the very first moments of a match, he must be very alarmed.

Demon Subduer moved around frantically. He couldn't figure out how he had just been hit by that needle, and so he no longer dared to let Demon Subduer to just stand waiting in one place. He leapt around the area, but he couldn't find any trace of Dark Thunder.

Playing dirty. Again, it was the dirty playstyle.

Tang Hao grit his teeth. Because Wind Howl was in a bad situation right now, the outside world had all sorts of criticism for their decision to give up on playing dirty. Tang Hao just hoped that soon, they could prove that their current style was much stronger than playing dirty. But now, on the individual battlefield, he was knocked over by dirty playing until he couldn't find north. And this person was Lin Jingyan, the former user of Demon Subduer, the old man that Tang Hao had already surpassed at that All-Stars with the "junior succeeds senior."

"Hiding and sneaking!" Tang Hao said in the chat, with some irritation. He wasn't someone who really liked chatting with the opponent during a match, as he preferred to use his fists to talk. But now, he couldn't even find his target. What frustration!

"Hiding and sneaking is another method of obtaining victory," Lin Jingyan answered.

"We'll see how long you can hide for," Tang Hao said.

"You just be more careful," Lin Jingyan replied.

Demon Subduer continued to move, turning and searching nonstop. What about Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder? Under Tang Hao's intense scrutiny, he couldn't hide too comfortably anymore. But clearly, he was extremely familiar with this map. To be able to create that incredible situation with the light earlier, did Lin Jingyan's understanding of and skill in using this map need to be mentioned?

Tang Hao searched and searched, but he couldn't find him. Lin Jingyan, however, had already finished another round of adjustments. Dark Thunder once again withdrew a Paralysis Needle, and now just waited for the right chance! Now that Tang Hao was controlling Demon Subduer to run around nonstop, it really was more difficult to find an opening.

But Lin Jingyan's view wasn't fixed on Demon Subduer's body. Instead, he was waiting for Demon Subduer to enter his field of view.

Throw!

A Paralysis Needle flew outward again. Demon Subduer's view was turning, clearly toward this direction.

But…

The entire crowd lifted their heads to look at the display screen. Even though Tang Hao's view was turned in the direction of the needle, there was a wall positioned just there. When Tang Hao glanced over, the needle was still flying behind the wall, and he couldn't see it! By the time the needle passed the wall and was in sight, Demon Subduer's view had already turned away, and then, hit…

A repeat of the match's beginning.

Tang Hao was going crazy, but what could he do? His mood had no way of dispelling the status effects his character suffered. Lin Jingyan very steadily reused the earlier series of attacks, forming a seamless combo that the opponent had absolutely no way of breaking.

Demon Subduer's health plummeted another 25%. He now had only half health remaining, while Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder had yet to be injured. Everyone watching felt as though their eyes would fall out of their heads.

Even if Wind Howl's results in the team competition were poor, their individual members were still quite strong. Tang Hao against Lin Jingyan, this conflict between old and new Brawlers had already been decided at the All-Star Weekend two years ago with the victory of the new. Everyone could see that Tang Hao's skill level was indeed above that of Lin Jingyan.

But that "skill level," in reality, only referred to technical skill. In terms of this, the old general really couldn't keep up with the new and cutting-edge. But in this battle, had Tang Hao had the opportunity to display his superior technical skill?

No. Not at all.

Both times, he had suffered a sneak attack from a Paralysis Needle. With one attack, his character was completely out of his control. What kind of technique could he display?

Using the map, Lin Jingyan could knock away half of Demon Subduer's health without losing any of his own. If this weren't happening before everyone's eyes right now, who could believe this match would play out like this?

Demon Subduer was once again knocked to the ground. But this time, when he jumped back up in a rage, he discovered that Dark Thunder hadn't vanished, but was instead right in front of him.

"How come you're not running?" Tang Hao said through clenched teeth, immediately preparing to attack. But Dark Thunder had already rushed toward him first. He hadn't run away, he had stayed here to continue launching his offensive!

"Perfect timing!" Tang Hao's spirits rose. The two unexplained ambushes earlier had made him depressed and frustrated beyond belief. But now, seeing that Lin Jingyan actually planned to fight him directly now, he grew incomparably excited.

Would a fight like this scare me?

The two Brawlers swung their fists and began a frenzied fight.

In terms of technical skill, Tang Hao was indeed superior. In this sort of direct battle, Lin Jingyan was at a disadvantage.

But in the end, the one who fell first was still Demon Subduer, and this time, he could not stand back up. His health had already reached zero.

"If I couldn't even take care of you when you were at 50% health, then I really should just retire." Lin Jingyan left this final message as he stared down at the fallen Demon Subduer. His Dark Thunder still had 17% health left.

Using 50% of his own health, Tang Hao knocked away 83%. It was powerful, it was domineering, as expected of the number one Brawler. But, he lost.

The crowd's applause was sent to Lin Jingyan.

Even though he was no longer the number one Brawler, even though he had fallen out of the All-Star rankings, even though the radiance of a God had already left him, he won.

On this arena, what fame or skill could compare to the simple truth of victory?

Only victory was the most real. What use was skill if it couldn't achieve victory?

The current Team Wind Howl included many such players with high skill. But they lacked victory, and thus they lost the faith of their supporters.

When Lin Jingyan came offstage, he looked at the audience section for the guest team fans. The seats, already somewhat empty, were quiet and still. Old Lu was holding Wind Howl's flag and just standing there…

Chapter 1319: Victory

1-0.

Tyranny took the lead in their home game.　　

This shouldn't have been anything surprising, but the one who lost was Wind Howl's current core player, Tang Hao, while the one who won had been Wind Howl's former core player, Ling Jingyan. The circumstances behind the outcome completely changed the flavor of it.

The cheers from the Tyranny fans in the stadium weren't too crazy, though. After all, the importance of this confrontation revolved around Wind Howl's past and present. The Tyranny fans weren't able to understand it. As for Wind Howl's fans? There were a few places where the away team fans sat, and right now, Wind Howl's fans looked very dispirited. The first individual round had just finished, and some of them had already gotten up and left.

Lin Jingyan returned to his seat, and his teammates congratulated him on his win. In many people's eyes, beating Tang Hao should be a joyous event.

However, Lin Jingyan didn't seem that excited. He was a gentle and polite player. He simply smiled as he sat down.

As for Wind Howl's side?

He didn't even look at them.

Even though he harbored some nostalgia for his character Demon Subduer and Wind Howl, the past was the past. He was in his declining years, but as long as there was still a path forward, there would always be a future.

His future was here… Lin Jingyan clutched Dark Thunder's account card in his hands.

Meanwhile, in another stadium, another individual round was about to be completed.

Blue Rain vs Tiny Herb.

Lu Hanwen vs Gao Yingjie.

The two most eye-catching players of the new generation, one directly being thrown into the main roster, climbing his way through the cruel competition, while the other was carefully protected, adapting to the environment step by step.

Two different methods, but both for the purpose of training the two into outstanding pro players. Right now, the two were no longer inexperienced greenhorns. The two symbols of the new generation were fighting 1 on 1 for their respective teams.

Formless Phantom Blade!

Lu Hanwen's Flowing Clouds let loose a high-level skill. Flowing Clouds was a rarely seen Greatsword Blade Master. Although his attack speed was slow, the area of effect range was greater. His Silver weapon, Flame Shadow, drew a clear arc in the air in an attempt to knock down the airborne Kind Tree.

"There's nowhere to run!" Lu Hanwen excitedly typed into the public chat. This youth seemed to have endless energy. Everyone could always feel the passion flowing through him.

In comparison, Gao Yingjie wasn't as flashy as him, but having been sheltered by the team, he had a more thorough understanding of his team's expectations for him. His thirst for victory was no less than Lu Hanwen's, and his playing on stage always appeared meticulous.

Despite being caught by Flowing Cloud's Formless Phantom Blade, Gao Yingjie wasn't flustered. Attacks from Greatsword Blade Masters were more powerful, but that was at the sacrifice of speed. Speed was the weakness of Greatsword users, and an area that could be exploited!

Disperse Powder!

Kind Tree threw a handful of Disperse Powder. It dispelled debuffs, but more importantly, it also reduced the target's attack speed. Although it was a low-level skill and its debuff effect wasn't too strong, for an already slow Flowing Clouds, it only exacerbated the wound.　

Hit!

Under the effects of Disperse Powder, Flowing Cloud's offensive instantly turned sluggish. Still, in order to land the Disperse Powder, Gao Yingjie had been prepared for Kind Tree to take a hit. But at that moment...　

Immortal Guides the Way!

Lu Hanwen cancelled Formless Phantom Blade and switched to Immortal Guides the Way.

Also a hit!

The powerful blow-away effect instantly sent Kind Tree flying. Flowing Cloud didn't give chase. Disperse Powder was difficult to handle for a Greatsword Blade Master. He had wanted to buy himself more distance, so he quickly put the effects of the skill to use.

This low-level skill with a blow-away effect had a very long ending lag, up to 10 seconds.

10 seconds!

Immortal Guides the Way didn't send the target flying far enough to take 10 seconds to return. Gao Yingjie wasn't willing to waste these 10 seconds. After being blown away, Kind Tree quick recovered as he landed, but he didn't get up after rolling. He swept up his broom and started flying through the air.

10 seconds?　　

It wouldn't even take 2 seconds for him to get back!

Frost Powder!

Another magic powder sprinkled down. This skill wasn't a direct attack though, instead it imbued his weapon with an ice element.

Morning Dew!

This was the name of the Silver broom in Kind Tree's hands. After applying Frost Powder, the broom glowed with a blue light. Fine ice crystals rained down everywhere it passed.

Attack!

Witches had strong close combat abilities.　　

Even though they mainly relied on normal attacks, through the application of magic powders and their ability to jump six times in the air with the mastery of their brooms, the "normal" attacks from Witches weren't normal in the slightest.

"You're not going to win like this!" A message from Lu Hanwen popped up in the chat.

Earthquake Sword!

Flowing Cloud's greatsword flung out a Spellblade skill. Closely following it was a flash of sword light, another Sword Draw.

A vertical Earthquake Sword and a horizontal Sword Draw, in addition to Flowing Cloud's abnormal attack range, crisscrossed into a gigantic cross as it soared towards Kind Tree. The attack came out of nowhere, and the intertwining skills complemented each other perfectly.

But...

"Attack speed…" Yu Wenzhou sighed from off stage.　

Slow… this flaw was deeply etched into Yu Wenzhou's heart. And Flowing Cloud's beautiful attack had a few openings because of his slow attack speed.

There might be openings, but could the other side seize them?

Some openings required strong perception and high skill to grasp. For example, Yu Wenzhou noticed the current openings formed by Flowing Cloud's two skills, but if he were in Kind Heart's position, he would have a very difficult time taking advantage of them.

Would Gao Yingjie be able to do it?　

No problem.

On Tiny Herb's side, Wang Jiexi quietly made this prediction when he saw this attack.

Gao Yingjie should be able to see and grasp these openings.

However, should be able to and actually doing it were two very different things.

Gao Yingjie didn't disappoint Wang Jiexi though.

Bearing the weight of Tiny Herb's future, Gao Yingjie seized the opportunity. Kind Heart swayed gently in the air, dodging the two intersecting skills.

Whoosh!

Morning Dew swung down, hitting Flowing Cloud.　

Magic powders could not be stacked, but Ice Powder's effect reduced the speed of the target and had a chance to freeze. Both effects deadly for Flowing Cloud.

Victory had been decided...

The audience could already tell.　　

Afterwards, there were sighs, and there were cheers.　　

The feelings stemming from victory always came from the two extremes.

The outcome of the battle between the two new generation stars had been decided. With Gao Yingjie's victory, Tiny Herb took the lead in their away game. On another stage, the two seniors of the old generation were still fighting it out.

Bang!

A deafening sound. 　　

The collision between weapons carried the momentum and visual effects from skills. The two characters bounced back and fell to the ground.

"How fierce! You're putting your life on the line. Aren't you afraid of breaking your hands?" Lord Grim stood back up with blood dripping from his mouth. A message leaped out into the public chat.　　

"Your record's going to end here." Another Summer of Sleep pointed his sword at Lord Grim. Sun Zheping replied ruthlessly.

"Stop talking big. Last round, Old Lin said the exact same thing. And do you know what the outcome was?" Ye Xiu said.　

"Old Lin? Didn't you guys fight Blue Rain last round?"　　

"Last last last round," Ye Xiu said.

Wild Blood Strike!

Sun Zheping ended the talk there. Another Summer of Sleep forced his way over. A bloody shadow formed around his sword and then flew towards Lord Grim.

Lord Grim immediately dodged it. The blood shadow hacked into the ground. The shattered earth suddenly shot towards Lord Grim.

Whirlwind Strike!

Another Summer of Sleep's sword released a whirlwind. The broken stones caught up in it smashed towards Lord Grim.　

This was Happy's home game and Ye Xiu's chosen map, so it was naturally a very simple one. But who would have thought that his opponent's frenzy of attacks would pressure Ye Xiu to the point of helplessness. The unspecialized blitz that no one in the Alliance could block wasn't being allowed to show up.

Retreat!

Another retreat!

Under these fierce attacks, Lord Grim continued to retreat up until he was no longer able to. Another Summer of Sleep's greatsword finally smashed into him. But in this instant, Lord Grim's body suddenly dispersed like petals. Another Summer of Sleep had only hit a fake illusion.

Shadow Clone Technique?

No, this wasn't it.

It was Shadow Steps!

Four Lord Grims surrounded Another Summer of Sleep. Which one was the real one? At this point, it didn't seem to matter. What was most important was that Lord Grim could finally start attacking.

In the end, victory went to Ye Xiu.　

The moment he took his hands off the mouse, he let out a long sigh of relief. This match had been too close for comfort. He had nearly lost. It was really hard to imagine how an opponent with a hand injury as serious as Sun Zheping fought more and more without regard for anything else. Had the second half of the season ignited his spirit?

But it was truly a pity. Every round, he could only fight a single time in the individual competition. Sometimes, he even needed to rest one round. The amount of competition he got every time probably wasn't enough to satisfy him at all.

Yeah...

Not enough at all!　

Sun Zheping stared at the fallen Another Summer of Sleep, who was looking up into the sky. His character probably wasn't willing either!

If only… if only I could play a few more minutes every time...

Chapter 1320: A New Point to Pick At

The curtains closed on Round 26.

Happy won against Heavenly Swords 9-1. Although their relationship was good, it didn't affect Happy's ruthlessness on stage.

Blue Rain versus Tiny Herb. The away team Tiny Herb utilized their strong momentum from Gao Yingjie beating Lu Hanwen, winning the following two individual competition rounds and the group arena. They went into the team competition With a 5-0 lead. However, in the end, the home team Blue Rain won and the round ended with a 5-5 tie.

Wind Howl versus Tyranny. Tang Hao losing to Lin Jingyan was undoubtedly the highlight of the match. However, they were still able to win 2 points, ending the round 2-8.

This sort of outcome did little to help their placements on the rankings. Team 301 beat Parade 8-2. Hundred Blossoms beat Bright Green 10-0. The distance between Wind Howl and the top eight was growing wider and wider, and in their next round, Wind Howl would be facing Blue Rain.

Wind Howl had the home game advantage, but the community did not think highly of their chances. In their eyes, Wind Howl was becoming more and more lackluster. Would they be able to win back their reputation? Everyone was already numb to this question, though, so not many people paid any attention to them. 　　

Round 27. The highlight match was the home Team Tiny Herb welcoming the challengers Team Happy.

After several rounds during the second half of the season, the Happy haters finally found a point to pick at.　

In the second half of the season, the teams played in the first half of the season would play again but with the home and away teams switched. Happy had started the first half of the season poorly, and while the second half of the season was a large improvement, it couldn't compare to their previous win streak. These haters compared the results from both halves of the season and quickly found the teams that had won against Happy in both their home and away games.

Samsara, Blue Rain, Tyranny...

These three teams had won in a dominating fashion twice.　　

As a result, an article titled "What Looks to Be Beautiful" was published in the Esports Time. The author was the Esports Time writer Ruan Cheng, who had been attacking Happy ever since Tang Rou's 1v3 challenge.

In the article, Ruan Cheng detailed the relationship between Happy's ups and downs and their season schedule. In the first half of the season, Happy had met many strong teams at the beginning, so their first few steps had been difficult. But after passing through this bump, Happy started finding their confidence through Beating weak teams. But this sort of confidence could not last. Because of the competitive format, where each team played the other twice, Happy once again faced these unbeatable opponents. And this time, whether it was home or away game, Happy still wouldn't beat these opponents.

"Those who hold hopes for Happy should give up," Ruan Chen wrote at the end of the article, "This team is not able to reach the top. If you think they can win the championships, you might as well just buy a lottery ticket. Being able to make the playoffs would be a joke with their strength. And in the latter half of the season, teams will muster everything they have to make it through the door to playoffs. If Happy falls behind, no need to feel disappointed. Relying on luck to make it to the end of the season is impossible."

"This Ruan Cheng is always out to get us!" Reading the Esports Time, Chen Guo suddenly shouted furiously.

"If you know, then why do you still buy the Esports Time!" Ye Xiu laughed at her.

"..."

Chen Guo was speechless. Why did she pick up an issue? Wasn't it because she was still hoping to prove these haters wrong with their outstanding performance? And the result? Nothing. Instead, any time Happy messed up even the tiniest bit, those guys would target it and talk about it endlessly. This time, they had actually labelled Happy as a fake powerhouse just because they had been double killed by a few top teams.

Shouldn't this label be given to Wind Howl! Why was it given to Happy instead? Chen Guo was absolutely furious.

"Don't be angry with these people. No matter what we achieve, as long as someone wants to paint us black, they'll always be able to find something to pick at," Ye Xiu said.

"Wind Howl went from a top team to their current stage, but he didn't say a single word about them. He's completely fixated on us," Chen Guo said.

　

"Next match, he'll probably be even more heated," Ye Xiu said.

　

Round 27, Happy would be challenging Tiny Herb. In Round 8, Happy lost to Tiny Herb 2-8, and Tang Rou had failed to keep her 1v3 promise, destroying her image at the end of the round. It was at this point that Ruan Cheng had started walking the hateful path towards Happy.

　

Right now, the league had cycled back. Happy would be facing Tiny Herb in an away game. This time, the match would be even more difficult. Ruan Cheng probably had an article written already and ready to be published. If Happy lost again, Tiny Herb would become another team that had double killed them. There would be even more proof that Happy really was just a fake powerhouse. Who knew how much ridicule would come their way? 　

Chen Guo was suddenly deeply worried.

Do like Ye Xiu said and just ignore these haters? Chen Guo just couldn't do it. Even if they couldn't persuade them to switch sides through action, Chen Guo hoped to at least give them a hard slap in the face. The problem was that they would be facing a top team like Tiny Herb in an away game. Saying something like "you have to win" would be unreasonable and put too much pressure on the team.

"In short, we just have to try our best," Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo sighed. She really envied Ye Xiu's calmness.

Sure enough, Ruan Cheng was very excited about Round 27 to an unprecedented extent too. This time, he had actually received an invitation to the TV station to be a guest, commentating the match together with Li Yibo. The highlight match chosen to be broadcast was Happy versus Tiny Herb.

　

"This time, we have a new face for our broadcast, however, I don't think anyone is a stranger to him. Please welcome Esports Time's special column reviewer Ruan Cheng! I'm sure many of you viewers out there have read an article by Teacher Ruan, especially the latest issue of Esports Time. Teacher Ruan's 'What Looks to Be Beautiful' had a loud reaction! Teacher Ruan has always had a different viewpoint towards Team Happy. I figured that Teacher Ruan would definitely be paying particular attention to the match today, so I invited him to the broadcast to discuss this match together with us. Thank you Teacher Ruan for coming today," Pan Lin introduced today's guest before the match officially began.

"Haha, you're welcome. Hello Pan Lin, hello Coach Li," Ruan Cheng greeted Pan Lin and Li Yibo confidently.

"Should we start off by listening to Teacher Ruan's thoughts on today's match?" Pan Lin asked.

　

"Haha, I still stand by the viewpoint I detailed before in the past. There is still quite a gap between Team Happy and the top teams. And today, Happy is facing a top team like Tiny Herb, who also has the home game advantage. I think the chances of Tiny Herb winning should be very high," Ruan Cheng didn't mind predicting the outcome of the match. Compared to the cautious Li Yibo, it was truly too big of a difference.

"Gotcha. What about you Coach Li? What are your thoughts? You seem to think highly of Happy these days," Pan Lin didn't forget about his old partner Coach Li just because they had a new invited guest today.

"Haha, Happy is a new team, so their potential is huge. In the past half season, their growth has been very obvious. I think that this team has a chance at beating anyone, so I wouldn't be too surprised if they won or lost," Li Yibo's remarks were still as sly as ever. However, compared to Ruan Cheng's clear-cut position, his evasiveness seemed to show that he still stood by Happy.

"Okay, we've heard the opinions of our two guests. Let's take a look at the stage. The two teams have entered the venue," Pan Lin said.

The camera cut to the stadium. The players on both teams were waving their hands to the crowd as they walked in.

"I wonder who Tiny Herb will be sending out first." Pan Lin asked. What he was really asking was, who would be fighting Ye Xiu today? Would Ye Xiu's winning streak finally end here?

"Most teams put their best players into the group arena to win those 2 points. Figuring out who will be playing in the individual competition truly isn't an easy matter," Ruan Cheng sighed, but the implications within his words were clear. He was saying that Ye Xiu was only able to reach his win streak because Happy's opponents rarely placed their core players in the individual competitions.

If he had said these words a few rounds ago, the reasoning would still hold up. But right now, Ye Xiu had won 26 matches in a row, an incredible achievement. Even if he had never encountered a top God, just being able to win 26 matches in a row was an achievement that seemed possible only by pro players competing in the online game's arena. The difference in skill between pro players wasn't so large that anyone could be casually beaten. Those top Gods had stumbled against countless non-Gods, but Ye Xiu had never faltered in 26 matches. Indeed, not meeting any top Gods was a reason, but using it to try and persuade people was purely for the purpose of denouncing him.

Ruan Cheng seemed to also know that focusing on this topic wasn't reasonable, so he stayed within the appropriate boundaries and didn't directly say these implications out loud. He simply mentioned it in the passing.

"Okay, the players on both teams are coming down from the stage. Ha, Ye Xiu is just staying there. The big screen hasn't even released the lineups yet!" Pan Lin said.

"Let's see who Tiny Herb will send up," Li Yibo said plainly.

Xu Bin!

Finally, the two players competing in the first round of the individual competition were displayed on the screen. Happy had sent Ye Xiu. Tiny Herb had sent Xu Bin and his Knight character Angelica.

"It's Xu Bin. What are your thoughts on this arrangement?" Pan Lin asked.　　

"Ye Xiu's unspecialized plays fast, but the Grind King Xu Bin made his name through his ability to slow down the pace. This matchup will depend on who is better at controlling the pace. Whichever side is able to drag the other into their pace will have a better chance at winning," Li Yibo said.

"It sounds like it'll be a very interesting match. What are your thoughts, Teacher Ruan?" Pan Lin said.　

"Yes…" Ruan Cheng simply replied with a nod. Even though he really wanted to hate on Happy, he didn't like to be slapped in the face either. Ye Xiu had already won 26 matches in a row. He didn't dare casually favor Ye Xiu's opponent.

Chapter 1321: Flash Past That Shield

A 26 round win streak was crazy.

When that win streak would end was undoubtedly on everyone's mind. The outstanding player who could break that win streak would look extremely amazing too. As a result, as long as it was Happy's away game, the home crowd would always hold high expectations for their home team, hoping that they would be the ones to end this legendary record.

Tiny Herb's fans were no exception. After Xu Bin's name showed up on the big screen, the crowd immediately let out wild cheers. It was truly rare to have such excitement for the individual competition. The excitement was all because of Ye Xiu and that ridiculous win streak of his.

Amidst the cheers, Xu Bin stood up and walked onto the stage. On the other side, his opponent Ye Xiu had already entered his player booth.　　

The home team Tiny Herb held the right to choose the map, and they naturally wouldn't give Ye Xiu the simple maps that he liked.

Corrupt Flower Garden.

Flowers, plants, rock gardens, fountains, pavilions, and winding corridors, a map with plenty of substance. Tiny Herb had chosen this map to counter Ye Xiu's playstyle.

The match began, and the two characters spawned.

Having chosen this map, Xu Bin had a strategic opening planned out. Xu Bin had Angelica take a roundabout route along the left path. He borrowed the rocks in the rock garden as footing and jumped a few times onto the top of a pavilion.

The map wasn't very large. This high point allowed him to oversee the entire map. Xu Bin looked around and easily found Lord Grim's whereabouts. It looked like Ye Xiu didn't mind playing tactics on this map with his opponent. Lord Grim was also taking a roundabout path at the opposite end of the map. When Xu Bin located him, Ye Xiu also noticed Angelica on top of a pavilion.

The two sides had both found each other, making their next moves more difficult to figure out. Xu Bin had Angelica continue standing on top of the pavilion and observed Ye Xiu's movements. Then, he saw Ye Xiu have Lord Grim run towards him.

We're just going to end up fighting like this?

Wouldn't that mean their strategic movements had been for nothing? Neither player would hold any advantage.

In the broadcast room, the caster and two commentators were starting to discuss this question.

"Xu Bin holds the initiative. There's no way he didn't think that his actions would also expose himself. Perhaps that was even his goal," Ruan Cheng expressed.

"Lord Grim is closing in. Right now, Angelica is already in Lord Grim's attack range. It's just that Lord Grim hasn't started attacking yet," Pan Lin said.

Lord Grim rushed towards Angelica, but Angelica just stood there and didn't run. Lord Grim wasn't just charging in blindly. He suddenly stopped. And at that instant, Angelica's feet had started shifting slightly. But after he saw Lord Grim stop, he also stopped.

"This distance…" The three in the broadcast room began analyzing Lord Grim's sudden halt.

"He's outside the range of a Knight's Heroic Leap," The three looked over the two characters' skills and quickly came to that conclusion.

"Oh? Heroic Leap is that much of a threat?" Pan Lin said.

"For a player who can seize opportunities, it's quite a threat," Ruan Cheng said.

"However, Ye Xiu seems to have noticed this point," Li Yibo said.

"The two really aren't budging an inch!" Pan Lin sighed. At this moment, Lord Grim stood just outside of Angelica's maximum range and confidently started casting a spell.

Angelica still didn't move.　　

This distance wasn't too close for a magic spell, and Xu Bin figured he would have time to react when the spell came out.

Blizzard!

Lord Grim casted a Blizzard. Hail and snowflakes crashed down.

Angelica stepped to the side and dodged it. He wouldn't be hit by this sort of skill.

Lord Grim casted two more spells, a magic one and a curse. Xu Bin simply had Angelica dodge them without any intentions of counter attacking.

"Xu Bin is starting his grind…" Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin had a headache. Xu Bin's slow grind was difficult to cast. He was just dodging Lord Grim's low-threat spells right now, but no one knew what his purpose was.

"You're not planning on coming down?" Ye Xiu spoke.

"There's no rush," Xu Bin replied.

"Then I'll come up?" Ye Xiu said.

"Sure!" Xu Bin happily accepted.

As a result, Lord Grim opened up his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. The umbrella's ribs flipped outwards and started whirring. Lord Grim floated up with a Rotor Wings.

Fly!

Lord Grim suddenly rose to the skies. Ye Xiu watched Angelica's movements closely.　

He moved!

Ye Xiu said he would come up, and he really did, but suddenly, Angelica came down.

Heroic Leap!

Xu Bin had Angelica use Heroic Leap. As Angelica jumped up, he slashed down with his knight sword. However, there was still some distance between him and Lord Grim! Ye Xiu was using Rotor Wings, and he wasn't going to crash into the attack.

Angelica crashed to the ground. The shockwaves from Heroic Leap carried a force that flattened the surroundings.

Angelica suddenly waved his hands towards Lord Grim, Taunt!

Lord Grim wasn't able to control himself and headed straight for Angelica. However, he had already let out an attack. Taunt didn't stop the target from attacking.

Angelica lifted his left hand. The Sighing Wall, the sturdiest shield in all of Glory, welcomed Lord Grim's incoming attack.

"Defend to attack!" Ruan Cheng said.

"Defense is the offense!" Li Yibo remarked.

Having been Taunted, Lord Grim didn't seem to have any choices. He could only crash into the shield.　

Shields didn't fear attacks. After blocking Lord Grim, Angelica could immediately counterattack. 　　

Chance!

Countless people shouted.　

But Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella also opened.

Shield versus shield.

Suddenly, everyone was uncertain.　　

Shield against shield. Neither side would take much damage, and the advantage of attacking after shielding no longer belonged to just Xu Bin. Everything had been reset to zero.

The two shields crashed against each other. Lord Grim had come from the air, so he had plenty of momentum. But in terms of shield strength, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was just a light shield. It couldn't compare at all to Glory's number one shield, Sighing Wall!

Shield Attack!　　

Angelica also used an attack.　　

The umbrella shield was no match. Lord Grim crashed into the shield and hung in the air, but then he immediately poofed into a cloud of smoke.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Angelica only hit a fake clone. The real body had flashed past the shield and was now in front of Angelica.

Ye Xiu didn't care about the control effects of Taunt. He actually wanted to get closer to the target. As a result, he just took advantage of Angelica Taunting him.

Falling Light Blade!

The sword was placed besides his feet, falling directly onto Angelica. The attack forced him back.

However, the knockdown from Falling Light Blade wasn't enforced. It could be teched with a Quick Recover.　　

However, Xu Bin unexpectedly did not Quick Recover and just fell to the ground.　　

"Beautiful! What precise judgement!" Ruan Cheng sighed. After Lord Grim's Falling Light Blade, a Sword Draw followed. If Angelica had Quick Recovered, the Sword Draw would have perfectly hit him. Who would have thought that Angelica would just fall like a corpse. The sword light from the Sword Draw brushed past him. After dodging the attack, Angelica immediately rolled to the side, his shield in front of him.

"Too slow!" Li Yibo shouted. Xu Bin's judgement had been accurate, but his reaction had been a tad slow. Even with the shield protecting him, Ye Xiu still held the initiative! After rolling to the side, Xu Bin should have immediately counter attacked.

But Lord Grim didn't seize this opportunity to attack.

A cold light streaked across Angelica's Sighing Wall.

"He activated Maelstrom Counterattack!" Li Yibo suddenly understood. No wonder he didn't counter attack. No wonder Lord Grim didn't continue attacking.　

Angelica had activated Maelstrom Attack, which reflected all incoming attacks back to the opponent.

"Slow has always been Xu Bin's strength!" Ruan Cheng smiled.

Li Yibo felt his face turn red. He couldn't dispute that. Xu Bin's previous two responses had displayed his slow characteristic.

"Ye Xiu's offense has been interrupted," Pan Lin noted.

"Correct. By not Quick Recovering and then activating Maelstrom Counterattack, he's forced the pace to slow down. Ye Xiu couldn't even start his offense before being pressed down!" Ruan Cheng said. He was overjoyed at Happy with the disadvantage. However, he couldn't go overboard on the surface! Even though he had showed his bias, he had to display calmness. He couldn't be like "Haha, it turns out you couldn't do it". Instead, it should be "Haha, I knew you couldn't do it."

"Is that so?" Li Yibo suddenly chuckled.

The Lord Grim in front of Angelica suddenly disappeared!

No, not disappear. To be more precise, he had disappeared from Angelica's view. Lord Grim flickered and hid using Angelica's Sighing Wall as cover.

Xu Bin hastily lowered Angelica's Sighing Wall, but he still couldn't see Lord Grim. Lord Grim had crouched down along with his shield's movements.

Xu Bin had Sighing Wall move horizontally, but in that instant, Lord Grim flashed in the opposite direction of Sighing Wall's movement.

Movement skill!

"He's passed!" Pan Lin shouted.

Lord Grim circled behind Sighing Wall and started sending attacks towards Angelica.　

"Lord Grim juked Sighing Wall like a football player," Pan Lin called out.

"Haha, Little Pan, that's an interesting comparison. According to you, Lord Grim hiding using the shield and crouching were all feints?" Li Yibo laughed.

"Haha, that's an interesting way to put it," Pan Lin praised back.

The two old partners commentated excitedly. On the other hand, Ruan Cheng was feeling gloomy.

Even though he hadn't dared to favor Ye Xiu's opponent in this match, he had truly hoped someone could bring down this record. Happy having such a show-off achivement was truly annoying.　

But it's probably not going to be this one... 　　

After Lord Grim flashed past Sighing Wall, Angelica was now completely exposed in front of Lord Grim. The unspecialized blitz began. Countless skills poured down on him, and Sighing Wall was unable to protect him.

"This situation… it looks like even Xu Bin isn't able to slow it down…" Pan Lin said.

"He can't." Li Yibo didn't speak at first. He saw as Angelica tried to slow things down, but Lord Grim used a movement skill to directly move behind the attack and then dealt the final blow.

The win streak continued.

Chapter 1322: Together on the Battlefield for the First Time

1-0!

26 consecutive victories.

Ye Xiu's record, still yet to be broken, reached a new high. Pan Lin and Li Yibo relished in the feeling as they discussed. To the side, Ruan Cheng chuckled along once or twice, in a sour mood.

The second battle of the individual round.

Happy, Qiao Yifan, One Inch Ash.

Tiny Herb, Gao Yingjie, Kind Tree.

When the screen displayed the names of the next two players, these players preparing to go onstage were both stunned, and each instinctively turned to look toward the opposing team's player area.

In Team Tiny Herb, they had been the closest of partners. But one was in the sky, and one remained on the ground.

Qiao Yifan had always looked up to Gao Yingjie, admiring his talent, envying the attention and hope he received from the team. In comparison, Qiao Yifan had never been clear what kind of player he himself would turn out to be.

Gao Yingjie had always known Qiao Yifan's situation, and he very much wanted to help him, but he didn't know how. When the team announced that the team was letting go of Qiao Yifan, Gao Yingjie mustered his courage to find Captain Wang Jiexi, but the answer he received was "the team doesn't need him."

The answer was somewhat cold, but very honest. Gao Yingjie understood that this wasn't a game of house. The team didn't need him: there was no reason better than this. In Tiny Herb, the team was everything. If the team didn't have the need, then even someone with hundreds of talents and thousands of skills wouldn't have any reason to remain. Even Wang Jiexi, with all his strength, had to change his own style for the sake of his team. What player had the right to place themself above the team?

And so, this pair of good friends went their separate ways, each taking their own road to Glory.

In the next season, Gao Yingjie became part of Tiny Herb's main force and was voted into the All-Stars. His stardom was immeasurable.

Qiao Yifan, meanwhile, joined Happy, this Internet cafe team and charged through the obstacles of the Challenger League.

They both paid attention to the other's performance, noticed the other's growth, and felt joy when the other achieved results.

In the end, Happy won the the Challenger League and made it to the Professional Alliance. They once again met. But this time, they were no longer teammates, but opponents.

In Round 8, Happy played their home game against Tiny Herb. Qiao Yifan had played in the individual competition against Tiny Herb's Ghostblade player Zhou Yebai. He'd won that match and proved himself, and with his new technique, he'd earned a lot of attention.

Gao Yingjie's feelings were complicated. On one hand, he was extremely happy to see Qiao Yifan's current strength, but on the other, Qiao Yifan was now an opponent, and his success had brought failure to Tiny Herb.

And now, they themselves were about to decide who would win and who would lose.

After they shared a glance, the two of them turned away, each taking firm steps onto the stage.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were also introducing these two with great interest.

"Qiao Yifan is a former player of Tiny Herb, entering the team at the same time as Gao Yingjie. I heard their relationship at the time was very good," Pan Lin said.

"Compared to Gao Yingjie's, Qiao Yifan's professional career has been much bumpier. In only three years, he's probably tasted warmth and coldness that many people haven't. A benchwarmer, eventually let go, joining the Internet cafe team Happy when he had nowhere else to go, taking on the Challenger League, then returning to the Pro Alliance, and it looks like he might even make it into the playoffs. Who knows, maybe he'll even play in the finals!" Li Yibo said.

"Haha, I agree with everything else, but maybe his luck was joining the internet cafe team Happy when he had nowhere else to go!" Pan Lin said.

"Ha, who would have thought that this Internet cafe team could get results like this?" Li Yibo laughed.

"Ahaha…" Ruan Cheng continued to laugh dryly to the side. Happy's current 1-0 lead prevented him from expressing his opinions. He was looking forward to Happy losing a match quickly, so that he could talk about the reasons why Happy wasn't a good team.

Qiao Yifan, Gao Yingjie, Ruan Cheng felt that his chance was here. Gao Yingjie had always been called a prodigy, and now he was already an All-Star-level player. And Qiao Yifan? A player that had been let go by Tiny Herb, he'd found a position for himself with his own strength, but the natural difference between him and Gao Yingjie perhaps couldn't be closed by just hard work. After all, the prodigy Gao Yingjie had also been working hard all this time.

The match began, and the two characters loaded in on opposite corners of the map.

"We finally have the chance to stand on stage together." A message soon appeared in the match chat. The first to speak was Gao Yingjie.

"Yes," Qiao Yifan answered. The last time their teams had fought, both of them had appeared in the individual competition, but they'd missed each other. In the team competition after, Qiao Yifan hadn't been on the roster. This was indeed the first time the two of them had met onstage.

"But it's a shame, we're standing as opponents now," Gao Yingjie said. Before, when Qiao Yifan had still been part of Tiny Herb, these two friends often talked about how they'd coordinate if they were ever onstage together, and they'd even done quite a bit of practice for it. But because Qiao Yifan never had the chance to appear onstage, the two had never been able to partner during an official match. And today, the two finally stood together onstage, but unfortunately people changed, and the combinations they'd practiced could no longer be used. The two were now opponents. Only one would be allowed to remain standing here.

"Good luck, go all out," Qiao Yifan said.

"I will," Gao Yingjie said solemnly. He was no longer that timid youth from before. His two hands controlled the keyboard and mouse without hesitation, and Kind Tree rushed forward.

Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had already advanced as well. This map choice leaned toward Ye Xiu's preferences - it didn't have too many complex features.

Soon, the two sides appeared in each other's views. In this situation where there was no cover and they were meeting directly, a Phantom Demon couldn't let the opponent get too close. Setting Ghost Boundaries required casting, and if someone was fighting them at close range there would be no time to cast. The power of the Ghostblade would shrink at least 70%.

Of course Gao Yingjie would know this piece of Glory common sense. As soon as he spotted One Inch Ash, he was already preparing to attack. A Phantom Demon prevented the opponent from closing in by using Ghost Boundaries, but a Witch had mid-range attacks, and to a certain extent could disrupt the opponent's casting.

But…

"So early?" Commentator Pan Lin shouted.

At this moment, although both sides had appeared in each other's view, they were still far from from being within attack range. But Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had already stopped moving forward and begun the casting for Ghost Boundaries.

"Isn't he being a bit too careful?" Pan Lin said.

By now, the casting was complete. Kind Tree was still relatively far away, so of course he wasn't affected. One Inch Ash had cast a Dark Boundary, which would put a Blind effect with 100% probability on anyone who entered it. This boundary wasn't placed at the limit of One Inch Ash's range, but slightly closer to himself. Once he set this boundary, One Inch Ash continued to charge forward.

In the blink of an eye, he had taken a few more steps, but then he stopped again and once again began to summon a Ghost Boundary.

"Whoa!" When Li Yibo saw how Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree had to circle around the Dark Boundary, he suddenly understood the meaning behind Qiao Yifan's placing the Ghost Boundary early.

Even though a Witch could ride a broom to fly, a Ghost Boundary's effects extended to the air above it. The area covered by this Dark Boundary instantly became a forbidden zone. By setting one here, Kind Tree was forced to go around, which increased the distance he needed to travel. And at this moment, One Inch Ash set his second Ghost Boundary.

Ice Boundary!

Another Ghost Boundary blocked Kind Tree's way. This new boundary bordered the edge of the Dark Boundary. There was no overlap, so the total area that these two boundaries could restrict was maximized.

Was the third Ghost Boundary on its way as well?

Seeing One Inch Ash's begin the movements of another cast, Kind Tree swept his sleeve and sent stars flying out.

Star Ray!

The stars became a ray of light shooting toward One Inch Ash, who dodged to the side. At last, his third Ghost Boundary summon was interrupted.

Lightning Chain!

Kind Tree once again waved his hand in the air, and a chain of flashing lightning fell towards One Inch Ash. Many of a Witch's skills used all sorts of strange magic items, and so most skills didn't have cast times. This was a big advantage for this class, and it was for this reason that Wang Jiexi could have his fast-paced, volatile, illusory Magician style. Gao Yingjie hadn't copied Wang Jiexi's style, but he took advantage of this speciality of the Witch class.

Two magic items in a row, both mid-range attacks, prevented One Inch Ash from finding the time to cast boundaries. Kind Tree, attacking and running at the same time, was already almost past the boundaries. But One Inch Ash wasn't just waiting where he stood, either. As he dodged these attacks, he was also changing position, and as Kind Tree circled around counterclockwise, One Inch Ash headed counterclockwise as well. The Ghost Boundary between them prevented Kind Tree from rushing toward him directly.

But a Ghost Boundary had a set duration, it couldn't last forever. Gao Yingjie paid close attention to One Inch Ash's movements - he couldn't let him have another chance to cast. But the issue was, even though Witches had the great advantage of not having to cast, they were also limited in range with their attacks from magic items.

One Inch Ash suddenly jumped back a few steps. As soon as Gao Yingjie saw this, he knew that he had retreated out of Kind Tree's attack range. And then, he calmly began another cast.

Yet another Ghost Boundary appeared in front of Kind Tree. Helpless, Gao Yingjie could only control his character to stop in his tracks.

Silence Boundary.

A character within this boundary would have all of their skills sealed. This effect was undoubtedly deadly in a high-level professional match. Kind Tree was again forced to go around the boundary.

"Qiao Yifan's control is excellent, but if he's playing like this, he's putting himself on the defensive side from the start!" Ruan Cheng finally found the opportunity to give some critique, and of course as soon as he opened his mouth he pointed out Happy's shortcomings.

"Hm, he might first want to establish the balance of the match, and then find an opportunity? Otherwise, how would he fight? If Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree directly got into close range, then he'd lose this match immediately! The current situation is pretty good. Given the characteristics of these two classes, it's not a surprise that the Phantom Demon is more on the defensive, no?"

"So that's to say, the plan of putting the Phantom Demon in the individual round is a bit hard to understand!" Ruan Cheng said.

Li Yibo was speechless. At this point, he was just using whatever he could find to criticize Happy! Everyone in Glory knew that Ruan Cheng was a stubborn Happy hater.

Chapter 1323: A Taste of Victory that Can’t Be Shared

It was true that a Phantom Demon had greater use in the team competition, but using that to say that their 1v1 strength was weak was just nonsense. Perhaps many ordinary players would think this way, but that was only because it was harder to play Phantom Demon in a 1v1. Also, the map that Tiny Herb had chosen for this individual battle wasn't good for a Phantom Demon to reach full potential.

Yet even under these conditions, Qiao Yifan was still able to place his Ghost Boundaries very well, preventing Gao Yingjie from launching effective attacks. This was something that should be acknowledged with certainty. To emphasize losing the initiative, that was very much nitpicking.

Ruan Cheng of course knew all of this, but right now, he was going to point out Happy's flaws no matter what. In his opinion, the chances of Happy winning this match were very low.

A skill level that couldn't compete with the opposing talent.

The difficulty of playing Phantom Demon in a 1v1.

The map disadvantages.

With so many weaknesses, how could Happy not lose?

Qiao Yifan's performance right now was much stronger than Ruan Cheng had anticipated. But just to maintain the balance of the situation, Qiao Yifan had already sacrificed a lot. And Gao Yingjie? He was merely saving his strength and biding his time. As soon as Qiao Yifan left an opening, he would instantly launch a powerful offensive.

Hurry, hurry and make a mistake!

Ruan Cheng shouted in his heart.

But as he shouted, he watched as the Ghost Boundaries bloomed on the battlefield, like an endless river blocking the way between One Inch Ash and Kind Tree.

Ruan Cheng was beginning to pale.

Saving strength and biding time?

Things weren't that simple. In order to force Qiao Yifan to move so carefully and meticulously, Gao Yingjie couldn't be careless with his own movements either. He too needed to make decisions and plays with care and precision.

Kind Tree's positioning, Kind Tree's long-range attacks, they were all trying to break Qiao Yifan's rhythm. Even though Qiao Yifan was on the defensive, he used his defense to attack. The rhythm of this battle was firmly in his control.

"I've always thought that Happy's Qiao Yifan is a player that has been underestimated," Li Yibo exclaimed.

"But if he just continues to defend like this, will he be able to win this match?" Pan Lin brought up the key question. Even though Qiao Yifan could use his defense offensively, controlling the battle tempo, his One Inch Ash hadn't used any attacks at all. There was no way he could win this match if he continued like this.

Li Yibo furrowed his brow. Qiao Yifan himself must realize this issue, right? But he was still working hard to maintain this current situation. What was his plan?

At this moment, Ruan Cheng suddenly shouted, "A mistake!"

For Ruan Cheng to become this excited, of course it was a mistake from Qiao Yifan. Because he was just a hair slower in setting them this time, there was a gap in the seamlessly linked Ghost Boundaries, and Gao Yingjie immediately seized this opening. Before the Ghost Boundaries could block him, Kind Tree called forth a Tornado and flew close to the ground toward One Inch Ash.

"Just like I said! Qiao Yifan's defensive strategy here isn't a method of victory! As soon as there's a slight opening, Gao Yingjie can seize it immediately," Ruan Cheng said gleefully, flapping his mouth without end. Pan Lin and Li Yibo felt sympathy for Qiao Yifan, but because Ruan Cheng wasn't without reason, they couldn't just begin arguing with him on air.

Kind Tree traversed the blockade of Ghost Boundaries, a handful of Frost Powder already scattered on his weapon. One Inch Ash, however, was rolling to the side.

This was a very simple map without many features, but it still had some. One Inch Ash's roll took him behind a crumbling stone pillar, and when he crouched down, the boulder shielded his entire body.

This is-

Gao Yingjie's heart jumped. After Qiao Yifan used the map features for cover, he instantly noticed something about this surrounding region.

Something's wrong!

Gao Yingjie immediately controlled Kind Tree to throw a Lava Flask.

The flask shattered against the ground, and the lava within burst forth to cover the area, including the area where One Inch Ash was hiding.

But just before the lava reached One Inch Ash, swordlight flashed from behind the pillar and a Ghost Boundary landed first.

As expected.

Seeing the Ghost Boundary land, Gao Yingjie didn't even need to think before controlling Kind Tree to rush in a specific direction.

"Beautiful!" Li Yibo shouted, but this shout wasn't praising Gao Yingjie's smart reaction. When that Ghost Boundary appeared, the situation on the battlefield suddenly became clear. One Inch Ash's earlier setup, along with this Ghost Boundary just now, was squeezing Kind Tree into a small area.

That Ghost Boundary that had been thought to be a blunder absolutely wasn't one. That had been bait! Qiao Yifan had seen that there was cover here and knew that he had the chance to cast a Ghost Boundary.

Gao Yingjie must have realized this after coming over from far away and seeing One Inch Ash's actions. But unfortunately, Kind Tree's Lava Flask had arrived just a bit too late. The Ghost Boundary landed first. Helpless, Gao Yingjie could only control Kind Tree to go to the position where Qiao Yifan wanted him. The damage that this Lava Flask caused One Inch Ash now was negligible.

Li Yibo glanced at Ruan Cheng and felt delighted.

Faceslapping, what familiar faceslapping! But before, the one who had been hit over and over was himself. Today, it was finally someone else's turn. With this guy here as contrast, Li Yibo could appear extremely wise and insightful even if he said nothing. Initially, Li Yibo had been rather irritated at this extra invited guest commentator, but now, he was glad that Ruan Cheng was here, setting off all these traps so that Li Yibo didn't have to take any damage.

Ruan Cheng's expression was extremely ugly right now, but the battle still hadn't ended. What would happen next? Li Yibo and Ruan Cheng were both experts, and so now that the battle had reached this point, both could tell what was the crucial point. Now, Qiao Yifan needed to cast one more Ghost Boundary to completely trap Kind Tree within. But he was currently in the middle of an expanse of lava, and the sustained damage was preventing him from casting. If he tried to face Kind Tree directly, he would also be interrupted for sure.

Cover. One Inch Ash still needed some cover. And so everyone's gazes swept around these ruins, to another worn down pillar that was eight units away from One Inch Ash's current position.

"Qiao Yifan must have studied and prepared all this beforehand. He's really extremely thorough with his planning," Pan Lin said, when the television broadcast focused in on this critical position.

"His earlier usage of Ghost Boundaries to maintain the balance of the situation was probably to buy time so he could look for an area on the map where he could develop his strategy. This map definitely isn't an easy one for him," Li Yibo said neutrally. He then prompted Ruan Cheng with a look that said "what do you think?"

Ruan Cheng cursed in his heart. Li Yibo's words just now were basically faceslapping him!

"Seeing how Gao Yingjie so decisively avoided the Ghost Boundary, I think he's already seen through Qiao Yifan's strategy. Eight units.. Will Gao Yingjie give him that opportunity?" Ruan Cheng still lifted up Gao Yingjie.

As the three of them were discussing, One Inch Ash suddenly rushed out, targeting that pillar that stood eight body-lengths away.

But Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree was a step faster. He threw a floating blue cloud of something toward that broken pillar, and very quickly, dark clouds formed above the pillar and thin shards of blue rain drops emitting a cold energy began raining down.

Hail!

Gao Yingjie wasn't going to compete with One Inch Ash in a footrace, nor did he want to try and take him head-on. He just tossed out this skill. The pillar could still serve as cover, but because the Hail would cause sustained damage, One Inch Ash could no longer duck behind it and cast. But to everyone's surprise, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash only took three steps in that direction. Before those blue raindrops had even hit the ground, he had already turned back the way he came.

One Inch Ash actually returned to the pillar he'd been hiding behind earlier. The lava was right under his feet, but no skill's effects lasted forever. Just as One Inch Ash hid himself again, the crimson lava on the ground was already dimming, hardening into still rock.

Not good!

Gao Yingjie had only just finished casting Hail. He hadn't expected that Qiao Yifan had merely rushed out as a diversion. Panicking, he immediately controlled Kind Tree to use another attack. But even though the Witch class had many instant-cast skills, there was still a time delay between throwing a magic tool and its effect activation. This bit of time was enough for One Inch Ash to lay down another Ghost Boundary.

Star Refraction!

By the time Kind Tree reached an angle where he could hit his target with these star cards that turned into magic rays flying toward One Inch Ash, the new Ghost Boundary had already landed.

This time, Kind Tree had nowhere to run. The Ghost Boundaries that One Inch Ash had placed one after another now linked into a huge formation, trapping Kind Tree within.

One Inch Ash stood forward.

For a Phantom Demon, trapping the opponent within your own linked Ghost Boundaries was already winning half the battle.

Qiao Yifan didn't hold back against his good friend. He meticulously controlled his character, summoning new Ghost Boundaries to perfect the arrangement. At this point, even though there were openings in his casting, he no longer needed to find some pathetic cover on this map. His own Ghost Boundaries finally became his most reliable and complete cover.

Qiao Yifan wouldn't let go of an opportunity like this.

His journey to this point hadn't been easy. If he hadn't met Ye Xiu, if he hadn't met and helped establish Team Happy, he likely wouldn't even be a pro player anymore.

And now, he'd grown from being an invisible presence let go by one team, to part of the main force of another team. And now, he had the chance to defeat the one whom his former team had labeled a prodigy.

How could he miss an opportunity like this?

What Qiao Yifan wanted was to prove himself to everyone, including the opponent in front of him now, his closest friend. But he still felt that it was a shame, that they had discussed this feeling of victory so often in the past, but had never had the chance to achieve it together. And now, the method of achieving it was to defeat the other side.

It's a shame, I can't share this taste of victory with you.

In the second battle of the individual competition Team Happy's Qiao Yifan won.

Chapter 1324: Trade

Happy had a 2-0 lead, which worried Ruan Cheng.

The entire Glory community knew that he didn't like Happy. If Happy were against some weak team, he definitely wouldn't have accepted the invitation for this event. But seeing that Happy would be playing an away game against Tiny Herb, Ruan Cheng felt like Happy would certainly lose, which was why he gladly ran over to slap their faces. Things weren't looking good, though.

He could tolerate Ye Xiu's win streak continuining, but a small-time figure like Qiao Yifan beating Tiny Herb's genius, Gao Yingjie?　

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were discussing this round with great enthusiasm. Ruan Cheng listened unhappily on the side.　

I'm not going to sit here and get slapped in the face, am I?

Ruan Cheng felt a bad premonition. Qiao Yifan's victory over Gao Yingjie made him uneasy.

The third players of the individual competition stepped onto the stage.

Happy's Mo Fan, Ninja Deception.

Tiny Herb, Liang Fang, Berserker Black Bamboo.

Seeing the matchup, Ruan Cheng felt his heart freeze.

After Mo Fan beat Samsara's Sun Xiang, the attention towards him grew. Happy had also given him more opportunities to go on stage, even so far as to include him in team competitions. His skill had received the approval of the community. It was just that people didn't understand his hit-and-run playstyle.

In this match, Mo Fan's opponent was Liang Fang, a very impatient player. Mo Fan's hit-and-run playstyle was a disaster for this sort of player.

A 3-0?

Ruan Cheng didn't even want to watch anymore. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were analyzing their playstyles though and just had to ask him his opinion.

"Mm…" Ruan Cheng replied spiritlessly, "Liang Fang needs to firmly hold the initiative for this match. This is the only way can he restrict Mo Fan's playstyle."

There was some reasoning to his logic, but it was mostly just empty talk. Who wouldn't be trying their hardest to take the initiative? Whoever held the initiative had an easier chance of winning. Who needed someone to tell them that?

The match began. Liang Fang headed straight towards the center of the map, while Mo Fan moved strategically.

The map Tiny Herb chose wasn't simple, but it wasn't overly complex either. Moving strategically could be done, but when Deception circled around to the center, Mo Fan found that there weren't too many places to mount sneak attacks.　　

As for Liang Fang's Black Bamboo? His line of sight was directly towards that side. Having chosen this map, he knew beforehand what places Mo Fan could possibly come out from. Mo Fan didn't lack patience, but in this situation, patience would just lead to a yellow card.

As a result, this time, Mo Fan happily had Deception walk out. Without saying a word, he attacked.　　

Mo Fan was direct enough, but Liang Fang was faster. He had been paying close attention to those few spots, certain that Deception could only come from there. As soon as he saw Deception come out, he released his readied attack.　　

Crimson Storm!

Liang Fang opened up with a Level 70 skill, quite a shocking move. Mo Fan was a bit surprised that his opponent would be so bold. He immediately tried to dodge, but the surging force just barely hit him.

Shuriken!

Deception attacked, throwing a shuriken towards Black Bamboo.

This Crimson Storm carried incomparable force, and its ending lag was just as formidable. When the Shuriken came, Black Bamboo could not move and could only take the attack. Then, Deception closed in.

Backwards Slash!

Right when the ending lag finished, Black Bamboo used a knock-up skill towards Deception. Deception nimbly leaped back and dodged it.

Flame Cut!　　

Flames came down facing the wind. Who would have thought that Black Bamboo wouldn't dodge though? Instead, he brandished his sword and let out a Wild Blood Strike. This attack didn't collide with Flame Cut. It went straight for Deception.

Trade?

Everyone who thought of this word felt dumbfounded.

Trading was a common Berserker strategy, but no one ever traded at the start of a match. This was because the effects of Blood Awakening didn't trigger until the user was below 50% health. The initial 50% health was no different for Berserkers, so it was usually used to get a feel for the opponent's playstyle and condition. Once their health reached 50%, Blood Awakening would activate, and then trading became a good choice. However, trading from the very start was rarely seen.

Liang Fang wasn't trading for nothing though; he was trading blows. However, recklessly burning several high-level skills in a row was truly a bit crazy.

The attacks from each player hit their targets.

Black Bamboo ignited into a flame man, while Deception was sent tumbling from the heavy blow.

Again!

As soon as his feet touched the ground, Deception straightened up and started advancing again. But the opposing Black Bamboo didn't even wait for the fire to extinguish. Half his body was still on fire as he also twisted that way and charged forward.

Dong!

This time, their weapons clashed, and the one to Guard was Deception.　　

Liang Fang wanted to trade damage, but Mo Fan didn't comply. It wasn't smart to keep up with a Berserker's frenzy. Once a Berserker reached a certain point, he would gain buffs. As a result, trading with a Berserker should only be done if he could gain an advantage from it. It couldn't be looked at purely in terms of numbers.

However, Liang Fang refused to let go and followed up with attack after attack. He let go of all defenses and traded. He didn't dodge any of Deception's attacks and ate every single attack.

"Liang Fang's playstyle…" Li Yibo was a bit shocked.　

Liang Fang's playstyle seemed somewhat excessive. But the problem was that it was extremely effective against Mo Fan. Every move he did was a trade. No matter if Mo Fan retreated or attacked, his plans were always interrupted. His hit-and-run tactics couldn't be displayed properly. Liang Fang was using this sort of rough and crude method to entangle Mo Fan. They fought and fought, and while it didn't seem like Liang Fang was gaining any advantages, Mo Fan wasn't able to get into his own tempo.

"Liang Fang is playing well today!" Ruan Cheng's spirit suddenly shot up. Initiative? His words had actually been spot on. Right now, Liang Fang firmly held the initiative in this 1v1. Any attack Mo Fan made would end up as a trade to the extent that sometimes, Liang Fang would be on the losing end. Even so, he still held the initiative. Mo Fan could only slightly win the trades, but his tempo? His tactics? He couldn't display them at all!

"Tiny Herb has done a lot of targeted research on Mo Fan!" Ye Xiu commented from the sidelines. Liang Fang's unbridled playstyle wasn't because of his Berserker class. Tiny Herb had probably prepared this playstyle, specifically to counter Mo Fan. Berserkers could trade and so could other classes, but Mo Fan could not. As soon as he traded, his most threatening three axes* could not be displayed.

"He's being suppressed," Wei Chen said.

"It looks like there's nothing that can be done!" Fang Rui said

The difference in health between the two sides could clearly be seen. In terms of the numbers, Mo Fan had the advantage, after all, Liang Fang was recklessly trading away his health. However, everyone knew that Liang Fang held the initiative. The extra trickles of health lost in each trade weren't trading for Deception's health, but rather his tempo.

"Kill!!"

Liang Fang roared in the chat. The more he fought, the more spirited he became. The more spirited he became, the crazier he fought. His attacks became even faster and even more swift, biting onto Deception even more tightly.

Colliding Stab!

Liang Fang had Black Bamboo use Colliding Stab. Unable to avoid it, Mo Fan would usually try and use a strong attack to trade, but this time...

Poof!

A puff of smoke. Black Bamboo's greatsword had hit a substitute strawman.

Substitution Technique?

He… ran?

Liang Fang was a bit startled. Before, when they had been trading blows, Mo Fan had never forced an escape.

But after retreating, he returned!

Deception rushed forward. Liang Fang regained his composure and readied to trade blows, even if it would be a losing trade.

Poof poof!

The sounds of attacks landing were crisp and clear. This time, the trade was completed in a straight forward manner.　　

"Again!" Liang Fang was having fun and started talking more in the chat.　

"Haha, he's playing so confidently!" Ruan Cheng was in a good mood. But after the trade, Deception stopped tangling with Black Bamboo and chose to retreat.

"Where are you going!" Liang Fang was surprised. He immediately readjusted his offense. When he rushed forward, Mo Fan suddenly turned back to receive his attacks.

Attack. Another trade. Deception once again ran away.

Liang Fang was furious.

It was a trade anyways. Running away and then coming back, was that really necessary?　

He didn't understand, so he continued implementing his original strategy. But Mo Fan had thoroughly changed up his plans. His three axes were being suppressed by this crazy trading, so he either attacked then ran, ran without attacking, or went all out on the offensive without running.

What type of playstyle is this?

This Mo Fan really loved this sort of hit-and-run playstyle, hah. Was it possible for him not to be so patient?　

The audience sighed. However, the pro players on the sidelines could see the purpose behind Mo Fan's repeated tussling.　

"Mm, nice!" After seeing a completed trade, Fang Rui nodded his head in approval, "Has that idiot Liang Fang still not figured it out yet?"

"It should be soon," Ye Xiu smiled.

Yes, he figured it out. It wasn't just Liang Fang, but the viewers who were paying close attention to the match had also begun to notice it. After Mo Fan switched up his tactics, the disparity between the two characters' health bars was growing larger and larger.　

Was it because of Liang Fang's unbridled trading? Of course, that was one reason, but more importantly, Mo Fan had started making meticulous calculations. Every time he traded, he would carefully think it through. Can I gain an advantage? Is the advantage gained significant enough? If the answers to those questions weren't satisfactory, or he simply didn't know, he would immediately turn tail and run. This was why Deception would sometimes run away and not make the trade.

"If Liang Fang continues trading like this, he'll trade himself to his death," Li Yibo chuckled.

"He probably won't dare to keep trading now, will he?" Pan Lin said.　　

"Then how will he stop Mo Fan?" Li Yibo said.

The answer was that he couldn't stop Mo Fan.

Chapter 1325: Fluctuating APM

One skill, one step back. In the end, Mo Fan ended up setting this repetitive rhythm. Liang Fang's reckless health trade immediately became out of sync. By the time he realized this, he had already traded his health away for a disadvantage.

He lost.

In the individual competition, Happy ended with a 3 to 0. The entire stadium was speechless.

"Hahaha, Happy's performing well today!" Li Yibo commented.

"Do they plan on obtaining another perfect victory?" Pan Lin wondered.

Ruan Cheng heart thumped. If Happy really did destroy Tiny Herb in their away game, then it'd be like they had thrown him here naked - he'd be completely humiliated!　

What the hell are you bastards doing!?

Ruan Cheng was even more desperate and worried than Tiny Herb's boss.

"Su Mucheng didn't go up for the individual competitions this round. Has Happy left her for the group arena?" Li Yibo said.

"Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, Tang Rou? Happy's group arena line-up is very impressive this round!" Pan Lin commented.

"In the eighth round, Happy's Tang Rou alone managed to wipe out two of Tiny Herb's members in the group arena and get to Wang Jiexi!" Li Yibo reminded them, "It's just unfortunate that the two players after Tang Rou didn't perform so well and were all defeated by Wang Jiexi in a 1v3 that turned the tides."

"However, it was after that round that Tang Rou stopped spearheading the group arena and switched to third position," Pan Lin lamented.

With that, the two side eyed Ruan Cheng together.

Yet, when Ruan Cheng had heard the two say that Happy had an unusually impressive line-up, his insides clenched. He didn't even register the discussion the two had afterwards.　　

"You think they'll have Tang Rou spearhead again?"

In the end, Ruan Cheng only heard that before the players for the group arena entered the stage.

Happy, Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, Tang Rou, as expected, an impressive line-up.

As for Tiny Herbm, they sent out Liu Xiaobie, Liu Fei, and Wang Jiexi.

"Seems like Tang Rou still isn't spearheading the round!" Pan Lin exclaimed.

"Yeah. Fang Rui leading and Tang Rou bringing up the rear, Happy hasn't changed that arrangement in a long time," Li Yibo noted.

"The match is about to start, let's see how the players perform!" Pan Lin announced. At the same time, the first player in each team were inserting their cards and loading into the first round of the match.

"Er, this map… It's a pretty rare sight in the group arena," the commentator and guests discussed upon seeing the map. The map Tiny Herb had chosen for their group arena was the same kind that Ye Xiu had set as his signature map choice this season: straight and simple. This kind of map often implied a test of mechanical skill. For individual matches, the maps could be chosen according to personal preference. However, in the group arena, there would be three people per team, and you needed to make sure that all three were comfortable with the map, thus, the map choice was rarely so extreme. Generally, maps with more varied content that could be useful in different situations would be chosen.

　

"This map choice… it'll probably negatively impact Happy's Fang Rui and Su Mucheng, but Tang Rou clearly prefers this sort of map," Li Yibo noted. "As for Tiny Herb… What do you think, Mr. Ruan?" Feeling that Ruan Cheng had gone silent for long enough, Li Yibo threw him a question helpfully.

"Ah… I guess they'll be alright since they're Tiny Herb?" Ruan Cheng guessed.

What on earth was he saying?

Li Yibo stared in shock and glanced at Pan Lin. Pan Lin seemed rather helpless as well. This Ruan Cheng really didn't have much mental fortitude! No matter if you're a fan or a hater, you should at least work hard to support your side! Even if its complete bullshit, that's better than this utterly defeated look after a 3 to 0!

Li Yibo and Pan Lin could only leave Ruan Cheng with his answer that wasn't really an answer. On the field, due to the simple map, the two sides soon met and clashed in an open fight.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Flying Swords' sword was as fast as lightning.

　

Liu Xiaobie was feeling rather depressed this season. He had wanted to become an all-star this season through his ceaseless hard work and improvement. Yet, Happy and Excellent Era's players had returned and the competition for this season's All-Stars was much tighter all of a sudden. Unfortunately, Liu Xiaobie once again wasn't voted in.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

　

Liu Xiaobie vented his frustrations through his mechanics. Flying Sword's attacks were swift and his pacing was solid. This level of skill was definitely enough to be considered All-Star level. It was unfortunate that the All-Star voting wasn't just about skill.

On the other side, Fang Rui, was in a very different position from Liu Xiaobie. Liu Xiaobie was just unable to become an All-Stars, and he, on the other hand, had been consecutively voted into the All-Stars, only to fail this season.

　

He also made light of this failure, expressing to the media that he always got in so it was pretty good that he had finally managed to drop out.

That sort of attitude was just asking for a beating to Liu Xiaobie. Many other also thought Fang Rui was unreasonable.

　

It was probably a little of both, but Fang Rui's performance really hadn't been affected by any of it. His performance had improved slowly as he got more used to the Qi Master, and his opponents, because of his chosen playstyle, often were unable to keep up.　　

However, Liu Xiaobie didn't fall into this disadvantage because he took the initiative to attack as soon as possible. His hand was speed rising dramatically.

Thus, the match progressed a little like Liang Fang and Mo Fan's match, both sides attacking fiercely and trying to prevent the other from using their preferred style.

However, compared to Liang Fang exchanging blows and blood, Liu Xiaobie had less to worry about with his offensive. For Liang Fang, he was also trading blood to win, and his defeat was because of it, too.

　　

"This kid's mechanics is getting crazier and crazier," Wei Chen exclaimed with a hint of envy, observing the way Liu Xiaobie was displaying his hand speed.

"The point is that he isn't just fast, but also very steady. He has everything in his grasp," Ye Xiu added.

"Fang Rui's met trouble this time," Wei Chen noted.

"Yes. This isn't a good terrain for him," Ye Xiu commented.

Ye Xiu had used this kind of terrain to bully quite a few opponents himself, so he naturally understood what sort of foundation Liu Xiaobie's advantage was built upon. He also knew that it was because there was nothing that could be used on the map, thus Liu Xiaobie's rhythm would be very hard to break.

Perhaps he could find some openings in Flying Swords' attack, but Liu Xiaobie's mechanics were just too fast, so fast that these opens flashed by. When his opponent wanted to use them, they were already gone.

The only thing you couldn't counter was speed.* 1

In regards to Liu Xiaobie, this phrase was rather fitting.　

"His APM is almost reaching 400…" The live broadcast gave a shot of Liu Xiaobie's APM data. Since the match was still ongoing, his mechanics were still ongoing, and thus the number wasn't stable, fluctuating at just under 400.

　

The system data wasn't smart enough to differentiate between effective APM and random keyboard mashing, but considering the situation on the field right now, there was little possibility for such noob mechanics to exist. Most, if not all, were effective.

For a single player game, even if Glory's mechanics were a little more complicated, an APM heading directly for 400 was still stunning. When the audience at the stadium noticed this data, sounds of awe rose from the crowd, and these voices were filled with pride. Liu Xiaobie was a player on their team, Tiny Herb.

For comparison, Fang Rui's APM data was quickly placed next to Liu Xiaobie's.

289, 290, 291…

The number kept rising.

"Fang Rui's APM is much faster than usual, too!" Pan Lin said, holding Fang Rui's previous match statistics.

"Of course. If he doesn't raise his hand speed under this sort of situation, he'd probably have been wiped out quickly," Li Yibo commented.

"However, there's still a 100 APM difference!" Ruan Cheng followed up.

Fuck!

Pan Lin and Li Yibo cursed to themselves simultaneously, glancing at Ruan Cheng.

Was this still that dispirited Ruan Cheng from after the individual matches? This kind of energy… Was Liu Xiaobie a Cleric or something? Had his near 400 APM healed this guy or something?

　

"Their hand speed has a gap, looking at the statistics, but from the situation, Fang Rui isn't at much of a disadvantage," Li Yibo noted.

"Heh. He's not at much of a disadvantage, but he's still at one," Ruan Cheng retorted.

"Fang Rui's current APM isn't his peak," Pan Lin added, looking through Fang Rui's info.

"His current APM is very steady," Li Yibo observed the APM stats on the screen. APM was calculated by the minute, but what was usually shown in a match was calculated by the second. It showed what the mechanics done in this second would be if maintained for a minute.

Fang Rui's APM was fluctuating at around 290, which meant that his hand speed was very steady.

"If given the chance, he'll give himself a burst of speed," Li Yibo said.

"What about Liu Xiaobie? Is this his peak?" Ruan Cheng smirked. He was, in the end, an expert, and wasn't ignorant.

Pan Lin naturally also had Liu Xiaobie's match statistics and, after taking a look, shook his head. "It's not… but, not all of his actions are effective. A lot of these statistics came from him making a bunch of useless actions at the beginning of a match to drive his APM up."

Li Yibo was carefully watching the match.

Chance. Fang Rui was waiting for a chance. Waiting for a chance where he could strike and break Liu Xiaobie's rhythm. Otherwise, if this continued, he would lose.　　

When would a chance appear?

Li Yibo couldn't be bothered to discuss with the other two. The pace of the match was so fast, so this chance would only appear for a mere moment...

There!

　

Li Yibo's eyes lit up.

"Cha…"

He only managed to get out the first half of the word because his speech wasn't nearly as fast as the two player's on the stage.

The APM statistics skyrocketed.

Fang Rui, 372!

This was his chance to turn the tables.

However...

He failed.

　

Just as Fang Rui's hand speed rocketed, Liu Xiaobie's APM also rose alongside it.

　　

442!

The peak APM of the match finally appeared.

Liu Xiaobie used his immense hand speed to crush Fang Rui's defense.

In the end, the first match of the group arena went to Tiny Herb's Liu Xiaobie.

Chapter 1326: Fly Forth

"What an intense match!"

　

Victory had been decided and Tiny Herb's stadium was naturally filled with applause. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were discussing excitedly and Ruan Cheng's smile filled his face.

Liu Xiaobie won and Flying Swords still had 52 percent of his health left. Tiny Herb had established a good lead in the group arena and Ruan Cheng was, naturally, delighted. In that moment, he seemed like a hopeless Tiny Herb fan.

　

"Liu Xiaobie's performance this round was amazing!" Li Yibo commented, "He managed such a stable performance under this continuous high hand speed, making no major mistakes. Truly impressive."

"Indeed, his grasp over this techniques has become more and more solid," Pan Lin noted.

"Let's see how he performs this next round," Li Yibo said.

"Heheheh," Ruan Cheng started laughing dryly again. Like a noob, he childishly started doing calculations in his head: 48% of health to take out Fang Rui, still 52% left. He totally still had a chance to defeat Su Mucheng. Then, there was still Wang Jiexi for Tiny Herb. Tang Rou 2v1? Haha, it was clear that Tiny Herb would win the group arena.

However, reality soon gave him a harsh awakening.

"Seems like Liu Xiaobie really exhausted himself last round…" Li Yibo observed, watching the match.

"Yeah, he's clearly making more mistakes," Pan Lin added.

"And no matter how powerful his offensives can be with that hand speed of his, he has to be able to close in on his opponent first," Li Yibo brought up.

"Su Mucheng is very carefully not giving him such a chance and even sacrificed a lot of damage for it," Pan Lin said.

"Yes. She's using a very clever playstyle. However, isn't she a little too careful? There's no chance of Liu Xiaobie replicating what he had managed yesterday. Perhaps Su Mucheng can play a little more offensively. What do you think, Mr. Ruan?" Li Yibo realized that Ruan Cheng had stopped speaking again.

Fucking useless!

　

Ruan Cheng was cursing Liu Xiaobie in his heart.

The possibility of defeating Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain with 52 percent of his health was rapidly approaching zero. Not only that, but Liu Xiaobie hadn't managed to find a single chance to close in on Su Mucheng. Ruan Cheng really was worried that he'd be wiped out without even dealing 1 percent damage.

　

Good thing was, Liu Xiaobie hadn't lost that badly. In the end, he still found a chance to close in. However...

Ten percent!

That was how much health Flying Swords ended up taking from Su Mucheng. Ruan Cheng's lips were trembling. He wanted to start cussing up a storm in this widely live streamed broadcast.

　

"Tiny Herb had started out well… But they didn't manage to maintain the advantage they had gained!" Pan Lin exclaimed.

"Liu Xiaobie might've done better in the second position with such a draining playstyle!" Li Yibo suggested.

"Mr. Ruan? Alright, let's continue to observe the match." Pan Lin had wanted to ask after Ruan Cheng's opinion, but seeing how he was barely holding back his anger, he was afraid that the other would pull the quality of the entire program down with his answer.

Tiny Herb's second player, Liu Fei, came onstage. She was another female , Sharpshooter player, ID, Tasselflower.

　

They were both female pros, both Gunner players, but Liu Fei's renown was nothing compared to Su Mucheng's. She wasn't even on the main roster for Tiny Herb and only had the chance to perform in rotation. In this round, she had been placed in the group arena, and had just happened to meet the number one Gunner amongst female pros.

"Though Dancing Rain is down to 90 percent of her health, there is a skill gap between the two. So long as Su Mucheng doesn't make any major mistakes, she should be able to win." Li Yibo, who was now uncertain about making predictions, was bold enough to make one now. It was clear that no one thought that there would be any suspense as to the result.

No suspense didn't necessarily mean no surprises, though.

The battle between the two female Gunners was spectacular. Liu Fei was no god, not even a member of their team's main roster, but if she could manage to stay in the two time championship team Tiny Herb, then she would definitely be rather skilled.

Her performance was unusually impressive this round. Li Yibo's saying of Su Mucheng being able to win so long as she didn't "make any major mistakes" was a bit of an exaggeration.　　

It was good that Su Mucheng didn't slap him in the face.

"Liu Fei performed very well, but unfortunately, she was met with an opponent that performed even better." When Li Yibo made such a analysis, there was a lingering fear in his heart. If Su Mucheng didn't perform better, then the tides may have turned.

When Su Mucheng won, Dancing Rain still had 21 percent of her health left. Tiny Herb had reached their third player, their last defense, their captain, Wang Jiexi.

From the 52 percent lead they had at first, until this 21 percent disadvantage, Ruan Cheng had the urge to run away. However, Tiny Herb's stadium was still filled with energy. The impact that being overtaken and falling behind should've had on these fans was nowhere to be seen. It was rather strange.

　　

"This atmosphere really is annoying!" Chen Guo exclaimed.

"Oh?"

"Look at these people. They're falling behind but as soon as Wang Jiexi appears, it's like they're fated to win or something." Chen Guo gazed over the audience in the venue, listening to their cheering.

　

Yes, that was the feeling the current Tiny Herb gave off. It wasn't like Tiny Herb was falling behind, but that victory was already in their grasp. Everyone was wearing an expression of utmost confidence. They completely ignored their future opponents, as if they were no more than bubbles that their captain Wang Jiexi could pop with a finger.

"Mucheng, crush him! Little Tang, crush him!!" Though she knew that the players in the booths couldn't hear her, Chen Guo still hollered.

　

Su Mucheng and Tang Rou, the two girls who were onstage on Happy's side were the two who were closest to Chen Guo. Seeing them ignored by the Tiny Herb fans like this, Chen Guo was exceptionally pissed off.

"It's not unreasonable that the Tiny Herb fans have such confidence," Ye Xiu chuckled.

　

"Who cares what reason they have." Chen Guo clearly wasn't looking for logic or explanations.

Ye Xiu smiled. The match was starting and everyone turned their attention back to the screens.

　

A simple and straightforward map naturally wouldn't have much of a build up. The two characters advanced, the chat remaining empty.

There was very little communication between players in today's match. Of course, there were some subjective reasons for that. For example, Fang Rui liked to trash talk, but he had been faced with Liu Xiaobie today, so there was no time to type in such an intense battle of hand speeds.

In this match, Wang Jiexi and Su Mucheng didn't seem to have any intentions to chat either. The two soon met in the center of the map and Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain unhesitantly used her attack range advantage to fire the first shot.

Boom!

Missiles flew.

Vaccaria's movement speed didn't dip at all, even riding his broom directly towards the missile. Just as it was about to impact, he swerved and the missile flew past his shoulder. The movement was smooth. Was this missile really an attempt to stop him? Can't feel it!

Clap clap clap!

The stadium burst into applause. Just a dodge and the Tiny Herb fans acted like they had seen the climax of a match.

"Getting excited over nothing!" Chen Guo gritted her teeth.

"It really was rather impressive!" Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo didn't reply because that voice of truth at the bottom of her heart told her that when Vaccaria narrowly dodged the missile without slowing down, she had almost abandoned her loyalties and cheered with the Tiny Herb fans.

"A technique that can really fan their excitement," Wei Chen commented, but then added, "But he wasn't just showing off."

Of course he wasn't. Wang Jiexi's action was simply to dodge in the quickest, easiest way. He had maintained his character's advance, so how could it be a mere party trick?

　　

Anti-Tank Missiles!

Dancing Rain jumped backwards, launching three anti-tank missiles in a tri-shot formation.

The three missiles came one after the other. Vaccaria once again didn't dodge, charging right forwards.

What was he going to do this time?

"Holy shit!!" As the stadium erupted into cheers, Wei Chen cursed.

Vaccaria had, somehow, flew forwards, spinning his body like a drill, and drilled right into the tri shot. Then, his spin managed to narrowly pull his body out of range of each of the three missiles.

Brilliantly fast, amazingly precise. The broadcast replayed this moment in slow motion over and over again, as if they'd rather play this than the rest of the match.

"He's truly skilled!" Even Ye Xiu couldn't help but praise. This was the one that had almost accomplished a consecutive three championships after he had made history.

Vaccaria charged towards Dancing Rain at top speed, seemingly unstoppable.

Of course, Su Mucheng wasn't that easy of an opponent. As Vaccaria advanced, Dancing Rain was naturally retreating. As she retreated, she attacked, it was just that this didn't do much to stop the other's momentum and the two were slowly getting closer.

Star Ray!

Vaccaria finally entered a range where his Witch could attack. As he flew, he began to throw out magic tools.

The Star Ray that was formed from a Star Card shot forwards faster than its user.

Dancing Rain dodged, and with the effect the movement had, Vaccaria continued to close in.

Stinger!

Su Mucheng attempted to use a large AoE to stop him.

Vaccaria flew a level higher and darted in and out of the falling Stinger missiles, as if the explosions had nothing to do with him.

However, the closer he got, the harder it was to dodge.

Laser Cannon!

This time, Vaccaria wasn't able to fully dodge the attack, and the Laser Cannon struck his side, causing Vaccaria to spin in the air. However, it wasn't able to completely stop his advance. As he adjusted his form, Wang Jiexi took note of the way Vaccaria was thrown; even if he fell, he'd fall as close to his target as possible.

"God fucking shit!" Wei Chen continued to curse. Though cursing wasn't a rare occurrence for him, watching Wang Jiexi's performance today, his cursing had been elevated to a frequency it had never once reached in the past.

Only cursing could express his emotions, because he didn't know how else to express them.

Wang Jiexi and his Vaccaria flew forth, carrying Tiny Herb on their shoulders and unstoppable.

Chapter 1327: Reason

Dancing Rain fell.

Wang Jiexi was just this type of person. He never failed at crucial moments. He would lose, but he would never make anyone lose confidence in him. As a result, even if he was one against many, even if he were playing against three opponents from Happy like last time, Tiny Herb's players and fans would still put their faith in him.　

That time, it was Happy's home game.

And this time, it was Tiny Herb's.

The moment Dancing Rain fell, Chen Guo could only see Wei Chen's lip moving. She reckoned that he was still cursing at something. As for the the actual contents? He probably couldn't even hear himself.　

The cheers from the Tiny Herb crowd had drowned out all other noise, and this was just the reaction after killing off an opponent with only 21% health left. If Wang Jiexi was able to win this team competition, how excited would these Tiny Herb spectators become?

Chen Guo really hoped a bucket of cold water would splash onto the crowd and cool them down. At this moment, Tang Rou's Soft Mist spawned onto the field.

Wang Jiexi was able to beat Su Mucheng using only 8% of Vaccaria's health. Compared to his incredible skill, this loss of 8% wasn't even considered as anything by many. The 100% health Soft Mist and the 92% health Vaccaria stood together. Practically everyone favored the latter to win.

"Wang Jiexi! He truly deserves his reputation!!" After taking down Su Mucheng, who had beat Liu Xiaobie and Liu Fei, Ruan Cheng became ecstatic. His state of mind wasn't much different than that of the Tiny Herb fans. Pan Lin and Li Yibo looked at him, wondering whether this guy would pounce onto the table and hug the screen.

"As long as Wang Jiexi is here, Tiny Herb is unlikely to lose the group arena," Ruan Cheng continued to sigh. His tone was extremely similar to that ofXiang Linsao

Pan Lin and Li Yibo was unable to respond to him. They were the official commentators of the match. Communicating with a brain-dead fan was impossible.

Fortunately, Soft Mist and Vaccaria had started fighting.

"Okay! Let's watch the match," Pan Lin's spirits rose.

"Dragon Breaks the Ranks!" Ruan Cheng shouted.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were stunned. Where'd Dragon Breaks the Ranks come from?

"Hahaha, she didn't use Dragon Breaks the Ranks?" Ruan Cheng sneered.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo continued to be stunned. Tang Rou indeed like to open with Dragon Breaks the Ranks, but this was an official match and the official commentary. Your way of explaining things was a bit too problematic, no?

The two didn't have the energy to complain. Tang Rou was very direct. Whether or not she used Dragon Breaks the Ranks didn't affect her style. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were listening to Ruan Cheng's nonsense as the two players fought. They had unexpectedly missed such a detail...

The commentators were suddenly at a roadblock. The two people glared angrily at Ruan Cheng. Ruan Cheng was watching the match closely with excited spirits. The two characters were going back and forth, but from the switches between offense and defends, Wang Jiexi held the initiative.

"Wang Jiexi is worthy of his reputation!" Ruan Cheng praised.

Tu tu tu!

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were feeling like Ruan Cheng was pulling aggro onto Wang Jiexi, but with his praise, the two started feeling more and more disgusted with Vaccaria.

However, Vaccaria having the advantage was a reality at the moment.

She's improved again.

After half a season, Wang Jiexi and Tang Rou fought once again. This was his first thought.

Especially in terms of rationality.

Tang Rou's eagerness to win was extremely high. Whether she won or lost, she would never compromise or retreat. However, there were always times where compromising and retreating were the better options. These weren't a part of Tang Rou's vocabulary though. She would always choose a single path and continue forward. This choice would sometimes surprise the opponent, but it would also sometimes backfire.

However, this time?

As he praised her improvement, Wang Jiexi could only force a smile.　

Her choices becoming more rational wasn't because she chose to compromise or retreat. It was because her choices became more precise when she charged forward.

Her understanding of skills had become more thorough, and she had accumulated more experience. She used everything she had to strengthen her always-forward playstyle.

This girl would always press forward when improving her own style. Wang Jiexi could only give her praise.　　

However...

Not enough!

While Wang Jiexi praised Tang Rou's improvement, Tang Rou once again felt the disparity in skill. Perhaps a part of it was because of the difference in equipment, but Tang Rou would never regard these as reasons.　　

She only wanted to win. She didn't want to lose.

A skill gap didn't necessarily represent a certain win or loss. Competition was fought, not compared.　　

But Wang Jiexi knew this reasoning even more clearly than her. He wouldn't relax facing a less skilled opponent.　

Bang!

When Soft Mist's Dancing Fire Flowing Flames swung, it hit the Lava Flask thrown by Vaccaria.　

The flask shattered, and lava flew out.　　

If Lava Flask directly hit a target, the lava would deal bonus damage. Wang Jiexi had unexpectedly used Lava Flash as an attack.

Lava splattered along with Stardust Extermination.

Dong!　

A parry. Soft Mist's Dancing Fire Flowing Flames blocked Stardust Extermination. However, the lava that splashed onto Soft Mist quickly dealt damage to her.

Sure enough, she didn't retreat.

Her offense had become more rational, more coherent, and more threatening, but what about her defense?

There were many ways to defend while attacking. Directly eating damage was very bold and aggressive, but the most optimal choice should be the most rational and the most effective. It wasn't single mindedly pursuing a certain direction.

Excessively using a brute force method might turn out like Liang Fang, who traded too much of his health away and lost because he was unable to get it back.

If she could fight Yu Wenzhou 1v1, she would probably have a clearer understanding of this point. Unfortunately, the chances of that happening were very low. It wasn't necessary though. Ye Xiu had probably noticed this point too.

Tang Rou didn't need to practice her offense excessively. She should be focusing her time on her defense. Maybe she didn't like to defend as a result of her personality, and she didn't like to spend too much thought on it. But the problem was that the more she improved on her offense, the greater the imbalance between offense and defense.

No matter how great you were, it wasn't possible to always be the one attacking. There would always be times when the opponent would force you to defend. When one had a big lead, using a brute force method like eating damage was fine, but what about when one had a small lead or did not have the lead? Such an irrational choice would be fatal.

Just like now!　　

A Star Symbol suddenly shot at Soft Mist's eyes. Tang Rou had Soft Mist twist her body to dodge it and then stepped forward to close she distance.

But with this step forward, Star Symbol pulled closer. The instant Star Symbol blossomed into Star Ray, the radiating light filled half of Tang Rou's screen.

The Star Ray didn't land on Soft Mist, but the following attack did...

Because half of Tang Rou's screen was blinded by Star Ray's light, she couldn't see the attack. It was just an instant, an instant that the viewers would only be able to understand if they watched the replay in slow motion. However, Vaccaria took advantage of this instant to land an attack...

Lost.

Tang Rou fell.　

Tang Rou lost again to Wang Jiexi.　

Losing to a top God in the Alliance shouldn't be anything strange, but Tang Rou wasn't willing. She was never content with losing to any opponent.

And this wasn't her first time losing to Wang Jiexi. If you counted their fights, she had never won once.

"Hahaha, Wang Jiexi. He truly deserves his reputation. This hand was too beautiful!" The commentary was overtaken by Ruan Cheng. This guy looked like he wanted to jump onto the table and dance. In particular, when Tang Rou walked down from the stage, disappointed and regretful, Ruan Cheng became even more excited.

"Tang Rou still has a long ways to go before she can reach a God! Do the viewers still remembers that 1v3 promise? I wonder if she still has such plans!" Ruan Cheng was radiating with delight as he remarked.

"Ahem, it was a splendid match," Pan Lin couldn't bear letting this guy continue talking.　　

"Tang Rou performed well today, but Wang Jiexi was more shrewd," Li Yibo said.

"Yes, Tiny Herb has won back two points in the group arena. Wang Jiexi didn't disappoint his teammates, the stadium, and all of the Tiny Herb fans watching this broadcast," Pan Lin continued to stir up the crowd.

"LONG LIVE THE KING!!" The Tiny Herb fans at the stadium shouted out this proclamation. Their respect for Wang Jiexi had reached such a level. Wang Jiexi didn't immediately walk down from the stage like Tang Rou did, after all, this was Tiny Herb's home stadium and the break between the group arena and team competition was rather long. He stayed on stage for awhile longer, waving his hands at the fans all around him.

Tang Rou went back to Happy's player area and smiled at the players comforting her. She sat down to the side rather dejectedly.

"Your attacks weren't bad," Ye Xiu turned his head and said to her.

"Not bad?" Tang Rou forced a smile. If they weren't bad, then why could she still not suppress the opponent?

"However, in a match, you can't always be attacking. Do you really think your opponent won't be able use even a single skill?" Ye Xiu said.　　

"I understand," Tang Rou knew that Ye Xiu's words were reasonable.

"In this match, how many of Wang Jiexi's attacks were able to stop your offense?" Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou stared at the replay on the big screens. From time to time, it would show her a depressing moment.　　

"How to maintain your offense without it being interrupted is something you need to be very very very mindful of. If not, your offense will always be stopped. Several times of that, and you'll be left wondering where your health went," Ye Xiu said.　　

Tang Rou continued to stare at the replay. Those sorts of moments flashed on screen again and again.

"Starting from next round, you'll be placed first," Ye Xiu said, "That way you'll have more opportunities for real combat practice."　　

"Okay," Tang Rou nodded her head. She understood the reasoning behind Ye Xiu's arrangements. Going third might be the important anchor for the group arena, but if the other two players before her performed spectacularly, there might not be much left for her to do. Only the person going first in the group arena had the most opportunities to gain 1v1 experience.

"That won't be a problem, right?" Ye Xiu saw that Tang Rou didn't mind and asked Fang Rui.

"Of course not," Fang Rui said.　　

Ye Xiu put on a helpless face: "I originally wanted you to go first, so you would have more chances to get used to the class change. I put her as third to be the anchor and now, everyone needs to go first to practice."

"Haha, this suits her the most!" Fang Rui laughed, "In fact, the person who goes first can also practice as the anchor if she still plans on a 1v3.

"It's too bad there's only one person who can go first," Ye Xiu sighed.